From PR News in Washington, I'm linked to contaminated steroids.
The Centers for Disease announces new meningitis sooner than usual.
The FBI has acknowledged it was a case of so-called PR News.
Because of fears they could end up in the hands of PR News.
PR News.
On Wall Street, 31, 13, 24, 5, and 78, GM says this is PR News.
Governor Jerry Brown now wants to allow lower-cost smog regulators.
Funeral services today for 24 smugglers.
The fungal outbreak appears to be connected to PR News.
Washington.
I don't know what I want, but I want it now.
Fried or fried, dear?
Now!
Fried?
I want my meat burnt, like St. Joan.
Bring me Calvin's horseradish with vicious mustard.
To pierce the tongue like Cardigan's lances.
The Soul Genius.
That's the trouble with Italian airplanes.
Too much hair on the wings.
Yeah, here it is.
Hello?
That's good.
Uh-huh.
I see.
I don't understand it.
All right, thank you.
4-7?
Right.
Yeah, thank you.
Well, just a minute.
I'll get a pencil.
Bye.
Hey, wait a minute.
Beach party, beach party.
It never stops.
I'm tired of this nightclub.
This band is so bad.
It never stops.
Why do I have to pay five dollars every night?
Beach party, beach party.
To Steve White.
Well, how many times do we have to play?
Beach party, beach party.
This worst song.
Over and over and over.
The genius beach party.
Over again.
The audience.
Nobody was getting a tan.
It is.
The genius beach party.
Wow.
So, are there any more questions that you can direct to the church at this time?
It is the seven long nights.
We'll see if we can fight our way through the studio and just sort of...
Whoa, tan, whoa, tan.
Nor's got it, that stupid band.
Well, that's not actually...
No, here, see, they're screaming and they're hurting.
They're turning over in the roasting oil of bad music.
Yes, it's just a horrible sight.
It's a good thing that you, the subscriber, don't have to watch this on any other...
Well, unless you have the TV on, of course.
...that you find out early in the morning.
And good morning to you.
Yes, we have a caller here just about ready to materialize here.
We're going to put him on hold just for a few moments.
Moments to let the nasty conspiracy vibrations...
Actually, you want to know what Darth Vader looks like, yeah?
Are you from KBFA?
KBFA phone line.
Yeah.
Tenth Planet callback.
And what is...
Yeah, what is the Tenth Planet like?
Tenth Planet callback.
Hello?
We can barely hear you.
Hold on now.
Can we turn the listener up, Bob?
I'm trying.
You're there.
We're trying to get you in here.
Okay.
Actually, you're probably using a conspiracy telephone.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
Okay, well, that's...
We're having a hard time breaking through the conspiracies.
Mind blockings and stuff, and we'll try to get you in here.
Hold on just a second.
Keep talking.
Okay.
Give it...
That's to give a signal.
Well, we can barely hear you, but...
Not to make you feel funny.
What is it that we...
What is it?
I wanted to ask how to get the tape of Terrence McKenna.
All right.
We'll have to ask him.
We're playing Kill the Caller tonight.
Welcome.
Yeah, is there any place I can write away for information on the...
Yes.
Yes, you can.
Box.
One, one, eight, nine...
Seven.
Eight.
Ten.
The other churches, you know, like tax-free and everything.
Better.
You got the wrong church, man.
This isn't tax-free.
This is a radio show in California.
But you can talk to those radio guys in just a minute here on the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Can you guys send me a donation?
Sure.
How much do you want?
Well, just a couple bottles right now.
A couple of bottles?
We can send you 50 cents.
How about 50 cents?
That's all we can afford is 50 cents.
The treasure of the subgenius.
So we call it 50 cents.
The open man is right here to give you 50 cents.
As long as you have the Bob given quality of slack to determine the lies of the conspirators
and to create new lies of your own.
Dear friends, the show.
Hold the wool over your own eyes.
And relax.
In the glory of Bob.
In the safety of your own delusion.
Relax in the safety of your own delusion.
And so.
Why afford that task to anyone else?
From across this land they came.
The subgeniuses joining at the lonely and solitary campground of Wisteria in the tropical hell of southern Ohio.
Surrounded by a national disaster area declared by President Barack Obama.
As sewers backed up.
Power cut out.
And people died like flies from a lack of air conditioning.
Even though you have the wonderful.
Well, no.
It was in one of those.
One of those areas that had been declared a disaster area because of that.
Rainstorm.
That horrible, horrible.
On earth.
That earthly hurricane.
The homage to hummus.
The hurricane that came through there.
An on land hurricane.
That came through there and destroyed Wisteria before we arrived.
Built beneath the earth.
And everything else.
Actually, Wisteria survived.
It was like an oasis.
Yes, only the subgeniuses were spared.
A miracle before all.
To show that the rays of bright, blinding, brilliant light shining through the clouds illumine only the humble camp of the subgenius pilgrims.
And we only had to pay.
A million degrees.
From the soles of my feet to the tippy tips of my whole ear.
I am a doctor for Bob.
And let me say that prior to this moment, I had the least ability to understand the doctors for Bob.
Of any subgenius in the church.
But tonight, with an artist elimination experiment being such a success.
I truly feel that I am for the first time a true doctor for Bob.
But Bobby is bigger than I.
Uh oh, I think he's caught it.
Doctor, give him something for his cough.
Alright, alright.
Here's a quarter.
Oh, that's not much.
Not much of a cough.
Well thanks, Douglas. I'll take over.
It's alright. You'll be yourself again in a minute.
I'm...
I'm so sorry, everybody.
Now you just drink this.
Are you a doctor for Bob?
I am a doctor for Bob.
I am a...
SON KILLER!
I'm beaten.
Asshole.
Freeman.
Eardrum split.
Hell of a doctor for Bob.
I don't feel well.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, I don't know.
I was the doctor and he told me what to do, but I didn't do it.
He said to take one pill three times a day, but you can't do that.
I think I'd rather die than do that.
I'm a doctor for Bob.
Man, it's a gas.
I figure, you know, some of those roaches they put out in grass and the glass acid will put you on the moon in an hour.
But reality?
That's where it's happening.
What?
What's the use of pretending?
I can't stand this anymore.
Don't, don't.
Doctor please.
Please, doctor.
Chandler said you went over to Georgia Street to see that doctor.
Yeah, that's right, Ed.
Short, short.
Short visit.
Poor guy.
Pretty bad, huh?
No, the guy's really a mess.
The beatnik walked up to the epileptic and said, oh, I don't hear the music, but go, baby, go!
Go!
That little clip was something called Underground System Afrobeat.
No connection.
I don't think.
Before that, the Puzzling Evidence show from KPFA Berkeley on July 20th, when Dr. Hal and Dr. Drummond had returned from our 50-next-day drill.
More of that later, plus Sam Singleton.
Before Puzzling Evidence, the Doctor Music collage was mostly by St. Byron Brown.
And, of course, the late Bob Warner from the 1985 subgenius album Bad Doctors.
More Doctors next week.
DJ Reverend Slutmaster Sarcastro did the titles.
And Leigh Murr does PR news and other collages.
Now, back to Puzzling Evidence and Weird Stuff.
Oh, weird stuff.
You guys are in some weird sex cult in the middle of Ohio?
That's right.
Waiting for rocket shots?
A UFO sex cult.
How can anyone even find the stamina?
It's exhausting.
And this being said, there were two weddings there.
The second one was performed with the bride and groom in the three-piece suit with the tie I thought was going to expire.
Man, he was sitting over there in the sun.
And he's listening to Stang go on and on about the Yeti making cycle and so forth.
He sat in the sun.
His girlfriend, or his new wife, his fiancee sat in the sun with him.
And they had these portable fans that blew on them.
I DJed for this event.
They smoked a lot of cigarettes and chewed a lot of gum while they waited.
Based on what was in the headphones.
A little nervous, I think.
Yeah, they're looking ahead to 70,000 years of wedded bliss.
They all fall in shame.
What do you mean hell?
Well, wedded bliss, the felicity of domestic dalliance.
Yeah, what'd he say?
Is this the part of the show where we eat ice cream in front of everybody?
Yeah.
Dr. Drummond is eating ice cream.
We announced about the ice cream again and again.
She has an eating disorder and can't eat unless other people are also eating.
Before she starts eating?
Yeah, I don't have that disorder.
I'm a hog.
I'll just start.
I'll just plow right in.
I'm not going to wait for everybody else.
I'm eating this and I'm enjoying it.
And I'm wondering what kind of a cocktail of foul chemical implants I'm getting with
this corn syrup.
Corn syrup and preservatives.
Did you worry about that kind of thing when you were in Brazil?
They didn't have that kind of thing in Brazil.
Or Bolivia.
Did they have an ice cream sandwich there?
Well, they had an ice cream sandwich, but you watch this old man run around in a circle
turning this thing that turned the tub and they got the ice cream out and spread it on
the thing for you.
So an old man made an ice cream sandwich right in front of you that had no preservatives
and additives and so forth.
You used the stinky old sweaters?
You used the stinky old sweaters.
And he melted the goat to get the ice cream.
No, actually there are Nestle's there and somebody else, but there is a lot of homemade
ice cream in Brazil.
Seems like a lot of people like it.
Real strange flavors.
Avocado, jackfruit.
What were those little red things?
There's one, it's called.
This is the hour of slack.
And if you're not listening closely, you're going to hear a lot of things.
And if you're not listening closely and paying attention, you are probably never going
to get it.
Oh, sorry.
That was the one little liquid slack.
The last bottle of liquid slack.
It's just liquid.
Would you like to share the straw with me, Dr. Howell?
The last in the bottom of the cylinder.
The sweetest.
Drops.
The last two drops.
Here, you have one.
And I'll have one.
Closer to the bone.
Let's cut this other drop.
Let's all have a drop.
Can you tell us more about?
About X Day?
Yeah.
Well, we had a giant roast pig.
So sue me, little Susie.
Called EMU somewhere else.
Dr. Howell and I did probably six, nine or 10 hours of the hour of slack.
How I miss your frenzied squealing.
During the hour of slack.
that time frame.
The meat is sweetest
closer to the bone.
And as we did
the hour of slack,
we sweated.
Did you lose some weight?
I lost some weight
during that.
You ate some out of
some bacon.
I just lost my teeth.
Oh, yes.
We did.
Despite all that
eating of meat
and steak
and especially the pig,
the pig went on forever.
And by the time
I got there,
many, many people
had been eating it,
but there were still
large amounts
of this animal
that you could just
saw off.
And it was all delicious.
It was excellent.
Yeah.
The only time
I've ever seen that done,
of course,
the head was out there
on display,
but I'm not interested
in that part of the animal.
The cheek meat.
Yes, I know.
Did it have an apple
in its mouth?
It had...
It didn't, actually.
I don't know
what it had in its mouth.
Now, they were lazy
on that one.
And those tusks there.
Those big tusks.
They were all lazy.
Yeah, they're not
They're not lazy.
They did a good job.
They did a good job
cooking the pig.
And then,
then Doc,
it was Doc,
not Doc Holocaust,
the other Doc
did...
Right?
One of those Docs.
There was a lot of Docs there.
He served
the wonderful steaks.
Yeah.
So, yeah,
it was nice.
We had some great meals.
And then,
while I think it was,
who came on?
Somebody came on
and said,
after the amino acids
that night,
went on for a long time.
Was that trademark
Gunderson
of the
Evolution Control Committee?
No, that was before.
This was after.
Remember,
there was some
person that played
until about
five in the morning.
That wasn't just
Pisces and Sud?
No.
Some...
He must have
already been asleep.
Well, I did
a night
with...
where I did a number
with Fat Mandy
and Princess
Rihanna.
Right, right.
Now, this was the final night,
the Saturday night.
This is the last night.
This is the final,
the final night.
This is...
You never say never.
...the worst day
of the mess
of your life.
I will have more stupidity.
This was their finest hour.
Hour?
Well,
Extinguish all smoking material.
Never, never, never,
never give up.
Shaken, not stirred.
Yeah.
Princess, we?
What are you doing?
Say, dance like a hoe.
Dance like a hoe.
I'm not allowed to use
the word hoe at home.
I can't even say home properly.
We're dancing like hoes,
so give us money.
The song says
dance like a hoe.
Yeah, we're garden implements.
This is the way we're moving.
Well, what if I say
dance like a hoe?
Then all of a sudden
it's all about
I'll get mad at you.
demanding too much.
You don't like the word hoe.
I hate the word hoe.
So you dance like a cavewoman
at the bottom.
Only if you put the apostrophe
before and the apostrophe after.
Because that shows
you're missing letters.
That's it.
That hate shows
somebody calls me a hoe,
I just fucking laugh.
Somebody calls me a whore,
I'd be hurt.
They leave off
those extra letters
and it makes all the difference.
I hate you.
That and what's in the background right now
was the rave music of either DJ Gravity or Poly Culture,
I'm not sure which,
from 15X Day with Reverend Suzy the Floozy and us yakking.
But now I'm going to do something tonight
that I almost never do on this show.
I'm going to play over 30 minutes almost straight
of one man talking,
and it's not even me.
That one man is probably
my brother Sam Singleton,
the atheist evangelist from near Atlanta, Georgia,
who was invited to anti-preach at 15X Day
by Reverend Suzy the Floozy of WREK Atlanta
after she met him at the Atlanta Atheistical Freethinkers
and Intelligent Weirdos Club meeting.
When he was speaking at 15X Day,
I was so busy recording or else recuperating
that I didn't really get to truly listen to his rant.
Tonight I was marking the cuss words in it
to remind him
that I had to move for the broadcast versions of this show,
which is especially ironic in this particular case.
I realized how tragic it was
that I broke his rant up into five parts for our slack.
Also, the very end of his rant is timely
in a sense that I dare not take advantage of.
So we're giving the rest of this show
over to Brother Sam Singleton,
the atheist evangelist.
When I first heard
that there was an entire field of theology
called apologetics,
I naturally assumed it had been set up
to deal with the problem of why God is such an asshole.
Why anybody with a conscience
wouldn't want to avoid him
like one of the plagues he enjoys visiting upon his children.
But no.
The study of God's mean side
forms a whole other branch
called theodicy.
From theo for God
and idiocy.
Theodicy.
Apologetics is about defending God's existence,
not getting him to say he's sorry.
Of course, if you can't establish that,
you can't expect anybody to take any of the other stuff very seriously.
You need you some faith.
The gospel according to Benjamin Franklin says,
the way to see by faith
is to shut the eye of reason.
Good point, Brother Ben.
Because if you got faith,
what do you want with reason?
Faith is the only thing you need to know.
Faith is hope gone insane.
The gospel according to Merriam-Webster says,
faith is firm belief in something for which there is no proof.
Well, if you got proof, you don't need faith.
Of course, that didn't stop some of the faithful
from trying to prove God's existence.
Apologetics grew up around trying to prove God's existence.
They were trying to explain belief in God
in ways rational people could listen to without busting out laughing.
As the gospel according to H.L. Mencken puts it,
trying to explain the unknowable
in terms of the not worth knowing.
Sorry's got nothing to do with it.
God's not sorry. He's just mean.
And setting aside whether God is too
cruel
or lazy
or disengaged to bother protecting His own children,
you're still left with all this stuff
you might as well not even try to understand
since you can't get there through reason.
That's always struck me as a sure recipe
for a spiritual discernment pissing contest
in which each believer claims that his revelation
trumps his sisters or brothers.
God showed me.
No, He showed me, ass lick.
Who was I supposed to believe?
The one person I knew for a fact God was not speaking to
was me.
He never said shit.
I began to suspect He never said shit to anybody else either.
Even as I continued to say my prayers
and tried to hang on to the naive belief
that my own personal God was on call at any time
to supersede the laws of nature on my behalf,
I could see He wasn't doing shit.
Either He wasn't paying attention
or He wasn't up to the job,
or maybe...
I want to pause just long enough to acknowledge
the agnostics among us.
The Gospel according to Merriam-Webster
has something to say about what makes an agnostic.
Bless your pink little hearts.
One who is not committed
to believing in either the existence or the non-existence
of God or a God.
God damn.
That doesn't sound very good.
Puts me in the mind of Revelation 3.
Because you are lukewarm,
you are neither hot nor cold,
I'm about to spit you out of my mouth.
But Brother Sam,
we wouldn't want to be too hasty in ruling out the God as I asked us,
for instance.
You can't say for certain that she doesn't exist.
Yep.
You're agnostic, I.
You see, I'll go way the hell out on a limb
and say outright
that there is no Isis.
No fucking Jupiter.
No teapot.
No Zoroaster.
No God.
No Jesus.
No none of them.
You go right ahead and be agnostic.
Just remember to set out some cookies for Santa.
The fix I got myself born into was not my fault.
At least not up to a point.
The point where I wanted people to stop treating me like a child.
The Apostle Paul said,
and Paul wrote in the 13th chapter of 1 Corinthians,
When I was a child, I spake as a child,
I understood as a child, I thought as a child,
but when I became a man, I put away childish things.
I got to that stage most teenagers go through
and some never outgrow
of being extra vigilant about letting anybody pull the wool over my eyes.
My bullshit meter was fixed in the super sensitive mode.
And it came to me
that with an omnipotent being on the loose,
every other being would have to be completely impotent.
God would have every damn bit of the power.
You and I would have none whatsoever.
No free will.
God damn logic.
In matters of morality,
an omnipotent God is as worthless as hair on bacon.
And even if an omnipotent God and free will were not mutually exclusive,
every prayer of repentance would still be meaningless,
would still be empty,
would still be coerced.
You can say you would have done it anyway,
but won't nobody believe you?
Put yourself in God's place.
How can you trust that somebody has done something willingly
because they love you or respect you
when you know they're getting paid for it?
Or they're afraid of what'll happen if they don't play along?
Again, they can say they'd have done it anyway,
but God damn.
It's an uneven arrangement all around.
God does not love you half as much as He wants you to love Him.
I pity God if the reward is absent
or if you take away the threat.
My people wouldn't have liked what the Gospel Corridor said.
And Einstein has to say on the subject of everlasting reward and punishment,
Man would indeed be in a poor way
if he had to be restrained by fear of punishment
or hope of reward after death.
Do you hear them tell it?
That was all that stood between them and their church-going friends
becoming the most vile and depraved pestilences ever to pollute the planet.
Fear of punishment
was why you didn't smoke,
drink,
cuss,
fornicate,
play cards,
dance,
go to the movies,
watch TV.
And why the hell would you do anything good
unless there was a reward attached?
Every action
was something of a transaction.
Just don't expect the quo
until you've ponied up the quid.
And I'm thinking,
anybody who looks to the Bible as a model for moral, just, ethical, or decent behavior
is fucking a dead dog.
You might as well look to the pre-Columbian Aztecs for moral guidance.
The difference
between the Aztecs and the believers in the God of Abraham
is that
thanks to some nice folks in the old country,
sacramental basketball played with the heads of those whose living hearts
have been cut out before their eyes
and shown to them as the last thing they'll ever see
is no longer recognized by the National Council of Churches
may have died out altogether.
But if Aztec nogginball is still being played,
then it's not the only thing that's going to be practiced somewhere in the world today.
Some folks say I should speak of it
in terms only acceptable to the athletes themselves.
That bugs me.
Don't make a public profession unless you want to hear back
from the public.
The Bible belongs to everybody.
Not just the ones that treat it like their own family album.
And anybody who won't even bother to read the whole thing
should have the good grace to refrain from pontificating until they have.
My people
like to make out like they some kind of
biblical authorities.
But they just pick at it
like picky little buzzards.
Careful to take only the parts that agree with them.
The parts they can swallow
and regurgitate without digesting.
By God they know the Bible says what it means
and it means what it says.
Even if they don't know what it says.
Let alone what it means.
So I tried to get my cousin Palmer,
he my Uncle John Wesley Middleboy,
and was attending Roberts Oral University at the time
to admit that the God he worshipped was a limited one.
A God-like.
Some kind of little old low fat God.
Since God either has all the power or he doesn't.
That switches either on or it's off.
There is no third position.
The best Palmer could come up with was that
God gave humans enough free will
to decide for themselves whether to accept him
and how to behave.
But he was still omnipotent.
I explained to Palmer how
he was as good as saying that
God is only relatively omnipotent.
He just said he'd pray for me.
And I still did not slap that boy.
Free will is hard.
You have to decide things for yourself.
Belief in God is a voluntarily self-inflicted intellectual lobotomy
performed by stuffing your cranium full of toxic sawdust
that crowds out brain cells and eats away IQ points.
Everybody's heard that quote from the Gospel according to Voltaire.
How if there were no God it would be necessary to invent one.
Do you remember what the Gospel according to Jean-Paul Sartre says about that?
How even if there were, even if God existed
it would be necessary to deny him
since the very notion of God negates freedom.
You're goddamn right, Brother JP.
Of course that's exactly what some people want, isn't it?
Freedom is scary.
Especially other people's freedom.
We don't want to be free and we can't have you being free either.
For some folks being God's livestock represents a kind of freedom.
Not just from personal responsibility
since an omnipotent God means no free will.
But from all rules.
Don't like natural laws?
Suspend them.
Can't get a definition?
To jive with your position?
Just make up some shit.
You never have to tax your brain trying to figure out how stuff works
because God is behind everything.
There is no question that you don't already know the answer to.
Cheap fantasy is seductive.
But stupid.
Stupid.
Well that's a mighty harsh word.
I don't like using it.
I just don't have a better one to describe betting everything you've got
on the hearsay promise of a payoff
that can't be collected until you're dead.
Palmer asked me.
He said, don't you want to go to heaven?
I told him, hell no.
Everybody in heaven is either an idiot or an asshole.
Because once you're there, you cease giving a hurry of shit.
All the loved ones you were so worried about back on earth,
fuck them.
I got mine.
It has to be that way or it wouldn't be heaven, would it?
You can't have grief or regret intruding on your bliss.
Or what would be the point?
No, it's burn in hell, losers.
I don't care if you were my baby, my husband, wife, parent, friend.
The selfishness is complete.
There is no more to be desired.
It's like the imaginary 40 virgins.
Suicide bombers get their puny little peckers and a peek over.
God damn.
See if you haven't come across this one.
I was talking to Palmer again.
Just the other day.
And I must have said, God damn, without thinking about it.
I do that.
Boy, it's been partial to God damn.
And Palmer starts in on me about how since I used the Lord's name in vain,
I must believe in God.
Well, I reminded Palmer how Proverbs 26 says,
Answer not a fool according to his folly.
Why the hell should anybody, believer or no,
give the first curly little hair on a red rat's ass whether anybody else is an atheist?
Let alone try to convince them that they're not.
Or worse, tell them that atheism is just another brand of belief.
Atheism is not a religion.
It's not a cult.
Atheism is to believe in God,
what a vacuum is to air.
The absence of theism.
If you sucked all the belief in God out of the universe,
what you'd have left is atheism.
And far less methane gas being released into the atmosphere.
I got more to say about God damn.
When Clark Kent's editor at the Daily Planet,
Perry White,
says, Great Caesar's Ghost.
You see, he's not actually invoking the specter of Julius Caesar.
Any more than saying holy cow causes sanctified bovines to pop into existence.
So I'm gonna go on saying, God damn.
I say it with a little G.
But it's okay if you hear it with a big G.
I'm pretty much gonna stay off politics tonight.
Other than to note that God is a parasitic slime mold
that's been sucking the brains out of the USA since before it's founded.
The pilgrims, the Europeans,
tracked it over on those shoes with the big buckles on them.
And over the past 400 years,
it's worked its way into all the questions,
all the cracks and crannies of American life.
We're not just talking about in God we trust on the money.
Every public school,
courthouse,
city hall,
the federal courts, the government itself,
they reek of God.
They got God smeared all over them.
I resent the hell out of my taxes being used to
promote God's brand name.
In God we trust.
The gospel according to Mark Twain said,
and it wouldn't sound any better if it were true.
It's like the government has to keep reminding me
that I'm permanently relegated to America's hind tit
just because I don't buy into that shit.
You ever think about the number of times you're exposed to the word God in the course of a day?
We gotta start paying closer attention.
Noticing when God shows up uninvited.
Every in God we trust,
every one nation under God,
every Ten Commandments monument,
every prayer that opens a session of a legislature,
every federal observance of a Christian holiday.
Not that we should get fewer days off.
We ought to be able to get them without celebrating our own marginalization.
These state sponsored professions of belief are designed to calm the insane.
Reminding the rest of us that we're merely visitors on the ward
is what you'd call an ancillary benefit.
Well the Constitution guarantees even the pathologically delusional
the right to speak any nonsense they like.
What they say in the privacy of their own loony bins is their own business.
As long as it's all between consenting adults and they leave the children out of it
and they don't prevail upon the likes of Brother Sam to pick up their tax burden.
The government already earned a rights to their program.
They're programming and does their PR for free.
You buy, sell, rent out property, hire or fire.
You are a business.
Pay your fucking share you deadbeat parasites.
And when citizens that do pay taxes
try to pass laws that require these civic leeches to chip into the community pot
who decides the outcome?
A bunch of legislators who could never get elected without professing belief in God.
Nobody cares that the gospel according to the article 6 of the US Constitution says
no religious test shall ever be required as a qualification to any public office or trust under the United States.
The problem isn't with the Constitution.
It's with the voter.
Of course you can always turn to the courts.
You'll know the building by the big-ass Ten Commandments out front.
The very courthouse where Sister Singleton and I go to do our county business has one.
I bet yours does too.
And God forbid you should ever be accused of a crime
or called upon to give testimony in a civil proceeding.
And if the bailiff asks,
do you swear that the testimony you're about to give is the truth so help you God?
What, are you going to call the proceedings to a halt so you can explain?
Well, I can't swear to a God I don't believe in.
So you can make a point of being a member of the one minority that political correctness hasn't gotten to yet.
If you don't believe in God, you're a fool.
If you got any sense, you'll say,
hell yes I swear to God.
Jehovah, Yahweh the Almighty, He whose name must not be spoken.
The Father, the Son, and the Holy Ghost.
Praise His holy name.
That ninth commandment posted outside the front door there commands me not to bear false witness against my neighbor.
And that's flat what I'm not going to do.
That I swear to God by God.
Swearing an oath before God is the nod and the wink that lets the government know you can be trusted to join the military.
Preside over a court.
Serve in Congress, the White House, the State House, City Hall.
You're one of them.
You promised not to call bullshit on the whole deal.
I may be willing to be mad at a God that does not exist.
But that's it.
I'm God damn if I'm on fear of God.
Sure some of His people bear watching.
But I'm no more afraid of God than I am of this flying spaghetti monster deal.
That is not to say there's nothing to fear.
There's nothing left worth worrying about.
You want to know what causes Brother Sam to wake up in a cold sweat at a quarter to noon.
Not be able to get back to sleep again.
Even with the 700 Club playing in the background.
It's knowing that this enthusiastic embrace of the improper.
This obstinate fidelity to falsehood is damn near an absolute requirement for the highest offices in the most powerful government in human history.
It scares the bejesus out of me that the people entrusted with our very lives are avowed fantasists.
Full fledged year round residents of the United States.
Who use our taxes not only to shove big wads of God up our asses.
But to wage sectarian war in our name.
As if it's us Christians and Jews against those Muslims.
I want it understood.
Brother Sam does not throw in with sanctimonious thugs and pious bullies.
And I don't give a first shit which fairy tale they favor.
The gospel according to Voltaire also says.
If we believe absurdities we shall commit atrocities.
You want absurd?
Imagine a universe without mysteries.
A universe that's a closed book.
I'll tell you one thing for God.
God damn sure.
Nobody ever learned anything from a closed book.
Atrocities?
Well start by torturing logic and language.
But save the most depraved shit.
For infidels.
Fellow believers.
Not that actual heathens.
Non-believers like Brother Sam shouldn't be maltreated.
That's what minorities are for.
I'll grant that not all believers are as extreme as the ones that raised me.
Or those that put out a contract on a cartoonist.
Or tell women or homosexuals that they're not good enough or smart enough.
And don't have a right to personal freedom.
But near as I can figure.
Once you take that initial step off the deep end of reason.
And accept God on nothing but faith.
You're down to splitting hairs over whether the sugar plum fairy has buckles or bells on her shoes.
You might as well grab a rattlesnake with one hand.
And a bottle of rat poison with the other.
And kick up a Holy Ghost can can to Hosanna sung in unknown tongues.
Whoa! I heard somebody say.
Brother Sam you done committed one giant ass generalization heaping all believers together that way.
I know.
Before we wrap up.
I wouldn't be of any count as an evangelist.
Even in the ironic sense.
If I denied y'all a chance to experience the taking up of an offering.
The church of the subgenius got enough to do without taking Brother Sam to raise.
So this is how we can do this without a fee.
And if you're hard up.
Just drop in anything that Brother Sam might find interesting.
Or useful.
Thank you.
If we have ushers would you start the little basket around.
.
Whatever you believe,
or do not believe,
you are more than the sum of those things.
Somewhere down the line, folks took to confusing
what they believe with who they are.
And that's why we can't even discuss this shit
without me having to worry about
somebody calling down a holy war on my ass.
The godly got enough to do without killing each other.
They don't need to be fucking with Brother Sam.
If I was the kind of evangelist that believed in sin,
the one I'd preach against
would be willful ignorance.
Because that is the most dangerous
and destructive thing I can think of.
Individually,
or as a group,
a really huge-ass group,
say 3.4 billion,
lying,
especially to yourself,
is one of those things
that you can't do.
You give it its head,
and it will flat run away with you.
You swallow the first lie,
and the rest go down easy.
If you can honestly say,
I believe I have a destiny,
and it's in the almighty hands of the God of Abraham,
or a blue elephant,
or the,
and I want you to come forward
and bring all the cash you got on you.
And just put it right here in one of these offering baskets.
Because you definitely ought to be in charge of your own finances.
Brother Sam will just look after it for you
until you come to your senses.
Or until the rapture.
Everybody else,
get out there and raise hell
and put a chunk under it.
That is the gospel according to Brother Sam.
Good night.
God damn.
Thank you very much.
Prayers go unheeded.
Of course they're unheeded.
How am I supposed to hear prayers coming out of my ass?
They talk of war against the faithful.
I beseech thee, rise up against them.
Smite someone who deserves it for once.
Malachi, every time I interfere, I only make things worse.
You're best off solving your own problems.
But, but Metal Lord...
What part of nay dothn't thou understand?
As Brother Singleton didn't exactly say,
he preached for free at X Day 15
and even had to buy himself and his wife
subgenius ministerial ordainment packages.
I hope that helping to spread his ministry
with this humble radio show and crazy man podcast
will make up for that.
And I can also suggest that if you want to know more,
simply Google Sam Singleton
or try
samsingleton.com
or
the Atheist Evangelist.
Pricebop.
So yeah, X Day 15 is nowhere to be found on YouTube yet.
It's so sad.
So sad, so sad.
I was chosen for some kind of
X Day...
I think everybody's just waiting for Stang
to put their official one.
They're all like...
The tripod shot from back in the room.
It could be 106 degrees.
I mean, what are you going to do?
Where?
I took...
I took some video.
I took some video of...
I had my GoPro camera strapped to my head.
Nice.
And I was walking around in the audience
and I'm taking pictures of the stage,
a video of the stage.
I'll have to show it to you.
It's parts of it.
It's kind of cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Shows you some of the potential of that GoPro.
But I was cutting people's heads off
because I didn't have it turned up enough, you know?
And I had this kind of stuff going on.
And for a while,
I was so sweaty
that my...
The heat from my head
was going through that thing
and was fogging up the external cover.
Sure.
And so I was getting these weird foggy vignette kind of things
on that, you know, it's a wide-angle lens.
Yeah, yeah.
That's funny.
But then that kind of went away.
But yeah, you've got to put that up on YouTube.
I'll show you that stuff.
It's the only video on YouTube ever.
Yeah, yeah.
And now that Facebook's slack hole went away,
it's like you can't...
There's nothing.
Yeah.
The slack hole, too, is back, but...
No, it's not.
The wind has gone from the sails.
The wind.
I'm blowing some wind right now.
I bet.
So are we.
But we just wanted to pick it up
because we were where the troopers fell,
and now we're moving fast through history.
That's what they do at X-Day.
These guys just got back here from the end of the world.
I got a bunch of stuff from X-Day.
Pictures, videos.
The whole time you guys were gone,
we were saying,
you're dead,
and you're on this flying saucer.
And you're in the pleasure saucers.
Yeah.
And I was lying the whole time.
You were?
Yep, because here you are.
Now, why would you do that to your audience?
Because I'm sort of like a man of the clock.
This audience that comes back to you week after week.
I'm sort of like a pastor.
You're sort of like a cult leader.
Yeah, sort of.
In a secretly famous way.
But not, you know.
But they don't know.
Who can possibly know?
All they know,
is that all this radio show stuff
is being done all the time,
all over the place.
And nobody knows where it comes from.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm detained at an airport in Istanbul.
Taken to an Istanbul police station for questioning.
The 2013 Rock and Roll Hall of Fame nominees
say Republican presidential hopeful Mitt Romney
could come loose during intimate same-sex campaigning in Ohio.
They say Google is in trouble.
They say they're illegally profiting from PR's reports.
But Google still must confront thousands of suspects today.
They say this is PR News.
So, will you be, do you have CDs to play on the Ask Dr. Hal of...
Well, I remember I sent a request to you with some material,
which I was hoping could be transferred to...
Oh, okay, sure.
You know, I didn't realize it was connected to your album.
I mean, boom.
I'm less than 12 hours.
...watching, but there's a hundred times as much as you can watch.
Yeah.
Which 10% should you watch?
Now it's...
See, that's the thing.
Information management is the key to the future.
How do you sift through all of just the subgenius channels?
You have to prioritize your...
Just the hundreds of channels that Stang runs on subgenius alone.
Only playing a few moments of subgenius.
Yeah, how do you possibly, in today's...
Well, it's an age-old problem, is that the...
How many...
You have to allocate your attention to the things that have the highest priority.
Because you've got a limited amount of attention.
Your capacity for attention is limited, and the time...
...subgenius business...
But your wants are infinite.
So what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
Yes, what are you going to do?
There we go.
Gonna steer her...
straight and true. I'm looking down into the
maw of the whole world. Somebody said
there's a pleasure saucer,
but I don't see anything down there.
Down there, it's partly concealed
under hundreds of tons of earth and rocks.
Yeah.
File here.
But according to a Native
American legend, it will emerge
one day.
Yeah, keep talking.
Oh, she wants a shiitake. Here you go.
Here's a portobello.
The only talking dog is shiitake,
who is now speaking
on the other channel.
You've been listening
to the Subgenius
Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack.
For free information,
write to
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio
or see
WC
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
A thank you,
Reverend Baby Bear.
And finally, Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
Slack is something
that's sometimes very ephemeral.
It only lasts for a second.
But sometimes slack can be
prolonged and drawn out.
The thing about slack is
it is never
truly achieved
until you reach the point
of realizing
that the only thing
that is important
at all
is right now.
Friends,
we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad
that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but
subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slack back
to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com
front page or especially
the radio page or the catalog
store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know
what it's like to be on the brink of
total poverty and we don't want any
subgeniuses to make their own situations
worse. But some of you
still have jobs.
Even $5
makes a big difference
even if it's only once a month
from enough of you.
$50 makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights.
Ohio.
Thanks for anything you can do to help
let there be slack.