What is God good for?
Call now and I'll rush you a free tape.
That's what we can count on God for.
A free tape.
No. No.
Yes. He did it.
He did it.
God is a content
By which we measure
Our pain
I'll say it again
God is a content
By which we measure
Our pain
Yeah. Pain. Yeah.
I don't believe in magic
I don't believe in I Ching
I don't believe in Bible
I don't believe in talent
I don't believe in and I'll say it again
I don't believe in Hitler I don't believe in Jesus
I don't believe in Kennedy I don't believe in Putin
I don't believe in
I don't believe in Maitreya I don't believe in Gita
I don't believe in Yoga
I don't believe in Kings
I don't believe in ideas
I don't believe in Elvis
I don't believe in Zimmerman
I don't believe in Beatles
I just believe in me
Local me
That's reality
The dream is over
What can I say?
Yesterday
I was the dream we found
But now I'm not born
I was the walrus
But now I'm John
And so dear friends
We'll just have to carry on
The dream is over
But dear friends, somebody else is just starting up
Look!
I know who it is!
I know who it is that doesn't belong among us!
I swear I know who it is!
It's...
The Self Genius Hour of Swag
Well that's not true!
S is for the suckers that live all around
U is for us, they're always putting us down
B is for Bob, he gives us our bread
G is for the guns they put to your head
E is for the eunuchs they want you to become
N is for the nuts they wish they had some
I is for that eye in the back of my head
U is for you, they wanna see you dead
S is for the shit that's all around
I'm a subtenuous motherfucker!
And I ain't no fucking clown!
In order to rule the world
You must first conquer it
Only on those bold terms
Can this total war
Result in total victory
Well don't you think it's a little late?
No
Well I do
I don't give a damn
Dead center
Yes, liberty reigns
I can't stand things that frighten me
That don't make any sense
Come on, let's get out of my brain
Yes, that's the right brain that was actually originated for people who were tired of pointing swords
The healing after Jesus was originated for your right brain
That's true
He's in a little can and we open him every 45 minutes
Now he's just squeaking
Be scary, call him
Stand back, stand back, okay
I was steering the ship toward the left
And you won't be able to
Now look out the window
See little people there?
See them?
No, stop
They're actually not people
They're a bad genius
They're there to scare you
They're in the human scrapyard
Please, if you're coughing all over your speakers
You're saying we've gotta clean it up here at the station
It is true there is a thing here I do not understand
There is a pain between my ears
For those who don't understand
Perhaps they're always on the short poopy end of the stick
Yes, the short poopy end of the stick
There's a lot of short doggy poop around to put on the stick
But if you want to live like a real man or woman
You must, you must
It is later than you think
It's later than you think
It is too hard
Than you
As chimpanzees are to humans
Humans are to us
Oh, hello
You're improving, Jack
You just can't seem to get rid of that streak of honesty in you
The one that ruined you was that damned Indian old Titi
You mean Olaskin
He gave you a vision of moral honor
And a vision of the order in the universe
And there isn't any
Those stars twinkle in a void, dear boy
And the two-legged creature schemes and dreams beneath them
All in vain
All in vain, Jack
Did you hear anything?
Listen to me
Two-legged creature won't believe anything
And the more preposterous the better
Whales speak French at the bottom of the sea
The horses of Arabia have silver wings
Pygmies mate with elephants in darkest Africa
I have sold all those propositions
And they were all fools and none of it matters
I slowly
Take theтоes
Now I've made the поверь
All my Andrea
Know내
Don'tNeack
I watched the world from an alien place
From a desert plain so far away
I hear the sound of the starlit night
Of an angel's song in a billion lights
Your world of people has no place for me
I've read the plea from an insane king
Your world of people suffocates me
It prisons me, it drowns me in ice
I watched the world from an alien place
From the tides of time and the shores of space
I stumble onward in a fever dream
In a landscape of lies, shaking a silent scream
Your world of people has no place for me
I've read the plea from an insane king
Awaken world, a little man
Of hatred, deeds, and evil
I watch the world from an alien place
Your world of people has no place for me
I watched the world from an alien place
From a desert plain so far away
I hear the sound of the starlit night
Of an angel's song in a billion lights
Your world of people has no place for me
I've read the plea from an insane king
Awaken world, a little man
Of hatred, deeds, and evil
I've read the world from an insane king
Awaken world, a little man
Of hatred, deeds, and evil
We're transforming this life
Asки and Sa
mosu
women, and these so-called culture.
But barbaric sinners think nothing of having their little bundles from God
hacked to pieces and flushed.
Never mind that God says thou shalt not kill, Exodus 20, 13.
Sinners have taken the matter into their own hands.
But remember, God holds the final trump card.
The judgment.
Revelation 20, verses 11 and 15.
10.
Mercy killers are also on the ascendancy in America.
They are progressive abortionists who have become hard to killing
and now wish to include the mommies and daddies along with their babies.
The honor of my father and mother getting God's command in Exodus 20, 12
interferes with it.
Their responsibility is so great.
The world does not know.
These six words must be related to Hitler.
My proclaiming fairy tales are both such thinking and planning exerts.
You be the judge.
So.
There you go.
That's like.
Doctors watching.
Right now.
What does this mean?
Here, wait.
You got to put your headphones on, Dave.
That one.
No, Warden, it's not in my booty.
You be the judge.
No.
But.
You be the judge.
You be the judge today.
But.
Judge tomorrow.
Compulsory death for all.
That's why the kids.
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
The problem with them TV preachers.
That's the problem with using your teeth for the needle on the turntable, man.
What makes people think they can flunk God's rules and end up in eternal bliss?
Flunk God's rules?
Yes.
What makes people think they can do that, Dave?
I don't know.
Flunking is easy, but flapping is harder.
Who do we think we are?
I got away with it so far.
I got away with it because Bob gave me something to get me off.
I got away with it.
Bob got me off.
And I got away with it.
I got away with dogs.
I got away with old ladies.
You got away with the bitches.
I got away with barbers with one eye.
I got away with three people's hands.
I got away with men who think they're Jesus Christ.
Then our brazen disregard of God's laws will be judged.
Revelation 22.15 declares,
Outside of heaven are dogs, sorcerers, whoremongers, murderers, idolaters, and whosoever loveth.
These are all the people from the lodge.
The dogmongers and the whores and stuff.
The day of the Lord is at hand.
And he shall come like a thief in the night.
Or he shall come somewhere or another.
The Lord cometh and the Lord goeth.
Come unto me, Bud.
This is your sugar daddy.
From his cat.
In the ever-loving great beyond.
So prick your ears up.
And be quick like to respond.
Cause daddy ain't too happy.
None too happy.
What did I ever create you for?
You ain't done nothing.
But make your daddy so.
It looks like evolution's no solution.
You just keep falling ever further behind.
You may be tanned and clean-shaven.
But ain't with little bit of hair in time.
Big hairy situation.
Every nation.
About to bring your daddy to his knees.
I just keep crying.
These people please.
You damn dirty apes.
What the hell are you doing?
Look at what.
You have done.
You damn dirty apes.
Who do you think you have been for days?
Cause I'm gonna catch you.
Gonna catch you.
Every one of you.
You damn dirty apes.
Gonna catch you now.
At the end of the mor.
Ready separately.
Based on palette and char,
for being you.
I thank you.
All thanks and a hundred Columbia.
Or.
guitar solo
Earthquakes, floods, and lightning
Very frightening
Oh, but that's just a little nervous twitch
But I'll be getting medieval
If you keep treating me like your bitch
So get yourself together
Now or never
Oh
All you need's a little self-esteem
To turn this nightmare
Into a sweet, sweet dream
You damn dirty ape
What the hell
Are you doing?
You damn dirty ape
Look at what
You have done
You damn dirty ape
Who do you think you have been
To win?
Cause I'm gonna get you
Gonna get you
Every one
I'm gonna get you
Get you every one
I'm gonna get you every one
And they are at this website, www.drexelent.com.
Drexelent.com.
That's D-R-E-X-E-L-L-E-N-T.
And now back to, well, some Lemur-ish cut-up collages,
puzzling evidences, howling over men, lonesome cowboys, and Chaz right here.
This is the night of the Holy Land.
So there's been all this talk in science.
Let's talk science for a minute.
Well, can I ask you one question, kind of a scientific question?
What?
Is it true that you've heard that there is a dangerous sorcerer or a demon,
perhaps it speaks from Dick Cheney's navel?
Really?
I don't think that's scientific.
Well, I don't think it is either.
I think it sounds like superstition.
It couldn't possibly be true.
It has nothing to do with it.
It sounds like an urban legend.
Oh, yeah, that's not science.
That's pseudoscience.
That's false science.
Okay.
But now scientists are pretty convinced that,
we're talking all about this lately.
The day of the Lord is at hand.
They're pretty convinced that we need to deprovincialize ourselves one step further.
And we thought that this universe was the only one,
and it turns out that they're pretty convinced that there's just multitudes of varied universes all existing.
They're real convinced of that, huh?
Well, if dogs.
If dogs can have multiple orgasms,
why can't we have multiple universes?
Mathematically.
So have you ever done the math with your slide rule and your calculator?
No, but I'm open to whatever.
You know, people come up with just as valid as anything I come across anywhere else.
That might as well be.
Well, yeah, and you know as well as I do that for all you know,
all that math that they keep talking about.
It's not real math.
It might as well be the same as the totem pole that some medicine man tells everybody to worship.
Maybe, but it's the best bet we got.
Well, it's an invasion.
I mean, it's a lettuce.
It's a lettuce.
It's farther than any of those other things have.
It's more like a money.
It took us to the moon.
We have probes going all over the universe.
What telephone poles have taken us to the moon, Larry?
I've been to the moon.
Not on a telephone pole.
Not the way you're talking about.
Yeah.
And I don't see no weird like eagles or thunderbirds on top of any ladder of numbers.
We're building a space station that got, you know, science.
You know, we understand a lot about a lot of things, DNA.
Well, Hitler almost built a science station with the world of fire and ice.
It's a lot farther than all the other.
You know.
Religions.
But Hitler built, almost built a science with fire and ice.
You've actually gotten things out of it.
Science is the most exacting religion.
They don't know what I'm talking about.
No.
The theory of fire and ice.
Hitler's theory of science was totally whacked out, and yet he produced all this weird.
Well, he didn't produce anything.
Well, they had the best Nazi flying saucers in the whole hollow earth.
Well, they believed in all this anti-grav stuff, but, you know, it didn't have any.
And they came out with that movie, Ilsa, She-Wolf of the SS.
Well, that was pure science right there.
For the CIA.
Now.
Who does?
Spelso?
Where are all those Nazi sonnets, dude?
No, they're on their 90s now.
I think they're too old unless they're taking Islan.
Amazing.
Islan?
Islan.
Your island paradise on the moon.
Attended to your every wish by a Nazi scientist from the year Zip.
Here's Klaus Friedrich, an early inventor of the U2, preparing to offer you a jelly donut.
Ah.
And here's you.
What?
Spending over a log in the hot sun as Ilsa, the She-Wolf of the SS, hands you her slide
roll.
God will make you his jelly donut.
And he has to.
In a country where freedom of religion is guaranteed by the Constitution, anything is
likely to develop.
Enter the Church of the Subgenius, filling itself as the weirdest cult on earth.
Like the one that's in the middle of the world.
What do they believe in?
Everything.
Who do they believe in?
A mysterious character named Bob.
Bob.
Bob is what will bring to, that's the plan of Earth.
And to you young man.
And to you if you will send a dollar.
If you send a dollar.
Another more.
Whether ocasional.
This is a church that does not play games.
And join the Church of the subgenious.
Genetic engineers working in secret laboratories.
You are going to relax.
Bob does not have body like Steel.
No, he doesn't even have a body.
He's still a head.
Yea, verily, for Bob should be praised.
He is being praised.
This is how we praise Bob.
This is how we polish Bob's mind.
This is the way we worship our Bob.
We take care of Bob like no one else.
Repeat after me.
No, you repeat after me.
Bob is ice.
Bob appears and Bob is light.
Bob is nice.
You know, just saying it doesn't make it so.
Bob is not nice.
Yea, verily.
I know, if Bob's looking in the window, are you the servant that opens it so he can piss in?
Weep no more.
Onions will no longer provoke tears.
I only know about it because I had to seek out the magic towel that night.
For Bob has arisen.
Well, you shouldn't have.
You should have been able to contain yourself.
Again and again and again.
It makes me want to go to Grandview Camping Center and watch.
Bob has arisen.
Bob never was.
He never goes down.
Sitting there by...
Really?
Bob is always up.
He's always up.
Always up, dude.
He never has to seek out the adult catalogs that other subgeniuses do.
And you must receive slack in Bob.
Those subgeniuses, too cheap to get on their own computer, must seek out...
Hey, now, you be nice to your little phone people.
Tiny little catalog.
At 848-4425-4520.
520.
520 man is mounted and moving.
No, let's not get dirty here.
Bob is...
Massively large, huge, erect collections.
Yes, indeed.
Moving toward bridge.
Oh, he's away from the bridge.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about it, Puzz-lean.
For the Puzzling Evidence Show, friends, and plus clips from the subgenius album Bad Doctors,
such as the song Mysterious Character named Bob by the great DK Jones, and now Half Man,
Half Biscuit.
Seriously, the following is a song by Half Man, Half Biscuit called 99% of Gargoyles Look Like Bob.
.
Jesus Christ, come on down.
Equilateral chainsaw
In debt I owe someone a fiver
Maybe I should try my hand at slag
James Dean was just a careless driver
And Marilyn Monroe was just a drag
99% of gargoyles look like bobtards
Mary had a little lamb
The doctors were astounded
Everywhere she went
Gynaecologists surrounded
They've been cooking on Blue Peter now
They're sampling the dishes
I don't normally like tomatoes, John
But this is delicious
99% of gargoyles look like bobtards
Take me home
The son of Jimmy Clithero is showing off his skills
He's shouting out
Where's my fur in chain?
The son of Jimmy Clithero is showing off his skills
He's shouting out
Where's my fur in chain?
Richard Li είe
I'm running guys
And my hand is just not enough
Richard Li shooter
Where's my fur on me?
Put it on
Thank you.
Don't tell me you're the future.
You'll be lucky to catch on at the phone company.
Your parents up there, you know what I'm talking about.
20, 25 years ago, they were telling us, you are the future.
You kids want to see the future?
Look at your folks.
Fat butts, saggy tits, beer, television, that's the future.
Look at me, I'm supposed to be a big success.
I built taco stands for a living.
What kind of bullshit future is that?
You got any sense?
Give them back their damn diplomas.
Give them back their silly fucking hats and stay 18 for the rest of your life.
You don't want to be the future.
No, no.
Forget the future.
The future sucks.
There he was.
Big as life.
Right there at the foot of my bed.
Jesus.
And he looked me straight in the eye and he said,
Want a drink?
There's more to love than just fornicating.
Sure, that's like eyes in the back of your head.
These mud-gobbling giant worms, which live on the edge of volcanic vents,
gorging themselves on massive huge piles of mud.
Just like those terrariums.
Just like the bacteria.
Just like the ones in Dune.
Only this mud is wet.
Biologists frequently say tiny worm.
This is truly wet mud.
Not like the kind of mud we used to have back when we were kids.
It was dry mud.
We used to have to make mud pies and to make them stick together we had to spit on them.
We'd like have dirt in one hand and a big pile of spit in the other hand and we'd like
roll them together until we had us a good mud pie.
Yeah.
And that was the only thing we had for moisture.
We had to take a bag of sugar back in those days.
Just spit.
Injecting worms with lab-made...
We didn't have candy back then either.
We had to just take a bag of sugar and carry it around a big old five pound bag of sugar
in our back pocket.
A big old tablespoon.
And when we needed some candy, we just stuck it into the bag and just took about four or
five big tablespoons, shoveled it down and that was all we had for candy back in those days.
Each one genetically engineered to make a different...
The show.
R.N.A.
All music.
Now when a worm dines on one of these babies...
You gotta have...
Those worms have to have lads to see underground when they're eating through the dirt like
that.
They carry little miner's helmets that let them mine through the dirt.
They're chewing, chewing, chewing, chewing.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
They chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away, chew away,
Oh, I can't see where I'm going, said Mr. Worm.
And he looked ahead and he had his little pointed knife.
He had his little yellow helmet on shining the way into the back of the goose, as it
were.
The pterodactyl...
The end of the goose.
...was a Cretaceous flying reptile.
Flying...
They thought it was a reptile, but actually it was a bird.
Although its wings spread and it shaved more than 27 feet.
It was a bird.
They found that it was only a simple bird.
It was a bird-like reptile.
Its body was only the size of a goose.
And yet its wings were 900 feet wide.
It was a bird.
It was a bird, yeah.
I mean, it was a bird.
We're talking about an entire century.
I'm not sure that it's a bird, but I'm not sure that it is a bird.
It's the Twinkie Bike.
Oh, well, it's a.
It's the widest proportion.
27 feet.
Or 30, actually.
Where's Bozo?
They asked me about Twinkies on my show, and they asked what the ingredients were.
Of course, all I could tell them was golden sponge cake and creamy fillings.
That's all you need to know.
You don't need to know anything more.
That is all on Earth you know and all you need.
We'll enter that in the computer.
Golden life.
That's good enough for Thor.
That's good enough for me.
The United States of Sponge.
Creamy, soft, whipped.
Yes, little caller, you have won the United States of Sponge.
Throwing everywhere in the valley.
As we continue to look for your requested songs, squeezing the commercial songs of the United States of Sponge.
Within the confines of its donut-like home.
Is it a bird?
No!
Is it a plane?
Oh my gosh, it's my name, I'm Brian.
The way I hide.
The way I wait all the way.
Oh!
Is it a bird?
No!
Is it a plane?
Oh my gosh, it's my name, I'm Brian.
The way I hide.
The way I wait all the way.
The Way I play.
The Flat Dog Singers and now Limur.
Now you listen to this!
Can I still have my dog?
No!
Oh no! Please!
Oh my gosh!
Hey, Boggs!
I have a special report on the camps to make to the Ministry of Education.
For the children.
Tally-tally!
You get 152 hits.
It may sound silly to you, but...
Something bothering you, boy?
Nuclear death.
Oh, God!
Oh!
Okay.
And I take it this place, this Mabel Street, is not unique by no means.
While we were in Italy, this woman walked up to my friend and threw my friend a baby.
And when my friend caught the woman's baby,
her other kids ran up and took what was in my friend's...
pocket.
So, um...
Let that be a tip for you, you know, if you're ever in Italy and, uh...
Someone throws you a baby,
swat it to the ground.
Swat it to the ground and scream,
I don't think so!
I'm just trying to take a bite out of crime.
The Lord took...
took the child.
He died a horrible death.
The awfulness...
of it...
staggers the imagination.
We're going to be using this corpse for a demonstration of placement.
And she looked at me and said...
She's dead.
I said, what do you mean?
She said...
She...
No, Sid.
I said, I went out of my mind.
And she looked at me and said...
I went...
to see...
the others.
And she said...
You don't have to be afraid of him.
That's all there is to it.
Rew, rew.
Ah!
Now I can't take it anymore!
Friends, are you going to let this happen?
Are you just going to sit by and watch this corpse rot?
Are you going to scrub its buttocks with a dog?
And apply mouth-to-mouth resuscitation to this rotting corpse in his WCSV?
Which do you want?
Prefer?
Don't you want to get down there and apply the kiss of life?
You guys are worthless.
I know we are.
Get out of here.
Don't you want to...
Get out of my radio station.
Let's go.
I'm going home.
Man, we cannot get one lousy carnivution.
My friends, I was in the spirit.
And Bob said to me, Sid, I'm going to have to call you home right now.
I'm Reverend Stangen.
I don't think he meant home to Texas.
How about?
I think he meant home to heaven.
A beautiful home away from heaven.
If he says because it's the only way to send a signal to these people because they don't
seem to believe.
Look it.
There's the gate.
You can travel there on a signal.
I'm being called home, friends.
A beam of light.
Bob's calling me up.
Now I see the rocking chair of eternal slack up there on that beautiful cloud.
Oh, yes.
Why, look.
There's...
Oh, yes, brother.
Look at how beautiful it is.
There's beautiful creatures of the desired sex.
Oh, yes.
And the sky is gyrating around the heavenly excremeditation throne.
And then just when you're in the gate, you thought you were in the gate in the heaven.
You made the ultimate mistake.
You didn't call 68769.
Oh, you could have.
That's the funny thing about it.
You could have at any minute.
Your family's thinking about it now.
Even after the ship is gone.
Oh, if you only would have sent his contribution.
You could have.
You could have had a coffee mug.
A beautiful logo shirt on.
Maybe for a new Twitter account.
But you blew it.
You fool.
Man, you totally blew it.
God, I can't believe what a geek.
How could anybody totally, totally, totally, utterly, utterly...
Well, all I remember was he had a chance to get one of those warm sweatshirts on.
And you were warned.
You were told, don't blow it.
Don't mess up.
And you messed up.
Because you didn't call 6900 in the 216 area code.
Oh, man.
Did you blow it, dude?
So that sweatshirt.
No, no, you didn't get that either.
And so he told...
Well, you know, and the 6900, the number itself you will get if you're not having sex and
you don't have anybody loving you lately.
If you just call that number 6900, 6900, because it's like, that's it.
It's synergy.
No, no.
Because 69ing is like...
It means belly button.
Yeah, 69, we each get something out of it.
You know what I mean?
Like it's an old...
Oh, there it is again.
Here they come.
Here they come again.
Oh, bleeding straight in the ass.
Oh, they drove us out.
There they go.
They never come around for long.
We don't want to touch you.
We want to rub your little round belly, listener.
We want to reach out with our fingers over these hair waifus.
We want to reach out with our fist and bust you in the face if you don't call.
We want to fist you, my dear friend.
We're going to fist you right in the face.
I tell you what, I don't want to do that.
You smell your feet from all the way across the escheleta.
Vino, vi-vi-vino.
Yes, I believe that Jesus Christ is a succulent, delicious, flavorful, juicy, tender son of
God the Messiah.
And I'll tell you what, because I was that desperate.
And this other male, he's being stimulated by the mating activity and he wants to have
a go too.
Oh, that's so sweet.
And everybody knows that.
Varusia Control speaking.
Go ahead.
We have a rhino.
Anything else?
He's bleeding pretty badly.
No, that's all.
I saw these guys.
A roller rink.
I saw the, um...
Who is this now, the Flat Yorn Angels?
It's, um...
Andy in the Walls.
Dick Clark, Dick Clark.
Yeah, Andy in the Walls.
Andy, it's Andy.
I saw the plastic exploding bananas at a roller rink in Columbus, Ohio, when I was a sparse lad of nearly 58 years old.
I was wearing chicken shoes at the time, and Nico noticed me in the front row.
She waved and threw some barbiturates to me.
She also rubbed that hefty groin of hers with a large red Italian scarf.
I wonder what that meant.
You think that could mean anything?
No, right.
Stop trying to see, you know, deep, hidden meanings in everything.
In what she does and everything, I guess.
Anything.
I guess I should stop.
Reality.
There is no reality.
No, I guess there is no.
I thought you were going to say all reality is interpretive, but you said there is no reality.
No, everything's relative.
Right.
We're not talking about Homeland Security or the black holes that could envelop us in a hundred billion years.
Who even knows which universe we're in at any given moment?
Right, right.
I mean, you know, right.
You know, you're here, you're there, you know.
Speak for yourself, man.
I am.
I'm stuck in the sand.
I've been in the same one this whole time.
Yeah, talk about strange.
I'm pretty sure of it.
Except for that one time when alternate universe man did his trick just to prove he could do it.
Attention!
Our next witness is Paul.
Oh.
R-O-T-S.
Thank you.
Clueless.
And we look forward to your testimony, Mr. Miller.
Today's hearing is important.
To the office furniture industry for four reasons.
Mr. Chairman, let me conclude by saying thank you.
You took a leave of absence with three children and a wife and a girlfriend on the side.
Bless his little heart.
How did you afford a leave of absence?
Pretty drunk.
Thank you, Mr. Donald DeRossi, who was established in 1927.
Thank you.
I'm back at home.
And so there they are.
Mr. Chairman, let me conclude by saying Teletubby.
Oh no, please.
Eyes burning like coals.
The bloodsucker affects me more.
Holy catfish.
That's awful.
Hey.
Where would my dad get rid of a body?
There's just one little thing you're forgetting, college boy.
You buried him too.
That was funny.
How you doing on time?
I'm going to need a little more time.
I will wrap up very quickly.
Thank you.
The purple dinosaur who has been called everything from refreshingly sweet to nauseatingly nerdy.
Well once again, rule toddler TV.
Menacing the Teletubbies.
I believe that the Teletubbies are, their time is on this, they are definitely.
Never seen them actually.
Their days are numbered.
They may as well put a fork in the Teletubbies once Barney hits the scene again.
Did you see this subgenius?
Hooded robe?
Subgenius hooded robe?
Clearly made to intimidate and impress and I'm guessing it dates 1980.
What's its origin?
The best item of its kind I've ever encountered.
Unfortunately, we have no information identifying the subgenius.
Robe is of excellent quality and thin black wool, 58 inches long from the neck, nine button
front, buttons are silver colored.
Permanently affixed to the neck is a 14 inch tall hood which comes to a point at the top
rear and then goes 10 inches forward to its front.
Which falls the face mask with one size fits all.
Wow.
For the men that want something extra.
At the top, the center of the hood, which would be at the top of the forehead is a white
two and a half inch by two and three quarter inch embroidered Dobbs face.
This is not amazingly boring stuff.
This is the real thing.
The bezel is amazing.
Has wavy white embroidered edge.
Yeah, this thing is on the back is a 12 inch high red inverted pipe.
Does it have the flap in the back?
With a white yarn flame.
How much does it cost?
That's the important thing.
How much are they charging?
It's $477.
Does it have the pyroflatulation flap in the back?
But it may be so ancient that it would fall apart.
It sounds like it's actually real.
Because if you didn't have that flap and it cost $475, you could risk actually igniting
it if you weren't careful.
Yeah, from some secret society or order.
Look at it.
This piece of hood.
With a skull and crossbones.
He thinks they like him, but when the UFOs come, the ladies are going to kill everybody
but me.
Well, you know, of course they'll spare the righteous.
That's what all subgeniuses think.
I'm helping channel the thoughts of all subgeniuses onto the show.
That means no one will be spared.
And no one will call.
They don't need to go to Brushwood.
The saucers will come and pick them up wherever they are.
They'll be instantly materialized.
It'll be like a rapture of subgenia.
Yes, thank you.
This is right now.
We're looking at a picture of all the subgeni sitting in their pretend first class seats
on the space shuttles, ready to leave.
Mysterious and threatening secret clan or society hooded rogue.
I was just telling you, it's a subgenius rogue from the early 70s.
Well, it certainly looks like a terrifying, intimidating.
It does, it does.
That's back when they used to paddle the pledges and all that stuff.
Yeah, we used to make them run the gauntlet.
The famous naked woman gauntlet.
We used to run them through.
They hated that.
Those bobbies.
They always hate stuff because they're nerds.
They're nerds.
And they're so competitive among themselves.
That's what's so pathetic about it.
They fight for the little place in the subgenius organization.
Just because the average weight of each of those women was well beyond 300 pounds, that
shouldn't have any effect on it if they were, you know.
Or where Philo has worked for a million years.
Thinkers.
Thinkers from beyond the sun.
The competitive world.
On the backside of reality.
Conspiracy biz.
Forbidden fantasies that boil up in a...
I don't know.
Drenched sunburst of fun and relaxation.
Rest and relaxation at last.
I don't feel relaxed.
This show makes me all tense and itchy.
From rest and sleep.
Which...
Yeah, you can earn money even while you sleep with our custom, sensual cyber brain pan turnkey
operation website.
And sooner or later.
We'll hire our best men with thee to go.
You will be on the cutting edge when you process those credit cards with 60% fulfillment.
We need to start one of those websites with just our own DCDs on them.
You must be 210 years...
I would slave to kidnaps, wars, and desperate men.
What do these spacemen want from us?
I mean, what are we negotiating for?
I mean, is it a good deal?
Is that what you want to know?
Yeah, I want to know.
What, are you trying to second guess the negotiating team, Bob?
Is that it?
I just want to know if it's worth the trouble I'm going through.
I don't want to waste my time if all we're going to get out of it is a few pictures of
space or something.
Okay, okay, I'll tell you.
Here, write this down.
All right.
All life on earth is going to be dead in five years.
Now, skip over to the other side and write this down.
What's this?
This is what they want.
Just write it down.
All the flowers, all the trees, all the little birdies.
Oh, and all the children.
That's it?
Yep.
Yeah, they're not as dedicated as we are, Bob.
You know, they have no incentives, no motivation.
What's this?
It's a vinyl map to show us where we're going to pick them up.
Well, we better not lose this.
I'd say, Bob.
I'll turn this story into a hurry if you don't mind.
Stargate.
One million forgotten BC.
Monsters.
Captain's Lord.
Monsters have taken over the interface once again.
And I and Mr. Stargate are going to be the first ones to get out of this.
Mr. Spook are helpless to do anything about it.
Visitors are requested not to throw coffee into the basin.
Irritating, Captain.
The censors have eliminated all the blue passages from my sex novel.
Still poking that big nose of yours and the things that concern you.
Okay, caller.
You fly Lieutenant Uhuru.
That nose is quite large.
I fail to see what the size of my nose has to do with the problem that we are facing
now.
You can be like the queen on Sex Planet.
What is it about my nose that makes you constantly comment on its prodigious size?
Do it.
I'm going to do it.
I never did watch Star Trek, so I don't know all the different characters.
What is it about my nose that constantly brings great attention?
Darth Vader was on it.
Darth Vader was on Star Trek?
Blast you, Spook.
Cool, man.
You know that your nose is in front to all decent Earth men?
Weird.
I'm picking up like...
That's what you keep telling me.
Are you out of your Vulcan mind, Spook?
Oh, I get it.
He doesn't have a mind, right?
Is that the joke?
A mind is a terrible thing to waste.
When the baby is done drinking, it must be unscrewed and laid in the basin.
I'm going to put the baby in a cool place under a tap.
If the baby does not thrive, I'll push Spook into the...
This cheesy nut butter is the cause of the alien's antagonism.
You know, I'm sorry.
I just...
I think I just sat on the racist peanut butter cups.
Boiled.
You did that on purpose.
I saw you.
Boiled.
Just so I could have them all.
I think you filled the racist peanut butter cups.
Oh, he figured out my point.
All right, all right.
Yeah, yeah.
Look at that.
Da-na-na-na-na-na-na.
I want to thấy the theme of my old movie, A Special
Voyage to see what's on the bottom.
Space.
The final frontier.
A bunch of old crafty stars pretending to go out in the ice
of the Starship KPFA.
It's continuing mission to boldly explore to smash-up the entire
starогдаove.
That's the monster that comes out and attacks the whole,
ship.
ật
Gott
what?
What kind of ship is that?
Every week there's a curtain out on the ship.
It pitches and rolls.
Everyone falls out of your seat.
Here's a harder one.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hard is right.
Oh, my seat.
Well, friends, Dr. Howell and the show there on KPFA.
Before that, a clip sent by the bishop.
And tons of Lemurian collage.
And remember, friends, you can always check out www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write to me at post office box 181417.
That's 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang.
And now Christopher Hyatt with the late occult scholar.
Israel Regardie.
The guru hymn.
This is a hymn dedicated to the grinning, giggling monkey guru.
Now, this is bliss consciousness.
Now, we have the roots of the tree.
This is the trunk of the tree.
These are the branches of the tree with the pretty leaves.
Now, in order to get bliss consciousness,
we must walk.
This is the root of the tree.
When the roots are watered, the bliss rises up the trunk of the tree into the branches
of the tree into the leaves.
When this happens, we have bliss consciousness.
Now, bliss consciousness is something that your mother will approve of.
Unlike sex and other sad things, this fits right on in with her.
She loves bliss consciousness.
Bliss consciousness.
Uh, pig.
Pig.
There is a happy land far, far away
Where little piggies grow three times a day
Oh, you should see them run when they see the butcher come
Two cut slices off their bum three times a day
This is dedicated to bliss consciousness.
Yep.
Ah.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Oh, shit, oh dear
Where'd you been?
I've been looking for you. Where've you been?
I've been looking fro you! Where've you been?
YouTube.com
I've been lookin for you! Where've you been?
I've been looking for you! Where've you been?
Oh, there you are!
Oh!
What do you want?
I was wondering. Where've you been?
Fans.
инки başı.
Bob Bob's Bob.