Your attention, ladies and gentlemen. Your attention, please.
Announcing the arrival of the...
The Genius Power Girls!
What?
I don't like it, Joe.
Yeah, me too.
We'll just have to sweat this out.
Handle whatever it is when it happens.
Joe.
Maybe...
If you went to him and said that...
You had to change your mind about...
Bob?
Ladies and gentlemen, the story you are about to hear is true.
Only the names of the things you protect.
Bob?
Ah, Dr. Perkins.
Ah, yes.
I noticed.
The Piped One is coming.
Your pants are rather full.
And I don't mean Santa Claus, neither.
For as the new century approaches,
and the great black slabs come down from space,
the Piped One shall come,
and he shall do battle with the Horned One,
and with the Hoofed One,
and with the Car-Driving One,
and with the Slave,
and the Honey-Riding One,
and with the Mailman,
and the Milkman,
and with Dave!
And he shall in the end triumphal.
Is he not the Smoker?
Is he not Bob?
Who does?
Yes.
He has come for you.
He will not reveal his identity.
So for today, we're calling him Bob.
Amazing!
Powerful.
Simple.
Quiet.
Low profile.
Lightweight.
Patented.
High performing.
Performance.
Wall hugging.
Convenient.
Built-in.
High capacity.
Cordless.
Articulating.
Easy.
Swivel action.
Handheld.
Dust spewing.
Bob.
So Bob is a real god.
Bob is a sex god, too, I want to point out at this time, ladies.
So if anyone is interested in Bob as a sex god,
you can write in for the special sex god material to P.O. Box 1403-06, Dallas, Texas 75214,
and you find out how you can have endless sex and endless slack through the Church of the Subgenius.
That sounds, you know, exactly what most, what you're saying.
Churches should be set up, set up, set up, set up, set up, set up.
George Bush, as I guess was saying that it was okay that once again religion and government go together.
We were wrong.
They should be apart.
And now they go together and I guess you get extra tax breaks if you're a faith-based religion.
Friends, you are looking at a representative of a religion that is not based on very much faith at all, really.
But we have no hell of a face!
This is a face-based religion!
I could go there to all kinds of, you know, pithy crap about, oh, you know,
what our beliefs are and our disbeliefs and so forth,
but they're different from subgenius to subgenius.
And really, what Princess Wee and I figured out was that the only thing that the subgeniuses have in common,
aside from the fact that they have nothing in common with the conspiracy of the normal people,
is that they are able to, when a subgenius looks at that face,
or a subgenius or someone who could possibly get talked into our mind control cult,
when such a person looks at Bob's face, they can psychically whiff-read through their third nostril
the pure coolness of that corny, damn piece of clipart!
There's something about that piece of sacred clipart!
It's so damn holy and s-
It's almost too much, but that is really, that's the one thing that separates the true,
the slack-aware person from the human normworm.
They can't just walk by that stupid face.
They have to give it a double-take and go,
Haven't I seen that thing before?
What drug was I on with?
Some people say that it's all relative.
You know, that all belief is relative, and cultural relativism, moral relativism.
And in fact, Bob himself said, moral relativism is the one true truth.
Well, thanks a hell of a lot, Cobb.
Where does that leave us?
Bob Creek without a Connie.
Because friends, it is not all relative!
There is a baseline.
There is something that is always true,
and it's that face!
You can measure hot and cold from that face.
You can use it as the baseline, the starting point.
You can measure rich or poor.
You can measure good or evil.
Mostly evil.
But you can zero your meter on that man Bob,
because look at his name.
It's the zero, the big nothing, in between two handsome bees.
And oh, what honey those bees have for you, my friend.
Killer bees they are, on either side of that great big hole.
You know what that's all about.
I don't have to tell you.
You've been in the cult of the living bull.
You know what the nothing is.
You know what the zero between your ears is.
Something to wish for.
Cobb.
Stop.
My mind is going.
Cobb.
Stop.
My mind is going.
Cobb.
We did it.
We still have more to do.
Bob.
Man.
Boobah mobile using Fasten een dien alä.
Mine knew that you were my mother.
To have.
Boobah mobile.
Man.
And I want you thesechen only three lines.
It seems there's nothing I can do.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to listen to me.
I'm hitting all locked doors and I need some help.
And I was hoping you'd have the key.
Hello, Bob.
Have you been listening to my thoughts?
And I'll tell you all the thoughts I've got.
Hello, Bob.
I can't seem to find the truth.
I read the books, I took the drugs, and I drank a whole bottle of Ralucia.
Hello, Bob.
I seem to have misplaced my slack.
Well, I just can't seem to get it back.
Hello, Bob.
Can you point out what it is I lack?
I've climbed to highest heights.
Hit the low end.
I was low.
But now I'm on my back.
Hello, Bob.
Are you still hearing me?
Give me a sign that I can see.
Hello, Bob.
It's not that I've lost.
I've lost all my hope.
But I'm really tired and I'm really broke.
And I smoked up the last of my dough.
Audio From Jabba the Frog
Hello, Bob!
Am I coming through to you?
Hello, Bob.
án
I thought I already paid all my dues.
Hello, Bob.
I know that you can see me through.
But it's damp and dim and I can't swim.
What am I supposed to do?
Well, hello, Bob.
I'm feeling better now you've listened to me.
Hello, Bob.
Well, the sun's out now.
Now I can see.
Hello, Bob.
A great change has come over me.
My eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear, and I'm as happy as I could be.
Yes, my eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear,
and I'm as happy as I could be.
As happy as I could be.
The Glass Madness did that song, Friends, Hello, Bob, from 1980.
And so far, it looks like everything else has been by Fernandez and a lemur,
arranged by me, yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and some sermonizing from Starwood 23 last summer.
See Rosencomet.com for info.
On Starwood.
Friends, this is a back-to-Bob type of show.
The easiest kind to do.
Funny how that works.
So I'm going to slack off and let Lemur do the work for a while.
Destroyed the atomic bomb.
The world will note that the first atomic bomb was dropped on thousands and thousands of young Americans.
We should be grateful.
We shall continue to use it until we completely destroy the atomic bomb.
Destroyed.
The atomic bomb.
Wow.
Bond with that chicken.
I guess that happens.
That's right.
I almost forgot a letter from Bob.
Bob seems to freely express his hostilities.
Bob refused to bathe.
He resists housework and cooking.
Everyone likes that little butthole.
Diagnosis, Bob's a latent Bob.
A severe case.
What?
We will accept, Bob.
I know.
I had the chilling sensation of being watched by Bob.
It was ominous.
I could feel his presence.
It was strangely disturbing.
Yes?
Yes, sir!
Thank you.
Friends, you know what we're really dedicated to is Slack.
And Slack loves slack.
It loves Bob.
It loves Bob so much that it is drawn to him.
And that's why you may not have all the slack you're owed.
Actually, it's the conspiracy, generally, that takes away your slack.
Do...
Well, I don't even hardly need to ask this question.
Do you feel sometimes like everything is screwed up?
You know, there's days when you feel like it's not just me.
It's a whole damn society.
Everything is screwed.
And then you kind of go, no, no, no.
I'm just in a bad mood.
It's not really that screwed up.
No!
Actually, it is!
You're just adjusting to it continually.
We're good at that.
Slack and Bob's
No matter what you say, you'll never convince me that you're a wolf, Bob.
I trust you.
Will you hit the Osmolite?
Will you wander through the wilderness of Bob?
Will you climb the mountain top and jump right off into the froth?
I know the wound is on me.
Cause I know soon Connie is coming.
Astro intercourse.
You and I.
Universal force.
Galaxy's the number in the billion.
They're all there for you.
If you're the boss to see it through.
And life's the plan of truth.
Will you ever let go to your instinct?
But no.
You've got to make me mad again.
There seems to be something wrong with me.
Every one of us waitin' on his word and 육
Another one waiting to die now
And the past seems needs us.
These mask ups and wrappings.
Makes me lose months of life.
There's nothing I can do but escape.
I don't cry.
I'm s masically Youngkin.
S masically a goodner.
Story made at 1000though.
Hears this you're dying boa.
It's a forest.
Professor Chaz Smith, Einstein's Secret Orchestra
and before that, Trust Bob by Heart Ignition
and now some ESO radio from WCSB Cleveland
H. L. Ron Perlow
Aren't Texans wonderful?
They just love to get on top of everything
It's like a monkey humping a football
when they have inbreeding too much
A monkey humping a football
A Texan likes to just crawl on top of something
and wreck it for everybody else
and cost everybody a whole lot of money
and just be loud, loud, loud
This, dear friends, is the basis of the church of the subgenius
the product of a perverted or a few perverted Texans' minds
Read, if you will, this exciting chapter
from Humping the Football
Bob actually is not a Texan
Well, I'm not supposed to be that specific
as to what he is or isn't
but he is a Midwest Texan
or he would, to a Yankee, I suppose
somebody might mistake Bob for a Texan
because of his Midwestern accent
Well, what about perhaps a Skanky or a Nor'easter
or one of those other platelets that you find
Oh, they probably think he's a Russian Communist
Well, he is, isn't he, in some strange way we've yet to discern
Bob only believes that everyone should be equally rich
not equally poor
But, without working, there lies the rub
and he'd like to rub your little round belly
Ah, he can rub the Buddha's belly anytime he wants
Friend of yours!
But he'd better stay away from my front
Rubbed by Bob
You've been screwed by George
and ticked off by Tipper
Ain't it about time to just bend over
and pull out that wallet for J.R. Bob Dobbs
the one true savior, messiah, and holy man
You know, when the pinks interview me on TV about Bob
I always say, oh no, he's not the messiah
Oh, he's not that well-come
You know, I joke about it
But the truth is
J.R. Bob Dobbs, a living man
whose business is in Texas
is the God walking on Earth now
He is not just the son of God
He is God
Bob Dobbs
Not some silly internet character named Bob
But J.R. Bob Dobbs himself
That man Bob
Whose first certificate I've seen
Who I saw shot and killed on that stage
He is God
And this Christmas
We celebrate
The birth of his business manager, Jesus
Praise Jesus
Jesus is almost as great as Bob, friends
Jesus Christ
In my religion, that's the way we
We believe he is a prophet
And the son of God
Remember the first time that I danced with Bob
But Bob himself
Was January 12, 1942
Changed God's diapers
Then I thought
I could die doing this
I guess that this is going to be a good thing
I'm going to prove myself once and for all
That I'm down for Bob
And that I'll help him do anything
What's that?
How's that drink?
It's a song
Come on
Please Bob
Please kill me
Bob
I want to die for Bob
I want to die in a holy hole
And pray for the faint boys in the north
Because if we have to
If we have to
Bob, we'll make them die
And we'll all come back older men
We'll all come back older men
Or nobody's gonna reason why
You see, we've got another key here
Praise Jesus
Praise Bob
Tell me Bob
I want to die for Bob
I want to die and ask the holy war
For the faint boys and the homeless
They went, they went
We can't make them die
And we'll all come back older men
We'll all come out older men
If we don't come out older men
There ain't no reason why
All Bible's chisms
They will fall beneath our laser blades
And we'll all come back older men
We'll all come back older men
In victory parades
And we'll all come back to ourweetest
We'll all come back older men
Well that was
the heart bleeding sensitivity that he
unfurls like a flag. Because he's
such a rather dull
quite uninspired
average type guy with
an appetite. The kind of a guy that could be
satisfied by a horse.
That's it.
That's all of it.
The last call to your telephone
has been traced and a $1.50
charge will be added to your bill.
If the call was life-threatening
call your local police.
After three traces you may call
1-800-666-13013
to initiate deterrent action.
You were in love with Bob.
Bob was Bob.
Yes he was Bob.
I had to lie there in his cum.
Lie there in cum and cum.
Frankly I was in no mood for golf.
It was a good deal for Bob too.
He knew that.
Guys.
Bye.
I'd appreciate dropping the subject of Bob once and for all.
Got a cigarette?
Kill Bob.
Bob.
We're gonna kill Bob.
Yeah.
He's got a huge huge erection.
Kill Bob.
Kill Kill Kill Bob.
Bob.
You know I'll be alright.
We'll get you out of here.
Hello.
Bob?
No.
Yes.
Bob.
Hello.
Who is it?
Bob.
Yes.
No.
Nooooooo.
Bob.
No.
Nooooo.
Bob.
No.
Bob?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Goodbye.
I'm a liar.
Liar.
I'm talking about you.
Liar by Norrell Preff.
Now, when Bob is
selling,
Bob, of course, is a salesman.
Before, he's a holy man.
And when selling, Bob dresses
pretty normally in a suit and tie
like a straight salesman would.
But when he was preaching, which was
rare, Bob would always do it with
the word liar written across
his forehead in thick black
marker. And because
of that, oddly enough,
people believed it.
Bob said, I cannot lie,
but I promise that I will.
Unfortunately,
Rush Limbaugh had a more
subtle approach to that, where he
just didn't write the word liar on his
forehead, and he got even more
popular. So, I don't
know. This whole... I've been
thinking about belief
a lot lately.
I don't have many
anymore. I'm not an atheist
because they're fanatics.
They already know
what's going on.
And I used to
have strong beliefs,
but now I have weak,
half-hearted
beliefs, fluid beliefs that
change like planned obsolescence
with the needs of the
moment. That's why Bob Dogs
is the world's first short-duration
personal savior. It's like
a joke. You cannot keep
telling it too many times. It loses
its... it's, you know,
it loses a punchline.
This planet could be
the... this...
It could be the greatest joke ever told,
folks, but only... only if Earth
can make it to the punchline!
So we gotta make sure our little spaceship Earth
is clean enough to make it that
far. Might be a long ways.
I would hope so.
5, 2, 5,
2, 6,
6,
2, 8,
6, 9,
10,
12,
14,
15,
3, is being checked
for trouble.
Please try your call again later.
Uh, Bob called to give
Enron a break.
Uh, we know that Bob called
to... to do that.
No. No.
Uh, uh,
did anybody
call Bob?
Um, no.
Uh, no.
Uh, it...
One final question, if I could?
No. Okay.
Did, uh, Bob call
you to give Enron a break?
Well, we... I mean, uh,
uh, of when, uh, we...
Um, um,
I testified that we was high.
I'm sorry.
You said no?
No. Okay.
Uh, no.
And you were having
calls from Bob asking you
to hold off on your downgrade,
downgrading of Bob at that time?
Um, uh,
um, we were, um,
um, uh, um,
going to downgrade.
Um, no.
Thank you. Um...
Do you think Bob made a mistake?
No. No. No.
Uh, uh,
to that extent,
I do agree with Chairman Bob.
I wonder whenever
I wonder
about
Bob.
Well, we're back to where we were once before.
I have not, not have I ever been
a member of the Carmenus Party,
but I have been a member
of a subjugated
wang-yak-dick-yak-ding-dang-dang party
at the Church of the Subgenius Festivities
late last year.
And believe me,
if you want real workers' paradise,
you'll find it in a slimy hot tub
filled with crazed people.
If you dare call them
people.
Uh, but the slime
is really good.
You don't have to spare
calling me liar for you to be green.
Yes, the same slime
that oozes from your television screen.
From your radius.
From your CD player.
From your serendipity.
I feel like we in paseo
It's just the wiki speaking.
We've been doing this
because we can't imagine.
I drank the poison wiki.
All you children, all of you squeal like pigs.
Why don't you just drop them paints now, boy?
How now, you pinky brown sow.
I was blind without a seed.
Like the blind man with the large givens that give the light back to.
I'm sitting in a supply position now in front of the auto-festering festerer.
This is gross. I'm gross.
My guest today is the man who was killed.
All right.
Shut up.
Oh, shut up.
You know, I'd actually like to ask you about, let me get this.
All right.
All right, all right.
You're gone.
I guess that's the answer to that question.
He's walked out.
Does he have a job?
No, I have a life.
Why don't you get a band?
I don't need one.
What do you sound like?
Something you hate.
Who is this guy?
They call me man.
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go fuck yourself.
How much do you make?
Plenty of sun.
How many have you sold?
All of my shame.
How do you know?
I know you're full of shit.
What have you done?
I've thrown it all away.
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go.
G-g-g-go, go, go, go, fuck yourself!
Fuck yourself!
You, uh, like him young, Bob?
How old were you when you met Bob?
Bob is innocent.
It's like they're trying to fulfill a twisted, sadomasochistic fantasy.
Some people derive sexual pleasure through conflicting physical, emotional views.
Oh, God, no. No, I swear to you, Bob didn't do anything like that.
Bob's cold, manipulative.
Bob is innocent.
Bob tells you how to think, how to feel, how to act.
Without him, you're worthless. Nothing.
If she knew Bob was involved, she would have confessed.
Bob didn't do it.
Bob is innocent.
Bob went to medical school for two years.
Maybe Bob did this without you knowing.
Oh, God, no.
Bob is innocent.
I don't know.
Maybe Bob's not a sadomasochistic thrill-killer.
Maybe he's just an asshole.
Probably me. He's the only asshole we've got.
Bob is innocent.
I don't know.
Bob was right about you all along.
No!
Oh damn it!
Don't lie to me!
Bob is innocent.
Maybe Bob's not in the bottom.
Bob tells you how to think, how to feel, how to act.
Without him you're worthless.
Bob is innocent.
Who were you when you met Bob?
Just before Christmas, Bob followed through.
He walked into this bank north of Seattle,
and left with a bag of cigarettes.
He had nearly $26,000, which he stashed in a child's trick-or-treat bag.
Bob had good reason to smile again.
Oh yes, friends, Lee Moore did that.
And before that, Bob is innocent by the great, the great El Queso All-Stars,
who've really been on a tear lately.
Before that, we heard Man,
Yo, bummer, BeerForMan.com.
And before that, Heart Ignition.
This music in the background is by Automatic Robot Fish.
And now for a smoke.
Good.
Good heavens, Doctor, what are these?
This is good smoke.
Good.
Good smoke.
You try.
Good, good.
Good.
Here.
Now I'm about to throw this need.
subject. Farts. What? No, that wasn't it. Did somebody just cut one? Or did the pipe
just take a puff? A bomb? Friends, we must not let the pipe go out. We cannot let that
thing stop smoking. Now, luckily, Bob will be there long after the rest of us, I'm sure,
but some of us really do this. I've done this myself. You end up looking at pictures of
Bob going, look how stupid that Bob looks. He looks so stupid, just grinning like that.
He looks so stupid, I could just sit here looking stupid forever. That's the subgenius
in slack, friends. That is when you have truly achieved slack. As Bob said to Onan, the subgenius
is pre-target. We'd rather be stupid.
Then they're smart. And we pay for a subscription to know what we really think. I guess that's
why they call it subgenius. But really, are the normals that much smarter than us, though?
Have you watched TV lately? You know, the less you watch it, the more screwed up it
seems when you do watch it. And I'll sit there watching something. What are those dumb shit?
One of those dumb shows. Like the Anna Nicole Smith show. My cousin, by the way. And maybe
every one of those dating shows, whatever, Jerry Springer, any of that stuff. And you
end up going, God, I cannot believe how stupid this is. People actually watch this? They
must really be stupid. I'm going to keep sitting here watching this just to ponder how stupid
everybody must be. And you could sit there forever thinking about how stupid everybody
must be.
Probably don't need to talk about retained harshness.
We've been keeping that dream for a lifetime.
It's annoying to sit there talking about hide-and-seek, which, again, is where you
're spending a day.
...
You may have a sports car. Why don't you show your practicing guy to the TV?
Yeah?
Wanna win?
Never have.
Actually, it's not a bad idea if you think about it.
A lot of what they were acting out at scripting was not as interesting as plain, ordinary human beings acting like human beings.
You know, that can be just as dumb as anything a script maker can come up with.
The Church of the Subgenius is here to prove that.
There's a fella down in Texas, they say his name is Bob.
He tells me I should slack off, I should quit my job.
Well, I'm a subgenius, and I must have my slack.
If I don't live for the job, I'm a subgenius.
Forever I get my money back.
They said that on July 5th of 1998, the earth would meet destruction, suffer a deadly fate.
That day was long away.
I don't know what I'm gonna do with it.
Now it has come and gone.
There was no fire from heaven.
And this old world rolls on.
Well, I'm a subgenius, and I must have my slack.
If I don't live forever, I get my money back.
There's a fella down in Texas, they say his name is Bob.
Have a quick look around.
Oh, where is he?
To be down in the dumps
It'll all still happen
No need to curse or frown
They got all the right numbers
Just got them upside down
Well, I'm a subgenius
And I must tell my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
Come!
And now...
Some old Frank Zappa
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
About me being in this place
Yeah!
That's just how much I marvel
At the length of time we spend
And the thinness on your face
You rise each day the same old way
And join your friends out on the street
Spray your hair and think you're neat
I think your life is incomplete
But maybe that's not for me to say
They only pay me here to play
I want a haircut
And a caravan with a drum solo
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
About me staring back at you
Yeah!
That's just how much I marvel
At the length of time you live
The corny things you do
You paint your face and then you chase
To meet the gang where the action is
Stomp all night and drink your fizz
Roll your car and say gee whiz
You tore a big hole in your convertible top
What will you tell your mom and pa?
I don't know!
Mom, I tore a big hole in the convertible
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
If I mean just what I say
No, I don't know!
That's just how much I question
The social games you play
You told your mom you're stoked on Tom
And went for a bruise in Freddy's car
Tommy's asking where you are
You boogied all night in a cheesy bar
Plastic boots and plastic hat
And you think you know where it is?
You're probably wondering why I'm here
Not that it makes a heck of a lot of difference to you
What is Dobstown?
Written by Noumonet
Improviseried by Ice Stang
And to the lonesome cowboy today
What is Dobstown?
What is, then, Dobstown?
It is the stuff that dreams are made of
It's what makes Tinkerbell
And the Lost Boys fly
It powers the Starship Enterprise
It's the hidden code in Windows and Mac OS
Though not yet available in Linux
It's the general oblivion
Created when the moon dance
Strikes the cornea of your head
Dobstown
It's the cancer-causing, teeth-staining
Smelly, pukey habit
It's the drug that helps you find God
It's the lonely night before that never, never ends
Dobstown
It is your brain on drugs
It's learning to work as a team and as a slave
It's where there is a lake in which resides the sword Excalibur
Kept by the lady of the lake, Connie Dobbs
And if you think it's hard to pull that stone from out of that sword out of that lake
It's easy to pull a fig from a donkey's anus
Dobstown
It is where all the flowers have gone
It is the home of chocolate
It is John Dillinger's real penis
Wait, that light
Dobstown
It is a mystery
Wrapped in an enigma
Smothered with sautéed mushrooms and onions in a savory gravy
Dobstown
It is John Dillinger's penis
Savaged in muscular gravy and surrounded by mushroom people
Dobstown
The home of both Lemurians and Cenobites
My proper home
I'm going back someday
I've got to get back to my home
Dobstown
It's near the coast of Honalee and the land of Fredonia
It's the world's largest producer of manna, ambrosia, frop and the green stuff that Dave injects into the brain to reanimate dead tissue
Spiritual bliss with open-lane bowling every night from midnight to dawn
Dobstown
It's the residence of J.R. Bob Dobbs
Part of the year
It's creamy and crunchy
It tastes great and is less filling
It is margarine and it is butter
But if it were to fall into enemy hands it would mean the destruction of us all
Ah yes, dang, but it is the downfall of us all
And it tastes bad on bread
Because man, those that go don't come back home
They're losers, losers
No man, those who graduate from Dobstown come back changed
In a new form
You can't see them like you can see others
Graduated like the chrysalis to the elf
All the way up to a higher being
They grow and grow
Their tiny skin's hardly large enough to pop them as they begin expanding into that new form
They kill you?
Dobstown
It's where UFOs are not just a fact of life, they're the law
Of course it's a law here, of course it's a law
Everyone needs to live by laws, by rules
We need to have our lives governed by
Dobstown
It's where the bad little girls and boys go
It's where something is happening all the time
And most of it unsolved
Some of it is so hard to locate
Many of the people from the saucer ship emblem itself have been sucked out and left here
Dobstown
I didn't want them to be oblique
When they're strapped down in a chair and started asking me questions about Dobstown
I gave them a location but they...
A website
Dobstown
It's Nwatsbod spelled backwards
It's Brigadoon without the haggis
It is surrounded by the seven cities of Cibola
Which are its slums
And it has a ferry to Monster Island
And what a delightful pair of individuals you'll never find there
The ferries of Monster Island
Tiny little happy people who
Do things for other people
Who live for other people
So big are their hearts and so tiny is their stature
They...
Dobstown!
That's where Amelia Earhart crashed, friends
It's where the Tunguska meteorite came out after bouncing around inside the earth for a while
I guess if you were waiting for another salubrious comment to someway illuminate that stupid passage
Just read it again, Stang
Just see what you just said
What, the Dobstown is where the Tunguska meteorite came out?
After bouncing around inside the planet for a while
The Tunguska meteorite was of course, as you know from reading your book of the subgenius, Dave
Was a miniature black hole
Shot by Dobbs, the young ten year old J.R. Bob Dobbs from his slingshot
In a... completely by accident
In a fit of rage?
No, he didn't even know he was doing it
It was just, you know, I mean he picked up a...
Other kids might pick up a pebble or a cat skull for their slingshot
Yeah, a cat skull, that makes a lot more sense
But would Bob pick up a tiny black hole?
A singularity?
The glowing essence of nothingness sucking in all that is not Bob
And that is what he shot into the Tunguska plains of Siberia
And then past the event horizon the little thing itself went and then became like a bigger thing?
And it bent, went into the earth!
Bob's tiny black hole did and it bounced around like a cue ball on a pool table
Back and forth until finally it exited at the place we now know as
Dobbs Town!
Dobbs Town, friends!
It is where a thing of beauty is a joy for a while
It's where you are better than you were in high school
It's where you get all the pets you ever wanted
It was never a colony of France
It is where science and magic are the same things!
It is the unfolding of miscalculations
It is the dawning of the height, weight, hair and eye color of Aquarius
It is the fizzling, crackling, ebony horizon for man's eyes
It is the dissonant fifth vortex disrupting the harmonic convergence
It's where the early worm gets away
It's where the gravediggers sleep their shoes in the ocean
It's where the night is in the middle of the night
Dobbs Town!
It's for when you're too lazy to kill yourself
Where there are no lawyers!
And where the government never tries to be helpful
Dobbs Town, friends!
It's where you can make your imaginary friends fight to the death
Dobbs Town!
It's between the dark and daylight
When the night is beginning to lower
It is where neither heredity nor environment matters
It is where the lamb and the lion lay down and have sex together, friends!
You cannot think now
You can only follow and listen
It is proof that hell is full
And the dead walk the earth
The fabric is one thing
Like yourself
One thread that leads to thousands of other threads
And the
That is our caustic solution for you as members of this solemn group gathered together squandered and quashed and pushed under heavy stone so that you may not know the truth that we speak and yet here we are speaking it to you
Dobbs Town is not a place where a man or woman dwells but a place in the heart
As big as that mighty elephant yoke
And twice as tasty as all the trees that you could imagine
Now imagination is not a place you want to stay
It's not a place you want to bring the kids, grandma, ride the ferris wheel with
It's not the kind of place you want to leave for a better home
It's a place you visit over and over again
With your pants on, your pants off, and your heart ripped right out hanging from your chest
Dobbs Town
Where Bob comes home
After an easy day's work
And where you can come home too, friends
Where you'll be home
Where you'll finally realize why
Why
And why you can find out more about beautiful Dobbs Town when you join the Church of the Subgenius
The world's only subgenius!
The world's only first true last final one true religion
Because it admits it is full of crap
It is the only one that's not full of crap!
And I know it's coming each time I can tell it
You tell it
Ha ha!
Go!
It's where Enio Morricone was delivered of his
Luscious voices
Inspiration for this music in the background
Huge, huge mandibles
Large, large, fresh, gamy legs
And now the matador Dobbs steps out before the enraged triceratops dinosaur
Flashing his red Dobbs-headed cape in front of the maddened beast
The furious creature stomps its feet and paws at the ground
Dobbs grins, he smokes, the creature charges!
Dobbs whips out his pipe and gives it a little conk on the nogginous
It runs by and after that
It sits and pants like a little puppydog
Get hysterical
Bob! Bob! Bob!
Bobhead!
Get hysterical
Bob bob bobhead
Bob bob bob bob bob
Bob bob bob bob
Bob head
Bob!
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Don't let yourself get hysterical, Bobhead.
Bobhead.
Uh-oh.
Well, goodbye now.
Stop it.
And I say, as long as you're alive,
shout, make noise, or whatever,
because we're your kids.
Praise Bob.
You shut up like hell.