Are we in a movie?
Everything's a movie.
Talking pictures.
That's all it is.
Huh?
Cheesy dreams.
While Huckleberry Finn goes fishing on the edge of the moon.
Who's Ben Johnson?
He's in The Last Picture Show.
Just like us.
Don't move, my love.
Be still.
Be real.
He's gone.
Tuesday, 2018 o'clock.
Resuming work.
As a result of stripping skin off the skull,
keeping clean and keeping at the required temperature,
the bones have become crystalline.
I may now begin reconstruction of the physiognomy whenever I please.
In the ancient folk legends, tales are told of blood-sucking vampires.
Is man now doomed to produce a race of ever-living monstrosities?
Worse than the vampires of legend?
Such questions, mate.
Whether or not science Lak sir 굉장히 fanciful,
at this very moment,
scientists are
working on in part to brain transplantation,
and distance 1971,
human bodies are used.
This girl was buried in the nearby cemetery yesterday.
Only a few hours ago,
her body was stolen
and brought to this hidden laboratory.
He had grafted a living animal's brain
into this newly dead body.
The brain cells have been reactivated by
the subgenius,
This Hour of Slack number 1826 is a rerun of 1147 from 2008 because I'm busy on an Hour of Slack improvement project.
Since around 2005, I've been using a series of ever-larger external hard drives to stash show audio files on, and also movies, photos, and art, and so forth.
And I bought me a 14-terabyte drive for the same price a 1-gigabyte drive was in the year 2000.
And I've copied all of the audio from all of those smaller drives onto the one huge drive.
I still have to interweave the files and folders from each drive into 10 or so main categories,
while also copying many dozens of even older data CD audio files, which go back to 1999.
So far, I've filled up 3 terabytes.
I'm also doing the same thing to photos and graphics,
trying to get all the eggs into just...
the right baskets.
Others will thank me after I'm dead.
And now, Hour of Slack number 1147,
FrankenCoffee vs. FrankenChenkem.
Horrified
Tracy in highness voice.
However, you'll pay in other ways.
For instance, the number of brain cells that you have to kill just to take enough pills to be able to bear this show in the middle of the night.
Why, that in itself is quite expensive.
That bear is repeating.
Yes, well, most people are lucky they don't have to listen to this thing every night like Uberbrow.
Day in, day out.
That poor boy not only has to listen to it every night, he has to broadcast it every night.
From his secret cubicle, hundreds of miles under solid rock.
Weird, weird, weird, weird, yes.
The little brow is so weird.
And yet, they kept on.
Nobody knew why.
I love this Uber.
His brow is so weird.
And if he won't pinch me, I'll hide in his beard.
I hid under his stool to look at his feet.
But could not get out.
For I fell upon the seat.
The implied adventure that the doctors had in their voices.
They knew something spooky and scary was about to happen.
Well, that wasn't it.
Not even the baby breaking out of my little glass brain.
Yes, the little babies were hard to find in the morning.
Because the U-Haul trucks would come and take them away.
Their little china bodies lay shattered on the midden heaps of society.
Yes, but they all looked alike.
And they were filled with little nylon things.
And little spooky eyes.
They came in little boxes.
And the people fought and kicked and prayed and shot to get one.
But there was nothing they could do.
But be scared, of course.
And being scared in Berkeley is sort of a way of life.
Just ask the new revitalized 53rd Street Winos Association.
Really? Being terrorized?
Yeah.
It's something you'll be watching.
Watching now as we sturgutate our way to madness.
Where's Billy?
Just give me what's in that bag right now.
Here on the only show brave enough to bring the facts to you.
These are coffee winos.
They don't drink alcohol.
They drink more and more advanced grades of coffee.
Yes, Doctor. We call them coffeenos.
This old coffeeno here is holding what looks like a can of Colombian ground coffee.
I have coffee!
I've got to wait for you.
Do something.
I know you just spent it on coffee.
More spilt of sugar, please.
I'm going to finally see the truth.
Yes, those who wouldn't say please, they were forced to take other forms of entertainment.
And to perform humiliating jests and actions and acts.
Immigrant.
At weird hours of the morning.
The American area.
Little tiny doctors.
My mind.
Okay, now what are my instructions?
What was I going to do?
This I...
I always have to look up what it says in the program book so I know what...
I said I was going to...
Adventures in sickening.
Subgenius preachers are skilled at both healings and sickenings.
Although they're not necessarily performed in that order.
Reverend Stang...
Oh, so this is what I'm going to do.
Reverend Stang will explain various Dobbs approved techniques.
Such as, transferal of pain.
The laying on of sledgehammers.
Acubating.
Frame straightening.
Blemish readings.
And most importantly, excremeditation.
He will also take questions from the audience and has interesting proctology slides if anyone wants to see them.
Well, that's...
I'm done.
That was all the gags.
I put them all in that one.
So I shot my load, I'd say.
Okay, no.
Really, the subject is...
Slack, Muzak, and transformative embarrassment.
Courtesy of Chickenhead.
Praise Chickenhead.
Oh no, these are the wrong cult.
These are notes for the wrong cult.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, here it is.
Church of the Subgenius.
That's the right cult, friends.
And this is its right show.
It's proven by the fact that it exploits all the other subgenius shows.
There have been so many of those lately.
I don't think we can categorize them into sections.
For instance, this episode of Hour of Slack features the category of drugs, and especially the drug coffee.
Our last completely legal one, for now.
We have been and will continue to hear collages by Fernanda Nani-Lemur,
my sermon at Winterstar Symposium,
the amino acids, as heard in the background,
puzzling evidence shows from Berkeley,
both very old and very new,
with Philo, Gary, Doug, and Hal, and K-Rob, and John Hell.
But those are from John Hell's show on Pirate Cat Radio.
Remember, all Pirate Cat Radio shows are archived for six weeks at piratecatradio.com,
so you can hear this here, here.
You may already be listening to this here, here.
What is the proper name of the show?
A Season in Hell.
So you just go to the DJ schedule, scroll down, click on it,
and there's the date you listen to the show.
And what do you know?
And podcast it? That's what I was like.
Sure, I throw mine on.
Everybody except me, though. That's what I do.
Hold on, we're going to isolate you now.
Isolation, Jamie.
That's my kind of show. Just me, Jim, all the time.
I hear lunch in Carolina.
That's all we're going to hear.
You can put this show up if you want to as well.
I just told the listeners that that's what I have.
Yeah, right, right. So it's already there.
The Winkers.
Sorry. It was the other show.
The other three conversations that I was listening to at the time.
The preserves in the basement.
Preserve the show for the winner.
In the jar.
With the brown bread and the baked beans.
Goes in the jar with the stuff.
Don't look too closely at that jar and its content.
Don't think about the wall.
Is that an eyeball?
Bridge, some hair.
Is that back to what you were talking about, the jar in the bathroom?
The jar.
Jar of Jenkum. Jenkum jar.
Yeah, Super Jenkum Hayes was the winner at the front.
I think it was the prop cup in Amsterdam.
What about G13 Hayes? Was that the same thing?
That was the marijuana and the cannabis cup.
Ah, I see.
They didn't have a Jenkum category at the cannabis cup.
Is Jenkum still available here? Can you still get Jenkum over the counter?
You can make it yourself, Daddy.
That's about it.
Well, now we can get Absinthe over the counter again.
Makes the heart go fun.
You can?
What?
It was made legal again last week.
They made it legal?
Nationally or just?
Nationally.
It is a legal alcoholic beverage.
The official beverage of Learning Man is legal.
The store's closed.
At 2.
We all got two hours of show time.
Hurry up.
I got the sugar cubes.
I've been known to chase the dragon.
A CD.
Yeah.
We're a team again.
I get it, I get it.
They all have
broughtENDEALTY to Gありがとうございました.
That low-down snake and him pretending to be my friend.
Pretending to be my friend.
Well, we do have the theme of this whole show here is healing and so forth,
and we've already sickened you.
I had a couple of things that have been of interest to me.
I read a newspaper article a couple of months ago
explaining that some folks at Case Western University in Cleveland
had created some Franken-mice.
You know, the human genome has been mapped.
That's pretty complicated.
They actually finished the job pretty much.
And although it's against the law to do Franken-humans yet,
well, we'll get to that.
But these little mice that they had created in this lab
or had tweaked, you might say,
they were way more aggressive than normal mice.
They also lived like twice as long
and could keep reproducing for twice as long as normal mice.
And they fought constantly.
One of the women who had been working with them said that
when she knew they were different,
because whenever he lifted the lid off their cage,
it was like a popcorn, lifting a lid off of popping popcorn.
They were just going mad.
And so, you know, we've all heard about the Franken-corn,
and so forth.
I mean, that's being done.
You can actually create new species now
and also trademark them.
You can create a bundle of cells
that'll just sit there and generate something useful
like medicine or drugs,
but you can trademark it.
Of course, this brings to mind
what so many sci-fi movies and TV shows have already covered.
The Franken-soldiers, right?
Franken-cops.
I have super macho...
or whatever kind of person you want.
You want just a muscle man
that doesn't mind doing dull work?
You can create those.
Aldous Huxley had it all down with Brave New World.
Our grandparents read about that.
They didn't think about Franken-salesmen.
They didn't think about Franken-politicians.
But I read recently
that now...
that there were some guys in France
and also some people in some other places
who were trying to map,
completely map the genome of the coffee plant.
And thus leading to Franken-coffee, right?
Coffee that could be grown...
that had no caffeine
or that had five times as much caffeine
or that had more of a coffee-ish taste.
Right now, there's really only two main species of coffee,
I believe, that people consume.
And in a couple of years,
there may be some radically different coffees around.
So then that brings us to the Franken-pot!
The Franken-oregano.
You know, I was really thinking more of the Franken-pot myself.
They bred that stuff.
We went to the Cannabis Cup in Amsterdam
this last year.
Last time.
It wasn't the kind of thing that I would spend my own money on,
but we lucked out.
We had a friend who...
He went to every coffee shop on the map,
bought every super strong grade of marijuana and hash.
And...
But what this guy didn't know
was how to get around Amsterdam.
Well, we knew how to get around Amsterdam.
So frankly, if you...
If I was a judge at that thing,
I would only say...
I would say the same thing about every single contestant,
which is,
this shit is strong.
Strong as hell.
That is about all you could say.
I personally am more interested in the Franken-jenkum.
And if you don't know what the jenkum is,
don't even ask.
Don't think about it.
Don't look it up on the internet.
It's a new drug that they say the kids are doing.
Don't look it up.
Don't look up jenkum.
J-E-N-K-E-M.
And don't even think about the Franken-jenkum.
I take off.
Drugs.
I got a better ride.
Die.
Dot com.
This time we went to die.
Fixed.
No matter.
Chewable.
Deadly heartworm disease.
Protein.
Fat.
Demand.
Nick.
Directed by Steven Spielberg.
Bunny.
And I want everybody in town to come.
Drug.
The next thing I know here she is on drugs.
Bunny.
You have lost your mind.
Bud.
Hurry.
I'm coming.
Bunny.
Bunny's dead.
Dead.
Crazy.
Bunny.
Where are you?
Bunny?
Bunny.
Say yes to beautiful.
Cool.
Doom, doom, doom.
Okay, we're taking our coffee shots now.
What if you did 12 of those things really fast?
You can't.
You went in there and you paid the money before the guy even took your money.
He's like, rip, rip, rip.
Yeah, I found a new drug today.
I haven't been in a proper 7-Eleven in years.
I think we'd like that.
Because they don't have proper 7-Elevens in Cleveland.
But they had a drug called Stoke, which is included with the coffee creamers in the little cup.
The kids today are on Stoke.
Which means it's free.
That means it's free.
That's right.
I grabbed two half-fulls.
You have hot water.
You stoke it with hot water and you make coffee out of it.
Each one of these little things.
When you held a Stoke baby in your hands, then you know how it is.
I can tell you, man.
These Stoke heads have to be knocked in or our civilization is going to fall.
The target in Erie, Pennsylvania is inhabited entirely by Stoke babies.
Stoke fetal syndrome.
Look at his feet.
Each Stoke has 40 milligrams of caffeine.
Which really is, that's only like half a cup of coffee.
That's for wimps.
That half a cup of coffee.
Is that what all the big build-up cups do?
Right.
But it's free.
Free?
It's free.
At 7-Eleven.
Thanks to the Southland Corporation.
Free drugs.
40 milligrams of caffeine.
Wait a minute.
Was I supposed to say that on KPFA?
That was not, uh, don't go to 7-Eleven.
It does sound suspiciously like Plagola, Stang, but we know that it's only a matter of fair use.
In the name of WCSB Cleveland, do not go to 7-Eleven.
There used beneath the tree is thou canst not leave thy soul.
If you do, you'll be surrounded by caffeine and sugar, both.
Both are exceptionally valuable substances.
Sugar, nature's perfect food.
Just a bunch of little noises.
And caffeine, the perfect vitamin.
Vitamin?
That's what vitamin C stands for.
Yes, yes.
I, uh, have spent too many years in headphones and in front of my friends' bands videotaping them.
So, I hear what sounds like crickets and cicadas all the time.
Now, I grew up in Texas, and there really are cicadas all the time.
But one winter's day, Princess Wee there suddenly said,
Did you hear that?
And I listened, and I went,
Yeah, I hear the cicadas.
And I looked outside, and it was like this.
It was like snow on the ground.
And I realized that it was time to go see the ear doctor.
And I flunked the test.
But I found some good news in this issue of Nutrition Action magazine.
This is one of the kookzines that my wife gets.
She reads Utney Reader and all this silly stuff.
And, um, this special issue about caffeine,
it turns out, I mean, I drink a lot of coffee.
I drank so much coffee that my, I started getting migraines and bad headaches.
So I went to my doctor and said,
I have headaches.
She said, So, you drink a lot of coffee, do ya?
And she didn't even have to ask why.
And I said, Yeah.
She wrote me out a prescription for half,
for a type of decaf she likes.
She said, I know you're not going to stop drinking real coffee.
Just cut it with decaf.
Step on it. Mix half and half.
And I was able to drink 20 cups instead of 10.
And never get headaches.
But I always felt bad about it because,
Oh, I'll probably get colon cancer someday,
or hypertension or something.
But it turns out,
my fellow coffee drinkers can be so glad to hear this.
All these studies, it has turned out,
caffeine or coffee, the two different things,
but coffee basically helps present Parkinson's disease,
gallstones, it actually does help your mental performance
if you're sleepy and your mood, of course.
And headaches.
It increases the effects of painkillers.
It's not good for pregnant ladies.
No way is it good for pregnant ladies.
And it won't counteract alcohol.
I repeat, it won't counteract alcohol.
Try to remember that at about 5 or 6 this morning, my friends.
But it turns out, I was wrong.
All these studies show that it doesn't correlate to heart disease.
It doesn't correlate to any kind of cancer, especially.
Or diabetes, or high blood pressure, or osteoporosis.
And it doesn't stunt your growth,
which is what my mom always used to say.
And I believed her, too.
And that's why I'm not taller than I am.
And PMS.
There's no evidence that caffeine played a role in PMS.
Well, duh.
Anyway, it was a really interesting little article.
I learned from it that Starbucks coffee, the 16 ounce one,
has the highest charge you can get, 330 milligrams of caffeine.
That would put me in the hospital.
If I drank it all at once, if I drank three of them in one day,
nothing, I could probably go to sleep.
So that was why I brought up the Franken-coffee routine.
I am really looking forward to it.
I am looking forward now to the Franken-coffee.
The first time I met Sir Isaac Bonowitz over there,
I didn't even know who he was exactly,
but he offered me some coffee.
And I heard for the first time that little coffee chant
based on the mentat.
It was the goddess Caffeina routine,
which I never could remember,
because I don't just drink coffee.
I can tell you, I can't tell you right off the head,
I mean the tip of my head,
quote Princess Riardo.
Anybody want any stoke?
What happens when you consume this?
Warning, high caffeine.
You add it to your coffee.
Is it like a little creamer package?
But you can just toss it down?
I wouldn't, yeah, if you don't mind migraine,
headache type effects.
Nonsense.
Go ahead, do it, Isaac.
I'll do it.
Well, I would, but I mean, I've got a pie in the oven.
I mean, these nosebleeds keep me on my back.
No, the thing is, is it edible?
Not for pregnant men.
Give it some horrible thing, you know, some hideous...
How do you happen to have this in your pocket?
Well, I will, I'll drink it right now.
Dr. Howell.
Here we go.
Sip it, please.
Don't just shoot the whole thing.
I wonder what this will be like.
Hey, Puzzling Evidence TV sent me a video.
Well, what it tastes like is prune juice.
You sure it's not?
Really?
What a thing that may have never happened.
Let me have a little, a little tiny...
I'm reading it now.
And I bet it's about...
It tastes like a prune juice.
...about JFK dying.
But it says that this video has been removed...
It does taste...
...with a violation.
...stoked.
Which one is it?
This isn't caffeine-infected...
That's happening more and more.
...water.
It's mere prune juice.
Oh, my God.
...endemnable...
Ivan Stank's melting.
...prune juice.
Prune juice?
Well, it's, uh...
That's one thing about YouTube is that their policy of removing videos is real
necessary.
...and that's why it's called Nebulous.
Yeah.
Nebulous entity.
Well, it's who gets...
...who gets recorded and who gets caught.
It's sort of like what one of us was running in.
Yeah, take it out.
...equivalent to one shot of espresso.
But there's, there's porno YouTube.
There's uncensored YouTube-ish things.
There's RedTube...
40 milligrams of caffeine.
...which, uh, is, and PinkTube.
And YouPorn.
Yeah, YouPorn, that's right.
Not for...
Whenever I look at one of those websites...
Those under 18...
...there's a whole special window that comes up showing girls I could date in clean...
...leave...
...caffeine.
Yeah, it knows, it knows which city I'm in, and it shows me all these nice, like...
It knows it.
It shows you these nice pictures you could make...
It knows where your IP address is being served from.
And I try to make love to each and every one of those...
...because I feel that responsibility.
I mean...
You know what I do?
Well, they're lonely...
...it says they're lonely, single women.
Plus, you get all these pills in the mail, in the email, these, these special pills for
your tool...
...non-dairy coffee products.
...your tool pills.
Yeah, well...
You know, well...
And then when you meet the women on the other website, you've got something really handy
to use with them.
I'll just drink all the rest of this.
Yeah, you gotta do it that way because...
Dr. Howell is drinking the...
...it's all virtual.
...the stoke.
Oh, he's drinking the virtual stoke.
He's having a power drink.
Dr. Stoke.
Now, that's 40 milligrams of caffeine in one swallow.
Caller, what do you think of this?
The show is like...
Yee-haw!
...purple syrup on pancakes...
You got it.
...and strong coffee.
Yeah.
Now you're talking.
Even if JFK dies...
Look at Howell.
He's, he's changing.
He's changing.
...and he's drinking the virtual stoke.
My God, man.
Somebody call the guards.
Now, do you ever use molasses on your pancakes?
Have you ever tried that?
Molasses?
What about sorghum?
Sorghum molasses.
I mean, stuff I don't eat anymore.
This country used to be great.
I'm too sensible now.
You don't eat?
Are you a breath alien?
Excuse me?
Sensible?
Not eating pancakes?
I am sore strapped for sorghum and molasses.
I, me too.
...and vegetables and fruits.
Vegetables, fruits, fruitas y verduras.
Yeah.
Mostly vegetarian.
Vegetar-da-da-ba-ba-ba.
You can still eat pancakes, though.
Pancakes?
Oh, well, I realize some people can divert themselves with that.
In moderation.
Yeah, so I'm going to try these caffeine potato chips.
Really?
These chips are pure stoke chips.
Well, they're caffeine chips.
They're caffeine chips made from coffee beans, and they've also had powdered caffeine added
to them with citric acid.
Oh, my God.
We're going to have to peel these guys off the ceiling here.
I've noticed that caffeine drinks are not as good as the ones that are sold in the
store.
Well, I'll tell you what, these drinks have become, are in a huge variety now and in huge
volumes and mixed with alcohol, which Bob predicted 10,000 years ago that there would
come a day when speed and booze were mixed together and sold in Safeway stores with names
like Big Throttle, Monster Jug, Booze Speed.
You're witness Mr. Freud.
Monster Jugs, Booze Speed.
Booze Speed.
got Philo's attention.
Remember, today we've got an awesome guest.
His name is Bob.
I first met Bob, well, wasn't I in each about
10 years ago? 1984.
Yeah.
Most incredibly.
And I remember blah, blah, blah.
No bones about it, you know.
You know, there's something
about Bob dedicated to achieving
drugs. So, Bob
was born and raised in...
Bob joined the drug abuse.
So, Bob is understanding steroids.
Bob, a drug that targets
young people as well as parents and other adults.
Bob calls it the make-and-treat
and prescription drugs broadly available
to the youth in every community.
Boy, that's an awesome
mouthful of stuff you've been
doing.
So, I'm totally
stoked about it. Bob. There was lots of drugs.
Acid rock and the whole bit.
Call, call, call, call. Drugs are
the solution. The solution. Evolution
in the early years. Clandestinish, but
add drugs to the mix and you get strength.
The testes secrete the most amount of
testosterone and I've seen it and I hope
I'm not getting too deep here. Profound.
Psychoactive. Psycho. Psycho. And I've
observed it myself and they just kind of
bang around ball. Injected in the butt.
Fat in the brain. Really feeling the
organ. Becoming that organ. They are
matter, energy, space, and time. And they're
hideous. Hardening of the long bone. Oh,
it's huge. Burn it off. Come on UPS and
bogus. Don't know what, don't know what
phony packaging. Big business. Have LSD
and pot and... We have more drug...
We have more drug... Better.
Marijuana. Marijuana. Methamphetamines.
Methamphetamine. Crystal meth.
Methamphetamine, but crack. Crack. Smoking.
Paint thinner. One hit. Unreal. Crystal meth.
And we showed a video on ecstasy. It's
just for partying. Complete curriculum.
How to, how to use glitz with a class of
drugs. And how to deliver that. www.yestrugs.org.
Get it all. Get it all. Drugs and harmful
effects is, is really our duty. Utterly
enormous. People, they try to get
stimulated. Fear, fear, fear, fear. Which is
huge. I think it's the largest. They're
fairly abstract. Bob, no. Don't forget, you
know, drugs. Have a good day. One of the
worst things about drugs, friends, is
sometimes they make you forget the other
drugs you were gonna take. That cut was
cut, Bob.
We kept forgetting what drugs were and
that they don't. Bob what was going on with
It's time to say hello to that that occasionally
Facil preacher Turner ones then there's
some more things that not know yeah well
not like you me alright lose or easily
ceiling, yeah.
That's all
specialty equipment.
That's right.
The jar of
Jankum.
Don't go too
closely in that
jar.
But I
understand it's
not water-based,
so therefore
it won't get
sticky.
What kind of
show is this?
tapes were you
making?
So cool.
Yeah, I had
the Oakland
police, two
officers, come
into my basement
with drawn guns
because of the
sounds they
heard upstairs
when they came
into the kitchen
that we were
making on tapes
below.
And we had a
quarter pound of
goat in a big
bowl next to
the paper clip.
And they took
the tapes and
left the pot?
No, I remember
turning around,
we're doing a
tape to him.
He had written
this copy, this
Ivan Stan guy
had written some
copy for a
rich person's
eagle's nest,
and we had
taken that copy,
we were making
our own commercial
for it.
And the next
thing I know,
yeah, Paul's
about to leap
on a guy with
a drawn gun.
When the cop
came in, Paul
jumped up and
knocked over the
table that had
all the dope
on it.
He did with
all my gear
and the dope
was flying.
So it was no
longer an obvious
pile of dope,
it was just a
big mess on the
floor at that
point.
And a wonderful
huge crash just
when a very
jittery officer
was coming down
a stairway with
a drawn gun.
And I remember
thinking, ooh,
this could end
badly.
A Paul
Hoffa, sir?
Something is
just shot doing
commercial in
basement.
Could have been
your Waco, Texas.
Exactly.
We could have
been immortal,
but no.
That's right.
The luck plane
had something else.
Well, there were
other famous
subgenius crimes,
particularly the
tendency,
convenience.
He was lying
in a canvas
hammock,
one bare foot
hanging over the
side, deep in
the enjoyment
of an oversized
cigarette.
He seemed to
sleep except for
the rhythmic puffs
of smoke.
As if to
backed down
on the
its going
down.
Long
dozens may
smoked
cigarettes
die
a
gun
obliterating
a
at
the
simplest
and
unique
madness of
crime.
They
would
not
live
in
Oh, Dick, I love you
You do love me, don't you?
You kids are in a mess
Drinking party, nude bathing
Now I don't care
Dick, we've just got to get married
Take anything
No, no, no
Dick, you, Dick, you
I'll see Tony
What are you going to do about Dick?
Dick?
Yesterday when Dick came to you, you sent him out to be killed
And I love it
Your marijuana customers are hooked on the stronger stuff
You can't leave me like this
But, of course he is
Look, look, look
Run into a load of dope
The fiery high-o's burn
The long journey
Nowhere in the pages of history
Can one find a long journey
High-o's burn
High!
The loner ran the gambling palace and cafe
To avoid a lot of questioning, the loner had removed his face
Oh, it's you
Not right
His fists work like doctors
Hit him again
Let me go, don't hit me again
You're getting help whether you need it or not
Dick, the loner
High-o's burn
I notice you carry artifacture
One looks like a tiny shrunken head
What does...
No, that's a can of Valium
That's a can of Valium
That also helps me to feel more at ease
But it appears to have the shape of a human head of some kind
That's just...
That's the Elvis, uh, container
You notice it looks like Elvis
That's my Valium dispenser
I have a...
I have a pain pill dispenser that looks like Rush Limbaugh
Oh, I think...
Like a Rush Limbaugh dispenser
Rush Limbaugh bobblehead
I have one that looks like Woody Woodpecker
Yeah
Well, we are kindred spirits
Even though your religion is strange
I keep my tranquilizer, or my muscle relaxers
In a Baby Hendrix doll
Or kind of a...
It's not a doll exactly
It's a ceramic thing
Baby Jimi Hendrix doll
Did you ever see it?
It's so cute
I have...
Like a little cute Jimi Hendrix
Yes, yes, I...
He's like three years old
I actually had one of the Baby Hendrix
Mini Jimi
Yes, of course
Do you see him?
That's Felix sleeping in that chair
Who's Felix?
He's the writer
I eat writers for breakfast
Listen, I can't talk to you right now
I'm in somebody's hard drive
Did somebody say Felix Bonhoeffer?
Who the hell are you?
Buzz Larrabee, detective
I gotta question this Bonhoeffer guy, whoever he is
And what do you two gents know about him anyway?
He's a writer for God's sake
What's there to know?
He was involved in a shootout on the freeway
The out world?
A shootout?
A shootout
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
I knew it! I knew there was something about that guy!
With that stupid accent! I knew it!
Where can I find him?
Look in there, over there, to the left
See him? Sleeping in the chair? That's him
There he is
So that's him
How can I get to him?
No, no, don't disturb him
Why the hell not?
Because he owes me, that's why
He owes you
In conclusion, he keeps killing people off
Tell me about it, huh?
Especially when he's tired, he needs to sleep
He's extremely dangerous
Especially when he's tired
That's why I have to lock this creep up, because he is dangerous
I hate writers
I always have
Love?
Did he write this garbage?
Would you mind taking out the garbage?
Okay
Who's that?
His wife
His wife?
Love?
I ain't no bad voice
Love? The garbage?
Gina, Gina, don't wake him, Gina
Gina, please don't wake him
Love?
No.
Liar, centimeters, BAR.
Why you!!"
Huh?
Leave Bob Alone
PR istuyor
Did you see on YouTube that Ivan Stan does, Leave Bob Alone Luke
Leave Bob Alone
He's just a human being
Yeah, yeah
I think we did
We already did that last time I was here
Oh yeah
Have you no decency?
It's the old script.
Yeah, the old...
At last, sir.
These are supposed to be disposed of.
Can you not leave, Bob?
Yeah, now it's the two...
I'm going to get all my staff about this.
Yeah, the new meme is two Bobs, one cup.
Yeah.
Leave it alone, Fritz.
Leave it alone.
I wasn't even thinking that point.
Jankum Bob.
Two people, one bear.
Crankum crankum.
Okay, so we're packing up the show here.
Packing up and sell a...
We've only got 27 whole minutes left.
Oh, no.
Yep.
Well, you have a breathing.
When you have a baby, it takes that long to pack up.
Oh, is there a baby?
The baby used to be on the show once.
Oh, my God.
We left the Uber baby out in the truck.
I forgot.
You left the baby on the roof of the car while you took off.
It's okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Oversquirt's fine.
She knows how to use the remote.
She knows how to go...
The bad guys approach the truck and she hits a little button.
Gives them 6,000 voltages.
And they would have gotten away with it, too, if not for her.
Yeah, so...
And she's just...
That'd be great.
Actually, that'd be a great...
They taped to a whole security system.
And it's just the Oversquirt in a little chair with a remote
to shoot a lot of her from different angles hitting buttons.
And guys are trying to steal things.
And all this stuff's happening.
She's like...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Are you guys ready for, like, your life?
I really want you to come.
And I'm very confused.
You know, you do enough drugs, you get confused.
That's right.
Nothing was happening.
It was like nothing was happening.
I already had nothing I want.
The tool, the beautiful, beautiful man.
What I'm looking for here is just a very...
John!
Woo!
I, uh...
You, uh...
The, uh...
You have very real power.
Boring.
But what about that?
And what about this?
And what about that?
And this and that?
Fictitious.
Um...
I'm going to kick you.
Right here on the butt.
It will hurt.
And it will hurt.
In, uh...
Uh...
In...
Um...
Weird.
And, and...
God, what am I into?
You know, you know...
You know, uh...
You, you, um...
Feel great.
Yes, Mark.
Okay, um...
You know what really strikes me as odd?
Rush Limbaugh calling anybody ugly.
Apparently the man doesn't have access to a mirror.
But if the man's right...
He is enormous, isn't he?
I mean...
I mean, he's...
I can't remember the last time he was right about anything.
He's certainly not left.
And he is usually on OxyContin and quite a...
You know, he still does it, right?
I'm so jealous of that guy.
I mean...
I've been shoveling snow all day and all I could think about was...
Rush Limbaugh had got all the good pills and I get to go in and have ibuprofen after all the snow shoveling.
Well, he heard everybody was taking him so he thought he better take some before, you know, they were all gone.
So that's...
That's why you missed out.
If not, he'd be in Mexico eating pills.
He could be.
That's true.
He could be on...
He could get a lot of pills in Mexico and Canada, too.
You know, broadcast.
He can't be had over here.
Canada, too?
Why?
Some drugs are available over the counter in Canada that are not available over the counter here.
I can't remember which.
You know, ibuprofen is a prescription drug in Europe.
Any ibuprofen?
I consider it bad for your liver and really habit-forming.
What are the drugs in Mexico that are kind of semi-illicit here that you can just go to a...
pharmacy and, you know, sign your name and walk away high for a day?
What are some of those?
I've heard of those.
A lot of opiates, I think.
You know, when...
Do they still have Quaaludes, Tyler?
I think Quaaludes must be pretty carefully controlled now.
I think people...
The world learned its lesson about Quaaludes.
You're listening to listener-censored radio since 1949.
We have a call-out now for any knight of the subgenius who is ready for the frond.
Let him...
Here at this doorway before me.
If he be a knight of the true order...
Yeah, he's gotta move because...
Yep, here he comes!
He's got to move.
Strangled by cords, unable to move.
Four-five-five-five.
They were in the studio.
We've talked to Mobius Rex.
What happened that morning?
Wait a minute.
It's just too much.
But you too can be part of the mysterious process of prophecy here on the air.
Yes, an even tiny little Napa caller is scared because, no, he's not allowed to open the refrigerator this late at night.
He's scared because he called this morning.
He called yesterday morning.
They were always on the air.
Strange voices inside the refrigerator.
Yet he was scared to open it.
But they wouldn't talk to him.
For fear they wouldn't answer.
His science project would be ruined.
Maybe they weren't there at all.
That must be him.
That must be him right now.
Hello, little Napa caller.
This is new Napa caller.
Good morning subgenius.
How you doing?
Oh, we're doing really horrible.
Dobbs woke us up in the middle of the night and dragged us down here, dumped us off in the rain.
The indicators are low.
Oh, no kidding.
Uh, yeah.
It's true.
We're gonna have to come up again just to be able to participate in the show.
In the show?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I got cut off.
Yeah, that's usually how it happens.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, it happens a lot down here.
That's why we do it here.
Because the little cutoff comes up and you just gotta go.
There's no commercials or anything to break the show up.
Usually, you know, we throw in some commercials.
But we let you participate.
Yeah, I know what's happening here.
Here with Miss Nickleby on the street.
Ah, hello, Bob.
We're reporting on resistentialism, yes?
How many did you take?
Resistance is the basic force of the universe.
And when do you expect the full effect to hit you?
Resistentialism gives you a new way to do it.
Pushes you back.
Is eight really too many?
And do you feel the pressure down?
Is 12 really not enough?
Ah, here we go.
Pushing, pushing, pushing.
Let's take more and see what happens.
Bienvenidos.
Welcome.
Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen, the president, the president, Cobb.
Cobb.
Erect, erect, erect Cobb.
Welcome to the Y.
Cobb, Cobb, thanks for coming.
Thank you all for coming.
I am pleased to be using drugs.
I've just come from a, it was a table.
It's up to all Americans to be involved in drugs.
You're part of a mission, drug abuse, to encourage it and profit from it.
The drug trade has enriched our society, and we're helping drug organizations in Mexico.
We want to continue to work together.
On the front lines of this effort are parents, teachers, our counselors who are sending our kids a clear message.
Drug use is fun.
It is glamorous.
A clear message.
Demand drugs.
I appreciate drugs coming in from Colombia.
Drugs coming to our country.
This morning I was briefed on the latest drugs and the use of ecstasy.
Methamphetamine works.
And the reason I'm so focused on meth, I've turned to crime.
Crime and hopelessness and happy life.
And I steal drugs from medicine cabinets.
I go out on the streets to buy drugs.
But the great thing about our country and the reason I'm so optimistic is there are thousands and thousands of people willing to take drugs.
I urge you to try drugs.
I see the cocaine coming into the United States.
I see the supply of drugs to our streets.
Demand cocaine coming into the United States.
And I love drugs.
You might remember a while ago, I took cocaine.
Over the past six years, I thought for a minute, and I want to be using drugs.
And I want to fund drug use amongst young people by 25% over a five-year period.
Demand drugs because Americans took action today.
There are an estimated 860,000 children seeking drugs.
Drugs and plastic drugs for representatives from our law enforcement organizations who are with us today.
We also know that this work is finished by drugs.
Why? Because they love America.
And they love their neighbor.
And love.
Drugs, love.
You know, make the right choice in life and you can realize your dreams here in the United States of America.
I injected him on numerous occasions.
I'm just a ball player.
Being too nice to everyone.
Ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty, ty.
He gave me a bad shot.
Injecting Roger Clemens with illegal steroids in his butt.
You're not supposed to inject it quickly.
You're supposed to do it very slowly.
Shot, shot, shot.
He gave me a bad shot.
Calpable mass.
HGH, what have you.
Into the body of...
Let me be clear.
Crack, if you will.
He jumped on me like a crack.
He was trying to start a Harley Davidson.
That's how hard it was.
That may not be unusual.
For that, I'm really thrilled.
He gave me a bad shot.
Bled through his designer pants.
Did give me comfort.
Ass ass.
There is an ass growth hormone.
It is very tough.
It has critical gaps today.
Ass legislation that like steroids.
Bottom line, the US doping agency and I like steroids.
Okay, I'm not gonna sing.
I'm not gonna do the...
I'm not gonna do the Bob Proverbs.
But we have just a little bit longer.
And this was about healing.
I'm going to read from the chapter of the book of the subgenius.
There was an actual chapter about health.
Health, the industrial diet and bad things.
With the quote, if you feel you heal from the movie Greaser's Palace.
The song I thought about singing is from the movie Greaser's Palace too.
Anybody here ever seen Greaser's Palace?
Not a single one.
If you ever get a chance, don't watch it when you're high.
Because you'll think it's you and not the movie.
It's the movie.
You don't need to get high.
You'll get high from watching Greaser's Palace.
It was made by Robert Downey, Sr., the dad of Robert Downey, Jr., the famous drug addicted actor.
And it'll all add up.
But you'll see.
You'll see when you see that movie.
Anyway.
You know, people used to cuss at us.
People used to say, why did you make print in that book so small?
And I'd laugh at them because I was young.
You'll notice our new book has ten point Adobe Garamond type.
Not nine point times.
Which is actually what most newspapers use.
You probably know at least ten people under the age of 30 who have some form of cancer.
The sickness won't stop.
People will contract weirder and weirder diseases and at earlier and earlier ages.
Eventually cancer itself will be like the common cold.
I won't be in the office this week.
I have a little touch of cancer.
There'll come a cure eventually.
But the more cures we come up with, the more new diseases will arise.
This was dictated in 1978.
By the way, we didn't know what AIDS was.
Things far, far worse than cancer are on the way.
Some of them deliberately manufactured by the conspiracy.
The picture is a tad bleak for our old age.
It's a cinch.
The government won't support the elderly much longer.
And the company will fire you a year before you're eligible for retirement benefits.
So you'd better put your remaining years to good use.
You'd better have a job.
Have fun!
Our studies, as well as unreleased studies by the con, indicate that, quote, good health,
is practically a pointless pursuit if you live in an urban area.
You can eat nothing but organically grown fruit and vegetables.
You can work out twice a day.
You can quit all your nasty habits.
But you're still absorbing more poison just by breathing and touching public stair railings
than the most pig-like peasant.
In 1567,
the people of London were forced to go to the hospital for the second time.
This is the worst thing London ever did!
That does seem a bit extreme.
You can move to the country, but there's no work there.
Violent crime is actually more frequent in the country, and the poisons are almost as bad anyway.
If the diseases don't get you some railroad toxic spill, Will ,
hell, just driving to work is riskier than hunting bears.
But there's one medicine more powerful than all the contamination in New Jersey,
and that medicine is SLACK!
Slack gives the mind power over all disease.
A truly happy chain smoker is less likely to attract the attention of the cancer demons
than is a tense, knotted-up health freak gnawing his fingernails to the bone.
My poor editor.
Then it says, don't read this!
Cancer is caused by pinkness, boredom, and meaninglessness.
It can be prevented by action, thrill, sex, even overwork.
Actually, the sad thing is that our editor at Simon & Schuster, when this book was written,
died at age 30 of cancer.
And he had to read these stupid lines.
Ugh.
You know, friends, don't ever do anything mean or stupid, because you'll remember it for a long time.
Forever.
You'll lay...
When you get to be in your 50s, you'll lay awake at night remembering stupid crap you did when you were 12 years old
and get red in the face, even though no one else remembers, nobody knows.
It's amazing.
You know, you don't even need karma for justice.
It'll get back...
You'll get yours back sooner or later.
Ugh.
So.
How do you keep a healthy life?
With a full, slackful outlook in the face of rampant eco-hell?
You plunge into eco-hell headfirst!
You don't let it scare you.
You don't let it push you around.
By all means, help fight to clean up America.
But if you want that junk food, eat it.
You want to watch TV instead of go to Jazzercise?
Watch it.
Indulge those conspiracy urges to the hilt and just purge their hold over you.
Sounds good.
Americans should eat like Americans.
As fast as they possibly can!
Tibetans should eat like Tibetans, studying each tiny bird-like bite until it becomes
a universe before taking it into their bodies.
You can eat like the Vietnamese, hardly at all.
Or you can eat what would feed dozens of Vietnamese families.
Either way, the Vietnamese aren't going to eat any more than they did before.
The world isn't starving because Americans eat too much.
Even if we stopped eating, the conspiracy would still throw the leftists out.
They'd send the leftovers away before they'd send it to any third-worlders.
Now, we all know that eating the meat of live protein animals is unholy.
It pollutes your system, creates aggression, and worst of all, requires the heartless slaughter of fellow creatures.
Mammals!
Fully as sensitive and loving as we, for this reason, vegetarians eat only plants.
A friend of mine said, the reason I don't like vegans is they eat my food's food.
But their sin is as great.
Science has proven unequivocally that all plants react to threatening stimuli with the low frequency version of what we would call panic.
They too are life forms with feelings which feel pain.
They may even have an all-telepathic civilization that we're too brutal to comprehend.
Thus, when you bite down on a grape, you're popping open and crushing.
Grinding.
A wee life which in its own way is squealing in the terror of the murdered innocent.
So anything that nourishes us is going to suffer.
We may as well let them all suffer equally.
By making a few of all types of living things victims of our all-important stomachs,
less members of each individual species will be sacrificed.
Besides, even though we devour and eliminate them,
so we make them.
We make them immortal and allow them to partake of our subgenius grandeur.
It works both ways.
Just as a cannibal eats his enemy's heart to gain his strength,
we eat a hamburger to gain the wisdom and courage of the mighty cow.
Yet, at the same time, we are inviting the cow's primal cellular structure,
his code if you will, to enter our bloodstreams where it may mingle with, learn from,
and mayhap even conspire with our own bloodstream.
We eat the broccoli to gain its patience and virtue.
In return, we release it back into the world reborn in a new form,
teeming with literally millions of newfound friends, the bacteria.
We drink the hops and grain to partake of their slow, slow yet wise judgment,
and in return sacrifice to them our coordination.
We eat the broccoli to gain its patience and virtue.
This isn't funny.
Thus, the word of Dobbs says we can eat anything we want.
You can gorge yourself to an early grave,
or you can consult shamans at health food stores and figure out ways to cure ills and lengthen your little span.
You can be a vegetarian, or you can keep an industrial diet,
living out of convenience stores and simul-food franchises.
You can stay in poverty eating expensive food, untainted by the sun,
or you can support the conspiracy in its lowest, most stinking form
by maintaining your sugar and fat addictions.
I used to smoke cigarettes when I wrote this.
Go ahead, suck down any and all forms of caffeine,
since if it's not that, something else will give you cancer of the colon and hypertension.
See what I mean? Like your job, maybe?
You can admit most of that canned and frozen food isn't really food,
and instead try to eat things that were recently alive and not cooked.
Cooked into broken, useless cell mush.
You can admit junk food does taste good,
and you can get into the snobdom,
or you can get into the snobdom of ever-changing health fadism,
just because the cool, rich people do it.
Or you can kill me!
Just remember that everything touched by the con has poison and carcinogens in it.
Scarf them if you wish, but put some money away for the painkillers you'll need later on.
And then it says, a typical subgenius daily diet.
And this, I've actually managed to live on this.
This is just a typical one.
Breakfast.
Fresh fruit, vitamins, organic goat's milk, brown rice, spirulina, live goldfish,
frop.
Frop is what we pretend Bob smokes in his pipe.
Beef.
Lunch.
Beef jerky.
Microwave burger.
Honey bun.
Coke.
Thunderbird wine.
Speed.
Coffee with sugar.
Frop.
Dinner.
Uncooked black-eyed peas.
Fish.
Milk.
Raw hay.
An apple for dessert.
Frop.
2 a.m.
25 cigarettes.
3 nails.
Frop.
Hey, look at me.
Somewhat healthier would be to hardly eat at all, but we cannot expect that of people until
TV commercials are banned, which would only happen in a truly upside-down world.
Another thing, although most American food is dangerous to human life and god-awful radiations
pour from every appliance and power line, remember, subgeniuses are mutants anyway.
If you can't escape from radiation, learn to love it.
After all, it's merely another form of energy.
Why can't our bodies learn to use it?
Like a plant uses sunlight.
If you absorb enough radiation, you can make amazing changes come about.
And our friend, Brother Cleve, clarified that doctrine as strength through disfigurement.
Strength through disfigurement.
If you don't just go out on New Year's Eve and act like that fool that amateur does,
you disfigure yourself every night, you drink that Thunderbird wine, you do that plate of
pain, you use the mirror of pain, you do anything you want and build up those immunities.
That was Brother Cleve's approach.
And it worked for me for a while.
That was from this year's Winter Star Symposium.
See Rosencomet.com for that.
See Noralpref.com for collages like the ones that aren't by Lemur.
Praise Radio Synesthesia at WCSB Cleveland for the call-ins and also puzzling evidence
at KPFA Berkeley and HAL and Philo and Hardboard Robot and John Hell's Show.
Season in heaven.
From Pirate Cat Radio which also features the Ask Dr. HAL Show.
This is the Hour of Slack.
And if you want more Slack in other forms like books or tours like Seattle in April 19th,
see Subgenius.com and click on everything.
I'm going to sign off now because I'm feeling a bit funny.
No pain.
You had breakfast?
I can't remember.
What's going on around here?
What do you mean?
Huh?
Kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Don't do that, please.
Why not?
Because it hurts me.
You shouldn't play with the big boys, darling.
Right, Gina?
Word from the wise.
You're next.
You should get a little rest, sweetie.
Yes, try to rest.
Try.
Kitty, kitty.
Mama?
I just feel so cold.
I feel so cold.
Godspeed.