Listen to yourself, Bob. You follow her to work, you open her mail, you eavesdrop on her
SELF-GENIUS POWER OF SWATCH!
Yesterday, I introduced into my body the largest dose I have yet dared,
wondering what this amazing experiment would do to me.
My transformation was complete within 25 minutes.
The fastest period to date.
Reconversion to normalcy was the slowest.
Almost an hour.
I was temporarily obsessed with the frightening thought I might never return.
Forever to be clutched in the savage grasp of a million lost years.
With all the future I exceed, I'll continue thinking grown-up again.
Over the thin, toilet in the street one next to the guys and
Sorry about that.
Oh!
Oh!!
I'm supposed to be baooping in my pants.
And you say you're just a little workout?
Didn't you say cool it?
After the tee wonder shirt!
No nothing!
Welcome to the Royal!
Now I'm opening this up again.
Real ninja wielder of the sacred, the spatula guy.
Okay spatula guy, head on up.
Friends, I've seen all kinds of artists, yo-yo artists, a couple of them here tonight.
Oh god, what have I been, squid artists, poo artists, you can make art with just about
anything.
The last night I met my very first spatula artist.
So how's it going everybody?
I'm new, they call me grill ninja wielder of the sacred spatula.
I learned this shit by listening to Digital Underground.
I'm sorry what was that?
I like it that way, it's alright.
It's all the vinegar that does it for me.
I once met a marine that was a member of the conspiracy, Mackinac, a friend of mine
who's a fan of Doctor Who.
And he was like, I'm full of piss and vinegar.
And I was like, sir you are more full of vinegar and water than you are full of piss and vinegar.
And I just wanted to say that to him in my heart right now in front of you.
See because like watch, watch this.
Okay alright, you know what's bigger than Scientology?
We are.
Like the subgenius is the way to go.
Bob Staten's fucking cock block Tom Cruise's any day of the week and it makes my heart
smile to say so.
Now, in terms of mysticism, which is one of the places where my heart lives, I have walked,
I don't know.
I've walked paths, I've seen death.
I've literally seen death.
It freaks me out.
But it's cool.
He's got a horse named Binky.
You know he helps Rince win the wizard.
I don't know how many of you follow Discworld but whatever.
As far as the situation goes though, I want to let you all know I'm glad to be here this
evening as well as this week because look, in my heart I've been a subgenius a long time
and Bob creeps me straight the fuck out.
But that's cool though.
Because he's supposed to.
He's supposed to be like, hey everybody, I'm going to sell you insurance but I'm going
to give you, I'm going to slip you the mickeys while you're doing it.
And you're like, whoa, this is the best insurance I ever bought.
He's like, yes it is.
Slack.
And I'm like, I have my heart smiling but I'm defecating myself at the same time and
I don't know why.
That's the beauty and majesty of this situation right now.
It's like a blues song, except not.
I'm too upbeat.
I was going to read some stuff from my books but maybe I won't.
I don't know yet.
We'll roll with this.
As far as the situation goes, mysticism and shenanigans, the binding of ourselves to our
reality and how we flow into it, through the glory of his pipe, isn't there like a saying
like say less, blah, blah, blah, something French that says this is not a pipe.
And it was Dadaism and shenanigans.
But see that ties into the kind of beliefs that we have.
What's that?
The Greek.
Okay.
See, I don't know.
I don't know.
I only know things.
I know random trivia.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And so the illusion of a pipe is what we deal in.
Dealing with illusions is one of the things I'm best at.
You give the illusion of depth.
I sit there on a two dimensional plane.
I give you eyes.
I give you truths.
I give you things you were never meant to see, but have brought home to your own lands,
blah, blah, blah, et cetera, et cetera.
Because I'm an artist and that's what we do, baby.
I will be glad to tell you all I know because I want to teach you guys a secret.
And I'm going to see if I can come up with a secret, if I can piece it together right
now at this moment.
Because I can feel your eyes on me.
I feel your vibes.
I can see the connections of you all.
The secret of art, a lot of people say it's communication.
It's creating that depth where it previously didn't exist.
It's taking something out of nothing and giving it to somebody else and then showing them
the value of its depth.
It's showing them the resonance that lives within our hearts.
It's giving it to somebody else and then showing them the value of its depth.
And it shows us who we are as humans, as people, as transcendents, as yetis even.
Yetis.
What's that now?
The balance of the spatula on the finger is a meditative process that helps when you haven't
been drinking.
But when you have been, you learn how it's done.
And you sit there and you're like, ooh, watch me twirl it.
Oh, I'm so skilled.
The beauty of the spatula, by the way, for me, is taking something that's a common household
utensil and making it something exceptional.
So you learn how to wield it and make it something great that goes beyond itself.
When you take something so common that the conspiracy is like, oh, it's just a spatula.
I don't even know.
Oh, I'm a Republican.
And you want to set them on fire and jizz on their tits or whatever you do with Republicans,
I don't know.
For the ladies, by the way, there's a secret.
You can totally jizz on someone's tits if you try hard enough, ladies.
You just got to want it.
You do a thing.
I don't know.
I don't.
They never told me how it's done.
I met a lady once anyway.
So I think she was a transvestite.
I don't know.
So no.
Secretly, though, the beauty and majesty of the spatula is taking something mundane and
making it something exceptional.
Okay.
And when you do this, it's a meditative process.
Connecting yourself to the great reality of life, what it means to connect and be a part
of transcend the conspiracy is doing stuff like that all day, every day.
One of us.
You were saying earlier that we were like part of the conspiracy and we're stuck in
it and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, you're right.
It's true.
But when you sit there and you move with it and you use its own ends to your ends, you
become something transcendent of it.
And you grow beyond the scope of the conspiracy.
That is why in my heart, Anubis lives and he says that's not cricket and that's what's
important.
So in the name of the subgenius, I grant you all a blessing.
I am blessing you with this spatula that makes me 10% better at everything.
And the first thing people want to do is spankings apparently.
They go, let me see your spatula.
Ah, spanking.
Spankings.
They do this every time.
So okay, it's going to be especially beneficial if you're going to spank somebody tonight.
But I'm blessing all of you.
In the name of Bob, in the name of myself, in the name of do what thou wilt and that
is the whole law even though Crowley was a douchebag.
Just let it go.
Just go with it.
Enjoy yourselves.
Make merry and carry on.
In the name of the subgenius.
You can't take me.
Don't tell me what to do.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
Now watch.
In spite of yourselves, it's going to happen anyway because I got the blues on my side
and I've taken the sadness away.
It is true.
I have.
Blessings upon you.
No.
You're dead.
But I will join you.
I will draw them for you.
Thank you guys so much.
That was a fucking harmonica.
That was great.
I just was like wow.
How many people punctuate a rant with a harmonica?
That's, you know, staying with staying there's a lot of firsts.
That's definitely a first.
A rant punctuated with a harmonica.
And a spatula.
I'm going to have to ret vị How are you doing.
Fucking droplets dog here.
Intro Dr.
As simple as this.
Just specific
Swimsuit.
Then we get a Dobbs doctor.
Dobbs doctor.
Who's Dobbs doctor?
Buds stretcher.
Doctor.
Doctor Buds stretcher.
Dr. Bob.
Doctor.
Paging Dr. Dobbs.
Dr. Dobbs.
We're looking for Dr. Dobbs.
Have you seen him?
I think he took that little nurse in in the back room.
Don't bother him.
Then he'll be in the bathroom
for at least three hours on a ship, right?
Because that's how Bob does things.
When Bob goes to work,
no work is occurred.
The only things that happen are what he wants.
Slack it.
For Bob.
All our dance are belongs to Bob.
All our funk are belongs to Bob.
All your knuckle babies are belongs to Bob.
All your juices,
your warm and tasty juices,
are belongs to Bob.
All our dance belong to Bob.
Even that ringworm you picked up on the shower floor tonight on your foot.
That belongs to Bob too.
All our dance belongs to Bob.
Bob owns the copyright on this song.
You know how much we get after royalties?
We get...
what's left in the bottom of a beer can of fucking backwash.
That's what we get.
Thanks, Bob.
Dr. Dr.
Bob!
Bob.
Dr. Dr.
Oh, Bob.
Bob.
Dr. Dr.
B.O.B.1.
Dr. Dr. Bad.
Dr. Dr. Dr.
Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr.
Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr.
Dr. Dr.
Dr. Dr. Dr.它 V.
...
Doctor.
Give a big round of applause for Radio Mike, who was on drums.
Seth Bichon is taking over drums.
Reverend 80 is on bass.
Stick has been on and off bass.
Biker Man is on...
Is that seriously a mandolin?
That's so awesome.
Biker Man is on mandolin.
Berg is on bass.
Dr. Flonase is on guitar.
Rock God is on guitar.
I'm just off kilter.
Philodrum is on whatever instrument he puts in front of him.
Which certainly is piano at the moment.
Gravity is on the hippie drum.
And Reverend Fox is on some weird electronic drum.
So, Rice...
Angry Larry was playing again whatever instrument he could get himself in front of.
Alright, so this is a fun one.
We're listening to a cooperate from you.
Thank you.
I was dreaming that.
I lost the scales from my eyes.
Oh, I lost the scales from my eyes.
What is that?
What is that thing?
Now they're open, I can clearly see
A whole world for me
Try to tone it all down
Oh
Just to keep around me
Just to keep her around
Oh
In the end it was still too much
She couldn't handle the rush
And it's all new
Amazing too
I can't begin to tell you
Ooh
I still wrapped up to see
Oh, what's good or not for me
Oh, I let my candle hide a cabinet door
I can't hide it no more
I lost the scales from my eyes
Oh, I lost the scales from my eyes
Oh, oh, oh
Thank you. I wrote that last Friday.
All right.
That was a new song by St. Andrew the Impaled of Pittsburgh,
recorded live by Reverend Suds or myself
at the 18X Day Drill of last July.
And yet, he wrote that song last Friday.
Whatevs.
Praise Andrew and all the other musicians and anti-musicians
who made it to the Wisteria Campground
and saw the show.
I'm in Southern Ohio to celebrate the end of the world together.
And hey, it still might end any minute.
So yeah, this is the third of the X Day cross-section shows
featuring many, many subgenies,
such as Reverend Grill Ninja, heard earlier,
the Giant Germs, featuring Reverend Angry Larry on guitar,
and the Brigadoon-like X Day jam band
Six Fisted Tales of Connie, as heard here
with Priestess Pisces.
neutrally ahead of this time,
as well as fervor
welcomed and
show of the week.
you drag the weight off
you to
Izzy for
And you put listened to something really interesting while we're live right now
You had your choice
The knowledge was before you
I heard your voice
You denied all that they told you
I cannot help you see
The mistakes you've made
I cannot save your soul
From the coming of existence
There is no cure for stupidity
You could have paid your learnings back
But now it's all gone
It's time to die
And to the angels and devils
Do you cry?
But never ask me why
There is no cure for stupidity
Do you cry?
Now you see what you've done
So don't play
There is no cure for stupidity
You'd be free or dead
If you listened to me
In an old house, there is always listening, and more is heard than is spoken, and what
is spoken remains in the room, waiting for the future to hear it. And whatever happens started
in the past and presses hard on the future. The agony in the curtained bedroom, whether of birth
or of dying, gathers into itself all the voices of the past and projects them into the future.
The treble voices on the lawn, the mowing of hay,
in summer, the dogs and the old pony, the stumble and the wail of little pain, the chopping
of wood in autumn, the singing in the kitchen and the footsteps at night in the corridor,
the moment of sudden loathing and the season of stifled sorrow, the whisper, the transparent
deception, the keeping up of appearances, the making the best of a bad job, all twirl
and the twine and tangled together, all are recorded. There is no avoiding these things,
and we know nothing of exorcism, and whether in Argos or Wisteria, there are certain inflexible
laws unalterable in the nature of music. There is nothing to do about it. There is nothing
to be done about anything. And now it is nearly time for the news. We must listen for the weather
report and the international catastrophes. Those two samples were by T.S. Eliot.
And that was Dr. Howell of the Ask Dr. Howell Show, reciting T.S. Eliot from memory. Howell is like the people in Fairmont,
New York, and he is the first person to write a book about the world. He is a great artist.
He is an incredible artist. Google Hal Robbins with one B and you'll see. In a little while,
we'll be going back to 18X Day for a little of the Doctors for Wotan reunion concert featuring
the Stang and Drummond families, a somewhat revised version of the classic bowl song Louie
Louie. But first, we're going back in time to the
year of the first.
The year of 1980 and the original Doctors for Wotan version from the first Doctors for Wotan album.
Philo and I both had different wives then. We weren't in the band.
Now we are
Hey! That's my Louie Louie!
Guys Göran Unless when the virus out there so
Louie, Louie, you want to?
Women Sounds Like MAR nunus
Louie, Louie! Louie, Louie, you make me run
Louie, Louie, you make me run
And I suck at music and I'll never trust myself to play that one tune again
Lily, Lily, are you a girl or a goat woman?
Lily, Lily, oh baby, you have some kind of weird mush in your glands.
Everything has a logical explanation in science. I refuse to believe the supernatural.
There must be some logical cause and effect to this, this unholy adventure.
Reckon there must. Any ideas?
Well, no.
I was just thinking something is missing.
I was going, oh yeah, my audio recorder.
And that's a big part of any Wotan band is the audio recorder.
Because it should be closest to the speaker I'm on.
I think it's on the sound booth.
It may be better there. It may be safer. It will certainly be cleaner.
The recorders will be much cleaner the farther they are from the doctors.
Because, you know, it's surgery. There's blood.
Stitches pop open. Gross black stuff comes out.
Did you cut your belly open again?
Are we going to do a best song again?
Did you cut your belly open again and show you the black stuff?
Well, I was just saying you don't want to get your tape recorder too close to where the doctors are operating.
Because you can actually destroy the sensitive blood cells.
You can get the black stuff on it. The ink core.
The ink core from the patient.
The ink core.
The spittle of the doctors.
Dr. Howe has a name for that ink core.
The black stuff.
The black stuff. Yeah, that black stuff you got in there.
Okay, so I'm going to go tune up my instrument a little more.
Keep talking.
I can?
Let's keep the audience vamping for a little more.
Why did you get up and tell me that?
See, he's bossy. Isn't he bossy?
You're not the boss of me, Dr. Dobson.
You're not the boss of me, gentlemen.
He's not the boss.
Well, he actually sort of is.
He's the great.
He has on the best.
Loud!
He is black.
His body.
I'm going to go ahead and just rip this.
There's my bobcat.
I'm breaking my eardrum on that last one.
Get these packages!
You don't need that eardrum. You didn't need that eardrum anyway, Dr. Drummond.
I've been doing fine with only half of one.
I think this is what happens.
Now, did you bring our playlist?
Yeah, yeah, here's the playlist.
Here's the playlist that we can play.
We need to play it.
Into the Word of God.
You mean that's where that song actually came from?
Yeah.
Well, I'll be.
I want to know if my face is on fire.
That's a question people ask themselves sometimes.
Well, not everybody. Some people don't even bother to ask themselves, say,
is my face on fire by any chance?
And their friends have to tell them.
Yeah.
Your face is on fire!
A friend would tell.
Oh my God, thank you for telling me.
A good friend would blow it out.
Would blow on your face so hard that it would extinguish the fire.
Would you tell me if my face was on fire?
Dude, your face is on fire!
You slam it in the paint and quit putting it out or you'll hurt yourself.
Oh man, thanks for telling me.
I didn't realize my face was on fire until you mentioned that.
God, if I could have burned half my face off you, you're a real friend.
You told me my face was on fire!
Yeah.
I can't wait until we get to this.
Louie Louie.
Louie Louie, Louie Louie.
Yeah, okay. Let's do that.
You know the big tails in the background?
Louie Louie.
That sounds like Louie Louie to me.
That sounds exactly like Louie Louie.
Louie Louie.
Listen to that.
Are you a girl or a girl?
I'm a girl.
Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a girl?
I'm a girl.
Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a girl?
I'm a girl.
Louie Louie.
I didn't know.
I wanted to say better.
But the sign said,
I see the goat woman.
And I did it.
I paid my 50 cents and I saw her there she was.
Louie Louie.
Dancing across the stage.
With the other girls.
And she looked so beautiful.
And her beard smelled.
And her udders.
Those distended udders.
Her udders.
Louie Louie.
She left her pellets.
Those little pellets.
All over the rug.
And the most beautiful of all.
She left behind on the stage.
As she danced.
Tiny pellets.
And I knew she was the girl for me.
Louie Louie.
Are you a girl or a girl?
Are you a girl?
I love you so much.
Louie Louie.
Oh come back to me Louie Louie.
She ran away back to the fairgrounds.
She said she wanted to travel
to the fellow beach and the she was part of it.
But I just
love her and I miss her.
Oh come back to me Louie Louie.
I want a ghost, why not ghost?
I am the ghost woman!
What the hell is this? Why not ghost?
Why not ghost?
Are you one of our girlfriends? Why not ghost?
Louie Louie, you are a girl and a ghost woman.
Yeah!
No!
The song is almost over. The song is almost over now.
Okay, we have to change songs now.
That was Louie Louie, Are You A Girl And A Ghost Woman.
Did you ever sing that in any of those Louie Louie marathons where they play every other song?
Louie Louie, oh baby.
You know, the big bands take a break every so often.
We gotta go.
Where did my recorder end up?
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
All my basic animal instincts were enlarged and inflamed.
Power felt as if it were bursting from every pore.
I gloried in my strength and ferocity.
Modern man was completely subjugated,
leaving only the irresistible instinct of survival
and the hungry urge to kill.
I was finally skinned,
I was goin' to jail,
Just so they would kick my ass.
IHyner.co..
I say pret reception.
That's as deep as ideals can be.
Merございます.
guitar solo
A fine instrumental by Six Fisted Tales of Connie, especially Reverend Angry Larry.
A tune I decided to call Drive-In Love.
The monster movie clips in this show, by the way, are from the 1953 movie The Neanderthal Man.
Between those clips and the music, what do you think you were hearing in a new Amino Acids album?
And speaking of new albums, there is another collection of Subgenius music out on Bandcamp.com.
Bob's songs number 8, Orally Transmitted Diseases.
You can find the link on Subgenius.com very easily.
It's the result of 10 songs.
10 years of stored up music by dozens of different Subgenius bands.
Most of it does not sound like the completely improvised and off-the-cuff spontaneous performances like you get with Six Fisted Tales.
Such as this unexpected version of Blitzkrieg Bob.
Blitzkrieg Bob
Blitzkrieg
Oh, self-centered lummox.
Everything you do interests me.
Everything you'll ever do interests me for the rest of our lives.
If you can't trust me, who can you trust?
I won't be laughed at anymore.
I would never laugh at you, darling.
Who would ever laugh?
They laughed.
They?
Me, that pack of thick-headed, egotistical stuffed shirts at the Naturist Club.
Lunacy, eh?
Long-exploded theories, eh?
A lot they know in their stupid obstinacy,
in their peevishness of mind and soul.
It's here, I tell you. All here.
After all this work, I've done it.
I know I have.
What? Done what?
What? Cliff, what is it?
The embodiment of my theories of memory stimulation.
The reactivation of the dormant cells of the mind of man.
Dormant cells?
Man is not of himself.
He's made of everything that has gone before.
He's part of every ancestor he ever had back to the beginnings of his human intelligence.
They derided me, those gentlemen at the club.
They scoffed.
I felt, why? At least couldn't they have admitted the possibility I was right?
Let's just take care of tomorrow.
Let's do it.
No tomorrow.
Let's take care of tomorrow, baby.
Let's do it tomorrow.
No tomorrow.
There is no tomorrow
For you, for you, for you, for you
Cause baby
There is no tomorrow
For you, for you, for you, for you
Man has lost nothing of his emotions from the dawn of his history.
He's lost nothing of his greed, his fury, his savagery, his jungle rapacity.
Why not his physical personality?
All right.
You deny me too.
I can see it in your eyes.
They put it into words, but you're thinking it.
Cliff, please.
There's no way.
You need to get some.
I didn't ask you to come here.
I know, but...
Please do me the favor by leaving.
Cliff, please.
Get out, I say.
You're no better than the rest of them.
You're nothing but a vacuum of ego.
Swelling, ready to burst.
Thinking your own empty desires to be all that there is in life.
But there are more important things than your puny adoration of self.
Ah!
Hey, hi.
Hi, hi.
Woo!
Ah!
Thank you.
I don't know.
Like a couple of months now,
I've had David Bowie stuck in my head
and it's like infinite loop,
which I initially want to blame
on the Guardians of the Galaxy movie
and Daydream.
But like,
I had to keep listening to Bowie.
And so I mentioned to Stang in passing
that I was considering doing a particular Bowie tune.
And Stang says to me,
you know, Princess Wee
is the world's biggest Bowie fan.
Well, then it turns out
that Robin is also
the world's biggest Bowie fan.
So, there is a song by Bowie
that many of you have probably heard
that when you really listen to the lyrics,
it's clear.
There's only one person
this song could possibly ever be about.
And that's Bob.
So, without further ado,
Man Who Sold the World.
Man Who Sold the World
I spoke into his eyes
I thought you'd die alone
A long, long time ago
Oh no, not me
We never lost control
Your face to face
With a man who sold the world
I laughed and shook his hand
I made my way back home
I searched for a foreign land
For years and years I roamed
I gazed and gazed instead
At all the millions there
We must have had a love
A love that was so strong
A love that no one heard
It's what it seems
A love that had shown
It's a trертure
It's not the way
It's a love that last People recently say
Who's killed these short-lived guys
That hope
Chosen to repeat
To honor
Another life
Who knows, not me, we never lost control Your face took space with a man who sold the world
La la la la ...
All right.
Praise Bob.
Thank you.
He took my frog!
Bob!
That bastard took my frog!
He took it!
He took my frog!
So I cried, I cried, I cried.
Bob!
He took my frog!
He took it!
Bob took my frog!
What can I do man, what can I do?
You see, it's Bob, and Bob took my frog!
Bob!
He took my frog!
He took it!
Pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, my friend.
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
From the Church of the Subgenius and the Blue Dot of Time Control Labs,
my name is Bob.
SubgeniusFoundation.com
With more than 10 hours of eargasmic ecstasy.
Only $10 per album or $1 per track.
Pull the wool over your own eyes all over again with Sister Melodious Chops.
Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger.
Brother Cleve Donut Duncan.
Jehovah Hates Bread.
Artemia Selena.
The El Queso All Stars.
Noral Prep.
Dr. Onan Canobite.
And many, many more.
Spend Money Games Slack.
Order now.
All rights reserved.
All materials are copyrighted by their respective owners.
Any similarities between anyone living or dead is purely coincidental.
Get rid of this.
Continues.
Please consult a physician.
Doors under 18.
Not a fly.
Void.
Or prohibited.
Operate.
Expires.
Log in.
Operators are standing by.