A subgenius
Our Hour of Slack.
Hour of Slack.
The Hour of Slack.
Sister Genies.
Bob.
Oh yes, dear friends.
And welcome to the first Live Hour of Slack in about a hundred weeks.
And this is, we had a good excuse for it.
For one thing, I can walk and wear a shirt and no bandages and all that.
But the other thing is, we have a special guest here at Stang Ranch at Tarzan's radio station.
And my friends, it's none other than the overman himself, Dr. Philo Drummond.
Yay!
Well, I'm glad to be here.
I'm awful glad you're here.
When was the last time you were on the Puzzling Evidence show?
It was like three or four years ago, right?
It was, let's see, the 19th of June, 2017.
Yep.
The 19th of June, 2017.
Goodness.
My swan song.
In public radio.
This can be your new pirate flag.
Congratulations.
My re-entry back into the mainstream of the non-mainstream.
The mainstream of the backside of reality.
Now, you guys remember to talk sort of close to the microphones.
Don't do a Susie on me, okay?
All right.
Or a Hal.
I won't.
Actually, doing a Hal is when you fall asleep with your forehead leaning against the wind.
You know, Hal would, he was like, at one point, he was,
would like anchor himself with his nose touching the windscreen.
Right.
And then he could kind of doze off a bit.
He'd sort of meditate for a little while.
It's really easy.
Nobody would realize that until they try to be on a radio show,
that simply touching your nose to the windscreen on a microphone has a,
I'm going to try that.
It has a hypnotic effect.
Hmm.
Ha ha ha.
See what I, see what I mean?
Hal was on, Hal was on to something.
It turns you into shimp.
Right.
It's a shimp.
Yes, friends.
It's, it's the, the first new hour of Slack in months and months, and it's a new year.
It's the conspiracy says it's 2022.
Personally, you know, I mean, obviously,
it's that's silly because the excess haven't arrived.
It's 1997 all over.
Right.
Yeah.
It might as well be.
I mean, we don't know who cares.
We don't even know what planet it's on.
Yeah.
All that old stuff.
I really, I'm kind of going for the, uh, the, that one theory of, uh, it's 1998 was upside
down all the time.
86, 61.
Yeah.
So we've got a lot.
We've got a lot of time.
A lot of time.
And that's proof that the world isn't really going to end anytime soon.
Well,
because we know it.
X day is going to happen.
And so how could the world end before X day?
We need X day to bring about the end of the world.
Right.
So, well, you know, the other, some of the rival cults feel like they have to have war
in the middle East in order to bring about the proper end of the world with Jesus.
That won't be the proper end of the world.
That will be like a sub sub.
That's just some one of the precursors of the world.
That's a precursor to the true X day.
Yeah.
We've got to wait.
Until 86, 61.
And some of us probably won't make it.
Right.
That red, that red calf and the, the, and the white Buffalo and all those different special
creatures have to come.
Yeah.
And be born.
The red heifer.
That's right.
Yeah.
The red heifer.
And the black, the black, the black Yeti.
Yeah.
The black Yeti has to be born.
I was thinking about the black Yeti.
We cut that from Revelation X.
The blue bull.
Because the black.
The black Yeti had the biggest.
No, the blue.
Of all the Yetis, the black Yeti, of course, had the biggest feet.
Yeah.
Feet.
And you know what big feet mean?
Big shoes.
Big shoes and big nose.
Yeah.
That's P-O-P-Y.
But we do had.
We did have.
Peewee and Lawrence Fishburne, in fact.
We had a blue ox.
It was Peewee and Lawrence Fishburne.
Lawrence Fishburne had the line, I think.
You know what big feet means?
Big shoes.
Big boots.
He was Cowboy Bob.
Yeah.
That was Morpheus.
Yep.
God, man.
Old Morpheus.
I guess acting is a thing where they act like something.
But you remember Lawrence Fishburne was in Apocalypse Now.
He was.
Oh, that's right.
He was a skinny kid.
One of the guys on the boat.
He was a real skinny kid that went surfing to Rolling Stones.
He got all shot up.
Yeah.
That's right.
That baby Lawrence Fishburne.
Wow.
Just never.
He was 17 or 18 or something in that movie.
Man.
These actors can play somebody of any age.
How could the pock-faced, giant, fat guy, Lawrence Fishburne, play that skinny 18-year-old?
Seems like one of those death-
Time control.
One of those Death Wish movies had Jeff Goldblum or what's his name?
Goldberg.
Goldblum.
Yeah.
Jeff Goldblum.
The girls love him.
No.
Is it Goldblum or Goldberg?
Goldblum.
He's tall and skinny.
That's why the girls like him.
Anyway, he was in, I think, Death Wish II or maybe some ... He played on those evil guys
that were trying to kill Paul Kersey after ... Or take advantage of the neighborhood.
He was like just ... He was probably the most nervous.
He was like a teenager.
The nervous evil guy.
Because he's always nervous.
Oh no.
What was that?
That was the automatic volume override.
That's what it was.
I don't know what that was.
If you make a big noise, everything goes down for a second.
It's on automatic.
Yeah.
That's the easiest way to do it.
How about this music in the background?
It's really soft.
It's French swing.
French swing.
By different bands that St. Byron Warner sent to Princess Waite.
Not me.
He sent it to her.
Well, he knows that she still has her hearing.
Something's wrong.
Well, we had a little bit of a conversation.
We had a conversation about music that he'd been seeking out.
And she can actually hear the notes and things.
Right.
Hey, speaking of music, now this.
Now see, that's where I could cut in a swing in Love Corpses.
Right.
Thing.
Yeah.
She drove me out of something.
Don't you go dancing with your blue jeans on
You better wear leather or maybe nylon
You won't have to wonder if you just got a stamp
You're looking at the bulbs in your underwear
Excuse me, mama's really big and small
And I get a lot of room cause I'm dancing with my heart
I need some place where I can hide
Cause it's a growing and a pushing and a pushing from inside
Feel it getting bigger, it's about to rip
I'm getting bigger, it's about to rip
My jeans are my jeans, I'm growing a bit
Excuse me, mama's really big and small
And I get a lot of room cause I'm dancing with my heart
Hey, kitty boy
I need a better place where I can hide
That's right, I'll tell you why
Cause it's a growing and a pushing and a pushing from inside
I need a better place where I can hide
It's about to rip
Dreams are my dreams
I throw with a thrill
She's a man
One that's really
Thank you, Paul
And I need a lot of room
Cause I'm dancing
With a hard-on
Dancing with a hard-on
I'm dancing
I got a diamond cutter
Dancing with a hard-on
It's a blue fader
The hard-dropping
Muscle of love
Dancing with a hard-on
Make way for the
I'm dancing
Dancing with a hard-on
Yeah, that's right
They know how it feels
When you've been
Dancing with a hard-on
I must really
Beg your pardon
I need a lot of room
When I'm dancing
With my hard-on
Yeah, it's about a guy
With a purple heart
Right
Proud of his purple heart
And it's
That was the way
I explained it
And it's stuck right
To the front of his pants
Yeah
Right on his zipper
See my heart on
Yeah
You guys were so ahead
Of your time
The Swinging Love Corpses
People may not understand this
But there was no spinal cord
Tap
At the time that
The Swinging Love Corpses
Were doing their
Commentary on the
Tropes of
Modern rock and roll bands
I think that we were
Co-temporaneous
At one point there
Because I remember
We got free tickets
To go see Spinal Tap
When they were filming it
But you
Yeah, when they were
Filming it
But you guys were already
Doing it
Yeah
You know, I always had
This favorite band
Festival lineup
That was like
It would open
Tenacious D would open
And
It was
It would have
A mighty wind
And Spinal Tap
And then the
Swinging Love Corpses
And then the final finale
Would be Frank Marino
And Mahogany Rush
Because he's serious
And he's a
He was a classic example
Of one of those
Over the top
Stadium bands
That had to have
The hour long
Bass solo
And then the hour long
Drum solo
I went to see him
In Cleveland
About ten years ago
He was still playing
And I made it
Through the drum solo
But then he said
Here comes the bass solo
I had to leave
I couldn't stay to hear him
The Swinging Love Corpses
We used to have
Our drummer was
Demanded his
His solo, of course
And so he was
Fairly self-indulgent
Which we promoted
Skippy Mojo Butcher
Mojo Skippy Butcher
Oh
And so he would go
Into his drum solo
And we would
Drag out the
Drum solo
And we would
Lounge chairs
And turn on the TV
And read the newspaper
While he did his
Drum solo
And finally
He'd be finished
And we'd put everything
Away and get back
Into the song
I liked the
Swinging Love Corpses
Songs that would
End for like
Five minutes
We had one
That was like
A minute long
And then would end
For like
Five or six minutes
Yeah
Ever more
Triumphant
You know
Buildups
To a
Trash
And then
The drummer would
But then they couldn't
Quite quit
You know
Just when you thought
It was over
Like the monster
That keeps coming back
When you think he's dead
Yeah
That was
There was
I remember there was
A band that had a song
Like that
I think it was the
It was the Outlaws
They had that
One of those
Takeoff endings
That goes on
That just goes on
Forever
And it's got like
Three guitars
Going at the same time
But you guys were
A very visually
Interesting band
Because you wore
Really cool
Hippie costumes
And
Back then you had
Long hair
Yeah they looked
Like something out
Of a quick silver
Messenger service
Crossed with
Country Joe
And the fish
Or something
And
That's the look
We were going for
Yeah
And it was sort of
Defined by the fact
That we had
Gotten all of our clothes
At the same rag merchant
I didn't know that
We went there
And dug through the
Popsicle box
And found our
Best outfits that way
Wow
Huh
Yeah
And then we
Had to wear wigs
And that was one of the
Cardinal sins in the band
Is that you couldn't
Take your wig off
Right
Well that'd be
You'd be breaking character
Well what happened
We did have that time
In Chicago
Where we were playing
In that club
That was about
150 degrees
On the inside
Oh my god
And it was like
Playing inside of an oven
Yeah
And you couldn't play
With a wig on
We had to take
Our wigs off
Or die
Flip your wigs
Yeah
It was really sad
Because
Yeah
Because they
Because they need
To just look like
Businessmen
And then our fans
You look like
Cable repair guys
And our fans realized
That that wasn't
Our real hair
You look like
Xerox repairmen
And AT
And yellow page salesmen
Yeah
And
Conveyor belt
Manufacturers
And things
So
Pharmaceutical salesmen
It was crazy
Our buddies on the show
And some of our fans
Were so sad
Because they realized
That we really
That really wasn't
Our hair
That wasn't
Our real hair
And that some of us
Were actually bald
Underneath
That's sad
Well you know
Now I can
I'd do both
I have real long hair
And I'm bald
Yeah
I'm bald on top
But I have long brown hair
It's all white in the front
Look coming
Coming towards somebody
I look like a little old man
Walking away
I look like
Some kind of pirate
Or barker
Or biker
Or a pirate
Who mated with an angel
I would keep
Reminding myself of that
If I were you
Yeah
Well I
Ladies
Ladies like my punk
How angelic
And yet piratical
You look
I have horny
From behind
Horny divorcees
Come up to me
From behind
All the time
I can't go on that
But then when I turn around
And look at them
And smile
They kind of
Their face drops
I'm so hopeful
Now I'm so let down
He had such a cute butt
And nice long hair
Yeah
But he's much older
Than my husband
He's much older
Than my dad
Goodness
The dogs are here
My goodness
It must be
It must be chilly outside
Yeti's here
Chupacabra is here
Oh there's an article
About chupacabras
My new skeptic
Oh really
Inquirer newsletter
I get in the email
I read a lot of
Skeptical stuff
Because I like monsters
And they cover monsters
And spooks
And I'm bad
I'm pretty skeptical
About most everything
Well you know
Robert Anton Wilson
Was skeptical about
Everything
And skepticism
And I'm not skeptical
About anything
He had kind of a
Why not both approach
Although he hadn't
He called it
Maybe logic
I've boiled it down
To why not both
Or in some cases
Why not all three
I think it's like
An extension of your concept
That I've applied
To disagreeing
And it's really
We just agree differently
Right
You never have to be
Disagreeing with anyone
The whole world
Can just realize
That they agree differently
Now see this is when
I should have
I copy stuff
Off of our secret news group
And there's a whole thing
About the differently
The differently everything
It was like you know
The differently moral
The differently sane
Of course
Was the first one
But we just
God
We've
Well that group
Really extends itself
To be more of a
Philosophical discussion group
Well I know
But I like
I've got a whole
Six pages of stuff up there
Just from the last three days
Of you
Me and Onan
And Sterno
Just
And Marty going back and forth
I mean Sphinx
Colonel
Sphinx
Yeah
We're part of a very
August
And elite
Assemblage
You talk about
Illuminati
And elites
And lizard people
And stuff
We've got
We've got it boiled down
To the five
Or six
It's only really five
Controllers
Of the universe
It's
You've heard of
Semi-sweet
Channels
And chocolates
We're like a
Semi-secret society
We're semi-secret
Semi
I didn't mean to say
Edit that part
Semi-semi
Out in the mix
Later okay
Semi-seemly thing
That part I was dumb
See my semen maker
No
See that part
Where I was dumb
Edit that out
And make me sound
Smart again
Okay
That's easy
I'll just turn it
Or turn it around backwards
Or something
That's really clever
No that means
You're giving the KPFA
Phone number
Yeah
Or the WCSB
Phone number
Come on
Call in
Why aren't you
Calling in
Because I have the problem
This show actually
Plays on
Several different
Actors
Actual broadcast
Radio stations
Not many
But they're the best ones
And people want to call in
And talk to us
And they can't
Right
They would end up
Getting somebody at KPFA
Or somebody in Cleveland
And
Why don't you just give them
Just right now
Give them your phone number
And have them call us now
Sure
216-320-9528
That's the
Call us now
We're waiting for your call
Right now
Yeah
If you get straight
What's the problem
Call us now
It's on the website
We're standing by
Subgenius.com
People go
Well Stang
I didn't know how to get hold of you
Why didn't you try
Googling Ivan Stang email
Or Subgenius phone number
That's the phone
That rings in my pocket
Nobody ever calls it though
Except Bernard
That psycho guy
Well I call it once in a while
Hardly ever
In fact you had to ask me
What my phone number was
Not that long ago
That's the thing
That wasn't me
Yeah
Well you had to ask
Yeah you've had
No you were asking
The address
Like what
What's your mailing address
It's like
He doesn't even know
The sacred P.O. box
Yeah well I was in a position
Where I couldn't look it up
But you were more accessible to me
Than other addresses
Here's how you remember
The P.O. box
It's like 808
It has eights
It has eights in it
But it's
We couldn't quite get up to
808 for Bob
So it's 807
Yeah
Mr. Yarborough has 808
And I'm waiting for him to die
I didn't say that
But your street address
Is different
Well yeah yeah
My street address
Yeah but the mail
Won't come here
This is too remote
And deadly
What do they do
With that box out there
That's for U.S. mail
Yeah some mail goes
So your junk mail
Goes in there
Yeah
But we use the P.O. box
807 Glen Rose, Texas
Come offers
And
P.O. box
But if he's like us
His children
Will then use the box
After him
They'll get 808
Maybe you can just steal
The box when he dies
And swap it out with yours
You know actually I could
I have thought about
Writing the guy a letter
And saying
Would you be open
To swapping post office boxes
And explain to him
That 808 ties into my business
Logo
Right
And probably he's going to go
No I should wait a minute
I don't want to be
Too much trouble
I don't need to
I've got all my
My business cards
And everything printed with that
I just don't think
I can do that
You want me to change the street
To Martin Luther King
Boy you nailed Mr. Yarbrough
And we don't even know
Anything about him
That's him alright
This is Garden Grove
You will not
You do a pretty good
Texas accent
Talk about that
I've been known to live
In this state from time to time
It's not
It's not a lot different
From a Kentucky accent
They kind of drag it out
A little bit flatter
Actually there's so many
Texas accents
It's ridiculous
Yours is a little bit
More Houston-y
I like to use a classic
A classic Houston accent
To most
To the average human
You and me sound
Almost alike
The people that told me
They had trouble
Telling us apart
Although I don't understand
That's true
I don't get that
The accent anyway
But not the voice
Timber
Dr. Drummond has the loudest
Most piercing voice
In the whole world
Next to yours
Princess Marie
Oh I didn't know that
Yeah that's why
You're the only two people
I can understand
I see
The speech
Everyone else just sounds
Like they're mumbling
I've been guessing
What Dr. Howell says
For 20 years
Because I get tired
Of going
Sorry
Sorry Howell
Can you say that again
Okay I'll say it again
They always overdo it
You know
Yeah
They get it
It's almost like
They're angry
Because you didn't hear
Yeah so they
So they say it like
Way louder than anyone
Would ever need it to be
I'm just differently
Hearinged
You're different
I can hear you guys
Fine
Of course I'm in headphones
They're cranked
All the way up
You know our TV
Is set on
A hundred
All the time
My grandsons
Came in
And literally
Like screamed
When I turned on
The Wii or something
They were like
Turn it off
Where's the volume
Please
Where's the remote
Please grandfather
Don't hurt us
That's my sister's TV
We never found
The remote for it
No
Stop hurting
His grandfather
Yeah
It was like that
They were going
Alexander goes
It's turned up
To a hundred
And I said
Welcome to the world
Of the hard of hearing
Boys
And I said
They just
Couldn't grok it
They've been forgetting
That their entire lives
Those poor sons of
Grandsons
Those poor sons
Of your
Sons of our sons
Sons of the pioneers
Those poor sons
Of your daughter
Those guys
Have it pretty good
Let me tell you
They really do
Yeah
These kids
These days
They don't have to
Try anymore
They don't
We can't do that
They don't try
They do
These zombies
These days
They don't have to try
These zombies
These days
They don't try
Now when I was a zombie
We got up at
Five o'clock in the morning
To eat the face
Of a
Of a grandma
Yeah but see
We're ripping off
Jane or Hyperclits
And
No no
And that means
We owe him a million
More dollars now
That's right
That's exactly right
Just for those
Five or ten words
Just for mentioning
His name
He's gonna
Stange me
Ripping me off
He sold thousands
Of Jane or device tapes
I know
Cause I've met
Three people
Who just
Memorized parts of it
Yeah
That means
He sold
Probably
Two or three thousand
Hundred thousand
We sold nine a year
Like we sold
Of all the media
Barrage tapes
Till we pulled it
That's about how many
Tapes we sold
Back then
Oddly enough
We're doing a little
Better now
Although whenever
Somebody buys a CD
I know they're old
I know it's a really
Old person
You know
I think the
Church is starting
To hit its stride
We're really
Kind of now
Finally
Starting to
Take off a little bit
After
We are
Well maybe in the next
I can
We've been saying that
For forty years
I think I'm seeing
A little rise
In the trajectory
In these numbers here
Well
Sandy Boone's
Seems like
Award winning
Documentary
Maybe the world
Is tilting
And the church
Of the subgenius
Available on
Apple TV
And Fandango
And others
Can you buy that DVD
On Amazon
Or anything
You can't buy the DVD
Period
I can
But I mean
Are they
Do they have plans
On producing
DVD
No
Really
Nobody
Put optical
Here's the last
My son said this to me
Dad
I think you're the last
Person I know
That still uses
Optical media
It took me a minute
To realize
He meant DVDs
And CDs
Here's what I say
We're using
Offline media
Really
Yeah
Offline media
Optical media
Is a type of
Offline media son
Someday
We won't all be
Connected to the internet
Anymore
And I'll still be
Watching a movie
I've been thinking
About teaching
Workshops
At places like
Starwood
Or Harvard University
About
Data
Capture
Post
Internet
You know
Post electricity
Data capture
Right
I would introduce
Them to
The pencil
And the
Sheet
Of paper
Right
Which a lot of people
Don't even
You know
It's like they don't
You know what else
You can do
You can teach them
The code of
Cursive handwriting
It's a special code
Oh yeah
That only some people
Can read
Yeah it's a secret
That's secret
It's a secret type of
Code now
Yeah
Right
That's why they wrote
The Declaration of Independence
That way
So nobody
So no one could read it
Yeah
They don't even know
What language
They don't want to read it
Yeah
It would hurt their eyes
To learn to read it
And their brains
Trump had trouble
Reading it
In a
You know
Typed up
Printed script form
And he goes
It's almost like
A foreign language
Isn't it
No
It's actually
Modern English
Who was this
Trump
Yeah
He was
They were recording
They had all the
Presidents that were alive
And a bunch of other people
Reading parts of
The Declaration of Independence
The Constitution
Yeah
Or the
Maybe it's the Constitution
And
Each one had a different paragraph
And apparently
The tape of Trump
Trying to do it
Is like the
Colonel Sanders
Tape
You know
He's like
He couldn't
He never got a good take of it
And he just
He didn't really understand
Some of the words
Do you remember that
That one where
It had Orson Welles
The peas
Yeah
That's so classic
I love that
See those aren't prank calls
We could cut to those
He's taken apart
The whole
Telling them what a
Poor job
Right
The writer's bad
The director's bad
He's just
Tearing them apart
Because they're telling him
To read it a certain way
You know
Yeah
It's just hilarious
There's a whole bunch
Of those
Seems like
Celebrity
Celebrities
At their worst
That's what it was
Celebrities at their worst
I bet
And they have like
John Wayne
And he's drunk
And he's doing
Something on stage
Yeah he's talking
To a cop
To a college
Yeah
A college
Graduation
And just a whole bunch
Of people that were
Really
Used to play that
Yeah
Chaz played that
John Wayne won a lot
Yeah
The drunken celebrities
I like that stuff
Trump will be on
One of those someday
Oh god
I can't even
Imagine
Remember that idiot
George Bush
All the things he would say
We're putting
We're trying to put
Food on
What did he say
I'm putting
Putting
You're trying
It's tough for you
To put food on
Your family
Yeah and you know
Fool me once
Fool me twice
You know
Yeah
Frankly I totally
It's like
Bush had so many gaffes
But that's the way
People talk
I mean come on
That's actually
If you cherry pick
Anybody talking in public
You're gonna
You can easily
Pull up all kinds
Of embarrassing
And now
Nobody can
And there's no
Private
Privacy anymore
So
And everybody has
Everybody's a reporter
With a cell phone
You know
So you can't escape
The gaffe anymore
Somebody's gonna get it
Well it's perfectly
Normal
And of course
Any gaffe
By anybody
Of any importance
Or anybody
You don't like
If it's somebody
It's the stupidest
It's proof of senility
It's whatever
It doesn't matter
It's well hey
Anybody can
You know
Stutter
But it all gets
Transformed into
It transformed into
Clicks eventually
You know
Yeah
Cause it's all about
Traffic and you know
Selling average
Advertising
That's
What rhymes the world
I used to think
That algorithm stuff
Was sort of sci-fi
But now I've realized
It's real
Very real
It's super real
It's
Neil Stevenson's
Novel Fall
You still didn't
Watch that movie
I wanted you to watch
Did you
The documentary
Social network
Social dilemma
Yeah I did
You did
I sure did
I watched the hell
Out of it
Scared the pee water
Out of me
Yeah
When I first saw that
That's when I decided
To quit
Facebook
It was the guys
Who invented the internet
Going man this stuff
Is dangerous
I don't want my kids
On this
People that worked
For Facebook and Google
And different
And Twitter
Yeah were higher ups
I mean these were like
People in high
Responsibility
And talking about
Those algorithms
And how they're designed
To
To inflame you
Yeah
Because that's
That's what you click on
The most
You're more active
You do more scrolling
And more liking
And more reading
And posting
Now see the next
Generation of phones
Will track your eye movements
Yeah
So you won't even
Have to click
It'll know exactly
What words
And what images
You're looking at
In my case
That's not a problem
Because
When you want to post
You'll just blink your eyes
No
Yeah
Right
Oh well you won't
Even have to
When you want to like something
You blink your left eye twice
It's just automatically
Saying what it thinks
You would say
Yeah
You don't even have to
It says
Oh I know this guy so well
He's looking at the like button
That's all I need
Is to indicate
The like button now
Well
We all three noticed
That all of a sudden
Our phones were making
These little movies
And
Which they've always done
But they were really
Pushing them at us
This morning
I was
Typing
Keystrokes
That said
Philo's coming
Actually
Hide your frock girls
Philo's coming
Hide yourselves cats
And so forth
But
The
My phone went
Oh Philo's coming
So it made
A Philo collage
Of all the pictures
In my phone
Of Dr. Philo Drummond
Which were
Of course
Hilarious
And it put this
Inappropriate
Sappy music with it
And made it even funnier
Don't you think
I look better
Cutting off that nasty
Big old beard though
Well
It got pretty big
You did look like
A cartoon character
Yeah
And
Now you just look like
Any old
Very
Very old
Cable
Old cable splicer
Yeah
Cable
Old cable guy
Yeah
Old pharmaceutical salesman
Well
You looked more like
A farmer with that beard
You know
Yeah
Particularly with my
Overalls on
Yeah
The funny thing is
Dr. Drummond
Is a farmer
That's true
He is
He's a real farmer
He's an actual farmer
I'm not
I live in a ranch
You're a rancher
And I'm a farmer
No I'm not
My brother is a rancher
You are a rancher
You have all kinds of
Livestock around here
I see them
Canine livestock
I really like
Ranch dogs and cats
Canine and feline livestock
But nonetheless
They require a lot of
Kibble and food
And walking
And cleaning up after
Canine livestock
And key lime livestock
Feline
Oh feline
Okay
Generally what's referred to
As livestock
Doesn't live in your house
Or sleep on your bed
Not anymore
But back in the olden times
When they first started
They had the livestock
Right in the house with them
They only had one room
And they were keeping them
Warm in bed
What about that red goat
Up there
Didn't that goat
Live in your house
Reverend Stang
That was the
The first or second goat
That my
My parents got
Before it was ever
A goat ranch
And I don't know what
Possessed them
To get a goat
But they
They kept it
They took it back and forth
Between Richardson
Near Dallas
And out here
At the newly built ranch
That particular goat
Old Big Red
Is his name
Big Red
Princess Wee
Is referring to it
A mounted goat head
A huge goat
Domestic goat head
That's mounted
Up on the wall
With Dr. Seuss like horns
Like a wild animal
Yeah
Like as if it was
Some wild animal
That had been shot
That was actually a pet
But it went wild
It went feral
Like Boo Boo did
That one time
And Boo Boo went
Boo Boo runs wild
Yeah
And the goat was running around
Actually this happened
In Trailer Park Boys game
Willie Goat did the same thing
He was running around
And became a rapist
It was a male goat
A billy goat
And it started raping
It went off the hook
It was off the hook
And it was causing
Total mayhem
And destruction
To other goats
We didn't have
Was it having its way
With the female goats
Yes but they weren't our goats
They were other people's goats
Were they bearing the young
Of this crazy goat
I don't know
But there he is
That's what happens
If you start raping
You start raping
If you're raping
You're a
You end up on a wall
Pet
And you start raping
Your head might end up
On the wall like that
That's not people don't
Goats don't like that
Any more than people do
There's a big old
Bighorn sheep
My dad shot that
And that bear
And that jackalope
Up there
Yeah
He shot that jackalope
There is in fact
A jackalope
Mounted head
On the wall
It's been
It was here
When we moved in
Oh so you can say
That these
You didn't
You didn't actually kill
Any of these creatures yourself
Me?
No
I only shoot
I hunt
Dr. Drummond
I'm an avid hunter
But I hunt with a camera
Don't you see?
Oh yeah I know
I know
The dogs and I hunt too
Are you going to have
A big year this year?
Oh
I don't
Probably not
Did you watch
See that movie?
Everything's going extinct
No
That was kind of
Jack Black and
Steve Martin
Are both
Bird watchers
Oh no
I meant to
Check that out
I thought that might be fun
You could tell
You know like
Probably Jack Black
Wanted to work with
Steve Martin
You know
I would
Sure
I'd like to work
With either one of those guys
What is this thing?
It's another spaceship
But it requires
A cord
You feed a cord into it
And you pull it out
And it flashes
And makes noises
Friends
But I don't have the cord
Tarzan's radio station
Is loaded
Is all powered by
A cordless radio
On a fairly small table
But it's really decorated
There's a
A replica 3D model
Of the moon
Up there
And a giant
Cabbage worm
Rubber toy
On top of a
Reel-to-reel
Four track recorder
That hasn't worked
For years
It just looks cool
And this spaceship
And there's
Three spaceships
Princess Wee has one
You've got one
And here's
Here's the good one
Man
Oh my gosh
That's a classic
Spaceship sound
Yeah
Who sent us this?
Uh
Cosmic Layla
Layla
That's right
Cosmic Layla
Yeah
What a character
Wee Ma Ma
The 92 year old
That lives here
She sat
And played this thing
Over and over
And over again
One
When she first
We first got it
She just
She couldn't
She was fascinated
Off of it
Yeah
She played that
Like over and over and over
It's a very haunting melody
It's kind of Mars Attacks
And it's a Mars Attacks
Looking plastic spaceship
Yeah it's obviously
Someone taking advantage of
Friends listen
The environment we're in
Is a
Kind of across
The decor is
Crossed between
Western
A fairly tasteful
Western style
With landscape paintings
And
Uh
You know
Subgenius
Slack altar
Archie McPhee
Susie the floozy
Bull daughter
Like many subgenius houses
Every
Bit of
Horizontal surface
Okay enough of that
Taken up with
Enough of that
Knick knacks
Toy dinosaurs
Skulls
Real skulls
Fake skulls
There's a
Up just over our
Mantelpiece
It is quite the collection
There's
There's a
A