I'm dreaming of the subgenius power of SWAT.
And in the next few, we are traveling through time.
Yes, we are delving deep into the past of the subgenius church.
And it's seeing exciting and terrifying memories and things you never knew before.
Are you ready?
Because it's going to be quite a trip.
It's been quite a trip for me, friends.
We're doing this for the Maybe Logic Academy online course.
A course in how to run your own mind control cult, do's and don'ts.
And history of the Church of the Subgenius, the first 100 years.
Honest.
If you don't believe me, check out maybelogic.org.
Anyway, friends, we've been studying the events of the years of 1981.
And 1982.
And 1980.
The early years when we first encountered our dear, dear friends.
Such as Palmer Freedies of Lies.
A dead wellman of puzzling evidence.
St. J. King.
St. Byron Werner.
Pope Sternodox Kiekefer.
St. Janger Hypercletes.
And the great Snavely Eklund.
And so forth, friends.
Yes.
Well, so join me as we go in this episode.
Back.
In time.
To the year of 1981.
The time of the first world subgenius convention.
Which luckily was filmed professionally by Larry Silkus of Showtime's What's Up America.
That's why some of the audio actually sounds pretty good in these.
And, friends, the spirit was so high.
And so were we, I must admit, in some cases.
Not all of the doctors survived.
Those early years.
Some lost their faith in Bob.
Some lost their love of Reverend Stang.
Some just simply died.
Quite a few have died since then.
It's a shame.
Anyway, friends.
You will see and hear in your mind's eyeball.
The fervor and the intensity of the early subgenius.
Which will last many years.
When Bob was new to us.
And we had just rediscovered our own inborn slack.
Yes, yes, yes.
And so.
Friends, won't you join me as we pull the lever back on our machine?
Our Wayback Machine.
And watch as the calendar pages fall away.
Night and day flap like a giant black wing.
and we watch the seasons wheel and pass in reverse
going back, back, back to the year of 1981
and the beginning.
So actually this was in November 2021 and 22,
the day of the John F. Kennedy re-assassination
and the 1981 first World Subgenius Convention in Dallas.
Put your hands, put your hands, put your hands
But what is there is killer, man, killer.
It would be breaking our brain cells asunder.
We'll mix it in the water supply at the convention.
I think we should put it in the hamburgers that we give away.
Oh, Doug, I'm sorry.
The Trillade.
You, Jim, you'll have to pardon Doug.
His mind is completely gone.
He's gone since the convention.
He still thinks it's going to happen.
He doesn't realize that it's already happened.
The convention will be a great success.
I can see it now.
300 men dressed as Bob, men and women with Bob masks
marching down the main street straight to Dealey Plaza.
Oh, we'll have a limousine with a Jesus and a John Kennedy inside.
And his dreams get more and more bizarre every day.
We'll have everyone shoot at it.
Really?
We'll have a lot of real guns.
Oh, it will be wonderful.
The froth in the water.
Tell Doug to send lots of tapes.
That's a perfect idea.
And Kool-Aid.
We'll force everyone to drink Kool-Aid.
Buck will bring the Kool-Aid.
Buck has a...
I should mention, friends, for the sake of clarity,
that back in those days, I was Doug Smith.
There were too many Dugs in the church.
There's also Doug Wellman of Puzzling Evidence.
And so I became Ivan.
So this is the big time.
So this is the World Subgenius Convention.
Six or seven guys standing around with their eyes half open.
Why don't you guys sit here and pick in the notes.
Get a thumbs up there.
So this is the big time.
Big deal.
Well, whoop-dee-doo.
Poo-dah, poo-dah.
Okay.
None of them are the real Dicks, but we have to have all those Dicks on hand.
Just in case.
You mentioned it's too big and there's more people than we expect.
And if we don't have anything left to do, we'll pass out the Dicks.
And let them all have a...
Well, these Dicks only last about five minutes,
but they will get their taste of it.
It's like they have a Bob Dick.
Yes, indeedy.
And what do you think?
Doug, do you think it would be a poor taste to put Bob Dicks on everybody?
And more especially than that, the Bob Dicks we can forego,
but what about putting Bob Heads on 50 to 150 people,
carting them down to Dealey Plaza for 15 minutes?
That's all the time any of us have to record the scene.
15 minutes.
Hell, that's four Super 8 cartridges.
It's a change and a half in an Aeroflex.
So, I say, yeah.
What do you say, Doug?
I mean, here in Dallas, Dealey Plaza is sort of a sacred place,
but most people have forgotten who that guy was that got shot there.
And like me, they didn't even know where it was.
So, you know, now they will.
They'll know that Dealey Plaza is where 500 Bobs shot the President.
And the pictures of the 500.
And Bob shooting the President.
And I want to know what part you want to play in this.
I mean, Doug, this Dealey Plaza thing, you haven't said anything about it, hardly,
except for the black cardboard limousine
and wanting to do some separate shoots earlier in the charade.
But, I mean, surely you must have a role in this.
This is like a damn passion play.
How much of the convention is ready, Dr. Drummond?
How much of the convention is actually ready?
It's about 72.8% ready.
It's Friday night at 6 o'clock?
72.9.
But if nothing else, I can get the big piece out.
Focus up on the face, please.
So I had a good time with you in Dallas.
What a guy.
I thought there was going to be 20 people here tonight.
I didn't know who.
Like, aren't they, huh?
Maybe there won't be anybody.
We won't even go.
I mean, earlier I've been thinking, I've been, you know,
there couldn't be too few people.
But now I'm thinking, I hope there is, you know.
I hope there's very few people.
Yeah!
Where did the mix board go?
Subject is panel discussion.
Yeah!
Woo!
Two microphones to every garage.
Two tickets.
Two tickets in every amplifier.
Let's have a stereo.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
27 doctors for Bob.
Waylaid by the conspiracy.
Woo!
Take one down and smash him!
26 doctors for Bob on the wall.
It's ultra meaningful.
Is Arnold Palmer here tonight?
Arnold's not here.
But I thought you'd look.
Good.
My name's Sterno Doxon from Little Rock, Arkansas.
Puzzling evidence representative Doug Wellman from...
Oakland, California.
Deep in the heart of San Francisco.
And we represent a segment of myriad doctor bands abounding now from coast to coast.
Have you been getting news on doctor bands?
Doctors for Odin, doctors for Wotan, black and white Oakland doctors for Payne,
doctors for Bob, the Arch Emulators.
There's Devo who's stolen everything.
Quiet!
Has life been bending you over lately, brothers and sisters?
Has it been your night in the barrel for the past few months?
Have you been down so long it looks like up to you?
Well, the problem is not a lack of Jesus.
No!
The problem is not a lack of Yahweh.
No, no, no.
The problem is not a lack of the Reverend Mayer.
The problem is not a lack of God.
A problem is a lack of slack.
A lack of slack!
A lack of slack children.
The conspiracy is all around you.
It surrounds you.
It's in these walls.
Look at that paneling.
Ordinarily that would be conspiracy paneling.
Conspiracy floorboards.
And ass-deadening conspiracy chairs.
But tonight those chairs, those grins, that faithful.
The Beef Street negorzea that sleム판 ресignashni Donald Trump have to leave this dinner
It belongs to Bob!
It's Bob's flower!
It contains slack!
It delivers slack up until you lay barely!
Give me a slack!
Slack!
Give me another slack!
Good God almighty!
Come forward young man!
The voice is normal speed.
It should be normal speed on this recording.
If the batteries are still...
Yeah, here in Texas everything's 10 times tough.
Well, anybody who knows how to play high school...
Ha ha ha!
Oh, hell no!
We're here at the beginning of the subgenius.
Tape on your situation.
And you!
You!
Dear overmodulated friends are here on the right channel.
But does that stop us?
No!
It doesn't stop Doug Smith.
You'll be able to hear on the exciting left channel.
The sound of the music.
Thanks to Ggasm, to your area.
In the background,
Dr. Philo Turner on saxophone.
Ivan Stang on speech.
Paul Riddies.
Palmer Vides.
On bass guitar.
The unknown man.
The unknown musician on lead guitar.
And Mr. T. Ggasm himself.
Unconsciously inside the bass drum.
The unknown man.
Now I'd like to...
Ha!
What?
No!
Ha!
Ho!
Hey!
Ha!
Ho!
Now we're really about to have a little
If you were in the night first,
This giant doctor's for somebody's jam.
Yeah, everybody here is a registered medical practitioner of the black arts.
It delivers slack up unto you, lay barely.
Give me a slack.
Slack.
Give me another slack.
Good God almighty.
Come forward, young man.
Stand before me.
This young man was never a wayward sinner, no.
This young man was always in a state of grace.
But there was one thing wrong.
He was brought up in the world of the conspiracy.
Yes, Bob had to fight the conspiracy in this boy.
Bob had to struggle to get inside this boy.
Tonight, tonight I'm going to lay hands on this boy and give him slack.
We finally shifted gears and we are back.
We've got the giant Bob head taped to the back of the Bob mobile.
Stacked full of some genius equipment.
And...
The overman is in the trunk.
Ha ha.
Waiting.
Waiting to be revealed.
At the height of glory.
As the subgeniuses from all over the world congregate and file, single file, down Main Street, Dallas, Texas to Dealey Plaza.
Where they will carefully and with restricted respect fornicate upon them.
The...
Grassy knoll.
Ha ha.
Oh, that is.
Look at that.
Ah.
What does it say?
Rock Wang.
Odin Wotang.
I believe that the message got through to our children out there tonight.
And that's why I came here was to try and influence our young persons.
To try to better this young man, of course.
To say, say it without saying bye.
Praise Bob, brother.
Praise the Lord.
That's right.
When you were there on the block.
It was weird, man.
Because I was just laying there.
It was like every refrigerator you had ever opened in your life.
It was Tom, Bill, and Bruce.
The problem with the subtenues is they don't pay well.
I don't think the Cadillac that I got was good pay.
I mean, that by itself is...
I can get a Cadillac.
The business already got me three Cadillacs.
I don't care about that stuff.
What I'd like to know is the TV dinners and the room with the fair mama while I'm here.
Is that supposed to be money?
Or is that something that I...
What?
You get a room with a store that?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
They're paying for it?
No, not for you.
Not for you.
Yeah, but for the camera, yes.
They're paying for it.
Ugh.
Wow.
For low Arnold Palmer's first words, his first utterances were...
Yeah, well, I'm real glad I flew down from Oregon for this, you guys.
Yeah, I'm real glad.
I think I'm going to get fired from my job for taking off the whole last half of the league.
Big deal, right?
Yeah, I'm so glad to be here.
I mean, it's like...
Thanks anyway, Doug.
Yeah, where's Bob, Doug?
Many people may wonder, who is Gebrog Fram?
What is his message for humanity today?
What is the difference between Gebrog Fram, for instance, and Jehovah One?
What's the difference between Gebrog Fram and he, Gebrog Fram?
How come we always talk about Lotan instead of Jehovah One?
How come we always talk about Lotan instead of Lotan?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, what kind of Otan is that?
How come all you people pay $10?
It's a stupid question.
No, I can't wait for the convention.
I can't wait for the convention.
It's wonderful.
Well, I'm going to go to the store.
Put Jim down on the Xeroxes.
I'm going to go to Smeet for a 14-year-old.
Are you ready to receive Slack, child?
I do.
I'm ready.
I'm ready to receive Slack.
Stand there before him.
Come this way.
Boys, is this young man ready for Slack?
Is this man ready to receive?
Come forward.
Follow him.
Come here.
All of you, come here.
Yes, you.
And you.
Hold still, young man.
Hold still.
Stay right here.
When we lay hands on this boy, look for the spirit of the conspiracy to leave the room.
I don't know.
But stand next to him and hold his arm.
This might be violent.
Give me that.
When the conspiracy leaves this boy, take his other arm.
When the conspiracy leaves this boy, the force will be violent.
It's not a fit site for children.
Take off that mask, son.
Are you ready, boy?
Hey, Douglas.
What?
What is going on?
Watch your eyes, ladies and gentlemen.
When the conspiracy leaves this boy, this room will be cleansed, but I'm not responsible
for the forces unleashed.
You saw Raiders of the Lost Ark.
And when a Nazi scum opened that artifact and they were turned to wax, you saw the end
of the devil's reign.
And when Ernest Borden had melted before your eyes, that's nothing compared to the force
of the conspiracy.
But the force of the conspiracy always yields to the force of whom?
Bow.
To the force of whom?
I'm gonna lay hands on this boy.
Are you ready, son?
Silence, please.
In the name of all conspiracy,
McDonald's French fries,
Trans Am T38 with those white mag wheels,
and chrome reflecting glass buildings,
leave this boy!
Now, hit it!
The power of Bob!
The sacred power of Bob!
Will the pipe bring this boy back? Yes!
The force of the conspiracy is strong,
but the force of Bob is stronger.
A pop on the Bob pipe will free this boy!
He rises! He rises! He's filled with the spirit of Bob!
Say hallelujah! Say hallelujah!
Say hallelujah!
Raise your hands!
Raise your hands, children!
It looks like your problems are all over.
I bet.
Well, it looks like there's nothing left to do but calm down.
It was a weird, strange experience.
I wasn't expecting it.
And now, though, I accepted it.
Yes.
Now, was that a good rant?
You can.
But I thought it never did.
I thought this subjeaned shirt was a lie.
That never gave me industrial consultation
or exorcism of the demon Negi.
But I found out I was wrong.
Through the love and the hate of Bob.
We'll see.
We'll see how long this transformation lasts.
We'll see if people should spend their money for this.
We'll see if it's as useful to you as your high school diploma.
Yeah.
We'll see.
Whatever.
Go to high school in bedroom slippers.
Yeah.
Free shoes.
Clemio Clemish clan.
I'm speaking in tongues.
Is this doctors for Bob or some cheap imitation?
Or is this doctors for Bob that blows the reed out of even toy saxophones?
Or is this an entirely different bunch of doctors?
It doesn't really matter what kind of doctor.
I mean, there's general practice.
There's no general practice.
There's nurse.
There's orthodontist.
There's orthopedist.
There's podiatrist.
There's pediatric.
There's pederast.
There's all kinds of guys to fix up what you need.
But really, you've got to ask yourself, is it the doctor you need or is it just the pills?
Wouldn't the pills be fine?
I mean, that way you don't have to go sit around in the waiting room and hope Dr. Chad
that neighbor can get to you.
You don't have to talk to all the dumb nurses and write him a chat.
You can just sit at home and get those pills for the video.
Really, that's all you need.
I will lend the pills.
The pills, well, it might help you get a better attitude.
That's the whole difference behind the medical situation.
We're not prepared to consult with you about it until we've talked to your bank.
You said truly you must lead the, you know, the treatment.
The child is the father to the man.
Which man?
The man, man, the man.
The man, the man with the plan to stick it to the man.
Hey, there's the man.
Well, officially, Philo, any comments before the end?
Just waiting for the transfiguration.
Oh, sorry.
The transfiguration is tonight.
It's tonight.
It's going to happen to me in just a few short minutes.
You're going to behold the transfiguration on that stage.
I'm going to perform the transfiguration on that stage.
I'm going to come on demure.
I'm going to start off leading the plot gently.
And before I'm done, I'm going to have this crowd knuckle walking from here to Palestine.
All right.
That's the kind of word I like to hear.
You'll wait and see what happens tonight.
I will be talking in tongues.
Hey, are we ready?
How many tongues?
Yeah.
Doug.
Hi.
Hey.
Applaus for Doug and technicians on set.
You're the hosts of the last episode ofечноaco, less towards the end time.
Don't get ALEX down.
He had a great time.
See you soon.
All right, pal.
Not too late.
We don't get too busy in a long time, do we?
There we go.
Thanks, everyone.
Yeah.
My crew and I are just enjoying what we're seeing on everything and no real changes.
All right.
We're going to come back and catch a couple of snow cold sunshades.
I can't.
$300.
That pill's too big.
Kill me.
Listen, you'll hear laughter in your head.
That pill's too big.
It'll choke me.
It'll kill me.
No, no, go ahead.
Go ahead.
It'll hurt.
I did it.
All right, all right.
I'll break it up.
Hey, this pill tastes, it tastes, it tastes kind of good.
In fact, I'm starting to feel pretty good.
Whoa.
There's Bob.
Bob, he's been here all along.
Yeah.
That's right.
The one-take rhythm killers, the music haters, the jackasses, the shitty Beatles, also known
as Doctors for Bob, the men of covenant men.
Jehovah One made a covenant with us.
He's met a mighty man, mighty healer.
That's his name.
Oh, Robert.
Oh.
Doctors for Bob.
Doctors!
...the uber-divers.
That's right, and a lot of you people who haven't spent enough money yet can talk Philo about getting the foot gland operation.
He is doing that during this convention.
He was a little bit drunk last night.
There will be numerous of our doctors who are present for gland escaping.
Another clinic has just been recently constructed in Dallas.
You no longer have to pay the expenses of flying all the way to Malaya.
The one that was burned down in Little Rock is well on its way to being rebuilt.
Thanks to your donation.
But we can always use more.
But in the meantime, if you really think there's something wrong with the clinic,
there's something dreadfully wrong with you.
Well, we're the person managers.
We're there to help the masses of the ill people, the sick, the deflated, the tired people.
And it's not the pills, it's not the prescriptions, it's not the doctors with the little rubber hammer who play.
Well, they're making the music of heaven itself.
Conservative. Clean out the...
Well, the tubes and things that you have.
The tubes that are plugged up.
Maybe by having a little bit too much money on you.
Yes, you can unplug those tubes.
We can sit down.
It won't take more than a half hour initial session.
You can fill out one of the applications for us.
Fill out our credit application.
You'll walk out of here with a bucket of pills.
Yeah, a bucket of pills.
A big, big pill.
They're big pills.
They're little pills.
We got little tiny pills.
Some of the pills, some of the pills you can drag over the wall.
You can pour them out into a glass of water or a glass of coke.
Some of the pills you have to put in other places besides your mouth.
Some of the pills, well, some of the pills you just put them in your shirtline.
Keep them near your heart and all that.
Some of the pills, well, they're dangerous.
And you should operate machinery on those pills.
What do all those pills have to do with that?
Well, it depends upon if you're talking about the buckets of pills or the quarts of pills.
Like we're talking about, and what we mean by a bunch of pills is not like half a bathtub full of pills.
It's the half of reality of those rotten buckets of pills.
And we're talking about it not being much fun when Johnny Law comes here and takes them pills away.
So we're talking about like these pills that we're talking about.
It's called the more.
Very simply put, the bunch more theory.
In other words, if you send us a little money now, we guarantee you'll get a bunch more later.
Not a little bit more.
Not too much.
Not a lot more.
Not just a quarter of the whole thousand bathtub pills, cut to the ring mark with money.
I'm talking a bunch more money.
I'll give you the money.
Raise the money.
And when the word of Bob becomes nothing but worn out cliché, that's when we'll get a whole bunch more.
If you'll meet us behind the park closet, I'll thank you, my son.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
We'll give you the money tomorrow.
One of the folk has just thrown a large handful of pocket change at the doctors.
Others are falling asleep.
Now the doctors are throwing the money.
They're launching the herds of the common metal peasants.
Over in the corner, a journal or someone is writing a dollar bill and passing it from doctor to doctor.
The doctors are smoking the dollar bill.
They say the smoke, the souls are going up to heaven.
Then they say some sign saying Halloween, Ils
The bloody head of John Kennedy is being rushed to Parkland Memorial Hospital.
Wonderful.
Yes, I can see that the bloody head of John Kennedy is being rushed to Parkland Memorial Hospital.
Leaving at the spot.
Memorial Motorcade here, 18 years to the day after the sneaky head was still alive in Dallas.
How many members are there?
There's two men.
Any other misconceptions?
What do you do with the money?
There's three members.
Nobody knows the name for Slackman's children.
Bob.
I'll tell you what, nine-tenths of the continent of Asia have not yet heard the word Bob.
These people need to be told that Bob's name is Bob.
I've talked to Eflin in 65 different languages and this takes five minutes.
It's Bob.
It's Bob's pills.
It all comes together.
And what do the exes have to do with us?
Well, the exes have brought these invented pills down.
There's an exes in there.
I can see two.
I can see the exes.
I want to know about the exes.
Yeah, there they are.
It's not a manner of liking exes or disliking them.
It's a problem.
It's obeying them.
Or not finding them.
Find these problems.
You know, your place on the nine-tenths of the continent of Asia.
You guys are a band of doctors, right?
Right.
We're actually three different bands.
Okay, there's three different bands represented in this case.
Doctors for Bob is historically the father band, spawning an unlimited number of other doctor bands,
which this fad of genius music is making us a lot of money right now.
And that's my primary motivation for being here.
Bob has nothing to do with this.
Yeah.
Bob has very little to do with everything.
And a lot to do about this.
So, I haven't brought this in my life.
What about our link-loader's daughter who did ask us and jumped out of a window?
No comment.
Oh, yeah.
I'm crying.
I'm crying a lot.
I'm crying a whole lot.
I'm crying so much too.
I'm crying a lot, lot.
I'm crying a real lot of much a whole lot.
I'm crying so much it's filling up buckets.
It's filling up my house.
It's filling up my yard.
It's filling up the streets.
The whole city's a river.
Because I've been crying a lot.
Yeah, there's lots of water around.
From the tear-drops.
They've been squirting out of my head.
I think I'll cry a hundred more tears.
Yeah, I think I'll cry a hundred tears.
In the last minute and a half.
Oh, now it's one second every second.
96 tears.
They've squirted out of my head.
Oh, my head's been squirting tears a lot.
Then I turn around and it's squirting a lot more.
Oh, I've been crying 96 tears.
And it's flooded the town.
Now we're floating out.
Now we're in the ocean.
And we're floating around.
And a lot of tear-drops.
Because you left me.
And it's your fault, bitch.
You left me.
You flooded the world.
It's your fault.
You have the lives of millions on your conscience for the rest of your life.
Because you left me.
And I've been crying a lot.
And it's flooded the world.
Oh, mama.
Look, I'm so mad at you.
I could just piss.
But if I piss some more, then it'd flood the rest of the world.
So I'm crying.
And I keep on crying.
And now it's your fault.
And all those people are dying.
Oh, I'm crying.
And baby, you can just go jump in the lake.
Because I've been crying, crying, crying.
And don't come back no more.
I'm not sure you've been crying.
Oh, I've been crying 96 tears.
96 million if you're playing on 96.
Oh, 96 big tears.
I cried 96 real big tears.
I cried 96 big old giant tears.
You remember that tear I cried?
You remember that big old tear I cried that time?
That was one of the 96 tears.
All those tears.
And then I cried that other time.
That back at that time when I was crying a lot.
I cried one big old tear.
And it was the 96 big tear.
I cried that day or that minute or that second.
Because I was crying a lot.
I didn't keep track of all of them when I cried.
But it was that one tear.
That one big old giant tear.
That one tear that just made my head split open when I cried it out.
Yeah, I split my brains out and my head was open.
And I cried that one giant big old tear.
That was the tear that I sent back.
Because it was big.
Too big for me.
Or too big for Smith and Jones.
That one big old tear.
Because I always thought I was crying.
And it took me two days to pass that tear.
Oh yeah, and I'm not lying.
I passed that big old tear.
And I split my head and ripped it open.
Because I was crying a lot.
And now this next line is going to be the end of the song.
Oh yeah!
Well, now that we're here in Potato Land,
why don't we go searching for some of the things
we couldn't find back in the real world.
Ah, the convention.
If I could control time,
I'd be right back on that stage
with Doctors for Wotan.
With our five guitarists and horn section
and three synthesizers and two drummers and
inspired madness.
And my true calling, of course, is the church.
And the church is, let me assure you,
making lots of money now.
I, Reverend Stang, took the money from the convention
and absconded with it.
I went to Bolivia with the convention money.
And the foundation has been pretty much broke ever since.
I've left my post at Sacred Scribe,
and let young John Pretorius take over.
It's tough.
I mean, we literally do burn Sacred Scribes out.
We burn them out about a year at a time.
And I was about burnt out.
So I've spent all the money.
I'm back in Dallas.
And I was supposed to be an overman by now,
but that didn't happen.
Still haven't had my third nostril open.
But they did do some of the surgery.
Philo did a little bit during the last Doctors for Wotan practice session.
Or practice.
We've never practiced.
Doctors for Wotan has never practiced.
We have only recorded albums.
And we have, we've just recorded our 17th album.
This time using the new Japanese cheap synthesizers,
the Casios or Taseos or whatever,
that Allsupgenius is now on,
along with their tape recorders.
Yeah!
Hey.
Okay, where's my...
What?
Wow, Doctors for Wotan.
Album number 18.
Yeah, we're glad you could all make it tonight.
Dr. Wotan over there is shooting up.
We're gonna have some Doctor time.
We're gonna be healing and cutting.
We're gonna be hurting and screaming.
We're gonna be a-fropping and a-cutting.
Yeah.
We know the Frop Lord's with us.
Yeah, hey, there's the Frop Lord number 6 down there,
just in from Tibet.
Ha!
Yeah, same to you, Frop Lord number 6.
The convention is over.
The peoples are dead.
The conventions are over.
The allegations are done.
And could it be your Hall is set?
I think I can.
I think I can. I think I can. I think I can. I think I can. I think I can.
Hey, I hear a tank delay.
I think I can.
Sandy, you can be anything you want to be when you grow up.
Sandy, you can be a fireman or you can be Spider-Man.
Or you can be a politician.
Or Sandy, you can be a terrorist and hurt people very much.
You can be what you want.
Are you afraid to look at the green
It's like a soapbox.
and Bark, yeah.
Aw, that sounds definitely the most powerful voice Bondadors have ever heard.
yeah, I'm going to win.
Take law into your own hands.
It's fun, fun, fun.
And for a good cause.
Is that paid for by the Church of the Subgenius?
We demand that Roman law be replaced by German law.
And they accompanied their promises with music.
Martial music that was appropriate for millions of loose-stepping Germans.
Music that began with a fanfare and thundering drums.
Music that inflamed people with wild patriotic fervor.
Music like this march played by a Nazi stormtrooper band.
Doctor!
I barely even remember being on stage.
It's all like a dream.
And, uh, I drove home literally in a trance.
From Dallas.
As you can well imagine.
That much input in that short of time.
Probably couldn't be endured
Probably couldn't be endured.
by anyone less than an apprentice overman or overwoman,
as the case may be, over hermaphrodite,
of which that species, I'm sure,
were represented by more than a few examples.
I haven't had that much cerebral stimulation since I don't know when.
But Bob was there. Bob was all over the tapes.
You never hear Bob's voice,
yet we can't release the tapes that have Bob speaking
because of the voice print problems.
But the reenactments are on the way,
and Bob, at the convention, Bob did possess the living bodies
of many great doctors, subgenius doctors,
Jane of Hypercletes, Sternokekever,
even myself for a very short time.
Almost all of us were at different times possessed by Bob,
and every now and then something we say on those tapes
is not being said by us, it's being said by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and believe you me, being the vessel for the voice of Bob
can wear you out quicker than running a subgenius convention.
It can wear you out quicker than taking the drugs
that show up at a subgenius convention,
which, by the way, I did not do until the convention was over.
There is nothing like being possessed by Bob.
It is horrible, and it's wonderful.
I mean, look at me.
I've been able to abscond with all the bucks and spend it all
and come back safe and sound,
and all the subgeniuses think it's fine.
Because, yes, I deserve it.
It's true.
I deserve all the money that the convention made.
Well, I can't even go into any detail on that.
Just such a resounding success.
So unbelievably financially successful
that surely, you know, the mark of Bob was just spurting all over it.
And I believe that it's important
that there be a subgenius convention in your area.
In your area.
All I can say is gut blowout unprecedented.
That was the absolute...
greatest...
party that I have ever attended in my entire existence in this life.
And I can only hope that the next convention will equal it.
I don't see how it possibly could.
Just from that point of Doctors for Bob being accepted as well as we were
blows my mind.
And we've never had a receptive audience,
much less an appreciative audience.
And to see, to actually see...
The power of Bob kept me on my feet.
I only committed suicide once during the entire convention.
Was risen from the grave.
Oh, God, you should have been there.
But you will be there.
You are there on the tape.
When will we be sued?
And which city will sue us?
The answer to these and other questions here probably will never be answered.
And are we protected by the fact that we're now in the uprising?
Or are they going to nail us in?
I'm going to be there anyway for my house.
My little air-con.
Hey, hey, this, this Subgenius convention is great!
Hey, I work for People Magazine!
I'm going to get you guys in there.
For sure.
You'll be big stars!
And you'll make lots of money!
Subgenius audience, audience!
Irritation techniques!
Total success!
The Bob Fendi Prize!
Well, aren't you going to ask us about Elvis?
Yeah.
The mega-fifth temple lodge of the Church and Subgenius of Little Rock, Arkansas.
One of the original schisms that was manifested in the first blight of dobsable energy to descend upon central Arkansas.
Which has been referred to by Bob himself as the savage mind of the country's interior.
The first temple was burnt down.
The first temple was burnt to the ground Bob.
Right.
Radical, the R.D. conspiracy, which we'll go into later, threw a firebomb into our first mega-fifth temple lodge, burned it to the ground.
So we aligned ourselves immediately with the first feces temple gog of Dobbs Orthodoxic, and the first whiskey-glorp church, and the first drug abuse church manifested by a chemical engineer, Radon T22.
So this explains our involvement in the Dallas Clinch.
And the journeys that have taken place.
Across the boundaries of the many states that were eliminated and have brought Texas and California and Arkansas together in an unholy triad.
Can bring about this power that we're talking about to bring us unlimited slack in the form of $100 bills, $1000 bills, and some such, you know, solid gold nine irons.
I'm currently the sacred scribe, just temporarily, of the Church of the Subgenius.
I'm going to get out of the position as soon as I can, because we burn the sacred scribes out very quickly.
Sad, isn't it?
Sad.
Oh, it's the head!
You're going to burn!
The bleeding head!
The Marla Palmer!
That's what head!
Now you can launch!
You can launch your bleeding head at Tramino!
You can skyrocket your head at Jack Nicklaus!
You can fling your head at Sonny Fono!
You can curl your head at Diddy Amin!
You can launch your head at Ronald Reagan!
You can launch your head at Arnold Palmer!
But if you don't launch the head at Arnold Palmer!
If you don't launch the head at Arnold Palmer!
You're going to burn!
As Bob said to L. Ron Hubbard in the letter,
he said, L. Ron, sure they may be bleeding,
but their money is green!
And this is all he knows!
That the word of Bob comes through,
even in the time of pain.
We're not asking for one penny for ourselves.
If we get dollar bills,
hell, we'll tear them up!
But it's the gift of the world!
You need to hear the word of Bob!
Roman!
Do you scan us on your view screen?
Yes, Earthman, I see you.
This means only one thing.
You have decided to take the easy way out.
No, Roman.
We have fought you to a standstill.
And we will go on doing it as long as necessary.
If you try to figure out our position,
you are wasting your time.
None shall escape me.
I shall find a way to rid this Earth planet
of humans.
No!
A human will not give up this Earth of ours.
But let me ask you something else.
What do you have to fear from us?
I want to know!
Mind control on out of control.
Tell me about it!
Well, some people say,
you can't have two people talking at one time on those tapes.
That's right, we can't have two.
Can't have three!
We've got a habit of one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, ten, ten, alone, no more.
I saw you back there not swimming in my sea
Bet you you dogs leave everywhere
The power of Dobbs!
This microphone is healed!
Healed by the powers of Dobbs!
The microphone is healed!
Is that Dobbs over there?
It's Lee Dobbs!
We have reports that Dobbs is here tonight in flesh, ladies and gentlemen!
Is that Dobbs?
Is that Dobbs on your foot?
Is Dobbs right on your foot?
I got this word, I saw Dobbs!
Is that?
There's Dobbs, he's over there on the wall!
It's Dobbs, there's a whole bunch of him back there!
It's the Dobbs!
The doctors do not need to know!
Not to walk on all fours!
The doctors defy the law!
The doctors walk on all fours!
The doctors do not need to know the law!
Elijah could bring fire down from the sky in the eyes of men!
David's mighty men were shielded from death by the covenant!
Bob, Bob, though some people may maintain that the head is filled with plastic medical tubing
and pumping fake theater blood,
and that's just a theory though, that's not true!
and wagulating, it's not true!
Other people that might claim that it's the bleeding torso that demands recognition,
that's not true either!
Right, and we maintain that it is the head!
There's a church that deals with the head,
and it's not bloody but now rotting!
A rotting pussy head as opposed to a seven!
Hello!
Really?
One of our mottoes, wounded head good, heel head bad!
Well, you are now listening to...
Wounded head good, heel head bad!
...the interview with Palmer Readings,
Palmer Readings!
Doug Weldwin, and Sternodon himself, who did most of the talking.
Is this what it sounds like inside a subgenius's head?
The big subgenius conference is going to be happening, the convention, the subcon.
And I wouldn't be able to either if I was, if the convention was in Oakland,
and I was cutting glass here and starving to death.
I'm cutting glass in Oakland, I'm just starving to death.
It's cold, it's wet outside.
I wish I had a little more time to think about it.
I'd take the money and get on an airplane.
I'd ride that sucker and I'd ride, ride, ride.
Ride to Dallas, Texas, the subgenius convention.
Get together and praise Bob.
Ride to Dallas, Texas, and join all the subgenius's, praise Bob for the job.
I'm cutting glass in Oakland, I'm trying to make a buck.
Hoping if I keep going I'll increase my luck.
I'm hoping and I'm praying that things get better fast.
If I don't improve, I don't know if I'm gonna last.
Oh, I'm cutting glass in Oakland, I'm just starving to death.
I'm cutting glass in Oakland, hoping for Dallas, Texas.
Hoping that I get there before the X's.
Cutting glass in Oakland, trying to make a buck.
Hoping to improve my luck.
I'm cutting glass in Oakland, trying to make a buck.
Well, I won't be there in Dallas, November 22.
You know I got a lot of things to do.
Hoping and I'm praying that I'll crawl from this hole.
Before them dice begin to roll.
Subgenius in Dallas, Texas, on November 22.
I won't be there, celebrate with them.
I hope you are.
Because this is the hour of slack,
and it's the Church of the Subgenius,
and our new official Post Office Box,
it's the old Cleveland Heights Post Office Box.
The Texas-Austin office had to move.
So now we're at Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118.
www.subgenius.com