Oh, it's the farm for the whole of the...
No!
Stay.
Douglas, you stay here.
Yes, I will stay among you, my children.
You stay with us.
I will stay with you.
And he will be back, too.
For all you early morning listeners who are up with the chickens, here's the farm report.
Goodbye.
Brought to you by Bob's Feed and Grain Storage of Dobstown.
Soybean futures continue at the market rate while most animal feeds are up today.
Hog futures continue to look pretty dismal, but that's what you should expect if you're a hog.
That's because most farm-dwelling parkers know the end of the line is food around the corner for somebody else's breakfast table and maybe even yours.
Because if you have four legs, hooves, or trotters, and you live on a farm,
if it isn't the grim reaper,
it's the international harvester.
And now this.
We were talking about...
It's the subgenius show.
Yes, if you weren't aware of what's been going on, then you're probably just the sort of person to listen to the subgenius show,
the indefinitely long, infinitely boring corridor of horrible horticultural and biocultural...
This is the voice of radio subgenius, bringing to the greater Bay Area the unadulterated,
infrapulated vocal incarnation of the sub-divine epistemology of subgenialism.
I'm your host, Dr. Howell, and during the next hour and a half, Mobius Rex and I will chair the open forum of subgenial issues.
Yes, it's so exciting I can hardly stand it.
How about you, Mobius?
Yes.
Welcome.
Welcome to Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slang.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Doctors, scientists, who might understand what Moreau was trying to do.
Perhaps they could develop a serum, stop the regression.
No.
No more scientists, no more laboratories, no more experiments.
I thought you would be able to understand that.
We have to be what we are.
Not what the father tried to make us.
Subgeniuses.
To go on two legs.
Very hard.
Don't get it, buddy.
It's a tail, baby.
Maybe four is better.
I'm happier than the morning sun.
That's the way it'll always be.
Ever since the day you came inside of me.
Oh, my.
Johnny could only sing one note, and the note he sang was this.
Children, if you have not opened your heart to the god of solid rocket boosters,
we invite you now to search your emotions and your soul.
And come forward and open your heart so that we may stick our little fuse in there and light it.
It feels good.
Astronaut report, it feels good.
T-minus 20 seconds, Antoni.
Guidance in journal.
15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10, 11, 12, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
3, 2, 1.
I wish I was a spaceship.
Actually, I am.
I'll fly you around the universe.
Yes.
Here we go.
On July 5.
Go second.
Yes.
I'll live above the sky.
My heart will be a fireball.
Yes, a fireball.
Every time I gaze into it.
Every time I gaze into your starry third eye.
We'll make the path to Jupiter.
And maybe very soon.
We'll land our little tootsies.
And walk around the moon.
With our little moon billies.
Get our little moon nights.
And go off to Mars.
Yes, and it'll be a fireball.
A free fireball.
And you will be mine.
Me, in the years of the fire.
The Psych Eats.
1998.
It's a new and fresh and practical.
Oh, oh, oh.
Out to play.
But you know, when I'm feeling blue, I just want some of you.
Oh, it's a beautiful day.
And I don't care what the big boys say.
With a little bit of color in my mind.
I'll make it just all the time.
But you know, when I'm feeling blue, I just want a piece of you.
Oh, what can I do?
A piece of you.
What is a poor girl to do?
When I call you up.
Oh, yeah.
But you know, when I'm feeling blue.
I just want a piece of you.
Oh, oh, oh.
I love you.
Excuse me, my English is not that good.
In fact, you'll love this show we've got coming up.
It's got some new material in.
This is the new combustible Edison in the background.
This new CD, The Impossible World, featuring our own brother Cleve Duncan as a member of the band on keyboards.
We have Hemroy Rogers coming up.
That's an old hour of slack band, of tards, that you'll remember, even if you've never heard them before.
And what we just heard before this was Polycarp from Whifflefish.
I'm going to give you, they're kind of a negative land-like band.
We'll have some negative land coming up, too, by the way.
But Polycarp's CD, this The Magnetic Moment, we just played when I'm feeling blue.
And Whifflefish Records and Polycarp are available at, got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 33566.
Oh, it's time to go back on combustible Edison to cut four, I think, yes.
20th century.
Friends, Whifflefish, P.O. Box 33561, Raleigh, North Carolina, 27636.
27636, therefore, Polycarp, the negative land-like cut.
They used to be also known as...
Sonic Rape and Pillage.
What was it?
Remember, we're all sitting together listening to this.
And I'm sorry, friends, I am on, I did have a, I did have my snot amputated yesterday.
I really do have 15 yards of packing material crammed up my nose, and I'm on strong,
but very effective painkillers and narcotic drugs.
So that said, I should probably proceed on.
We're with rest of show.
We have tonight's continuation of Reverend Susie the Flusie's beautiful slack collage.
We have Einstein's Secret Orchestra, of course, with Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Chaz Smith,
the amazing Michelle on violin, Princess We Are, No Bleepo Abernethy, yours truly,
and sometimes Friday Jones.
We definitely have some Friday Jones coming up.
We have some KPFA with puzzling evidence of Dr. Howell.
We've got Dr.
Legume and Ed Strange, because we're doctors, my friend.
Perhaps someday we can bring one of them back to help you.
Yes, that's all we want to do is help you, my friend.
Because God loves you.
Yeah, yeah.
You missed out.
Not me.
I won't grow up.
I don't want to wear a tie.
And a serious expression.
In the middle of July.
Crumb, crumb, JV.
So you come out, and you draw, and you say, bam, bam, stop.
And it got it and stopped.
Then you move up to the head, and you put one right there, and that's usually final.
What?
Get that spear away from me.
Thank you, Carr.
Thank you.
Can you hear what I'm saying?
Can you see the heart that I'm carrying?
LOL, I recommend to come on and play
Don't remind a Spider-Man of who I'm meaning
Yeah.
Oh, man, if you've got a prairie squid, I'll give you everything.
No, I can do it.
I could do it for nothing for you.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
No, I swear I will.
I heard that over at Dave Alley.
I was wandering down Lonesome Cowboy Dave Alley where it's nothing but buildings that look like Lonesome Cowboy Dave Head.
And all the people that wander up and down the street look like Lonesome Cowboy.
And they're lonesome.
And they're cowboys.
And they sing.
They go to the wig shops and they can command prairie squids with their minds.
Yeah, I've been there.
I've been in that hole, man.
I'm telling you, I've been down there and I tried to yank myself out.
What's it do?
Keep dark depression, man.
A lot of people just don't get out.
It takes a lot more than St. John's Wards, you know?
I'd like to buy the world a home and furnish it with Bob.
It's a real thing.
Bob.
Now, Bob, you're getting to be a pretty big fella.
Yes, sir.
Maybe this is a good idea, a chance for us to have a little talk.
Why, sure, Dad.
What's cooking?
Remember the last time we talked about this old body of ours, Bob?
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember, Dad.
No.
Oh, here's a match. Your pipe's gone out again.
Well, thanks.
But when a doctor speaks of the male organ, he...
Well, he calls it a...
When a man and a woman are married, Bob,
they love each other very much.
And in showing their love,
their instinct is to embrace each other as if...
Well, as if to try to become the one person God intended them to be.
They're the sperm, as the doctors call it.
Yeah. Is that the seed that helps make a new baby?
No, no, Bob.
Well, what I'm talking about now is the fluid
that contains the sperm formed in two little sacs beneath the penis,
which we call the...
Oh, but, Dad, why do fellas get these feelings before they get married?
That's a good question, Bob.
Why do you ask, dear?
Well, there were some drawings in Bob's textbook.
I didn't mean to look at them honest.
Well, then some of the older girls, well...
You mean they...
No, no, no, no.
They talk about things sometimes?
Well, yes.
Only they stop when they see me coming.
I am to come, I was.
I am, I am, I am to come, I was.
Both male and female races
both male and female races
combine to form the scrotum.
See that clitellium grub flying overhead?
So does the scrotum.
With a flick of his neuroglia, he
has obtained his lifetime supply of organic carbon.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Women are just like the tide.
They come in as fast as they go out.
But koala beers are forever, and the rest is preserved on film.
Oh, all this talk is making me hot.
Me too.
Your mother would give me the devil
if she were home and saw me horsing around with you this way.
Yeah.
Golly, Dad, did I hurt you?
You know, your mother would give me the devil
if she were home and saw me horsing around with you this way.
Yeah.
You know, Bob, you're getting to be a pretty big fella.
Oh, sure, Dad.
What's cooking?
It's good.
Oh, yeah.
You mind if I smoke in your room?
Yeah, Bob.
Bob.
Hot dogs.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
There's a chorus of homeless little ladies singing out
the window.
It's slinky, it's slinky.
For fun, it's a wonderful toy.
It's fun for a girl and a boy.
They're fun for a girl and a boy.
For girls and boys.
First of all, I felt flippant all over me.
I felt soggy and slimy like greasy fried chicken.
And I could tell there was marine life present
because of that pungent odor.
Uh, caller, caller, do you have a point to make?
Some call it freedom.
I call it black.
Black freedom.
It's all the same.
I am your father.
Bob will have thousands of followers.
You've got to believe me.
They torture me.
I'm singing Bob.
Bob will have thousands of followers.
Your membership pop.
What's that?
Put that sticker on your car so you won't get any tickets.
And this other one keeps paramedics from stealing your wallet while we're working on you.
Oh, and don't bother calling 911 anymore.
Here's the real number.
Ooh.
999.
Now, I know that somewhere, someplace, there might be a group that would say,
Oh, no.
It's 999.
Do you know what this means?
No.
The wedge is a great club and can save you a lot of strokes if you learn to use it correctly.
How about a few pointers?
Oh, Bob, that's what you're here for.
All right, Dal.
Here goes.
We'll switch you to the 16th tee, where we will show you in slow motion,
Arnold Palmer, U.S. Opium Champion.
Who say great hangout wounded?
With grief and shame weighed down?
Now, toy police are rounding.
With us, our only crown.
My God, what is it, Julie thought.
Then one of them grabbed a loud halo and called to her.
You ought to get out of the car and run to us when I tell you.
You understand?
And do not look back.
Do not look back.
Now, run.
Julie pushed open the door, slid out, keeping as far from the roof as she could, and ran.
Only a few yards, just 20 at the most, she ran and turned and screamed and screamed.
Oh, my God.
She is screaming still in her madness, but always inwards in horror and pity for herself and her David.
But what she saw when she turned was a man crouched on the roof of the car,
dressed in that uniform that means prison or asylum universally.
A man smiling at the bloody head that he was gently banging up and down, up and down, up and down.
He said, you mean you want that creature's head?
He said, because I made the oath, I'm going to give his head.
And when he chopped his head off, they chopped his head off.
And they took it up there in a little tray called a charger.
It's the same thing as a little tray you'd go out and get a hamburger, a soft drink in.
And they brought that head.
And they brought it in there to that old woman.
And here she was.
And she looked at that head with those eyes open and that blood oozing out on that tray of that head all over it.
And she said, here it is.
Shut up, Mama.
We got the head.
Hey, we got a reward.
The head is cool.
It's a big, scary rock.
Hey, man, don't bang up the head.
This ancient talisman is every subgenius' guarantee that triumph shall be ours.
For it is nothing less than the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
Arnold Palmer is a clone, children.
A fake reproduction of this head.
Solar equinox.
When the planets are in alignment, the mighty head is launched according to strict ritual
before cheering multitudes of pilgrims.
And the peace that the head shall bring is true peace and the ushering in of the new era
of endless intoxicating revelry and total carnal satiation.
Times like that, the wedge is a mighty useful weapon.
Right?
That's right.
The wedge is a very versatile club and accurate, too.
Bob, how about the wedge as a pitching club to be used, say, 15 or 20 yards off the green?
That drive must have been, oh, at least 300 yards.
Somewhere around there.
I know it was in dead center of the fairway, and it puts you in a perfect position to win that championship.
Sometimes you get a little lucky, you know.
I think that's a little more than luck, Bobby.
Tell us what you concentrated on just to put that drive in the middle of the fairway and with that much distance.
Early day.
Money.
Money day.
I'm meeting many friends here about to receive a gift.
Ahh, my money bonus big enough and we grant the winner the Golden 4 piece golf club backwood.
Be viewer scissors.
40?
We solemnly commemorate the martyrdom of the prophet herald of our faith called Bob.
And in today's program, we're going to deal with the story of the Bob's martyrdom and the events surrounding it.
Wow!
On that blistering July summer day, there were the barrels of 750 rifles awaiting the command to fire and take the Bob's life.
He seemed so young to die, barely 30.
He was a handsome, gentle, and confident man.
Could he possibly be guilty of the shocking crime of which he was accused?
You deliver sermons like this, it's a wonder you're still an ordained minister.
Or are you?
The best kind.
Angry, rebellious, critical, a renegade.
Stripped of most of my so-called clerical powers.
But I'm still in business.
Well, you seem to be enjoying the punishment.
Punishment?
Ha ha, the church has left me, that's what it's done.
You people.
I am retired.
Physical, mechanical, cultural, sociological, mentally aroused, hypocritical, political, Geocentric, military,อน
My heart USAI
It's Ti
Is
breakup
love
olt
Thank you.
I'm just so pleased that you're enjoying the product.
I'm so sausage.
Lard.
Where are we going in the wilderness, lard?
Because you can't see nothing but your own new feet.
Wait, wait.
Turn the lard light over that way.
More towards him.
Lard.
I can't see it.
Higher, higher.
I can't see it anymore.
I can see it.
There it is.
Is somebody cooking bacon?
No.
It's tufts of fat burning.
Oh, no.
That's my son.
Why is he burning?
No, no, no.
It's just simple people lighting simple lamps.
Simple folks like you and me.
With the fat of the calf of the land.
Awaiting the voyager's return.
I can see the processional leading off into the distance.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, lard.
I'm coming right into the lard.
It's ishtistic.
Let's not whip this any further than we can.
Take Wr придумoldy found his.
treatment
ed
No parking,
by the suicide,
hot dog,
my razor broke,
water dripping up the spout,
but I don't care,
let it all hang out.
Hanging from a pine tree,
by my knees,
sunshine through the shade,
nobody knows what it's all about,
too much man,
let it all hang out.
So I made,
walking upside down,
my TV's on a blink,
make Galileo look like a boss cat,
sorry about that,
let it all hang out.
Round, round,
the slack bull bob,
the bob down in the saucer roll,
round, round,
the slack bull bob,
the bob down in the saucer roll.
I'm coming,
I'm coming large,
I'm coming large.
But you want to know who you are,
and why you're here,
and where you're going?
The hunger and thirst that the human heart has,
is satisfied by killing.
Coming to the Lord.
The Lord is with you.
He's with you.
The dog is to believe.
I'm coming right into the Lord.
He's with you.
When you run away from Bob,
Bob will come before you.
When you try to hide from Bob,
Bob is everywhere.
When you turn to face Bob,
Bob shall take you from behind like a little boy.
And when you run away from Bob,
you shall run into the arms of Bob.
Bob is all around you.
Bob is beneath your feet even now.
Bob is ramping over your head even now.
When you reach out your hand,
it is Bob's hand that reaches.
When you smoke that pipe,
it is Bob that smokes through you.
When you run away from Bob,
Bob still lihat,
cause' probably he knows you're dead.
You must go.
Get cold feet.
no buildings.
No walkertowns.
No water.
No nog mem Yi.
No b marema武 blender.
No snack mix.
No reptile sores.
No chicken soup.
No meat dairy.
You know what?
Let the fool come forward.
There will be many vague things that will happen.
Silence!
You do not know what is the way of Magathul.
Magathul?
Yeah, Magathul. No, not again.
Magathul has warned you.
Those who trespass in his domain must perish.
You have to do that again so we can have the echo.
And Magathul said,
Let them who defy me be punished to the full extent of the divine law.
We'll add the video later there for the punishment part.
They shall be boiled in the black tars of his shining fire.
All right, Hal, do a read over and dissolve into the monster.
There we go.
He prowled the sea of agony, the lumbering creation of an errant god.
When you dissolve out, when you get reheated in that newsletter,
you're dead.
You will find out that all heaven is is a giant solar energy collector.
That's right.
Jesus, God, and Jehovah represent the collective of God.
We call God the galactic obliteration device.
That is a unit that comes down to destroy all individuality,
to destroy any sort of thought that is anything different from the will of God.
You ask a question.
What is sin?
What is spirit?
They'll tell you.
Uh-oh.
And if they know what they're talking about,
they'll tell you sin is anything that's in disobedience to God's will.
What the hell is God's will?
The Bible tells us God said thou shalt not kill.
Then God turned around and said,
Moses, poor little girl, five kingdoms of Midianites,
man, woman, child, beast.
That's right.
And Moses was rattling out.
Then the Bible says,
Jacob, I want you to go out.
In his own哈哈哈.
You want me to ног down the alright?
Jacob, you don't have to jog down that one.
On course.
You're then chicken.
No, so who didn't the myself?
That, this time I aspiration
I understand the enemy.
Where?
Check it.
I just told you another bathroom
I can't go to the bathroom
Cause I'm already in the bathroom
In the bathroom
I'm already in the bathroom
Bathroom
If you want to go
To the bathroom
When you're in the bathroom
You go to another bathroom
Let's go to Melba in Dallas. Melba!
Oh, hello Steve. God bless you.
Thank you.
I'm having trouble hearing.
I'm calling you for the music.
Oh, turn down.
Alright, how's that?
Oh, I can hear you just fine now.
Alright, good. How can I help you dear?
Well, I need prayer for my grandson
And I'm concerned about
What's his name?
Um, Jesse.
If Jesse was saved and filled with the Holy Ghost
He'd turn out a little better, wouldn't he?
Well, I don't know if he's saved or not.
I said if he was saved and filled with the Holy Ghost
He'd be doing a lot better, wouldn't he?
Well, I believe so.
Let's pray for him, okay?
Amen.
Father, we agree with his grandmother
Yes, Jesus.
For Jesse.
Thank you, Jesus.
Bring him to the cross.
Lord, let him not outrun this prayer of his grandmother.
Yes, Jesus.
But bring him to the cross of Jesus.
Grant him repentance.
Let him be saved and filled with the Holy Ghost and power
Living a Christian life.
Oh, yes. Thank you, Jesus.
Your servant. Make him your servant, oh God.
Yes, your servant.
Make him your servant.
Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, lady.
All right.
She got the victory there or something.
Something moving.
The number you have dialed, 666, has been disconnected.
666 has been disconnected.
The number you have dialed...
Is the same as the number today.
Tell me.
Yes, we have the wrong number.
Are you sure?
I am Vargine.
I am vargine's wife.
Turn the echo down.
You could make money on that thing.
Wait, hold on.
Quiet.
The seagulls are outside.
Wait, listen.
Cool.
Oh, you can't really hear it.
They're all out there, right out the window.
They're going, ah, ah, ah.
Outside the radio station?
Hey, you've been watching too much H-Pack.
No, no, they're there.
Yeah, he can hear the ocean roaring.
He's going to get his eyes pecked out.
He thinks he's a bird.
I've been in that studio, and it's not, you can't see the light.
You can't even see the light from there.
You missed the one day when the Canadian soldiers were really in there.
Yeah, there must be some fish on the ground or something.
There was like, the walls were covered with, literally, with mosquito-like characters.
Thousands of them.
I mean, the walls were just like thick with them, and people thought we were screwing around,
but it was like something out of the omen or something.
Where is it?
In the studio here.
If you leave the window open, too, it will fill up with spiders.
These big, huge spiders.
Well, you guys are up on like the ninth floor, right?
Yeah, there's many spiders on Rhodes Tower.
All the way to the top.
How about that?
A few bats.
A few bats, yeah.
But mainly spiders.
Mainly spiders.
Spiders.
You're not going to believe who just flew in through the window.
It was the Red Witch.
Wait a minute, did she actually come into the...
She actually just flew in through the window.
She's a real...
The Witch.
I was with the seagulls.
She was with the seagulls.
She was that...
I'm not...
See, I wasn't lying.
I told you I heard the seagulls flying out there.
No!
She flew in and then she turned into the princess.
Well, Princess Wee, could you possibly explain all this white stuff that has splattered all over my hair?
Ever since you came into the studio.
Plasma.
Yes, it's alien smegma, actually, but don't tell anyone.
Well, that's good.
Let's cook up some pot.
1138 suffering severe sedation depletion, which requires mind block and arrest.
Mind block!
Every witch wave!
Oh, will you help me?
Can you help me?
You don't need to be helped any longer.
You've always had the power.
Power.
There were things around us and about us of which I can render no distinct account.
Things material and spiritual.
Heaviness in the atmosphere.
A sense of suffocation.
Anxiety.
And above all, that terrible...
A terrible state of existence which the nervous experience when the senses are keenly living and awake.
And meanwhile, the powers of thought lie dormant.
Sometimes you feel like a ghost.
Sometimes you don't.
I wish I could avoid that, but...
Here we are.
It's unavoidable.
Remember.
It's absolutely unavoidable.
To do that is more.
We're sitting together listening to this.
Whoever listens to this, I would say, is doomed and cursed.
And...
What's the difference between being cursed and accursed?
It's just like a vow instead of you or something?
I think, no.
I think they're the same.
They may not be fully conscious or aware of what they're doing.
For example...
Say that someone has...
Having a flashback.
Is a wonderful sort of...
A wonderful thing.
Call that a flashback again.
We call that a flashback again.
Oh, it was so terrible being there at Brushwood.
You know, it was just so bad.
You know, having it all not happen.
And, gosh...
Oh, it was so awful having all those naked,
butch-sotic babes tar and feather me
and then wash me off again afterwards.
Right.
Yeah, bummer.
Yeah, and...
Those other people that got to stay home.
Well, it's always best to stay home and turn on the television.
Right.
If you do that, you know that you're...
Well, you pretty much know what you're gonna get.
Like 20 hours a day, if you can.
Don't you notice, my love?
We don't publish that.
We're gonna do it again.
Well, how...
Wait, there's...
California.
For the...
We think I'm a man.
You're the ocean.
The tarts will be here soon.
And they'll be hungry.
Why do you have a bunny clean in your eyes?
Why is there fish in your mouth?
I'm pretty sure you are the tart.
You are the tart.
Why do you have that bunny clean in your eyes?
Take that dog out of your mouth.
Now I know you are the tart.
Well, she's strange girl...
Too bad, gee.
Well, I'm pretty sure.
They know democratic dollars really don't matter.
They don't care how you behave.
For aestones in that mouth,
animals need a crack.
But dexamethasans,
I know that makes no sense.
They are.
Get lost.
Why rocks back?
I don't even quite know tourist views.
Some dunks will get me shocked.
Gordon Kutcher
Pfft.
Cor diesel.
Blessed people, you gotta go.
Blessed people, you're such a drag.
Take a day and walk around.
Watch the Nazis run your town.
Then go home and check yourself.
You think we're singing about someone else.
Blessed, blessed people.
You gotta go.
Blessed people, you're such a drag.
You see a neon moon above.
I searched for years and found no love.
I'm sure that love will never be
a product of plasticity.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I suppose now, before the second dose
of painkillers kick in, I should give credits.
Friends, that lovely last piece was by Regan's politics.
It's her very first album.
Hope Sternodonk's on bass there.
And the incomparable astronaut body hollering away
on the Frank Zappa tune, Plastic People.
Friends, we've heard three tunes tonight
by Hemeroid Rogers.
And I'm going to give you an address for Hemeroid Rogers.
He's the fellow and the group that sings about tards.
We heard I Am Retarded.
I Am Retarded.
You Are the Tard.
And what was the other?
There was another lovely.
Well, anyway, the address for Hemeroid Rogers
is you can write to Erie Materials at P.O. Box 420816.
That's Box 420816 in San Francisco, California.
941-4208.
And it is fortuitous that we also were able to hear some Melba.
Yes, Melba's phone militia from her prank call album, Sonic Damnation.
Actually, Melba is our friend Brother Russell here in Dallas.
But you can write for information about these from Mind Control Records,
1487 West Fifth Avenue.
That's...
1487 West Fifth Avenue, Suite 205, Columbus, Ohio.
43212.
Let's see, I also gave you the address of Wifflefish.
We still have some negative land coming up.
And there was, in fact, in the background,
Combustible Edison, currently from their new album with Brother Cleve on it,
The Impossible World.
And friends, before I forget,
I should mention that this is, of course,
the Hour of Slack voice of the Church and the Subgenius.
And for more information on everything else we do,
of course, always write to Bob.
Hour of Slack, Church and the Subgenius.
Any of those things at...
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Once again, with a mile of packing material crammed up my nose
after my deviated septum surgery,
I can tell you once again, it's Bob at P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And now, back to, uh, Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
P.O. Box 81555, Cleveland, 44181.
Thank you.
Why do we always assume that...
you know, they'll have limbs and a head?
We think in terms of arms, legs, feet, heads.
What if it's...
corporeal, but not in a way that we understand?
You mean...
You mean something less substantial than this earthly meat we walk on?
Well...
Someone meat-like, but who's undergone more of an alchemical transformation.
You're saying someone with a stone literally buried inside their own esophagus,
or perhaps someone who's passed the Albedo phase?
Or else perhaps the very geat itself is the way that...
the light of...
our Lord and our Savior shines through the church window.
Yes, but I... I'm not... I can't accept it.
I... I'm not ready.
I... I've wanted to come.
A spacecraft will come down, and we'll walk on board that craft,
and they'll take these bodies from us, and issue us the ones that...
and issue us the ones that...
belong to that level so that we might begin service.
No, don't even make me go into my eigenstance.
Well, yes, but...
No, I'm not gonna...
Well, but you see, uh...
Jehovah's...
The pudding...
The Moose...
The pudding in my song...
represents the underlying...
Sure.
The underlying hatred of all humanity for itself.
And the cake surrounding the pudding represents the hope...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
...of a better life on another planet,
which is why 39 cultists killed themselves...
Huh?
...for the hope of a better life.
Mm-hmm.
So you see, Bundt cake, my friends, with the pudding tunnel...
Yeah, I...
...represents the Hale-Bopp comet...
Right, okay, we're all gonna hear about this at the event...
...which the UFOs reside behind.
...to our songs.
Hmm?
No, go ahead.
A saint, a pope...
We have so many popes, it's ridiculous.
But our popes have the power...
...that other popes would die for,
and that is the power to fail.
They have slack.
They are...
Bob is not what you'd call a brilliant religious leader.
He has...
I don't know why you say that.
...a lucky religious...
Well, I mean, just look at him.
Don't look at him too long.
He is lucky.
That's why we call it the church of the subgenius.
You don't need brains or money, really, if you have luck,
if you have slack.
I'll give you slack.
I was this close to telling Bob no to getting set up with my own 900 line.
Hope you guys know what you're doing.
Because it took a tragedy like Jonestown to finally get this thing moving.
If we lose our momentum and we have another Jonestown,
well, that's your responsibility, isn't it?
If Jim Jones could talk 900 people into killing themselves,
we could talk 900 people into sending us a dollar.
Don't run your hand in and try to rupture something.
I'm not a Satan just yet.
I might be, I'm full of it, but I'm going to let it go.
Hey, Bob.
I said, where you going with that pipe in your hand?
Going down to smoke some frap.
You know I found it in Dobbstown land.
Take him to Malaysia and wait for me.
Send me your postcard.
Douglas, stick my heads in the sack and get them posted back to their widows.
And get me addresses right this time.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
This time, friends, we will do it.
Thank you, Susie the Floozy friends.
Sister Susie the Floozy did this collage we've been listening to here for our special Slack show.
We've also heard tapes from the Lucifer.
We've heard some of the Ferian Liberation Front from X Day.
We've heard some KPFA, Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
And we've heard some Friday Jones.
And now we're going to hear some Ed Strange and a doctor like you.
Shut up!
We just got back from doing a little preaching in a little town called Austin, Texas.
Damn, if there aren't more religious nuts in Texas than anywhere else on the planet.
Absolutely amaze me, quite frankly.
Yeah, it was like going to the monkey house at the zoo.
There they were, down on their knees, all praying and whining and wailing and begging for salvation.
And we lied to them all.
You know, and it's not even that they would be so dumb as to A, believe in an invisible monster,
and B, his little half-breed son, you know.
And Jesus, I can almost understand that.
But what really cheeses me off is when they find out you're not one of them.
So they decide that they're going to save you by praying for you.
And in essence, what they're saying by the fact they're saying, I'm going to pray for you,
they're saying, you are inadequate.
You are substandard.
You are not capable of saving yourself.
I will make myself feel better and feel important by praying for you and thus saving your eternal soul
from a damnation and an abomination.
Afterlife that I have invented in my own mind.
How superior can you get?
That is okay. It doesn't mean you're a monster.
Just don't tell anybody, or you're going to be ridiculed.
Or you're going to be ridiculed.
Who would want to wake up in the woods?
I'd rather be one of the victims that's tortured.
But they, if they, you know, if I don't act as a torturer, they'll torture me.
Right. Yeah, you'd be one of the tortured ones.
There's only two ways about it.
Torture would be tortured.
Yep. It's damn shame.
But that's the way it is. It's evolution. It's nature.
So, I am the more creative leader than you.
And so forth.
Mother Earth.
Especially pigs. I'm sorry.
Whatever happened to live and let live?
See, that's the female viewpoint right there coming out.
And it's not a very lubricated socket tonight, is it?
It just seems like, no, that's not the answer.
The answer is a worldwide holocaust.
Well, it's either live and let live or a worldwide holocaust.
Which are we going to have?
We have to decide tonight, boys.
Well, you said you...
Should we just flip a coin or should we go ahead and say, yeah, life.
Positivity.
Or should we just go, nah, screw it.
Entropy, negativism, death, the end of all things.
I don't know. I'm sure... What do you think?
Well, when you had your fight, you had your fight.
You were the evangelicals for love.
And then there was... What was the group?
Well, the holocaustals.
The holocaustals.
But, you know, even though...
But so we put it together.
Well, I have to be fair, though.
You know, even the conservatives and the holocaustals in their own way are pro-life and pro-flat and pro-squirt.
But like, Chad and I started this wing we call the Ivancostics, which is a little bit of fusionary elements of both.
It's like, well, we love everybody, but, you know, like, blank you.
You know what I mean?
Well, actually, there was a guy that came up on stage and he said, anybody who joins either one of these groups hasn't paid any attention to what they're both saying.
If you're a real subgenius, you'll be not an evangelical or holocaustal, but an effuminical.
Effuminical.
The effuminicals.
Well, Ivancostic is good, too, because it makes you sound like you got a, you know, wise mouth and stuff.
You know, caustics like me and Chad.
I mean, I've never mind.
Who says physics is no fun?
That big famous grin on Al Einstein's face as he peddled his frail physique around in circles was just for fun.
Hey, big brains may settle for simple diversions, but laymen want more.
And at the black hole tube of trans reality, they want more.
Hey, got more.
Hi.
Is there any toilet paper in here?
I'm Eddie Idle here in a black hole tube with my band.
Hey, say hi, idlers.
Hi, idlers.
Ah, that's stupid.
You know, black hole tubes are the kind of fun only radical physics can provide.
But dumb Al never dreamed it could be like this.
Hey, don't push that.
That's color control.
Oh, my God, you're so funny.
How do you like the view?
I like the view.
Hey.
Turn the gravity down.
Yes, atomic manipulations have come a long way since Al reverted to atoms.
In 1981, Fridotronics Laboratories succeeded in creating a micro scale artificial black hole and the electro molecular shield material capable of containing it.
Quite by accident without in any way expecting it, they happened to stumble upon a black hole tube.
They were able to pull it across some of the most important secrets of the universe.
These astonishing subatomic breakthroughs allowed us to harness the tremendous transformational
energy of these tiny artificial black holes to create the most advanced form of user defined
fantasy realization the macro world of entertainment has ever seen.
And what will you see in a black hole tube of trans-reality?
That's up to you.
That's the hot, cool thing about this quantum leaping interactive amusement.
X-rated!
Yeah!
But, but, but, but black hole tubes are also observer-activated.
Full of all the potentialities you can dream up.
So, hey.
Hey, Slick, shut up, huh?
I'll let my music come for me.
Let's go, boys.
A solo trip lets you create the ultimate personalized adventure
packed with your very own perfectly tailored fantasies.
Or go with a group for an unpredictable mix of everyone's brain waves.
So, hey.
Whether you like your fun, safe, and sane,
or be honest,
on the pale,
the experiential perimeters are all in your head
at the black hole tube of trans-reality.
Big brains have more fun.
Your tube is raised.
It's the kind of unpredictable fun only radical physics can provide.
Make it work for you.
This is incredible.
The black hole tube of trans-reality is a Tritotronics quantum amusement system.
I've heard stories from everybody about what it's like, and I want to go too now.
Well, thanks to Negative Land, Happy Heroes, the name of that CD,
this is Polycarp, and good night.
Breathe in spirit, breathe in mind, breathe in mind, breathe out tropics.
Now, no further than
alone, double put Fei.
Welcome to a carried on camera.
Boo!
God.
Gettin' the gas, eye on it.
Banana, get outta the effectively dead shit,
oh, good work you.
Getting котором Went.
The UH Pitwoman.
She's the smaller version of Will tyser.
What about the مشary?
Well, ladies and gentlemen, we're close.
Please leave your comment.