Ladies and gentlemen, welcome aboard our McDonnell Douglas DC-88 space liner for today's mission to Mars.
The captain has asked that you remain in your seats at all times.
And please, no smoking.
Attention, please. Folks, this is Third Officer Collins speaking.
I'm your tour guide today, and I'll be telling you about what's going on during the trip.
Right now, we're on final countdown, and you can watch our liftoff on the lower screen in your cabin.
I'll speak to you again after we're in space.
Mission control, this is Mars 295 ready for departure.
295, roger. Countdown is going.
Going up in 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
We'll meet again at midnight.
Do a little dance, Rich.
I said, I'm mad.
Praise and grace, how sweet the sound that saved a wretch like me.
I once was lost, but now I'm found.
I was blind, but now I see.
Now there's one you don't hear in a bar every day.
Father, Son, Holy God.
Well, well.
Moses went on to the mountain high to find out from God why did you make us.
Why?
Secret words he held a secret room.
He said, ba-ba-ba-loo-ba-ba-ba-ba-boom.
I did not put you here to suffer.
I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
And the kid, I'm having a good time now, now, now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go, go.
Hey, hey, hey.
Let my people go.
All right.
Yeah.
Chosh, a victim battled a Jericho.
He tell the boys with the horns, get down and blow.
They reared back, aimed their bows at the stars.
He said, beat me, big daddy.
Hey, two.
I did not put you here to suffer.
I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
And the kid, I'm having a good time now, now, now.
Let my people go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah.
Sing it, boy.
Let my people go, go, go.
Let's dance, dance, dance, yeah.
Let'sland that.
Palm joy.
Come on.
I grade, I grade by eyes and sit sound.
You see you on the spot, in stadium.
Me, yeah, yeah.
Ain't no fright, damn.
No I two.
I ain't noare though.
I don't know you want make a mess, all right?
Jesus went out for a walk with his mother
The scribes and the Pharisees
Plotting over their mother
They locked him up and
They threw away the key
He said, why's everybody always picking on me?
I did not put you on a solver
No, I did not put you on a wife
I put you here to help one another
Yes, and the kid I'm having a good time now
Let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
Let my people go
Got to let my people go
Yeah!
Those other religions,
they want 10% of your income right off the top.
They want you to provide for them
in your will.
They want you to pressure your government
for billion dollar contributions.
They want you to double your taxes
so that they don't have to pay any.
And what does Bob ask for?
30 lousy bucks.
They're the ones with the extravagant cathedrals,
the lush synagogues,
the giant mosques.
And what do we have?
One hour a week on non-commercial radio.
Now, forgive me if I go out on a limb here,
but doesn't that sound just a little lopsided?
Of course not.
It sounds a lot lopsided.
But we got something they don't have.
It's called slack.
And I don't mean the artificial slack
they try to market for a profit.
Hey, folks, play the lottery and win free slack.
Uh-uh.
I'm talking about real slack.
Internal slack.
Slack.
From within.
The kind that feeds on itself like a breeder reactor.
It radiates a warm, fuzzy glow that lights up our lives.
It's an inner peace they will never know.
And therein lies the basic difference
in our religious philosophies.
They stress pain, suffering, and sacrifice
because on the outside, they have everything.
But on the inside, they have nothing.
They're morally bankrupt.
Empty shells.
Just poor, pathetic souls
tormented by inner demons of guilt and self-loathing.
But we Sagini, we are the exact opposite.
While on the outside, we have so little,
on the inside, we have everything.
And that's why we're smiling
and Bob Dobbs is smirking.
Because we're rich with slack.
And for all their money, it's not for sale.
Herein does the word of Bob praise Bob!
Amen.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Ñ So long, everyone!
We're all here tonight to praise Bob.
He's kind of shown us that Devo works in parallel ways
with other pockets of humans on this planet.
Where we thought we were alone,
we know there are now other human forms
that believe in conscious mutation.
As he knows, Bob is merely an enema for a constipated society.
These people here are here to help a constipated society
blow it out their ass.
Have you ever met Bob?
Well, like I said, Bob would appear in my bedroom
and chase me around, making me do jumping jacks.
I know what you do
Cause I do it too
Through subversive measures, Devo passes on the word of Bob
by, uh, we, if you take a look at our last album cover,
his name's been airbrushed into the rubber hairlines
of each of the band members, right next to the word sex.
Do Bob and sex go hand in hand?
No.
Well, Bob is a kind of total altercation
all consuming sex.
We're like explosions
That lead to feeling good
We're like ideas
That change the world for good
There's nothing past the stop and go
There's nothing but the up and go
There's nothing like some in and out
There's nothing more than what you know
Yes!
About the only slack that I get anymore
is worshiping at the Holy Temple of the Yoni.
Tell us about that.
What's that?
I'm sure your audience don't know what the Holy Temple of the Yoni is.
Can you tell us?
It's the female delta.
The female delta.
And that's where you worship.
It's penis fuck pussy.
Oh.
Pussy surround please.
Oh, I see.
State your occupation please.
A libertine and a seducer.
Sex fiend.
Oh yes.
Pure and simple.
A libertine and a seducer.
State your address please.
Paradise.
Paradise?
I can well understand that.
Is there anything religion can do to help me find my friend?
Well, we could join together in prayer.
Uh-huh.
But is there anything useful we can do?
No.
Hello friends and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled, What If?
It is called that for good reason.
Because you see, everywhere I go across this great nation,
everywhere I tour, every performance I give,
some sincere but misguided Christian
accosts me in the parking lot
and barks a curse we've all heard a million times
for the last two thousand years.
Sinner!
They shriek, eyeballs bulging and bony finger pointing.
You may laugh now, but come judgment day,
what if you're wrong?
If I had but a dime for every time that thinly veiled threat
was hurled towards a subgenius,
I'd have more money than all the trial lawyers
in California and New York combined.
Yet, as mean-spirited as this rhetorical question sounds,
it is in fact a legitimate challenge.
What if, Bob forbid, we are wrong?
Such a premise.
It's difficult for subgenius to contemplate
because one of the cornerstones of good salesmanship
is confidence in the product.
We will succeed because we know we will succeed.
It is a self-fulfilling prophecy.
To even question the outcome is not only defeatist
and anti-Dobbsian,
it is subgenius sacrilege.
And yet,
in the interest of open theological debate,
we will consider just this once
the question of what if we're wrong.
Now theoretically speaking,
not that it is statistically probable,
but hypothetically imagine if you can
a world come July 5th, 1998,
where there is no excess invasion.
Oh, it's painful, it's painful dear friends, I understand.
But remember, this is only theoretical.
A planet that is not surrounded by an angry alien spacecraft.
A globe not littered,
a globe not completely polluted
with the corpses of conspiracy dupes.
Oh dear friends,
it would be a sick society
still dominated by paints and normals.
An earth where corporations, governments, and well-equipped armies
still loyal to the system,
continue to uphold the status quo.
They fight to maintain their tight totalitarian grasp
on the very throat of freedom.
Oh, it's a nightmarish vision indeed,
one that makes my head spin,
but one we will contemplate nonetheless
in the interest of free and open debate.
Yes dear friends,
this dark future of Dobbsian defeat
and conspiracy conquest,
this desperate future
where the last subgenius forces are holed up
in the underground bunkers
awaiting the final onslaught
by conspiracy mercenaries
is a vision we do not want to contemplate
but will this one last time.
As the Kelvin bombs explode far above
on the planetary surface,
Stane and his subgenius generals
huddle beneath a flickering light bulb
pouring over maps of subgenius tunnels,
subway tunnels, and underground sewers
examining any and all possible attack routes.
They will be determined
determined to fight to death
and take the maximum number of normals with them.
Why?
Because we hate you!
They will be dedicated to honoring Bob
through a dignified Dobbsian death.
It is even, it is then
that some weak of heart heretic
will step forward,
or probably some Bobby,
who always dreamed of being
a real subgenius warrior for wartime,
but when the chips are down for Dobbs
wants to cash out,
this weak-willed wannabe Bobby
will show his first real courage
when he steps forward and whines,
But Reverend Stane,
Bunker!
you promised we'd have something to show
for our membership fee.
The bunker will fall silent like a tomb.
The collected gas will cause
the barometric pressure to plummet.
The bobbing above will pause in divine reverence.
Stane will slowly turn to the trembling traitor,
glare into his frightened little face,
and with the thunder of Daniel Webster
will proclaim the same answer
I gave the Christian in the parking lot,
and that is this.
Even in hell,
we'll have the one thing
the conspiracy tried to deny from us
all our living lives.
The one human right
they'll never be able to take from us again,
no matter how much they lie about what we did
or what they didn't do.
It's the one virtue Christians will never obtain,
no matter how much they beg,
pray,
or grovel to their God.
I'm talking about respect,
self-respect,
the only commodity that can't be bought,
traded,
negotiated,
or stolen in any of the conspiracy marketplaces.
Appreciate it. Hallelujah.
It's a concept foreign to all pinks and normals
who serve the system.
They may have stolen our freedom,
our slack,
and even our lives,
but by virtue of our very defiance to them and their ways,
we've earned a self-respect they can't even pretend to want.
And you want to know why?
Why?
Because their religion is based on submission,
while ours is based on independence.
Yes!
Praise Bob!
Give me a praise Bob!
So that, dear friends, is our answer.
That's what we get,
even if we're wrong,
come Judgment Day.
The honor and dignity of self-respect earned
through a lifelong fight for independence and freedom.
Only the devil
could possibly resent a man
for wanting to be free.
Any God
that wouldn't want his followers to be free
is no savior,
but a tyrant,
an enslaver of souls,
a devil in disguise.
And that leads me to my question to the Christian.
It's terribly original, so brace yourself for it.
What if,
what if you're wrong?
Come Judgment Day.
Please think carefully before you answer, dear friend,
because remember,
your very soul dangles in the balance.
Hear it, it's the word of our praise Bob!
Amen!
Praise Bob!
Praise!
Father Choke Mama!
This is the age
with the big machine
The age of darkness
The age of bad dreams
There was a light
in the oldest show
I had his back with a vengeance
and he burns to the bone
I had the band
with a plan
and I wanna grow up
to be a renaissance man
I shall discover
the meaning of life
I shall discover how to fly above
I shall discover
America once in my life
And I shall discover the love, oh joy
I am a renaissance man
By Leonardo
Raphael
Raphael Michelangelo
And they got nothing on me
Give me a brush, a push
and a pretty girl's face
I'll be painting my name
on every scene
or different place
I have the band
with a plan
and I wanna grow up
to be a renaissance man
And I shall discover
I shall discover the meaning of life
I shall discover how to fly above
I shall discover America once in my life
I shall discover love, oh joy
I am a Renaissance man
Oh, light, light, wash over me
Over the land, over the sea
Star of Bethlehem, I
Be shooting in the dark tonight
This is the age of reasoning
Got an explanation for everything
I've seen the Shroud of Turin rip
Moving mountains made the size of a silicone chip
I am a man with a plan
And I want to grow up to be a Renaissance man
I shall discover the meaning of life
I shall discover how to fly above
I shall discover America once in my life
And I shall discover love, oh joy
I am a Renaissance man, oh joy
I am a Renaissance man, oh boy
Renaissance man
That's what I am
The transmission. Stand by for transmission.
Oh my god! It's time for the show!
The only show that not only massages your prostate, but actually is part of its natural growing diet.
I'm Dr. Argus Q. Fox, and with me today, as always, is your host, Fid Julie!
Hi guys!
And somewhere else I think there's peas.
Yes, it's true, it's peas. Radio the way it was never meant to be. Time for the show!
Yeah, that's what they say.
This time for the show, on free things, radio the contents of the show in a manner that is inconsistent with its labeling is illegal.
Also, this show is produced in a facility that processes gluten, so there may be trace amounts.
I'm allergic to peanuts.
You're allergic to what? Say that again?
Peanuts.
Oh, okay, well...
Keep your mouth closed around me, buddy.
I want to mention that BreatheRink Radio is totally user-friendly with its onboard chat-friendly room,
and the only people that don't seem to be able to use it is some musician in Connecticut.
I guess that guy was just dumb.
But fuck that guy!
Yeah, that's what you get, idiot!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
We're enabling the audience. We're bringing a new multimedia sphere of information.
And we're bringing a new audience influence to you!
Our friends.
That's right, because here on Time for the Show, we don't just have our finger on the pulse of society,
we have our hand wrapped around its...
It's, it's what? Its genitals? Its throat? Its... feminine wrist?
Its dirty, poor throat.
All right.
Yeah.
If you'd like to send an email to Time for the Show, send it to timefortheemail at gmail.com.
I'll be looking at it, maybe.
All one of our listeners can send your complaints now.
But hey, I mean, that's triple the regular FreeThink Radio slot, I guess.
So, we're doing all right!
The numbers don't lie.
When it comes to hijacking a radio feed from some guy you never met before,
well then, by golly, we're the best at it!
I mean, it's not exactly pirate radio, because I guess we actually...
I don't know.
We actually have, like, some sort of permission to be here.
Do we have any values in which we must uphold?
Well, we got permission to do the show without permission.
Exactly.
As long as he can... has plausible deniability, then the show never happened to begin with.
Well, that's a poignant and wonderful speech, if we could only have heard it.
I don't think I can make a radio show unless I drink some coffee.
Can you?
Yes.
You can?
I can't drink coffee. It makes me nervous.
It gives me the jitters, man.
Um, not drinking coffee gives me the jitters.
Like this music gives me the jitters.
This is something called Juno Reactor.
I don't know if that's really a person's name or a program that is used to make Juno music.
But that's what our background music is.
And what we just heard a minute ago was the first little installment of the podcast called Time for the Show.
That is sort of like the Scrumcast of the Podcrusters.
It was Argus Fox, Fid Chooley, and Reverend P.
Wow.
Before that we heard the Rainmakers doing Renaissance Man.
That's a song that's only on one album, I think.
But it's a favorite song.
Of course, Papa Joe Mama was ranting there.
We heard some old collages from Leemur.
And some yakking by Mark Mothersbaugh, Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh, back in 1984.
The Rudy Schwartz Project music that we heard was, in fact, the Rudy Schwartz Project.
With enhanced Florence Henderson.
There was a little bit of Papa Joe Mama, Slack is Not for Sale.
And at the very beginning we heard another Rainmakers song.
Well, they were doing Amazing Grace and then a live version of Let My People Go Go.
Their big hit.
The one hit they ever had.
If you can even call it that.
I don't know if it was a hit exactly, but I actually heard it on the radio once.
Wrote the title and the band down.
Never heard the Rainmakers on Dallas radio again.
But that is, yeah, that was their first album.
And now we're going to call Dave, rather than Dave calling us.
Yes.
Let's call the Dave.
I have to put in my special...
Your special code?
Yeah, my special code.
Because you've got to know the code.
And I have to know his name and his number.
There.
We should...
Yeah, listen to that.
Sounds like a phone ringing.
Yeah.
This is the Daveston.
Hello?
Recording everything going fine.
No trouble.
Right now?
Yeah, right now.
I have to remember to turn the recorder off after about 25 minutes.
Because we have that much talk time.
Before...
Well, I thought I looked in the mirror and I looked like the guy in Nosferatu.
You know what I mean?
You look like that?
Or...
No, Dave.
Actually, Princess, he does...
If you know which character he's talking about, he does look a little like...
He does not look like that.
Nosferatu.
No.
Max Shrek as Nosferatu.
Dracula.
No.
In a silent movie.
Like, he was like, what's his name?
And Candy had a gleaming white hump on his forehead.
And then the huge blood vessels that course through his veins like a mighty river.
You know, I have a giant vein in my forehead that pulses.
I know.
When I get real mad, it gets...
And I'm swollen and I probably shouldn't say this on the radio, but when I...
What my friends do when I get out of hand is they just put their thumb on that vein and
it makes me pass out, that forehead vein.
Yeah.
It's kind of like the Dead Man's Switch on the old train.
Right.
Princess, we...
Short circuits me either by doing that or lifting her shirt.
And that usually shuts me up.
If I'm throwing up.
throwing a fit.
That's an advantage women do have.
All they have to do is lift their shirts
and it shuts you out pretty good.
They can distract.
Well, the idea is to just change your,
shock you out of your bad train of thought.
It's kind of like with the dogs.
You know, when you're trying to train a dog,
you just distract,
but get obsessed over something
and you just go the other way.
That surprises them
and then they calm down
and they're like,
that wasn't working today.
There was some,
I guess there was raccoon on our walk trail.
There was raccoon poop
on all of the rocks.
Yes.
And all over your shoes you might have.
And I think that our new little guard dog
was really wanting to guard us
from those raccoons.
Of course, he's a treeing walker coon hound
and he has no choice.
But he can.
He gets to this point where he wants to be,
he wants to run in every direction all at once.
So he's darting right, left, up, down, all around.
It's insane.
He wants to run everywhere.
We're out in the woods.
We're out in the woods
and he is surrounded by varmints.
There really are varmints everywhere
and he wants to chase all of them at once.
All at once.
But it can't be done.
In fact, he can't chase any of them
because he's on a leash.
Oh, poor guy.
For now.
Poor guy.
He's strangulating himself
every little walk he takes.
He's stuck in his joy forever
except for he's strangulating himself.
Yeah.
I'm familiar with that one too.
That's what Jake used to also do.
He's just like half like hang himself,
strangulate himself,
trying to go in so many different directions.
And every, you know,
how many times you got to see a bird
before you don't react like,
it's a bird, it's a bird.
Yeah, but Jake was your twin brother.
Not a dog.
That's the difference.
He looks like Nosferatu too.
No, no, no.
Especially a few years after he died.
Hey, I'll have you know,
my grandmother was a fishmonger.
That was an easy way of making money around here
in the old days.
You know, you get a cart,
you walk around going for fresh fish
and stuff like that.
Now they don't have any fish you can eat anymore.
From like Erie,
you mean?
They had these like Lake Erie mussels
that were similar to clams
and they had oyster shops around
as well as the many, many fish houses.
Well, they still do
and they have all those invasive zebra mussels.
Yes, but you can't eat zebra mussels
because they're zebras.
Well, you can't eat anything out of Lake Erie
because they're all,
they've all been eating toxic compounds.
Yeah, it comes from most people's shampoo
and their plumes.
The lake of Erie.
That's why those fish and chips taste like soap.
That explains it all.
Yeah, well,
the environment should get much worse very soon.
Judging by the kind of new laws that are being passed,
I think they're pretty much trying to kill
all the poor people
and make everyone,
who wasn't already super poor,
super poor.
And everybody who was already super rich,
super richer,
all five of them,
or ten of them.
And destroy all the protected places.
Yeah, all the protected places
all have to go now.
Ruin public schooling forever.
Right.
So, you know,
the average kid doesn't get to go
grades K through 12.
Right.
Teach children
the only place that they can learn real news
is the Russian internet
and everything else is fake.
Oh, I hear you laughing,
but it's sad,
but it's true.
It's not contrary to the average.
What do they call that?
Like an abolitionist,
only you got to be like a sharp teeth.
And you like,
you're like really,
yeah.
Vampires?
Yeah.
Vampires.
I don't know.
People are regravitating back towards grandpires.
Grandpires.
They're,
well,
that's because they've,
they're running the government now.
Grandpires?
Yeah,
grandpires,
really old vampires,
real fat old vampire,
bloated,
tick-like,
small fingered vampires.
Most vampires have real long fingers,
but the new,
the new vampires have tiny little stumpy hands
like a Tyrannosaurus.
We shouldn't make fun of people with disabilities.
Like a childish monkey.
Little small type sim,
simian organism.
Little,
uh,
fellowship monkey in the name of the 12.
Well,
what's cuter than a little fellowship monkey?
Except when you get a whole tribe of them together,
pretty next thing you know,
they're inventing nuclear weapons and lobbing them at each other.
That's how they get involved in macrocephalic nuclear war phase.
Sometimes the brains get so big they explode.
But I guess the Toledo,
or not Toledo,
but the,
uh,
Tokyo Power Company,
where Fukushima was,
it was so crooked.
The whole,
the whole place is so crooked that made everything that happened,
happen real easy and stuff.
Are you talking about Fukushima in Japan?
Fukushima.
Yeah.
Oh,
that would never happen here at the Comanche nuclear power plant just down the hill from us.
Up the road,
up the road.
Steak from?
Huh?
Sure.
What is that?
Where you got that glowing steak and baked potato from?
No,
you can't cook with it,
but it is where the six legged frogs and the giant grasshoppers come from.
Oh.
Yeah.
The mutated jackalopes that have,
we heard tell that rattlesnakes are evolving the ability to not rattle because rattling just gets them killed by humanoids.
So there've been more and more cases of rattlesnakes that don't rattle.
So they can sneak around,
Barry.
They don't rattle around people anyway.
The ones that just grew up with without the urge to rattle when monkey people come around.
Those are the ones that survive.
Yeah.
And they avoid the toiletry drowning too,
because that can be very painful in your life.
The toiletry ground.
Yeah.
Like sometimes people want to commit suicide back in the home and different other institutions I've been associated with.
I was tired of going to get going to the toilet and drown myself.
Oh,
well,
you're in toilet and snakes have been known to do that too.
You say,
well,
sure.
Sometimes when they get out of the hyena point zoo or any of those other famous places,
you have to be aware.
Famous.
Hi.
Yeah.
Parker.
So,
well,
you know,
one of the hyenas.
Point.
Kings point.
One.
Hyena is pork.
I'm sorry.
Zoo.
That's my Massachusetts.
Right.
Well,
there's there's it's a chain.
Yeah.
Hyena.
It's always.
It's even out here too.
There's three of them like within eyesight right now.
Hey,
no sports.
We have,
but we have,
there's a chain of,
uh,
abusement parks here called Jackalope world.
Oh yeah.
The,
they have a giant life-size Jackalopes of every kind.
It's cute ones,
mean ones,
good guy,
bad guy,
Jackalope.
So it gets off kind of cartoonish,
but it educates children about Jackalopes.
Yes.
Are they animates like in,
like in neighbor world or very,
very,
very crudely.
They have a little motor that makes their jaw open and close,
or maybe their tail stiffly swings back and forth.
Well,
it's a good thing that they don't,
they're part of the track Pacific current,
because.
I guess Fukushima already pooped in Alaska 12 times.
Fukushima pooped in Alaska.
You say,
are they picking up the advance?
And what's the,
what,
what are these tails are?
Tell me if from your scientific facilities and radio,
autonomic curiosity,
if you've ever heard of these like huge islands of junk floating around the Pacific that are even connected from together.
Well,
they're not really islands.
They are,
uh,
you,
it's not like you can walk on the floating plastic in the ocean.
It's part,
it's more like an awful,
it's thick with plastic particles.
There are massive masses.
There are,
it's,
it's yeah,
there,
but it's not like an island made out of junk.
You couldn't,
you couldn't do anything with it.
All it's good for is choking fish and other organisms.
Yeah.
Organisms.
Wow.
You like organisms.
I think about organisms.
I think I stole that from Ren and Stimpy,
Ren specifically.
Oh,
I forgot about that or else I wouldn't have contributed anyway,
because I was thinking about Wilhelm Reich and the Oregon,
Oregon Baboon Patrol and all the other,
all the other sidekick simian baboons and monkeys that we were talking about before.
Well,
and,
and Bob did Wilhelm Reich one better.
He had the orgasm onic chamber,
which was actually kind of just a large suitcase.
And one,
one person at a time would get inside of it and basically masturbate.
That was Bob's orgasm on it,
but it worked.
It did work.
It smelled horrible though.
Yeah.
And also it got the lawsuits from the duct tape and everything.
It was real beat up.
It was very large.
I mean,
it was big enough to hold a person,
but it was,
it was gross.
It was just really gross.
The orgasm on it chamber,
he called it and he would,
there were people,
I,
I think Trump's dad paid over a million bucks an hour to sit in there and that sweltering,
stinky giant suitcase.
And well,
you know,
well,
that's what they say.
You know,
you can never believe all that stuff,
but I guess as far as a multi-billionaires go,
there's a very,
very strong possibility that the old man was in there.
Billionaires can't have sex unless they inject a solution made from rhinoceros horn with mixed
with tiger penis and elephant tusks and Republican brains.
What that's the rarest ingredient.
That's really,
really.
Yeah.
It's,
it's very,
well,
it's a fair,
it's a fine,
if you,
if you take a million Republicans and grind up all their brains,
you'll,
you could maybe get a line.
And that's what kind of like,
that's what Trump does every morning.
Just resume when he wakes up after two hours of semi twitching sleep and starts tweeting.
He does a line made from a million Republican brains who all,
who all donated.
They,
they gave it to him.
He didn't even have to buy it.
He,
he didn't even have to pay for it.
In fact,
they paid him to take their brains and snort it up.
I'm sorry,
but that's just the whole relationship between you and the squid bar and the people hanging
from the ceiling in the Trump Gazette.
Well,
the thing is,
I mean,
I have a lot of Republican friends,
so I don't,
I don't say this lightly.
I mean,
my,
I have relatives,
beloved relatives who probably voted for Trump.
Yeah.
And,
and,
and because I love them,
I feel like going,
well,
that was stupid.
Like it was so stupid.
I can't even begin to imagine how stupid that is.
But except for the fact that thanks to my training in subgenius land,
I'm afraid I can imagine a lot of stupid.
Right.
I mean,
even when it's even a subgenius has to call somebody else stupid.
That's bad.
Of course,
there's lots of Republicans.
Well,
there's a handful of Republican subgenius is calling me stupid.
Cause I was going,
I'm not voting for Hillary just cause she's a woman.
That's the only reason any of them voted for.
So only cause she's woman.
I heard that over and over and over again.
I was like,
no,
that's not what we were saying.
We were saying we're going to hold our nose and vote for her.
Uh,
uh,
because she's not Trump.
Right.
That was basically what it came down to.
I mean,
of course she's an odious trampire or grandpire or whatever we were talking about there.
I can't tell the difference between them.
And then there's the wee wolves.
Yeah.
Really watch out for the princess.
Wee wolves.
Oh,
that made me how they make,
they make everybody else how.
Yeah,
I guess that's the way they tell the story.
Yeah.
it's getting really,
really,
really difficult to make out which parts are against each other and which parts are
part of the same part.
And why anybody's playing the head game to make all this head game out of everything
anyway,
because it's like,
they like to write a very interesting story about the evolution of mankind on the surface
of the planet.
I hate guys like that.
I think they know it all,
everything.
And they just look back on everything and it's sociological.
I think it's a sociological experiment.
Like,
you know,
the fact that all these people are going to die and all these people are going to not
have enough money to live.
And I was just looking at the richest people in the world and I thought these idiots could
totally restore Puerto Rico with,
and they wouldn't even,
there wouldn't be any money gone.
Right.
They could solve most of the catastrophes in the world and help all kinds of people
and they wouldn't even miss it.
Why,
why,
why?
Well,
Dave,
the reason that the fact that you're asking this question that explains why you're not
rich,
dude,
you've obviously got your values completely backwards,
right?
They have no feelings of guilt or remorse when they do something bad or everything is
for self defoed.
Right?
They don't think of it as bad because it's good for them and they feel like everybody
else is just being stupid.
If they,
Or trying to do something good for someone else.
It's like, why not both?
You know, why not both?
I don't know.
That's where I'm standing from.
You know, when you're faced with what everybody else thinks is a choice between stark good and stark evil,
I tend to go, why not both?
Because you're going to end up with both anyway.
Anyway, the most evil has been done in the name of good.
Although I don't know that the reverse is true.
Do you think much great good has been done by people who are trying to be evil?
They were just bad at being evil and they accidentally did great good?
I think I've witnessed that a few times.
People that were on the verge of becoming one of the greats of the underworld and stuff like that
and it turned out to be.
It's really kind of stupid.
I knew this guy that he wanted to just be a mass serial killer,
but he never quite got around to it.
Instead, he invented cures for cancer.
And he hated himself.
He felt so let down.
He just felt that he wasted his whole life, his calling as a serial killer,
and instead had gotten, you know, obsessed over this silly hobby of curing various types of diseases.
He was so ashamed of himself that he wanted to be evil.
But he failed.
He didn't just fail a little.
He failed terribly.
He kept people alive.
That's so sad, too.
For him.
It was fine for the people.
The guy could have been evil or he could have been good,
but instead he was just a failure.
Or he failed to connect or communicate whatever the misunderstanding was.
And, boy, that's just, that's really sad.
What was his name again?
Penbroke Jaffelston.
Dr. Penbroke Jaffelston.
Yes, he wanted to be Jack the Ripper, another Jack the Ripper,
but he ended up being a Dr. Jekyll, a kindly, kindly guy.
He was Mr. Hyde screaming to get out inside that Dr. Jekyll.
I kind of know how it is.
I'm a really, really innocent.
I'm an insecure fat nerd inside a, a young fat nerd inside a seemingly confident, skinny, old hippie.
Screaming to get out.
Or whining to get out more accurately.
You know, that doesn't have, I don't have the confidence to scream.
So I'm just kind of whimpering to get out.
I want to get out and be, I quit.
I want to be an insecure fat nerd again.
Instead.
Instead of the skinny hippie.
Yeah.
I want to worry about whether people like me all day long.
That's why I think the book Neighbor World is so essential for anybody climbing the ladder to success.
That's true.
It gets you ready for real life.
It will.
I mean, it gets you ready for something.
I don't know if you'd call it real life.
Right.
There is not going to be any more real life.
Right, but that's, yeah, exactly.
That's the point of it.
It's like, it gets you ready.
It gets you ready for no real life.
The illusion.
The pure fake news, where even your breakfast is fake news.
Fake food.
I love that.
Fake everything.
That's deep, man.
It's deep.
That's an even better quote.
Put that one in there, too.
What you just said about eating fake breakfast, you know, items, chromosomes, stuff like that.
I think that was brilliant.
Because what the hell do I know?
You know, I had my brain smashed.
I had my brain smashed seven times with a shovel.
I couldn't stand up again until they took me out of the county court.
Well, of course.
Where do you think Obama got his Democrat brains?
Well, he was a...
To snort.
He was a homosexual from another planet.
And he ran a, what's it called, a parlor down where the mechanics were.
A pizza parlor, was it?
Full of child abuse?
The child sex pizza parlor scam?
I think...
I think probably George Soros.
I heard Amazon bought that.
Amazon bought that chain.
And Google, and so did George Soros.
And, yeah, all those guys were involved anyway, at least on a spurious level.
You know what I mean?
Wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
Speaking of spurious, I just discovered there's like this little odd button on my ancient RadioShack audio mix.
And I reached down and thought, where did that button come from?
And it's not a button.
It's a very strong, tiny magnet.
It is a magnet.
About the size of a screw head.
Yeah.
Yeah, screw heads.
Back of cigarette papers.
Is that what it is?
Yes.
It holds a cigarette paper thing shut?
Well, what's it doing on my electronic equipment, sapping the brains out of everything?
Oh, now I get it.
That is something that I do not know.
That's how you get high in neighborhood.
Oh.
Yeah.
At least that's what they've been telling me for the last couple weeks.
You see, it's very, very hard.
Why would there be a rolling paper closing magnet?
Because your wife is a hoarder.
Oh.
And things end up in places where they're not supposed to.
Oh, a hoarder.
God, I guess I didn't hear the whole word the first time.
Yeah, very funny.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
That's very, very funny, dear.
No wonder you...
Ha ha, I forgot to laugh.
Okay, that explains a lot.
A whole lot.
You explained that you were an hoarder, right?
Yeah, a hoarder.
What time is it?
It's a hoarder-per-sav.
You know what?
The show is over.
A hoarder-per-sav.
Just about...
What is that?
I'm a hoarder-per-sav.
A hoarder-per-sav?
Uh-huh.
I like that one.
That's pretty good.
I mean, people could take it the wrong way.
A hoarder-derp-er-sav.
Derp.
This has been Hour of Slack number 1,651.
Woo-hoo!
Recorded at Stang Ranch, although in Texas, although Lonesome Cowboy Dave is in Ashtabula.
We're connected by magic.
And friends, you can...
That...
And we'll be back next week with...
Genius.com.
That's where you can go and look at things.
Yeah, read things.
And you can read how to get an even better thing to read called Neighbor World, which
is a classic dark humor science fiction bull-dada novel by Lonesome Cowboy Dave that's 122 pages
long.
Yeah.
I mean, you know...
And so, yeah.
It's way longer.
It's way less than a dollar a page.
It's more like a dime a page.
And each page is...
A thousand.
It was worth at least a dollar's worth of yucks and grins and horror.
That's cheap, but price the price.
And thoughtfulness, stuff you can chew on.
Yeah.
With your brain.
Well, that's for male intelligence and stuff like that there.
But I thought you said it was 325,000 books.
I mean, pages long.
No.
122, I think.
You can pick one up and look at it.
Have you already been drawing animation in the borders of it?
Hey, this song that's coming up now is the Rainmakers.
Once again, I managed to work in three Rainmakers songs in a show.
Wow.
And this one I thought was really funny and poignant.
Poignant?
Yes.
Little Tiny World.
Oh, I was hanging around London and doing TV.
I was singing my heart out on the BBC.
A little girl stopped me on the street, I thought, to ask for my autograph and tell me I was hot.
She said with a twang, I thought I recognized you.
You used to pump my gas back in old KC Mizzou.
It's a little tiny world.
My head's as funny as a bee.
Everybody's chucking it up.
Come on now, this laughs on me.
Well, I went to a party with my new girl.
When we got there, we ran into four of her old boyfriends.
One was with my ex-wife.
One was with my gay brother.
One was with my masseuse.
One was with my date's mother.
See?
Everybody there had slept with everybody else.
When I heard it all, I figured I slept with myself.
It's a little tiny world.
Just like a little tiny town.
Everybody knows everybody's business.
And everybody knows my town.
Oh, yeah.
She's got a little baby girl.
A good job and a sob and a new age world.
I really can't blame her for running off with him.
I'd like to marry him too.
That is, if I liked men.
We were wedded for life.
She's stuck in my craw.
But I wish all the men would y'all to live.
To my new husband-in-law
It's a little tiny world
Man, it's as funny as it needs
Better get to hooking it up
Come on now, this laughs on me
Oh, I was stranded in paradise
On an island all alone
I had everything I wanted
But I just wanted to go home
Put an ode in a bottle
And I put in a drink
It was all recycled paper
Filed in a gradeable ink
And I waited for weeks
For the next one
So that answer I yearn
Don't throw your crap in the ocean
No deposit, no return
It's a little tiny world
Just like a little tiny town
Everybody knows everybody's business
And everybody knows what's down
Yeah, it's a little tiny world
Man, it's as funny as it needs
Better get to hooking it up
Come on now, this laughs on me
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
Yeah, it's a little tiny world
Well, and that was the Rainmakers
And now we're back
For the extra time
We got an hour done, right?
I think
Jeez
Yeah, I think we got
We did?
Yeah, we did
But see, the internet people
Get to hear another hour
Or whatever
I mean, another 20 minutes or so
Where we really talk about
How they can send 35 bucks
To the church, the subgenius
Get ordained
And get a really cool new pack
And starting off
I think probably next week
They'll have the right address
On all the pieces
All the 25 pieces of paper
In a membership pack
It will be an hour
They'll have the new dress on
Once it is fleshed out
With all of the special things
You know, Dave
Well, that was
I gave the credits
So he knows what they were
But there's
But yeah, friends
I had to change
The address
In about
50%
Of places
On printed material
Using Photoshop
And we're reprinting
All of the stuff
That goes in a subgenius membership kit
The pamphlet number one
Pamphlet number two
Your giant frameable excuse doctorate
And doctorate
There's the all inclusive divine excuse
And the doctorate of the forbidden sciences
The membership card
The 8x10 of Bob
The tree of knowledge poster
The salvation or destruction poster
The Connie Dobbs pamphlet
And all the ads
The ad sheets all have the address
Had the address wrong
As of November
In about two dozen places each
And I went in with a microscopic Photoshop
And changed the old P.O. box
To box 807
Glen Rose, Texas
And that's where you can find
Neighbor World
And the Book of the Subgenius
And everything you need
To get Slack
And all you really need though
Is the knowledge of Slack
That it exists
And that you were born with it
And have lost track of it
Now whatever your situation is
You can still have Slack
In fact if you're a subgenius
You must already have it
It's just not being sequenced
Or used properly
It hasn't
The scab has not fully broken off
Yeah you couldn't blame the user
Because then that would get you
Into a circumsuit
As an example
You know what I'm saying?
No
What's going on there
In your neck of the woods lately Dave?
I mean what's your update?
Your news report?
What's my chicken neck of the woods?
Yeah
Well let's see
It's been
The weather hasn't been terribly awfully bad
It's been the 40s a lot
I know I checked the weather
And everybody became very excited
It's 52 and stuff like that there
And then it's supposed to be in the 50s
For another couple days
And it's supposed to be cold
And most of these days
It'll be dreary and grassy
Which is really just really wonderful
For your attitude
Like the citizens of northern Ohio
Bloomy and dark
The weather and the citizens are the same
Cold and gray
Cold, gray, dreary, cloudy
I'm telling you it makes my nipples small enough
And really perky and everything
And not in a good way either
No it sounds cold
I hate it
I like sunburns
And sunshine and fresh air
Well
Funny of it too
Well I mean it's kind of a trade-off
Down here in Texas right now
As we approach Christmas
It's 70
In the 70s
Breezy, sunny most days
Which is really lucky
Because all of my stuff
Is in a non-climate controlled shed
Waiting for the new shed
To become insulated
And thus a bit more climate controlled
And it's not the winter I'm worried about
It's the summer
And that's the trade-off
For you see Dave
Although indeed the Cleveland winters are rough
And you have to shovel snow out of your driveway
The Texas summers around here are fatal
They are of a non-earth like nature
And the cold air can also be fatal
If you don't have adequate flow
And you're not using your home
Right
And
Or even you know
You need to spend a lot of money on heating gas
Well Dave now if your old furnace goes out
You can drive two hours over to Cleveland
And live in our house
Until our old furnace goes out
Because I think our furnace is from 1920
The house is from 1910
I think this one is 1912
Could be 1923
Yeah I mean right
So
You better talk to our renter about that dear
He may not want a roommate right away
Well yeah you can freeze to death
And you can also die of heat exhaustion
Why not both?
That's what I just keep saying
So for a while there
Princess we and I were
Kind of in a relationship
We had to do it this way
Even though it's made us terribly broke
We were wintering in Texas
And summering in Ohio
By necessity actually
And Princess we is going to continue to do that
But I've realized that somebody's got to hold down the fort here
Because there's
The fort is being
It's under attack constantly
By aliens
KKK members
Cowboys
Hostile natives
And we're going to have to do that next week
Wolves
Coyotes
Bears
Inflamed
Snipe birds
Hey I was
Looking at the
The Texas Wildlife Department
Website
To see when deer season ends
And
They showed snipe
Hunting season
On the official Texas website
Snipes
Snipe birds
Snipe hunting season
That's a joke isn't it
I think so
It's interesting that
The state
I know it's interesting that the state
Well the
What was good about it was they didn't
You know it was right up there with mule deer
White-tailed deer
Pheasant
Turkey
Wild turkeys
Snipe birds
You know
Just to help keep fooling the rubes
And that is kind of a Texas tradition
To just rattle off a bunch of grubs
And do all this shit
Absolutely made up lies
In such a
Nonchalant way
That people believe it
And then
You tell them
A truth that is very surprising
They think you made up a lie
That's worked for my Dad
And me
I made a career out of it
Not much of one
But it's
What I have
Yeah
And you
And you work in the news media
See
It's the same difference
Yeah
Yeah, you're spindling yourself once it gets to the artichoke,
and you're the only bunny in those yarns.
We're all just whore derpersavs, I guess.
Whore derpersavs?
Yeah, whore derpersavs.
The next show, I think, is going to have my grandsons on it some.
About two weeks ago, we recorded another grandson show,
and they're terrible because the kids are absolutely wild,
and they're child subgeniuses.
It sounds just like a subgenius radio show,
only they're really children.
They're not just adults that are very childlike and all talking at once.
They're off the hook.
Yeah, they're off the hook.
So it requires a bunch of editing.
But I'd say...
I'd say they're a little bit easier to understand than they were last year.
I did listen back to some of it.
It's hard because it's deafening.
Yeah, there's a little less screaming this year,
but not totally without screaming.
Yeah.
Yeah, Dave, we're training our own replacements.
Age 7 and age 9.
When we're age 90 and dead,
then age 20 and 24...
I'm going to be 22.
We'll be able to take over.
Or whatever they are, we'll be it.
I don't want to do the math.
Take over what?
I don't know.
My empire of a college radio show.
Well, I knew you had an imperial tazootie bag, but I didn't think you were that close
to it.
You know what I mean?
Well, but you're the special guest star of the empire.
Oh, yeah.
You're the imperial jester.
Yeah.
I don't want to forget that because you owe me $24, remember?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'm going to have to get that.
I still...
Actually, I do have to calculate the Neighbor World stuff.
Calculator, bling, bling, ding, ding, bling.
Yeah, I bet you'd rather have me do that sooner than later.
Why not both?
I'll calculate it soon, but not send it to you until later.
Much, much later.
How's that?
That's another very, very old put-off, the substantialized jocular version.
It's not funny.
And I could also, like most publishers, I could say, well, I'm sorry we only sold 24
copies in the whole last two months.
Unfortunately, that might well be true.
It's kind of sad how many subgeniuses have not been mailed one of those by me.
I know everyone who hasn't bought a copy of Neighbor World.
Shame on you.
I think they were liking it.
It's mostly...
Most of y'all.
I'd say it's about 99.9%.
I understand why they can't read.
They haven't read a novel since they lied about doing so in high school.
We have at least one friend that's proud of not reading.
Well, he's a Republican.
That goes with the territory.
I'm proud of being a Republican.
They're against reading.
They don't...
You know, they're trying to shut down these schools that teach reading.
Know what I'm saying?
No.
Unfortunately.
So, I hate to get political about it and so divisive, but it's...
They started it.
Unfortunately, it is true.
They did start...
No, no.
Nuh-uh.
You are.
Okay, now look, kids.
If you keep this up, I'm going to have to get in the backseat with you and you don't
want that because I'm driving.
Damn, kids.
That way.
You're the best.
Guys, you're on the old right there.
I like that one.
Damn, kids.
Is that a really...
I think you've actually tried and failed at it.
No, you quiet down you kids or I'm going to have to slap you naked and hide your clothes.
Sterno overheard one redneck say that to another redneck in their colorful language.
Both of those.
Not like mine.
Both of those or just the second one?
Always both.
I'm not talking about the weird either.
the cerebral hemorrhages or any of the
misqualifications over the last
few years, let's let bygones
be bygones.
I just...
They're going bye-bye. That's why we can't do it.
They're gone. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
That's my
Boris Karloff imitation.
Well, in the first movie.
That's about all he did.
Yeah, that's right.
He was a thug guy,
right?
But he kept on screwing it up and made him
look like Boris Karloff.
You're thinking of the Black Cat, I think.
No, I'm thinking
of Arsenic and Old Lake where
Boris Karloff played
the brother. Well, probably both.
Played the evil brother.
Played Clark Kent, not Clark Kent.
Stephanie Davis.
What's her name? Boris Karloff as
Superman.
No, I meant Corny Grunt. That's my joke
for Gary Grant.
Look, up in the sky.
Well, Dave, I think we're starting
to wind down here.
Winding and winding.
I can't...
The Burning Man music is getting louder
in the background. You can't hear it.
I'm starting to yearn for
Mel Torme. I think there's a problem
here.
Oh, now I hear the buzz.
I turned off the music
and I hear Dave's buzz.
I like your buzz, Dave.
Can I come over to your house
and rub that little round buzz of yours?
Listen to it.
Kind of halting and stuttering.
That's a proud little buzz.
It didn't go away this time.
It's coming and going.
It's very intermittent.
It goes when you talk and then it comes back
when you stop talking.
Well, I hope I didn't buzz up
the entire occupancy.
No, no.
That's why the background music is there.
Besides, like I said, there's ambient noise
in Tarzan's
radio station.
I think when we started...
No, we don't have the heat on, do we?
We don't have anything on.
It's just air noise.
These crappy microphones and the fact that we're in a
giant,
one really big barn-sized
room.
Luckily, there's big curtains
right near us that help
keep the sound from being
flat.
Or bouncy or something.
I don't know.
Is there an echo in here?
Here, here, here, here.
Boy, there sure is.
There is a buzz now.
Listen to that buzz.
It's louder than the buzz in my brain.
I don't think...
Really?
You're lucky, then.
It's not nearly as loud as the buzz in my brain.
I can barely distinguish which is my brain
and which is your buzz.
My brain
is louder than your brain's buzz.
And then there's the
tinnitus or tinnitus
or tinnitus.
That's on the high end.
This is in the mid-range, dude.
That's a 60-cycle
hum, I think.
It's just the sound of electricity
in a bad wire
that moves
every time you breathe.
One of my favorite things.
So, yeah.
Welcome to the future, folks.
Well, you're on the landline, though.
Your phone could be worse.
You could be on a...
on a cell phone.
Those are often way worse.
The buzz is actually not as bad
as a cell phone that's crackling
and breaking up.
And when it's gone,
it sounds absolutely wonderful.
Yeah.
It does.
Well, yeah, it does, actually.
But it's not gone.
Much every blue moon.
Well, one of these days...
One of these days,
you'll be in a different house
with a different phone.
Right.
And you might ask yourself,
what is this beautiful house?
What is this beautiful room?
We just saw the Trump version of that.
God, that was fucking...
Oh, we're making a radio show.
Sorry.
The Trump version?
My son sent us a link
that some brilliant person
had made a video
where they took that
Talking Heads song
and put Trump's head
on David Byrne,
but they replaced
all of the lyrics
with Trump saying
each individual word.
So it would cut to...
Give me a typical sample lyric
from that song.
And you may ask yourself,
well, each of those words,
and would be him saying
and at one speech.
You would be him saying
you at another speech.
Ask yourself would be another speech.
So it was all Trump's voice.
Right.
Perfectly matched to the song,
to the original song.
And sampled well and nice, eh?
It was an editing tour de force,
you might say.
It was.
And a coup de grace
at the same time.
What's the name of it on YouTube?
I don't remember.
I don't know.
Just Trump Talking Head.
You would Google...
Water flowing down...
You would Google
Trump Talking Head song.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, the algorithms will know.
Before you even finish typing it,
they'll know what you want to know
because so many other people
already typed that in.
Water flowing underground.
Yes, that song.
Letting the days go by.
That song.
I never did have that album.
I really wasn't that into talking about it.
Same as it ever was.
I had dinner with that band once.
But the whole time I was like,
I didn't actually ever even have
a bootleg tape.
I did have a bootleg tape of their album.
They were for the rich office worker intellectuals.
I guess I was really into Devo and Elvis Costello,
but they didn't seem art school.
And to me, Talking Heads was like art school guys.
Or people.
Did you see them perform live?
I did.
I did actually.
And in fact, because there was a time there,
David Byrne was a...
I was interested in subgenius
and he was going to have a subgenius scene
in that movie of his, True Stories.
And I drove him around and hung out.
Got ignored by him and Steve Tobolowsky
while they discussed the symbolism of the script.
And that was where I started thinking,
what?
People actually make movies where they talk about
what stuff symbolizes?
Oh, give me a break.
Only critics think that way.
But no, they were really good.
The little girl in the white dress,
symbolizes purity or something.
I was going, what the?
What the?
Look at your type of butter.
Did they learn how to do that in art school or something?
I mean, that's what you tell the press
when you're at your premiere.
Oh, speaking of premieres,
my son's movie has had a sort of a premiere.
It's about to have an LA premiere
that's going to be much bigger.
It was at the Houston International Film Festival,
but that turned out to be not a very, very big one.
It was a very big film festival.
But the movie is called Solver,
and the trailer is out.
And Reverend Bleepo Abernathy did the sound sweetening on it,
which makes it sound really professional.
And my son directed it, so it is really professional.
It was a real good little murder mystery.
Cool.
With a little sci-fi twist at the very end.
It's the cheapest end of the world,
mind control movie ever.
It's only got about eight people in it.
And only four of them have very much dialogue.
But it is clever.
Oh, yeah, it's clever.
It's tricky.
Because it's about puzzles.
It's about solving puzzles.
And apparently their campaign, their advertising campaign,
they have a website where you go and do puzzles,
to solve solver type puzzles.
And that's the first thing that comes to mind.
But I've got enough trouble trying to figure out
how to dig myself out of that hole in No Man's Sky.
My video game character fell into a hole in a planet,
and he can't get out.
He started trying to dig his way out with his laser blaster,
and it all just sort of caved in on him.
And now he's stuck.
I may have to start the game over, if I can't get out.
It's like, it's an existential dilemma.
That you came up with.
No, it's an accident.
This game, I don't know if it's a glitch or a feature,
but my character got himself into a situation
he can't get out of using, in the physics of this
completely made up world.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Stuck in a damn hole.
He went into a mine.
Or a cave.
And he actually did fall into a hole.
And he thought, but it was full of jewels.
So he thought, oh, I'm gonna start mining my way along here.
Blasting out all this jewels with my blaster.
But it kind of backfired.
He got away from it.
There's no light down there, except from the blaster.
And now he can't find his way out.
And he's me.
So I'm, you know, in one of my other lives,
I've got a real bad problem.
In most of my other lives, I'm fine.
I can drive real fast.
And one of my lives, I'm a race car driver in the future.
And I can get killed over and over and over again.
But still drive real fast.
And comes right back to life.
Yeah.
And of course, in several of my other lives,
I hunt monsters.
And I'm very good at that, actually.
Well, I'm no pro, but I'm a good amateur.
And I don't play Grand Theft Auto much anymore,
but I was a criminal in that.
And...
That's what most people were, yeah.
In some games, I'm a beautiful, skinny girl.
Leaping and hopping and slicing heads off zombies.
So feminine.
I think you're a sick individual.
No, I'm just a normal American playing video games.
No, I agree with that, Dave.
That's sick.
Zombie stuff is sick.
I hate all the zombie stuff.
You don't like walkers?
No.
Our dog's a walker.
I know, but I don't like any of that.
We walk all the time.
We're walkers.
No, I don't like any of that zombie, dead zombie.
If we were living dead walking people with a walker,
we'd be walker, walker, walkers.
I don't like any of it.
We walk a walker dog.
And if we were zombies,
we'd be walker, walker, walkers.
We're walker, walkers.
That sounded like a funny joke.
We walk, walk, walker.
Well, that sounds pretty stupid.
We should probably stop recording.
Yeah, it certainly does.
Let's see how long, wow.
Let's just say 50, 52 minutes.
So that's another 20 minutes after the approved hour long.
And we're just all, it sounds just like
a damn phone conversation.
I don't know what it is.
There's no music behind it and it's buzzing.
No.
Yeah, it's buzzy.
No music.
But who cares?
It's the internet.
Yeah, who cares?
They can turn it off after the hour, you know.
So, well, my back hurts too.
I get claustrophobic after a while here.
And yeah, claustrophobic, oh, because having to wear the headphones?
I guess or something.
Well, yeah, it is.
It's so.
It's not comfortable like the radio station.
It's cramped.
We're at a kind of a small table.
And not only is the table small to begin with,
it's made even smaller by a giant reel-to-reel deck
that I've got set up here just because it looks cool.
My dog's eyes are rolling up in his head.
It doesn't work.
This reel-to-reel deck, I need to repair it.
It's partly out to remind me to try to repair it someday.
But mainly it just makes Tarzan feel like he's a good guy.
Tarzan's radio station looked like a radio station.
You know.
Why do you call it Tarzan's radio station?
Because it was developed for campgrounds.
And mostly it gets used on picnic tables
surrounded by rustic wooden structures.
And it's held together by snot and scotch tape.
It's the cheapest old stuff.
You know how your phone buzzes and is crappy?
Well, Tarzan's radio station was made...
It's like Tarzan's treehouse.
Or the Little Rascals.
It could just as easily be called the Little Rascals radio station.
With the S backwards, yeah.
I've got a quartz crystal and a tin can.
We can make radio.
I've got these instructions that I downloaded
from Captain Future radio show.
Well, I like that idea too.
But yeah, it's Tarzan's radio station
because it's like Tarzan's house.
It's like something Tarzan would build.
Or maybe the professor on Gilligan's Island.
You know, he'd make a station,
a radio transmitter out of the boat's spark plugs
and a coconut.
Some shells.
And Mary Ann's earrings.
Now, you know,
a perennial question on the internet
that gets asked a lot is,
who do you go for?
Mary Ann or Ginger?
I like both actually, I must say.
Well, and here's the really sad thing about that.
They're leaving out Mrs. Howell
who, frankly, is unbelievably rich.
And she's pretty hot for a grandma age person.
I mean, I'd hit that.
Not when I was 12 years old
and Gilligan's Island was on.
I didn't, you know, she looked like a grandma.
Well, I look like a grandpa.
So, after you get rescued,
who do you want to be hanging with?
The vapid, idiotic movie star?
The nice but not very glamorous Mary Ann?
Or the lady with a billion dollars?
After her settlement with,
from Thurston Howell III?
I think I'd rather be with Don Knotts
and Mayberry R.F.D.
Because those guys are all real heterosexuals
and criminals and stuff.
Well, I'd rather be Don Knotts
and the love god.
He was, in that movie,
he's this nebbish,
nerd birdwatcher
who is tricked by publishers
into acting as a sort of a front man,
Hugh Hefner.
It's like, what if Hugh Hefner
was really an unwilling nerd
who didn't want to do any of this stuff
and he's forced to live this Hefner lifestyle?
And it was Don Knotts.
It's actually a really funny movie.
Yeah.
And I learned something about our subgenius movie.
I realized,
I was taught by watching the love god
that you gotta have a montage.
And that we can get through a whole bunch,
we can just cut out a bunch of dialogue
by having a good visual montage
with the right song.
Yeah.
That's what Don Knotts did.
So if it's good enough for Don Knotts,
hell, it's good enough for any subgenius movie.
Yeah.
So, well, Dave, we should go.
Well, have a pleasant afternoon.
I actually have to get up early in the morning.
The dog wakes us up at eight o'clock on the dot.
Well, I have to go frop up and go to the bathroom.
Well, yeah.
Well, of course.
Yeah, why not both?
Well, believe me, that's part of the plan.
Yeah, there's gonna be shit involved no matter what.
Good shit.
Yeah.
We got that right squirin'.
Okay, Dave.
Okay, Stang.
Well, good night.
See you, Dave.
Good night.
See ya.
Let's see.
How do I do this nicely?
Okay, he hung up.
There's the music.
It's still there in the background.
The dog is asleep.
Well, I'll do it.
Okay, yeah.
So, I guess I'm gonna have to catch up with Dave next time.
Yeah.