The following broadcast is a subgenius production.
This is a subgenius production.
The answer.
Yes, it's a new day.
It's a new day in Riyadh.
It's a new day in Baghdad.
The sun is rising over the desert.
It's a new day and the sun rays are shining red, white, and blue.
All over the world.
There's swirling sands below Basra.
A jackal howls.
Oh, wait a minute. He's on his way to the mall.
Soon the entire planet will be covered in drop cloth and duct tape.
Yes.
All will be safe.
We will tape up every board, every window.
What about?
That is about shaving yourself for five hours until you suffocate to death.
That's John Ashcroft's idea of a subgenius production.
Silly joke.
They're making jokes now, Chaz.
Guys, that's what's going on today.
Really?
They're tickling our funny boners.
They're trying to get us to split our, you know, our corpus callosum.
Duct tape.
And there's a big split between our brain hemispheres.
I'm glad to hear that.
They want to fight.
Duct tape and cellophane wrap.
Because they were...
Well, in some places, there's some clubs in New York City where you have to pay extra for that treatment.
To have your corpus callosum split?
To have your hemispheres?
No, the duct tape and saran wrap treatment.
Well, usually it results in a hemispheric split.
If it's a joke...
Man, look at all the Valentine's stuff.
They actually managed to scare me that maybe they weren't just playing good cop, bad cop, and it was only bad cops.
I think what they're playing is retarded cop, sleeping cop.
And you're sitting in a cell by yourself going,
Get me out of here!
You!
And then the crazy cops come in and he goes,
And the whole time you're stuck in the same cell with lonesome cowboy Dave.
Or Mr.
Guillotine.
Yeah.
Or Chuckie Chicken Cheese.
Or one of those other strange people that appear.
Or Duke the Trucker.
Well, he's been outlawed.
He's been banned.
Along with a bunch of other malcontents that are wiping up the airwaves with their hot sauce and sweat.
I think it's the media's behind all of it.
I think that whole thing was a hoax.
I think that the Twin Towers falling down...
They're still there.
That was a hoax.
They are still there.
It was all a hoax.
It's an optical illusion.
It was an optical illusion actually.
Caused by a...
What's the name of the really, really good Vegas magician?
The guy that made the Grand Canyon disappear?
Not Karnak.
What's...
Carbuncle?
Merlin.
No, no, no.
This is like a real...
This is like a Vegas guy.
He's got like...
He's got a twin sister or something that wears a bikini and, you know, like twirls the scimitars.
No, that's the other guy.
The other magician.
The disappear with the disappear.
Well, anyway, it's supposed to be a big success, but I don't think anybody's even aware of what's going on.
Who?
Osama was?
No.
He was one of the bootleg...
Have you guys got the new bootleg terrorist type?
No, but I've got tapes.
My legs taped together.
I've got 20 different translations for it.
Here they come.
Comes on our first airborne.
And only if we were all Native Americans too.
We'd not only win the war, but we'd also win back...
The country which was taken from us so many years ago.
White eyes, you will now return what is ours.
You with your forked tongues and your fig-shaped feet and your funny little goat ears.
Go back to Europe where you came from.
And have a nice day.
And here come the baton twirlers that headed their first 101st airborne.
The Screaming Eagle Templates, as they're called.
Look at those dresses.
That's absolutely crazy.
What they could do with those flaming batons.
And look at what if we're actually juggling a flamethrower.
And her teeth exposed to the wind.
And the sand.
And the dust.
And the eternal heat.
What do those smoke signals say over there, Lieutenant?
They say you better not talk about the Commander-in-Chief or you're going to do three to life for talking nasty.
Have you heard that?
The recent?
What did you say?
Two things that are too silly.
That aren't, you know, that are on the edge of funny and nasty about President Hex.
You could be put in jail for three years like a person in North Dakota was for saying that.
Now, I'm disclaiming myself from saying this.
Some guy said...
They get down on our music, man.
They say, hey, man, turn that down.
But did they ever listen to the words?
Yeah, really.
Did they ever listen to the words, man?
When you climb into that Subaru vacuum cleaner at five miles an hour, think who it ain't.
Me.
You're no Senator's son.
There's no silver spoon stuck in your colostomy bag.
You're free as the wind, but only as far as those stretched-out clothes will take you because you're a po-boy.
A po-po-po-boy.
So, what are them poor guys, eh?
Line up for sandwiches, children.
We're going to take care of your knees and your elbows and your...
The braces on your...
Your head.
And also the wounds that you've incurred over your...
Things are getting a little bit paranoid around my wounds.
I've heard about a website that was closed down by cyber attacks.
It was specialized in war protest-type news.
Oh, so they were hacked.
Well, they were more like flooded by some bot with so much stuff that basically they were knocked off the air by...
It must have been a Justice Department bot.
They got the bots.
Yeah.
You know, it could be anybody.
But, like, I was...
I saw this hilarious little cut-up of a State of the Union speech on the Internet.
I thought, well, I'm going to download this down from that and use it on our Slack.
Princess Wee said, don't.
Don't do it.
Don't download it.
It's not funny enough.
There's code in it.
No, I'm afraid they'll come and get you.
They're watching you through the screen.
They know.
Now, that's not illegal.
Group of complaints.
Finally, this is a group of social criminals.
These big...
People in the space program.
Nassholes, I call them.
In case you haven't heard, the latest disaster for the rest of the universe is that the United States is going to go to Mars.
Okay?
Oh, yeah.
There's a bigger disaster that happened.
We lost seven great American heroes.
We're about to lose seven million great American heroes entitled to most of Seattle.
Seattle.
Oh, you guys are worried about those North Korean nuclear weapons hitting the West Coast, right?
You're not worried about Kim Jong-un?
Everybody on the East Coast is paranoid about germ bombs and dirty bombs being set off in their harbors.
The nation is hacked neatly in half like a filleted steak waiting to be grilled.
On the Pacific Rim, they're giving them the Korean Rim job.
And, of course, on the Eastern Seaboard, they're ready to board the planes with Iraqi dissidentals.
And other dissidentals.
I know.
Well, it does make me more eager to say, newcomer!
You know, just because.
Well.
I mean, it works that way.
I think a lot of people in your position, you know, as a standing, necrobiotic, comic, paraplegic.
As someone too old to be drafted.
Too young to be escorted from the building.
Not living in Los Angeles or New York or Washington, D.C.
Not literally languid enough to be free-festered.
You have to wait for the biopsy.
You have to wait for the biosphere to increase.
And you're going to start expanding.
Actually, you know, their joke did start scaring me.
The other night when the Northern came in, the wind was whistling and howling outside.
We don't call it a Northern.
Like a crazy, well, Blue Northern.
That's what you guys call it.
Yeah, right.
Well, it was scary.
And I was laying in bed hearing that wind and thinking about the duct tape.
And my kid in L.A. and my other kid in Dallas.
Without enough duct tape.
Cleveland.
Nobody.
This would be an embarrassing place.
You would attack.
Yes, it would.
It would.
It's an embarrassing place to be attacked in.
You're pretty safe here in Cleveland.
I would think so.
Way down low on the list.
Destroy the booming steel industry or something.
Right.
And the old BPO.
They moved.
That would have been a target.
Yeah, because they're just cranking out tanks down there in the flats.
Tanks upon M1 tanks are rolling out of the flats by the dozen.
Is that what that smell is?
Every day.
Yeah.
Steel industry is so vital here.
We're making a patch.
Blackhawks.
This is the place to be if you want to blow up another country.
I mean, if you want to get into the blowing up business.
If you can take over Cleveland.
With impunity.
If you can.
Yeah, that's.
It's like in the 50s, like the music industry.
If you can, you know, you're successful in Cleveland.
Yeah, today it's.
If you can take over Cleveland, you've got it.
You've got the whole country.
Well, now.
Just got to get Cleveland.
Couldn't a bunch of, like, ice soldiers just stomp across the lake?
Blue ice soldiers?
They don't have those anymore.
Canadians.
Everyone freezes up.
Well, they are.
They are socialists.
And as a consequence of being socialists, they are quite crisp or, you know, tensile.
You know, like a frozen thing.
Like Frosty the Snowman.
Yeah, you see them skittering across the lake like so many Canadian soldiers.
Yeah.
藍洛
Obi-Wan.
Um.
Bowl.
A.
Thank you.
That's all for now.
That's all we know.
This is the end.
A place for us
Somewhere
Hold my hand
And I'll take you there
And we'll have
We'll have
Somewhere
There's a place for us
There is a time for us
Somewhere
Hold my hand
And I'll take you there
Sit down
Ooh
Ah
sworn to life
and and
Closedcia
annu
annua
annun
This is plain
Affordable
You change
Thank you.
Now I'm back to change your mind
Now I'm moving right in time
In a world that's turned on time
I see what's going on behind my back
I'm a people boy
I'm a disco dancer
And I keep dancing on and on
I'm a people boy
Oh no
I'm a disco dancer, baby
But I think that something's wrong
I'm a people boy
Oh no
I've been sleeping twenty years or more
I remember that time ago
Now I'm back to change your mind
Now I'm moving right in time
In a world that's turned on time
I see what's going on behind my back
I'm a people boy
Oh yeah
Somewhere with Deebo
Dear friends
Ah, loved soldiers
Oh no
We're so wrongfully outnumbered
Ah, we would like to wrongfully remind you of the legendary snacks being produced in your mind right now as the Fluffing Box is being sold to the United States.
The
boats includes
Do most of the events on Cotton College must include sources and their reports on the
sounds.
The
Amy films amazing
I see you
Please know that the
called the
What a laugh.
That was the last time they took a peaceful breath of air for six years.
The Pentagon and a bunch of other quack-o-whack-o of the Hordegard clique
decided they were going to go the full distance.
Yeah, that's right.
Snowshoes and onions for the whole pack.
And we're not talking about Cub Scouts.
We're talking about maulers, murderers, midgets, people without eyes.
We're talking about the scum of humanity.
Humanity.
Yeah.
The fighting.
That's who we're looking for, kids.
So line up and join up today.
The Church of the Subgenius is looking for...
Mental soldiers.
I want to be a soldier. I'm wax.
I'm not a real man.
Be what you want.
Be all that you can be
and much, much more
that you will never be.
You can be what you want with...
Because it's a church of love.
These are love soldiers, baby.
The soldiers have...
They got their guns and holsters
all oiled up
and ready.
Ready for the sacred fight.
That holy battle.
It's just a kiss away, baby.
It's just a kiss away.
Just a kiss away.
And I'd like to explain to you now
how the Patriot Act,
or not the Patriot Act, I'm sorry,
the Homeland Security Act,
it works in its full efficacy.
To understand well,
first take the scotch tape
right here in your hands.
Place the top of the scotch tape tube
right below your nostrils.
Pull the scotch tape down over your mouth.
Now, you're not leaving out the plastic wrap
that goes over your mouth.
No, no.
That part out of there.
And then after you've taped over your mouth...
You're going to express yourself freely.
To prevent expression
and poisonous mass weapons of destruction.
Also thought crimes.
Then get your duct tape and your drop cloth
and cover the nose orifice
to protect your lungs.
And if you'll cover up your nose and mouth,
eyes and ears completely,
then you can save
a lot of money on drops
that don't have to do your windows or doors.
You won't think this is so funny
when that botchoo toxin,
plague, smallpox,
radiation germ comes
wafting in down your chimney.
You didn't board up your chimney, did you?
No, you forgot.
You took the boards out
because you thought Sandy Claus was coming.
Well, Sandy Claus might be coming, all right.
He might be coming with something
like you don't want.
He might be coming with something worse
than a bucket full of coals and switches, my friend.
Sandy Claus.
He's coming with the promise of heaven.
He knows the combination of your locker, baby.
I'd like to remind all of the quality people
with the steps you need to get, um, you know, uh...
I'm sorry.
He's a mean banjo picker, too.
Just listen to him.
Make sure his socks are neatly strapped
to the inseam of the butler's front.
Wow.
Make sure the socks are high enough
to ward off any sort of toxic elements.
Make sure the bio-tox...
Thank you.
Put your head between your knees
and kiss your knees goodbye.
You said that politically correctly, my friend.
They used to say that to us in fourth grade.
Yes.
During the, um, duck and cover.
As the way to protect yourself
from, uh, nuclear blasts.
That was the way we'd worship.
You're gonna die!
You're gonna die in the hot, cold war, babies.
So put your head between your knees
and kiss your little tokers goodbye.
Because you're going to heaven.
You're gonna see Jesus.
When those communist mamas...
That's when you're gonna see Jesus.
Of course, I was raised in Fort Worth, so...
They may not do that in the public schools here.
I don't know.
Mind you, Stan, I...
I was raised in Fort Worth in the 90s.
I was raised in the 50s.
Well, that was at least...
A little different from the...
One of the implants you were born and raised in.
How is it different?
And that...
Well, I'm telling you,
you had a number of overlays, we call them,
in your psychic programming.
And so you think that one of them
had to do with what was the last town
you mentioned, El Paso Auto?
Uh, Hunchkiss.
Hunchkiss Valley?
Where did you say you attended grade school?
We all had to hide under our desks
and put newspapers in front of our eyes.
Ah, no, but you were hiding under an assumed identity
while the other children were hiding under their desks
so neatly.
And so full of slack.
I was doing both.
I was good boy.
Well, you were as good as you could be
in considering the wavelength.
When I kissed my ass goodbye,
I Frenched it, baby.
Oh, and you were known for it?
Did I just say that?
Yeah, of course you said it.
And you meant it, too.
You, you...
I was just wishful thinking.
You know, I've seen dogs do that.
And you always, you go,
why would I wish I could do that?
Well, that's what they say about Turks.
You know, when the dog snaps and barks at you.
That dog knows it's going to become soup real soon.
Now, see, that music makes me want to go fight
or send somebody else to go fight in my place.
Some young, expendable, nice person.
Makes me want to play lacrosse.
Some sucker.
Some unicorn.
Tomatoes.
Dance.
Oh, man.
Go swimming for catfish.
Bite myself.
And cure the wrath of dobs.
Is this a segue into a more cerebral part of the,
uh...
thing?
Before this.
The song about, uh, necrophilia?
No, a secret necrophilia.
It's not overt.
It's real overt, Dave.
Yeah, yeah, it is kind of overt.
It's totally overt.
It's about...
Condemn arise.
Yeah, I mean, it's, it's...
I can almost smell it.
Yeah, there, you know, there are kosher distinctions
between putting your milk in your cheese
and your rotting fly shig in your same refrigerator.
It reminds me of an old poem I used to not say on this show.
You used to say it frequently.
It was an old lash from what, what was, where was it from?
I met an old gal in the grave here.
I met an old gal in the grave.
Yeah, but we won't go into that.
Al, let's just listen to Alice for a second.
I never even knew you're now rotting the face.
While friends and lovers mourn your silly grave.
I have other uses for you, darling.
The company was piling on all kinds of defensive...
What do you think?
Well, I mean, um...
Nor of dungeons to ourselves.
I, I ask you, I mean, what do you think?
What do you think?
I mean...
Poison pills, gold disparages.
I ask you, I mean...
Who name it?
How do you, what do you, should we go in?
Should we go in?
Shh!
Let us have faith.
So...
That right makes might.
Saddam's much vaunted berms.
So, what?
Dang it, this thing doesn't work better than that.
And in that faith...
Saddam!
Let us to the end.
Fool!
Ah, they have to do our duty.
They're starting to get it.
I don't understand.
It's all I'm taking from you.
Get back here!
Yes, you're a kind of slanderer!
Saddam's court rapist.
Hey, shut up!
Fool!
I take care of all his raping.
But, uh, make sure...
Dr. Drummond, don't tell me you believe that silly propaganda about Saddam Hussein's court rapist.
Yes, I am a court rapist.
Oh, you are?
Oh, well.
Well, tell us more about, uh...
Uh...
This handsome Mr. Saddam Hussein.
He's on the tips of everyone's tongues.
He's being talked about in the highest social circles these days.
Old Saddam.
I call him Saddam.
Was a mighty man.
A mighty butcher.
But he went crazy that one time.
Took too much acid.
Is that what it was?
Yeah.
Too much acid.
You know, too much acid has been the downfall of many saintly worlds.
World leaders.
And now he's just a crazy mockery of a man.
These obstacles only fueled my big dick passion to win.
I remember when that happened to Ford.
Yeah, that's true.
Pull it out of your...
When Ford started doing too much acid...
What was it, Gary?
I would own that company.
Where's Gary?
It seems like sooner or later every president ends up doing too much acid.
Why?
I don't know.
Because it feels good.
Because they like to.
Yeah, people like to get high.
So, watch.
Gary wishes he was high.
So, where's the caller?
And the stretch caller.
Where's the caller?
Hello, caller.
Is that you?
Does it work if I punch it over here?
I'm going to agree with you on the president taking action.
I mean, look at a code statement.
I always look doped out on something.
Jesus Christ.
What is he, chopped up on coke?
When I was asked whether we would accept bids in the 600 to 700 million range...
Is that Ronald Reagan?
Oh, God.
I answered...
Man, the guy had a screw loose there, man.
That's a price we wouldn't even begin to be interested in.
Oh, the caller seems to feel that our country is going downhill and the presidents behave
as if they're going downhill.
Oh, they look like them.
They look like them.
Oh, but they're like that.
Callers, what do you have to say about this truly original and startlingly original observation?
That's bad.
Good thinking.
Next.
That's bad.
The country going downhill.
Could this be?
I've never heard such a suggestion.
Your country is going downhill for 15 minutes at a time.
Oh, but that's good.
That's good.
Well, actually, the country goes downhill for about 15 minutes and then it goes up for
a while.
It even kind of gets up and down, up and down.
Sometimes it goes uphill for a long time.
Then it goes rushing down, speeding, out of control.
And then sometimes it'll take a left turn right in the middle when you think it's going
to go straight.
It takes a crazy left turn.
Casey Jones at the wheel of our country.
Calls it a Louie.
Says hook a Louie.
Casey Jones, the fastest train racer of all time.
And he was...
Little people, long people think that he's driving.
He's driving.
He's at the helm of Spaceship America.
Casey Jones is taking us in orbit around the moon and back.
Who says this country's going to hell in a handbasket?
Hell.
We're going to the moon and back.
You're going to the moon, baby.
We're going to the free stop in Hooterville.
The moon, the future in Hooterville.
That's American's destination.
We need to learn old devil the words.
We'll finally get to go to college.
And that's the way it was with Puzzling Evidence, Dr. Philodrumm...
Don Joyce of Negative Land and that show, Over the Edge, which combined with the Puzzling
Evidence show and Michael Pepe, Bishop Joey, Gary Gabrogfran, and of course, as always,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Chaz Smith, Princess Wiardo, and yours truly, Reverend Ivan the
Lone Stang, all right now and back then.
Oil.
Covered in oil.
Lapping it up.
Got to get that Lincoln.
Man, that's pretty cool.
Lincoln now has a SUV.
It's really big.
I thought he was dead.
Didn't they shoot that guy at the Ford Theater?
No.
I'm still alive.
That's the closest he ever got to a car was...
Oh yeah, a Lincoln was a Ford, wasn't it?
Boy, it gets confusing, doesn't it?
I know.
It's pretty much the same as the way all the other...
They began the cloning experience...
I drive a booth myself.
They began the cloning experience back in 1957.
And one of the first things they did was they made a bunch of Lincoln clones.
Well, they also cloned Mussolini also.
And they also...
What's the guy who came up with the term?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
He was a youngster.
There was a warehouse full of Hitler's brains in South America.
Yeah, but they can't find the right cranial snap.
It's the plaster end, because they vary in size.
All they can say is, mock schnell, mock schnell, mock schnell, mock schnell, our bite-mocked
fries.
Ridiculous.
And how would he know if our bite-mocked fry?
You know what I mean?
As far as he knew, our bite-mocked French fries.
I mean, unfortunately, a lot of people were French fried because of that phrase.
But I don't think it was old Adolf Hitler's fault.
No.
But he was a good-hearted guy, basically, wasn't he?
Oh, he was an artist.
But he was a frustrated artist.
Well, you know, they can be pretty moody, can't they?
Hey, man, what happens when they don't make their million bucks before the age of 25?
When somebody wipes their derriere on your best of show?
He tried to sell his land.
I hate that Norwegian.
He was a perfectly good landscape painter.
He couldn't sell them.
But, you know, hey, anybody would get a little bit bent out of shape over something like
that.
He wants people to know that he's a good artist.
And穗 in the Ellyphon Tower stallions as it depuated by in Vienna.
It was a beautiful sight.
And everybody, everybody everywhere knew that someday he was going to go somewhere special.
Maybe Jamaica.
Reminds me of my good friend Papa Duvalier.
And Joey Ramone.
Oh, what a little boat they went out to the silver sea in.
In Haiti.
Haiti was a—Bob used to do a lot of business with the Haitians.
Yeah, he threw the looking gas.
They called old Bob.
You could get a lot of good fetus brain tic.
issue there. Now, that was a man.
No questions asked. None of this silly paperwork.
No, no. He had the layered
personalities. Whatever you want, that's the
one that's there. Bob the architect.
Bob the smoker of
royal herbs. Bob the
shoeshine salesman. Finally,
when Papa Bob was dethroned in Haiti,
we had to go to
China. But we still got
a lot of dolls. We still got a lot
of Bob Voodoo dolls with a lot of pins
to sell.
I mean, I thought we did.
I don't know. Maybe we didn't.
We sold out.
Bob Voodoo dolls were
very popular during the last war.
The war with Mars. You remember,
don't you? Yeah, and the other, that was the
layered personality, 52.
But I think we
fought Mars to a draw in that layer, didn't we?
Yeah, well, we're gonna go back.
We'll be back. We'll be back.
We'll show those rotten
sticking Martians control our nuclear
beer. We will be back.
All the Martians. We will be back.
We will be back.
We're getting our beer!
I don't want to do no beer!
We can't get to the
building, man.
Even the Jamaican Martians
must all be wiped out.
That is, we can find them on.
Well, you can't exactly kill them because they're not
exactly alive. But we need the oil,
too, for the robots to run the robot
soldiers. We need the Western oil.
We need the pubic hairs in the
arch. Our soldiers will
go all rusty.
We've got them not going to die.
We're not going to die.
We're all going to die.
May their swords never grow
the rust that lands
them here in Happlegate
Harbor, next to the
Mayboat Parade, as the flag
shines brightly.
A thousand, thousand
gallons of water have
churned by this magical spot
and still people come
to watch, to sing a song
and play the ukulele,
and to dream of those magic,
Days before they were transformed.
Ah, man, I'm not about ready to get up yet.
It's still freezing out there.
So cold.
I wait for the springtime.
I wait for March 25.
25.
That's the number on your shorts.
That's your cue card.
That's the number on your wrist.
That's your number in line.
Very, uh, you must have been first in line for the camps.
Number 25.
I tattooed on my neck, too.
Look at this.
I have a little tiger underneath.
Can you see it?
We like punctuality in our camp inmates.
Well, you want some puncture marks?
If you look on the other side there.
Oh, that's very good.
I see you've been tortured.
Well, I did it myself.
Did that happen?
Did you do that here at this camp?
Or at the last camp you've had?
I've done it at every camp.
Yes, every camp I've been to, I have saved them the work.
Do the guards suck your blood from the back of the wounds?
No, they videotape.
They have some...
Of the prisoners, of course.
The other, your fellow.
Your fellows, of course.
Well, they're on the front row.
But the archdiocese keeps a very, very close watch
on what I do in between acts.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, they love to rip off subgenius show business ideas.
Oh, they love to rip everything off of it.
They do.
They whip their clothes off and they grovel in the oil
because they have filthy love and unpleasant love.
That's why they must...
Love for robot fluids.
Yes. They must be destroyed.
They come onto the battleground
when all the robots are laying around wounded
and bleeding their oil out and they bathe in the fluid,
these vicious religious fanatics, non-subgeniuses.
Someday their kind will be wiped out.
Yes, wiped out.
We'll run them all out.
That's right.
It will be the great grandmother of all battles.
And the festering uncle of all dupe shows.
Ready to appear on your screen at any time your brain is ready.
Notice how I tagged the front and the top
with the non-existent concept idea thing there.
That leaves scissor space. You can put in any concept.
So what are you saying? You're saying scissor space?
You're talking about, like, the excellent corpse thing?
No, no, that's just technical talk, radio talk for, you know, editing.
The sound later. So we can insert the other concept.
Oh, you're talking about the thought process.
I'm talking about the NSA labs in Langley
and what they're doing with this art project.
They're the cut and splice jobs on your memory.
No.
No, I thought it was yours.
No, it's your memory. I can't remember now.
It's your language pattern, too.
I'll take your word for it.
I'm afraid you're going to have to.
Well, that's what they said.
That's what a pitchfork in my butt says.
That's what you're saying.
That's what that cute little pair of sailor pants says.
I should have listened to the Baptist.
Yes, yes, you should have.
Where are the wooden shoes? Where are the wooden shoes?
Your hair's on fire, hombre.
Now, that's the mark of a true friend,
a man who'll tell you when your face or hair are on fire.
Well, at least when you're almost done.
You know, so many people in today's world won't even go to that much trouble.
Say, your hair or your face.
Your face or your face are on fire.
Are they going to go, hey, man, your face is on fire?
No way.
They just walk right by and pretend they don't see.
They think you know what you're doing.
They giggle at you, laugh at you.
And they let you go all the way with it.
Oh, look, that guy's face is on fire.
Well, you must know what he's doing.
Free will, man.
You know, laissez faire and so forth.
Yeah, it's the new age, you know.
Maybe he's doing his own thing.
Here is the most incredible thing you have ever seen.
A man with an eye on fire.
A lid lodged in his hip socket.
And a woman who claims to be his friend.
They're not quite...
I'm sorry, did you want me to...
Well, the surrealist parade continues down Main Street.
There the Man Ray float is.
I think that's what that is.
It's kind of hard to tell what it is.
Oh, and here comes the hobby horse itself.
The da-da.
Oh, look, they've got a man riding the stang.
Isn't that cute?
Oh, that's Bill Clinton.
He's frisking the bull dada, yes.
Oh, yes, the running of the bull dada.
Here we go.
Notice the pikes, those special pikes.
Those are called frop sticks that the soldiers there use against the bull dada.
In Pamplona, we run the bull dada three times per day.
Before the orange fight and after the tomato fight.
And here is the leader of the pack, Mr. Hotfoot Tooth Whistle himself.
I wear my little red hat and my little white cotton shirt and my red pants.
And I take a lot of the drugs and I run, run, fleeing down the street
away from the Tyrannosauruses, which they release here at the running of the Tyrannosaurs in...
Papalona.
Pamplona Jurassic Park.
I notice you are running.
I'm wearing the...
The majestic Brontosaurus seen here with a different head.
It's being led by the clowns.
Look, the little clowns behind him.
Some of them are wearing butcher's aprons.
Those trucks you clean up after.
Carrying little cutaways.
That's a lot of fine meat on the hoof.
Although I don't believe those dinosaurs actually have hoofs.
There's a lot of tension down on the street here.
They'll be letting the carnivorous...
Dinosaurs out, of course, at high noon, exactly.
And then after the weigh-in, I guess we got the shoe ceremony for some of the behind quarters.
Spaniards and tourists down there are incredibly drunk.
Well, the Spaniards are always drunk and the tourists are always very close to the bloodshed.
So I don't think we really...
You know what I'm saying.
30 people were eaten at last year's festival and the crowd ate it up, you might say.
They love this sort of thing.
I think what the actual statistics were, there were 25 people were eating.
Oh, here comes the stripper.
Here they come.
Well, here they come right now.
The cave stripper babes or what are they called?
They're from Holland, I think.
The Neanderlites.
Yes, they don't...
Neanderlites and they...
Incredible, they don't even shave their legs.
And they make sure that the bottle caps are fully and completely open.
And look at how sloping the foreheads are.
That's a sign of beauty to them.
Yes, they find that attractive.
And they're twirling the cave torches.
And I guess that's supposed to scare the old dinie, but it doesn't seem to be...
It's symbolic.
No, it's symbolic.
Yes, it's part of their beautiful, lovely culture.
And really, I'm sure the males find these cave ladies very attractive.
Well, they love the culture and they love the petri dish.
They put the culture on and some of the ladies can save them from it.
But at least they're there to give them their own engrams
and perhaps smoke what's left, the remainderings, I think.
Well, the crowd is certainly into it.
They can't wait for the slaves to be brought out and fed to the dinosaurs.
Is the gate ready to go up now or is it going to go down?
I'll tell you what, this virtual world we're in is so much better than the tedious real world
with its duct tape and drop cloth, don't you think, Dave?
Well, we still do need to use a little bit of duct cloth and drop cloth.
Uh, duct tape and cloth.
Oh, but then we wouldn't be able to see these amazing, gigantic dinosaurs...
Well, not from this crawlspace, but...
...these crowds of drunken Spaniards and all these happy, happy subgeniuses.
Here at the Pamplona Running of the Dinosaurs X Day 2012.
And we've got a front runner right in here, Pablo Neres,
who was in there for like a good solid 45 minutes
before having part of his slats removed.
Pablo, what's the situation down on the ground?
It is rich Corinthian leather.
My wine sack and my nut sack
are of rich Corinthian leather.
You're supposed to say my wine sack and my...
What was the other one?
I am no...
Uh...
Brutal cave person, my friend.
You are a Buddhist, though, aren't you?
I am a... I am a surrealist artist from Barthelona.
I am Dali, everything romping, yomping and yomp.
I use only squid ink for my black paint
and squid blood for my red.
And that is all I have.
That's all I need, red and black,
because I remember the revolution.
That is all I live for, is my memories of the revolution.
That's... Because there never was a revolution.
I just had to... I love to think about it, if only...
In times like this,
I like to remember the story of Stang's Overcoat.
The next day, there were so many hungry and poor.
Not one has a fresh overcoat.
But Stang is in the front of the pack,
leading the victorious soldiers.
And one says to him,
Stang, take my beautiful new overcoat.
And Stang says,
I will not wear a clean new overcoat until every subgenius has one.
What the hell have I forgotten?
I... They fell for that one.
I'm a fool.
Now we're down to the last moments
of this radio program.
This is the first time
Praise Bob.
And hail Connie.
And hail the extreme factors
who have forced the nurture here...
That is unbelievable.
...in the Celery House,
where the nipples are strong and free,
the odors are everywhere.
But, Nanza, it's a corny copia.
A corny copia.
We're not afraid. We're not afraid.
Her cup runneth over,
and I'm spilling my words
all over the ground and the air.
Smell it.
Like the old fish market.
Like squid vomit.
A squid.
Let's grab a squid and wrestle with it.
And kill the show.
To hell with the show.
Life is short.
And may the devil take the hindmost.
Shorten.
Mary, leave a good-looking squid corpse behind you.
Ha-ha!
Well...
That's it for another week.
And I hope you enjoyed it.
I'll be marching off
to the internment camps for radio disc jockeys any day now.
I long you for this camp, buddy boy.
You look like you've got three marks.
One on forehead, one on neck, and one on foot.
That's a great bridge you got your men to build there, Dave.
That's a great blastodermia growing in the Petri, Dave.
You seem to have built it in the wrong place and upside down.
It just goes from one side of the hill to the other side of the hill.
It's supposed to go across the river.
Goddamn you, Stang.
I can't.
I must do it right.
I don't care about this bloody war.
If this bridge has my name on it, or at least nearby,
or perhaps in the next town,
if someone will just scroll my name on a piece of paper
and mail it to this number, this address, send it to...
A bridge named Dave.
Box. Box.
Box one eight.
One eight one four one seven Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Four four one one eight. Praise Bob.
Until next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the winner, sack in the saddle.
And God save our Quinn.
Don't worry, Boris. We'll get to all of the cages eventually.
But first, you must climb into, and then escape, the cage of B-B-B-Bob!
Check out www.subgenius.com
or write to me, Reverend Ivan Stang, at P.O. Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or, subgenius at P.O. Box 204206.
Austin, Texas 78720.
For you must heed my words!