The reason I'm not at the PR news is because I'm in a...
Self-genius.
Power of...
You can tell Bob wants to win this.
Honestly, it's a reassuring thought,
because he wants it just as bad as the rest of us do.
Feet wide and just bob from side to side.
Turn the dial, and you're wiggling,
you're bending, you're bobbing, you're lunging.
I'm working the abs, the lower back,
my hip flexors, my glutes, my...
And after a while...
Having fun at the same time.
It gets to you.
Sit down, Bob. Take that shirt off.
Okay, all right.
Okay, now...
Turn the dial.
Bobby's judgment may have contributed
to saving millions of lives.
Rumors aside, Bobby's hard work paid off.
Bobby freed me of...
Bobby, meanwhile, is backstage doing the dirty work.
Turn to Bobby,
the only person to take the pressure off.
Oh, what a relief.
Thanks, Bobby.
And thanks, Bobby.
And thanks for that recording, The Large.
More of that to come.
This may be one of the more insane hours of Slack.
Even more insane than last week's show.
Although I'm only guessing that last week's show
will be insane because I'm assembling this one,
number 1,336,
before we do the live show, 1,335.
At this time of recording,
I'm hurriedly assembling shows in advance
because pretty much all of them are going to be
in the hands of a subgenius house sitter
and go on the road for a few weeks.
And I learned the hard way last year
that a somewhat deaf person
cannot edit hours of Slack in a moving car.
Luckily, we'll probably get to do a live show
with Pope's thermodocs in Little Rock
and two with Puzzling Evidence and them in Berkeley.
So it won't all be reruns.
Also, there's still much unheard ranting and music
from 14X Day, the Starwood Festival,
and the Northeast Ohio Witches' Baldi Vival,
all of which I'm trying to edit in advance.
Tonight, in fact, we're returning to the
Wisteria Campground Cafe stage
for recordings from 14X Day,
the first ever live show by the Ministry of Slack.
Now, we often play clips from Puzzling Evidence
and Reverend Susie DeFluzzi's Bob Slacktime Funhouse shows,
from KPFA Berkeley and WREK Atlanta, respectively,
both of which have been on those broadcast stations
for decades.
The Ministry of Slack, however,
is part of the new generation of subgenius radio,
unfettered by broadcast rules,
since it's strictly a podcast
and not beholden to the FCC
like Susie, Puzzling, and I am.
They've been making shows for several years now,
and you can find them on the web.
You can find the link to them on subgenius.com
in the radio section,
or just Google Ministry of Slack.
The funny thing about that show
is that most of them live in different cities,
and it's all done by phone and then edited.
At 14X Day Drill,
the whole gang was together in person
at the same place at the same first time.
And it's not an easy place to get to, as you'll hear,
partly because they are a bunch of untrained potty dogs,
and partly because they were drinking.
What you're about to hear is not uncut.
In fact, Reverend Exister pre-censored it for me,
and maybe forgetting that we also do
an uncensored internet version of Hour of Slack,
and he partitioned it
so that I could insert songs and collages
and give it the usual Hour of Slack treatment.
But first, let's listen to earlier that same day
when Dr. Howell, Priestess Pisces, and Papa Joe Mama
discussed both the Bulldada auction
and the All-Star Show.
In the upcoming first live Ministry of Slack performance.
I see our auctioneer is wandering this way,
and in about 10 minutes or so...
We're about ready to have the Bulldada auction.
If you want to purchase some unforgettable keepsake,
this may be the time to cluster around,
that is, in a few minutes,
and begin the frenzied bidding.
And again, if you have not registered,
there will be goons.
They are hired goons, actually.
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that.
Who will enforce the registration policy.
How unpleasant.
It is a sad day when the subgeniuses have to hire goons
instead of having volunteer goons.
Where does this come from?
We want volunteer goons.
All right.
It's a new one on me.
But, you know, one should not be surprised.
So we'll have another 10 minutes to register,
another 10 minutes to buy schwag,
and then again we will have the auction in 10 minutes.
And just think, you know,
whatever item it is,
you got in that auction,
that means that you survived the ferocious bidding,
the elbow-hitting competition of the person next to you,
those who are doing what they could
in order to sabotage your efforts.
It's a dog-eat-dog auction.
And I'm sorry, we took all this time to promote, you know...
Well, you've got to do that.
It's radio.
You've got to talk about the next thing that's coming along,
and that's the Bulldada auction.
It's incredible, stupendous, remarkable.
The finest show of its kind ever produced anywhere.
It slices, it dices,
it even makes Julian fries.
And while we're talking about things that are coming after the Bulldada auction,
we also will have live ministry of Slack will be joining us,
and they will be doing something not unlike what's going on here,
but with fresh young faces who are excited and not at all jaded or bitter
or not even slightly disappointed yet.
Well, there's such a thing as expecting too much, priestess.
But we can hope that there will be those who are constant in their devotion to our cause,
who won't let us down at a crucial moment.
The ministry of Slack will not let us down.
Like a bursting safety pin or splitting belt.
While the conspiracy dupes...
They said they will feel us up, not let us down.
Adventures in time and space.
Transcribed in future tense.
Amanda!
I forgot all that shit was in there.
I thought it was in some stuff.
Yeah, it's the interlaker.
Can you predict what will come in 100 years?
Or in 10?
Or in the next minute?
Some people think they can.
Nuclear science, mathematicians, astronomers, biologists.
They'll predict the shape of the future because they make the future.
Because they see beyond the known dimensions of time and space.
Into the unknown.
Dimension X.
We go ahead now in time.
The ministry of Slack.
Bob?
operates in the last Aphsys time.
Is needed to control manpower trans zitten disciples
and cause power loss.
What is not of the former was used to empower iron espers to
Guard to inverses the carta de sorority on the union of feldit,
Those of West
The ministry of Slack.
Montainer 130x categories.
the command fieldностью
ISO 13
1-1-3-0-1-3
Well, hello kids, and welcome.
This is the very first time that the Ministry of Slack is broadcasting at X-Day.
Live!
Can you imagine it?
We're here.
This is your brain on old.
I don't know.
It's your brain on old, your brain on hold.
This is the Ministry of Slack, so hold on to your butts.
It's like looking into a mirror.
This is what I do at home.
It's kind of what you guys are doing.
Just sit around and drink.
Yes, well, that's how we start the show.
Usually that is how we start it.
So, where are we starting today?
Oh my God.
Well, you know, it's amazing.
You guys just blew in here.
Literally, yeah.
We just arrived.
My God.
Via the walkway.
We just flew in from Jersey.
And boy is that joke old.
I said nothing about my arms flapping, sir.
It's bad jokes, though, that have to get us limbered up and ready.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
What is the torrent that's going around now?
It's like everything that's ever been done by the Ministry of Slack.
It's up to what, five gigs now or something?
Yeah, with two whole seaters.
60 gigs.
Yeah.
I hope I'm still seated.
That's 55 plus five more.
Sorry.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I thought that the only torrent that was going around was Bob.
Every episode of the Ministry of Slack is available via this torrent.
Except for the good stuff.
I'm going to tie you up and treat you like a torrent.
Man.
See, that's the only torrent that's really worth seating is that Bob torrent.
It's not illegal.
It's just out there, but you can feel free to pay.
And it's freshly baked.
Every day.
That Bob time torrent comes around.
Yeah.
I mean, it's strange because it's like, actually, this is the first time I have met, I mean,
a lot of us have met for the first time.
Let's see.
I mean, this is the first time all of us have met.
We physically are like here.
This is the first time we've all ever been together.
That we can actually talk to each other and look at each other in the eyes.
All right.
Let's do it.
I'm bottom.
No, I mean, y'all met like last year, right?
But y'all didn't do a live thing.
So now we're.
Some of us were here.
Yeah.
Or Kill Me Radio last year.
Some of us were here, but the death stars were not in alignment.
So that's why you should all shudder.
Because we're all here in one place.
At the same time.
So something's going to blow up.
Something will.
I feel it like it's on the cards.
Yeah, you know, I can arrange my shorts.
I feel something blow up.
I hope it's the earth.
Oh, no, that's not the wild butt hurt, is it?
Wait, I've been dying to do this all my life.
Wait a minute.
I just.
Is this thing on?
I just wanted to do that forever.
And finally it's appropriate.
Well, now it's there for posterity.
Okay, good.
Or I should say for posteriority.
Mm-hmm.
You're such a commodian.
Yeah.
No.
Woo-hoo.
Hey, punk.
When I get out of here, I'm going to tell you a new.
Self-genius.
Power of.
Surprise.
I'd like a receipt for that.
Yeah, me too.
So one of the things we were talking about, like, Aidy and me were like, we've like omens
on the way here.
Yes.
The road is full of omens, people.
I mean, we knew we were going to make it up here at X Day, regardless of whatever kind
of anti-slut.
We were, we were, we were unfortunately victims of, we overcame.
And it was nice to see those beautiful signals on the road telling us that, yes, we will
truly make it here to Wisteria with time to spare to do the Ministry of Slack.
They overcame and they came and they came.
We went through like five tiles.
It just doesn't stop.
It's an inevitable flow.
It really is one of the important things that you have to watch for when you're traveling
Mm-hmm.
is the signs and portents on the road.
Because some of those signs have been there for a while, but it's a time-delayed release
of information and slack from the over-Uber Dobbs head, letting you know that today, now
is the time.
$30 for salvation.
And if you're already there, then hey, you're on the right road.
You see where it's going.
Like driving up here, we saw like an exit for Bobtown.
Yeah, outside of Dallas.
Back in the state of Dallas.
That is certainly a sign.
And you saw-
And we were even talking.
No, Bobtown Road, Dallas, formation of the church.
Dobbs Motors.
Dobbs Motors in Tennessee.
That is more signs.
Yes.
Bobtown, isn't that one of them all-women prisons?
Perhaps.
Yeah.
And it was a nice family of pinks who had, you know, they had the Dobbs Motor like insignia
from the dealership.
And we're just like, that is so wrong, but yet, you know, we're on our way.
Well, of course, Bob Dobbs sold those vehicles to those pinks.
Of course he did.
Of course.
It was just, you know, one of those you had to be there.
Oh my God, what the fuck?
Bob.
In fact, we had to slow down.
We even had to say, hey, is that somebody?
We thought maybe it was official church propaganda.
We're like-
So you were rubberneckers for Bob.
Just for a second.
Okay.
Once we realized that the guy had his cap back on and had about $100 worth of gold around
his neck, we realized, nah.
It's something that people don't always realize.
Dobbs is the great galactic salesman of repute.
So of course he's going to have his fingers and, you know, other various body parts.
And all sorts of different businesses.
Diversification.
Yes, diversification, diversa-mutation-def-ication.
That's a portfolio you can believe in.
Or extra meditation.
Yeah, or extra meditation.
The Ministry of Slack marveling at the portents seen on their difficult cross-country road
trips to Wisteria Campground near Athens, Ohio.
Funny that Bobtown Road in Dallas they mention...
The second subgenius publication, Stark Fist No. 1, featured a photo of Philo Drummond standing under that very Bob Town Road sign in 1979.
Anyway, that gives us an excuse to cut to yet another sub-simp or subgenius-related show, Radio Synesthesia,
which follows Hour of Slack on WCSB Cleveland, hosted by our good friend Dr. Sinister.
Here we hear his rather candid description of his trip from Cleveland in frigid northern Ohio to Wisteria on the Ohio River way down south,
where you can tell it's July and no longer a big city of the Northeast.
It's so weird going to, you know, the last time I traveled that far from home was last November for the Detroit revival.
And, you know, that meant I crossed a state line.
I went into Michigan and frankly, I felt more at home in Detroit than I do in southern Ohio.
I can't believe I'm in the same state.
I think that the state lines that we have drawn in this country are completely arbitrary.
And it was it was like another it was like another country almost.
The dirt is red or pink.
But yeah, yeah, they've got red clay down in southern Ohio.
I knew about that because I've got family in Marietta and I used to go see them when I was young.
And I was familiar with the red clay, but I did not remember how hot it would get and how humid it would get.
It was like over 90 degrees every day.
And the humidity was such that like, I don't know.
Actually, it might have been like maybe it was so hot.
Maybe the temperature outside exceeded my body temperature and it wasn't actually sweat.
Maybe it was just condensation.
You know, you put a cold drink out on a hot day.
And all that moisture appears on the sides of it.
That's just condensation.
And maybe that's what it was.
Maybe I wasn't really sweating.
Maybe it was just that hot out.
Hard to tell.
You know, I mean, the show really like when we do this show, it's like we literally I think we do about maybe like an hour meeting every week.
And then between me and Exister and whoever contributes, we just do music.
So it's like we're on the spot now.
We've got to like.
Right.
There can't be any lulls now.
Oh, how the hell?
There can be lulls.
There just can't be.
Skype won't shut down on us now.
So there is no excuse for.
Well, and you, the audience, are the closest we have to cut ups.
So we don't have any to play.
So be that cut up.
Cut ups.
Now, they're not that funny.
Yeah.
Feel free to come up here and dance if you like.
And talk over us.
We don't mind.
We could use.
Any demanding jig that you want to dance.
We'll be more than glad to watch.
Official Ministry of Slack Fly Girls since it's 1991.
Even solid gold dancers would work at this point.
It's not only gold dancers.
That's a soft metal, though.
How about solid iridium?
That'd be good.
Solid iridium.
Two shows ago.
Yeah.
So we are the hippest trip in America now.
Oh, that's right.
We outpace Soul Train.
The Dobbs Train is the hippest trip in these benighted states.
Super cool.
And it's fall down for more slack.
Oh, this one.
Rock on.
We'll have a look at.
That's lovely.
Gee.
Thank you.
On the Boardwalk in Atlanta City
by the Rudy Schwartz
Project from the new CD
they switched to cornmeal on
Sealand Records, negativeland.com
negative spelled without the E.
And now to a goodly stretch of the
Ministry of Slack show live at
X Day.
So once again
we are the hippest trip in America now.
And most of our audience
is about to break theirs.
Hey you know what's kind of funny too
because both announcers have silvery voices.
Silvery?
Yes.
Well polished.
The hippest trip in America.
No, no, where are our manners here?
So we could have some
greenhorn listeners, some new
listeners that have no idea
who we are.
So I think we should do
Dobbs roll call.
Go down the line and say who we are.
So if you want to punch us later
you can. That's a stupid show.
It's the worst thing I've ever seen or heard.
And I'm deaf.
By far the worst part of it.
We talk over each other more than
puzzling evidence. They don't shut up.
Well, I'm Reverend Exister.
One of the original
founders of the Ministry of Slack.
He's the big toe.
His blood,
his sweat, his semen,
his very bones are embedded
in this ministry.
We would not be here without him of course
because you're a dirty squirrely man.
Yes I am the Reverend Dementio
the 80th otherwise known as
Reverend 80 otherwise known as
Reverend AXDX
otherwise known as Reverend Axe
I am Reverend Slender Bob
I guess the newest member
of the Clench.
And who does most of our mixes now.
This man does amazing work.
If you've heard our show before
and in recent times, a lot of it's been due to him.
One of the most hard working men
in show business.
Thank you.
Our current show would not be what it is
without Slender Bob.
That's nice.
I'll say it.
We have to have show.
Not S-H-O-W just S-H-O.
It's like the Ministry of Slack started off with a video show
on Ustream.
You did all the video.
You did pretty much all of that.
Then you had submissions.
And I burned out.
Many many hours a week.
But now it's even better because the visuals are in your mind.
You're whiff reading those visuals
those mental visuals
with your third nostril friends.
So you don't have to worry about
visuals on a computer.
It's a lucid dream in real time.
You either f*** off or you rip the wrinkle.
Whatever you're going to do.
So normally when you listen to the show on the internet
there's a little bit of ranting and talking
and lots of music.
But back down the line.
Did we do McGee already?
We did myself and Slender.
See this is a peanut gallery.
That's what this is.
I see what's going on here.
The pockets.
Somebody's blushing.
I'm Reverend Pockets.
Hello.
Mob.
Like every morning radio show
we have to have a hole.
Far far more.
The holy stark fist of Connie herself.
I'm here to break up the sausage party.
That's my sole purpose.
Pretty much.
She's the on this bull.
But more importantly you know what she does?
She checks us.
Go back to our minds.
I mean remember last week?
She said that we were.
Oh she checks herself too.
Before she wrecks herself.
She gives me a horribly bad English portion.
Because when we're going to.
She corrects us.
We wreck ourselves all together.
Well we get wrecked and we get bit.
But I seem to be having to do an introduction for myself.
Hello again brothers and sisters.
This is the alchemist.
Orpheus Stain.
I heard there's a random tent.
Indeed.
I'm going to watch out.
I'm on the wisteria.
It's very similar to that classic song.
The Phantom Windbreaker.
We have the phantom tent.
We don't know who this person is.
There's only blurry photographs.
We can't tell gender from this.
They're being analyzed but all we know.
Is that they're leaving steamers.
In the tents of.
Like a yeti.
Watch out for that spore.
If it's there you run.
You run quicker than you ever have.
And you get out of here.
Because they're coming for you.
Or you can do the opposite thing.
That I've heard that it does make wonderful jenkum.
If you are a bold enough individual.
To harvest and ferment this.
That takes work.
But we know the true way to make jenkum.
Oh that's right.
It is illustrated.
Is it in the yeti book over there?
No.
God that book sucks more and more.
Yeah there's like a.
You can think about jenkum in there.
She's right.
I believe that is covered actually.
There is an image in this sacred text.
Are you huffing up?
The first step to getting jenkum.
There it is.
The harvesting of food.
It's an overman dropping his night soil.
Excremeditation out in the open.
The first step to jenkum friends.
It can be yours.
You drew that in.
The stars are awesome at night.
After you leave that porta potty.
You got that fresh jenkum high.
It's true.
What is the blue chemical that they put in the jenkum these days?
What is that new.
It's the kids all of it.
It's blueberry flavoring.
It's not nickel sulfate?
No.
I like to call it blue loo.
But that's just me.
Blue moon, blue monday.
Blue balls.
It's true.
Those jenkum huffing steam chambers.
You look up at the stars.
And you think the exes are bound to see us now.
That's the great thing about being able to do this show on the internet.
We can really just like go.
Sometimes we do get really filthy.
Filthy than we are now.
It is a filthy show folks.
It's really filthy.
Because we are at home and we are comfortable.
And there is nobody watching us.
We have no FCC to.
I mean we have seen all of us.
This is one of the major differences between us and other subterranean shows.
We have no FCC to.
There is no FCC control over us.
I would not put that on the show.
I would not want to be in Snake's position to have to edit.
I know right.
We wouldn't have a show anymore.
It would be done.
It would be like a five minute show.
It would be like Red Fox in 1973 put on like prime time.
It's why his ears don't listen anymore.
Because they don't want to hear that.
They are sick of it.
They quit.
They are fed up.
I've only been doing it like broadcasting for ten years.
I can imagine like.
I haven't been doing it for as long as Suzie and Ivan.
As long as they've been doing it.
It's like you know.
Praise those who have come before us.
In this honorable subgenius tradition.
We lift our glasses.
To those of you who actually have experience.
And know what you are doing.
Well done.
We are the mere embryos.
Of the giant yeti.
Fully grown.
I don't need this.
But I've seen him for a while.
I don't know where he's been.
Do you have any idea where he's been?
I think he's been on a sabbatical.
At the seminary.
What does that mean exactly?
It's a guy thing.
Well on the sabbath they go on a sabbatical.
And they are in the seminary.
Of the disseminating semen.
She likes that word.
They disseminate semen.
We're going to watch TV while you guys talk about that stuff.
With the semen.
In the Navy.
No.
I cannot even imagine a place with no VCRs.
Now, how am I going to watch the pageant on no VCRs?
Well, we're in the past right now.
Way long ago.
I'll just have to watch the pageant live on one of the major networks.
Oh, my God, Bob, would you do that for me?
Would you come to my baby's pageant?
Yeah, I'll watch it live.
But it's going to be televised, right?
Live, televised, televised?
No, we have to be there live.
I can send one of my minions.
I'll send one of my minions.
Next week in Dallas, we have a husband and I have a pageant,
and we would just love for you to come.
Okay, I'll be there.
Either me or one of my representatives will be there.
Now, Philo, don't you say that,
because you sent that last representative, and he was not a nice man.
Well, I'm still waiting for that write-up
so that I can give him his performance appraisal
and just dismiss him properly through the proper legal channels.
Performance appraisal?
I don't.
I don't care, really.
I've just got to be truthful about this.
It's not that I am not, you know, supportive of my husband and his job.
Hey, Vicki.
All that, but I just don't care about, I mean,
he has been performing now for like 40 years on that thing radio.
Yeah, that's true.
And we know he's good now.
What is the problem?
You'd think it would be like by now, people would know what it was like, right?
I'm going to take that into consideration.
Dr. Philo Drummond, taking it all into consideration
on the puzzling evidence show of January 20th, 2011,
with a caller who sure sounds like she's from around Dallas.
Anyway, these are the elders that the young ministry of Slack were talking about,
even elder than I, for I was merely the first Bobby.
Dr. Drummond turned me on to Bob and knew him personally.
I never was allowed to meet Bob until about 30 seconds
before he was assassinated that first time in 1985.
That was 1984, not 1985.
Thank you.
And the puzzling evidence show predates the hour of Slack by three years.
It started at KPFA in June of 1982.
Although I was there at those first two broadcasts,
heard on our old media barrage tapes.
The music in the background, by the way, is Boron Nuzzle,
live at 14XX.
And now back to the ministry of Slack,
which will be interspersed with a brag of Brother Cleve Donut Duncan,
one of the early influential proto-er subgenii,
and so cool that he did an album with Esquivel.
Praise Brother Cleve, praise ministry of Slack, praise Connie.
Praise the Connie, praise the Yanni.
Oh yeah, Yanni, what?
Hey, there's nothing wrong with a little panfalutin.
Right?
Praise the Lord, pass the ammunition.
It depends on what they're doing with it.
I can play the panfalutin.
No, I think we're about to have a schism up here.
Look out.
I usually pan the flute in the right channel.
Pan the flute, yeah.
There you go.
This is the ugly facts of this show.
Five days, two days.
We're pretty much raunchy cheese for your dirty nachos.
It's a lot of jokes for the most part.
Yeah, but basically, you know, cater to the lowest crowd.
And then the occasional reference to Bob, and then, you know, the occasional, like,
drop the $64 words for the higher crowd.
Hey, you listening to this who thinks this is funny, go to subgenius.com.
And while you're at it, click on the link that says register to be a minister now.
That's what we do normally.
Going to the obvious, I think it's because, you know, 1998 is now.
This is the year.
You guys said it as you came in.
There are all the signs.
You know, there are signs of Bob's everywhere.
This time it's time.
Everywhere you go.
And, you know, they've been getting a lot more.
Because the time is truly the end times.
By hook or by crook or by cheek.
Bob.
We all got here.
You guys don't know this because you just arrived.
There is.
Someone here.
Like that.
Gee, how can I explain?
How would you explain him?
Well, it's as if we've all been doing this for so long.
Something finally manifested.
It was a manifestation, yes.
And he's right here.
The mental energy put into it for all this time has drawn a certain individual.
His name's Bob.
There's a salesman here.
He's from Texas.
He's a salesman.
His name is Robert, but he goes by Bob.
Yep.
He's from Texas.
And he models on the side like the great Dobbs did, which is how we have the Dobbs head.
And I had doubts.
I asked this man to see some proof his name was really Robert or Bob.
And I looked at his ID.
The end of it said J.R.
That's right.
Well, and everything that happens to him, every good thing happens by accident.
You know, there was a there was a point yesterday where I saw this man that we like to call Bob in his lovely tailored suit yesterday.
I know.
He's a snappy dresser.
He's a quite dapper gentleman indeed.
I knew.
Like Bob himself.
Reverend Dapper.
That's his name.
I think I may have just saw the real J.R. Bob Dobbs walk off into the sunset.
Folks, we're getting raptured this year.
The gleam in his eye.
And somehow no one has killed him yet.
Annette's saying something because if you're a regular listener to the show, you know that I do a cavalcade of different voices.
He's a veritable mill blank.
Well, the fact of the matter is.
That's the only way I can get a call.
Across to you people how important it is that you get right with Bob?
Not that you get right with Bob.
But at every second, every, I Ode every nanosecond, before those saucers come is a chance for you to get other people to come to Bob.
So that when you get up to your saucer you can say, I duped this many.
Yeah.
And you, yes you, can be saved.
But if, if, and only if, you get right with Bob Bob,
Tonight or this afternoon or tomorrow morning or sometimes during lunch or if you go off to take a nice healthy extra meditation
You can say you know what I'm gonna. I'm gonna give myself over to Bob
And by that virtue I am in touch with forces greater than men I dare you to kill me
I am NOT a duplicate conspiracy. I know more than they do I am a subgenius. That's all I need to be
I'm one of the good guys I shall prevail
Let out the crazy man inside you he knows what's what smile when you call me a fanatic me primate me over man
I said to the pigs give me your money you won't need it the future offers you not for destruction
You wake up, and you go I was duped. I was played played like a puppet
Yeah, fucker have the rest of my wallet you cheap cheap
Okay, I bet you $50 right now. We're not on the roster next year
We're not on the roster for next year because it's happening this year
Are you talking solar year?
Just soda Papa
Actually McGee brings up a good point mentioning time, and I don't mean that one
I mean the terrestrial wristwatch, but several people here unfortunately been asking me what time
You're not talking about the the quintessential wristwatch
That Zappa talks about in his music indeed the same
Same dirty rest watch fruits the pinks
What time is it am I hungry? I gotta look at a watch you don't even have
Now
Alright, I'm gonna wind up that Bob watch are you gonna kill it kill that time kill that Bob watch cuz Bob's here?
He doesn't know me
Look at watch
Stop me big Bob. Oh, okay. Okay, big Bob do what is the Bob?
Oh
Something
Oh big Bob
You smell like rubber and you're really sketchy
your
Got punked by Big Bob like weird dream
Come on
Gentlemen as it landed here at hysteria
14 what one faithful listener asked for the subgenius he said you on the corn report. Well, we do we do have the
agricultural commodities Bear
what were ya?
We have frop.
Frop is up to 25.
It's up to 25 from 13 before.
And beef has gone ahead and raised itself from 13 to a good hard 22 and a half.
Well, the problem with the beef is that, like any good healthy beef, it smells.
So beef is down to a negative 6 because you don't want to be around that beef.
Well, the corn and squash is splattered into the spinach loaf, which is now at about 250.
Give me a little more.
252 on the Jenkin-Rector scale.
Now, the important thing to know is that here in beautiful Wisteria, we are in an area.
Wisteria?
Because Wisteria!
Okay.
We are in an area where people play this traditional corn holing game.
They throw a corn cob through a hole.
And there's something subgenious about that.
If they're that dedicated to corn holing.
We are in the wrong.
We're in the right place, brothers and sisters.
I want to see some pictures of that.
You probably take the pictures of that.
Yeah, I mean, it's like...
You'll be in the pictures of that.
When does the actual corn holing begin?
Well, it all depends.
I don't know.
I need to check the schedule.
Cornelius?
Well, if you want to get that perfect shot, you drink that corn liquor.
And you throw that corn cob.
And you hope to Dobbs that it makes it through the hole.
Otherwise, they're going to cut off your other leg!
I just heard this guy, Bob.
He fits into everything.
What was Bob saying?
I'm a perp.
And I arrest cops.
And I eat people.
Yeah.
I can smell a cop.
Retarded nonsense.
Right.
He gets all lit up and wired.
And you go, right.
Exactly.
You are right, Bob.
That's called being me-tarded.
Don't be me-tarded.
Circle Church, you moron.
Is Ego's at some newfangled Linux program?
Circle Church?
Yeah.
Circle Church.
Circle Church?
There you go.
I noticed that you young folks talk a lot faster than Dr. Howell.
Well, we are able to.
You know what it is?
It's all the damn answer.
I said, hell, I'll talk fast.
You know I can talk fast.
I mean, hey, if you don't push that button, I mean, hey.
I mean, forget about it.
Don't blame me.
I mean, you got to point that at me, that hand.
You got to point your hand.
I didn't create change.
No, you didn't.
No.
He's a monster that made himself.
We can speak.
We speak slower at times.
We enunciate.
Yes, we can.
We use very bad grammar.
Because I speak English good.
It depends on the material.
Circle Church.
You guys haven't been trained by having to go to radio stations.
Hell no.
Actually.
Actually?
Oh, no.
I had a year of that.
No, we have no FCC.
This is a major difference between us and all of our subtenuous shows.
We are free.
We're all over.
We're a bunch of, like, what?
Everywhere.
North America?
More than.
We've got Leach in the room.
We will probably carnival barfers in another life.
But now we're just yakking on the radio, filling the air with our foul stanchions.
Those doctors of the air.
Push for a different market.
And that is the modern state of skull farming.
See, that's the thing.
Because we can be doing show, and meanwhile, we can be looking at the finest Yeti porn.
Right?
Hey, Sting.
One time I left my webcam on.
Teddy can party with that.
Thank you.
All right.
Next, we have the most famous artist on the showing, that line justbird of
with kas meine taiwo sei,
Bunu
RuRAV
The large did the crunching of water music that was.
We heard the Ministry of Slack live at 14X Day, more to come.
A collage by Reverend Dr. Royal Decapitator.
And the large again, or before, depending on how you look at it.
And now back to Ministry of Slack on stage in a moment when I left the video camera
and approached them to compliment them on their lack of built-in old-school radio inhibitions.
I can tell.
Nah, we still have our Dobbs brand diapers on.
Oh, fine, yeah, go ahead.
That one's the durable.
I bought her a whole bottle of it.
And we need more bottles.
We accept donations, as all doctors do.
A little image for the people who are listening, who might hear this later.
It's like, we just got here.
People are here.
People are just now arriving to Wisteria.
Imagine a bunch of drunks screaming into a microphone.
Imagine, like, a hair metal band going,
Hello, Detroit!
to two people.
That's what we're doing right now.
But for those of you ladies at home who all of a sudden got moist,
that was the melodious voice of the good, sacred scribe, Ivan Stang.
Yes.
Not to be confused with or Doug.
I've been staying.
Doug?
Okay, now you said you wouldn't do this.
Now, now, Brian.
What, what are you talking about?
I'm in Todd.
You want to go there?
Todd?
Let me tell you.
I was going to shut up right now.
Let me tell you, the Church of the Doug Geniuses sold last year.
We burnt that to the ground.
Then Bob stopped by.
And Bob read them dirty limericks.
The pressure off.
Bobby.
This is clearly a photograph of Bob.
And what's really sad is it's actual size.
It is a, he is not a large man.
Let's try this.
This is Bob.
Bob is a simulated man as a punching bag.
And I'll give you a sense of what it's like to hit somebody.
Okay.
So let's go ahead and try a palm strike on Bob.
Okay, palm strike on Bob.
Right here.
Go in a straight line, straight in to win and aim for his nose.
Go right through it.
Way to do his nose.
So what am I?
So.
Just like that.
That's me, Bob.
Like a big truck driver.
I'd rather mean Lester.
That's me, Bob.
Like a big truck driver.
I'd rather mean Lester.
So just like that.
That's me, Bob.
Like a big truck driver.
I'd rather mean Lester.
That's me, Bob.
Like a big truck driver.
I'd rather mean Lester.
I'd rather me Lester.
Lester.
And here he is himself, Bob in the flesh.
Ah yes, Reverend Dapper.
This is my friend, be true, J. Hart.
Now this is a form of Bob that you can actually look at and not have your head explode like this.
And yet his whole life has led to this moment.
Yes, being at FSA and being called out on this moment by the Ministry of Slack has led to this holy moment.
You cannot fool us, Bob.
Unfortunately...
He laughs!
No!
He laughs like the granny Bob's would!
He doesn't say a word!
No!
Come to the camera and show thy grin.
Unfortunately, Bob...
You can't kill this, Bob, because this is one of the...
We're gonna have to kill you.
This is one of the rare collectible Bobs.
Exactly.
There are only so many variants and repaints past the original Dobbs.
Poke Dobs gotta kill them all.
Poke Dobs.
And I wish I could hear him, but yet I can't.
I can't bring my...
Why are we speaking so loud?
What?
Huh?
This is like the classic...
...creckled ginger Dobbs of ancient Lemuria.
So maybe in some form there is some kind of slackful reincarnation for this young chap...
...who hasn't even read the fucking books yet or anything.
He just knew that...
I have to go here.
I have to spread the word.
There's a rainbow on his hat, right?
I fed him some chicken last night.
Rainbow in the Dobbs!
That would be the internal sunshine of the spotless behind.
Also known as butt hurt cartoon.
The internal sunshine of the spotless shart.
He's a little bit of a chicken with the little
little
Abraham Lincoln was enjoying a performance of Our American Cousin at Ford's Theater
with his wife Mary Todd, Army Major Henry R. Rathbone, and Rathbone's fiancée Clara Harris
when John Wilkes Booth approached from the rear and fired a .44 caliber bullet into Lincoln's brain.
The president was then carried across the street to the Peterson House, where he was placed on a bed too short for comfortable repose,
as blood and brain tissue seeped from the base of his skull.
As he lay dying, Lincoln's subconscious turned to the microhela Nepenthecoa,
and as of then undiscovered species of miniature frog,
which existed on the island of Borneo in Southeast Asia.
The adult microhela Nepenthecoa rarely exceeds 12 millimeters in length
and is thought to be the second smallest frog species in existence.
It is named for the plant on which it thrives, the Nepenthes ampullaria,
a carnivorous pitcher plant with liquid-filled cubs attached to tendrils
in which the tadpoles of the microhela Nepenthecoa grow to maturity,
their eggs having been planted on the exterior surface of the plant's cubs.
The adult frogs produce a dissonant rasping sound from dusk into the early evening,
and this grating frog chorus echoed through what was left of Lincoln's mind during his final hours.
He began to visualize his head,
and an upper torso he framed on a shiny copper disc.
Peeking over the edge of the disc was a tiny rasping frog,
which made eye contact with him as if to say,
Come join us.
Meanwhile, somewhere in a Malaysian rain forest,
a pea-sized frog dreamed of staring over a giant copper wall into the eye of a bearded man,
and the bearded man realized,
that they were being watched.
The Rooty Schwartz Project
The Rooty Schwartz Project,
a track called Abe from the year they switched to cornmeal,
Sealand Records,
before that Ministry of Slack at 14X Day,
before that a bit of collage by Decapitator or The Large,
I can't quite keep track at this point.
Once they're cut up,
they sometimes lose their names, the poor things.
But now we return again to The Return of...
The Return of the Son of Butthurt.
Yes, The Return of the Son of, of the Clone of, of the Mecha...
The Dawn of Rising of...
Butthurt Part 9, The Gaming.
This is true.
Butthurt Number 13, Butthurt vs. Santa.
Number 9, Number 9, Butthurt is dead.
Plan Butthurt?
Planet Butthurt.
8 is not enough.
Ah yes, Plan Butthurt.
Butthurt 13, Butthurt in the Ghetto.
The system by which you make people flame out and hate themselves
and prolapse from so much butthurt.
Exactly.
Using reanimated bodies of dead subgeniuses.
And that's what we're talking, folks.
You get prolapsed.
That's all we're asking.
It's a distance contest of prolapses.
Exactly.
Unless that's taking it too far.
Just make a raspberry of your mind, people.
What does that even mean, 80s?
No, make a rosebud of your mind.
One rose配せ sweet raspberry the rosebud!
The final episode after marketers she was honest all at it
was a successful yes.
Use following classicalliftback at the end if you like.
Like a Şey Ass.
bodysuit voice
Art Busy
We won the fight back at normal were we were?
How was that?
Yes, something called Outmouth did that track there.
They, or it, remain mysterious to us.
To come, more live X-Day Ministry of Slack and Dr. Howell and Collarges by the large.
But the important thing you should know is that this is the Hour of Slack, number 1,336 from the Church of the Subgenius, www.subgenius.com.
To learn more about our books and DVDs and such, or for the prisoners out there, post office box 181-417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
We have a lot of listeners in prisons. I'm not surprised.
When I hear that whistle blowin', I hang my head and cry.
Now back to the Ministry of Slack as the whiskey really kicks in.
There is no, the end times are flushed away.
We have got exactly 11 and a half, maybe 12 minutes.
You know how I know I'm a subgenius?
Because I have like 42 eardrums and I can focus on every single thing you guys are saying simultaneously.
It's true.
I am a superior.
You're asking how much change you will have in my pocket right now.
You are right.
It's slightly correct, brothers and sisters.
Can I get a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Yeah!
They've bought it hook, line, and sinker.
I will sell you this empty beer can for 78 cents, my friend.
Oh, really?
Hey, that's a hell of a deal.
To an all-you-can-eat buffet in Ethiopia.
Just $1.
I'll send you, I'll sell you a scaled model of Ruby Ridge.
Complete with...
A little explosion.
Oh, man!
Never again!
I'm gonna talk to you about Bob.
Psh!
Big Bob will smack you up so hard.
And I said, Big Bob's the truth.
Okay.
Look at me!
Oh, here he is, Big Bob.
He's always in the streets, huh?
Oh, okay, okay.
That guy in the little car, yeah?
Big Bob!
Welcome to the bigness.
Yeah, yeah.
Goin' down, Bob.
I'm gonna butt-hurt you guys, like, sometimes.
Not that we're not hiding in the internet.
We're all gathered here together.
We can see each other.
I have a secret.
We can slug each other.
Ooh, Puppets has got a secret?
I'm going to lay out the butthurt.
Come on, baby.
Do it.
Let the butthurt flow.
I just get up and I walk away and I come back 45 minutes later.
What was that about?
Did you just talk about talking?
She always gives an excuse like, oh, I need to give Legume his cream.
I need to go make dinner.
The little monkeys are running around naked, but we know that she just needs a break.
I need a break from us.
I need a break from all your slag.
It overwhelms me.
It's true.
It's intoxicating.
It's why we keep doing this.
Exactly.
We just keep coming back to each other over and over.
It's like why you go to that XXX adult theater off on Highway 3.
I can't quit you guys.
I leave and I come back and I come back.
This is all about my sweetheart.
This is for Lizzie Borda.
So you can hear the lyrics now.
Crash party at 12.
I'll see you at 12 and raise your 20s.
I love my beautiful wife.
But she's got no tongue.
And just the other day she said.
Honey, I love you.
Yeah.
Damn.
I don't want to take it away.
I don't know why.
Pimples and braces.
And for those who are listening by radio, it is truly brutal.
I have to make a plug for one of our regular businesses.
Pee Pants Pizza.
Killing and killing and killing.
The pizza that keeps you wanting to urinate.
You can pick it up.
At your local Hovermart.
Hovermart.
For all your subgenius and hovering needs.
Good old Hovermart.
I haven't heard from now.
Now available at Hovermart.
The best stuff.
The Ministry of Slack.
When you came to Asteria.
There's no Hovermart there.
Located 1,000 miles.
Do not play this tape.
While you are submersed in water.
While you are cooking back baking in Canada.
Do not play this tape.
While you are cooking camel soup.
While you are reading.
Religious material.
Do not play this tape.
While you are...
After the Ministry of Slack,
there of course also is Grindhouse Movies
every single night this year.
Every single minute.
Every single night there will be grind...
really awesomely bad movies down the hill.
Also, for those of you who prefer a more
automotive related experience,
there is a drive-in that will be played tonight.
Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
I don't remember exactly what the films are, Dr. Dark.
The Imaginarium of Dr. Dark.
Dr. Dark's Drive-In.
Big Man in Japan?
Okay.
Friends, if you've never seen or heard of Big Man Japan,
you don't want to miss it.
You owe it to yourself.
It's like a Japanese monster movie as done by David Lynch.
It's an existential Japanese monster movie.
And this version, it has subtitles
so you can actually understand what they're saying,
unlike Philo Drummond's copy.
I believe the other film is the Lost Skeleton of Kadavra.
Isn't it the sequel to the Lost Skeleton of Kadavra?
Or maybe even the sequel to the sequel?
The Lost Skeleton Returns Again.
Well, I guess that skeleton wasn't that lost then, was it?
There's only really two movies out there in which the sequel was better than the original.
One being Terminator Judgment Day and the other, of course, being the Lost Skeleton.
Oh, come on. What about The Godfather?
What about One Million Years B.C.?
That's not a science fiction film. I'm talking sci-fi.
No, Aliens.
Oh, see? Aliens was a very creditable sequel, too.
I thought the first one was better than the sequel. It was a credible sequel.
Yeah, but the sequel expanded the first one instead of starting chopping away at it.
Well, the first one would have been better as well if they had followed the original script.
They did leave a few of the really gross scenes out, if you can imagine.
It was planned to be worse.
And now you see us standing naked before you,
revealed as nerds, talking about our favorite scenes in monster movies.
Well, you better get used to it.
Because that's the way it's gonna be from now on.
And, of course, you don't, at the actual X Day event,
the pink conspiracy dupes, they'll go charging into a trash bin
in order to retrieve the gum in which Arnold Schwarzenegger has spit out and sell it on eBay.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Big Bob is here! Big Bob is here!
Big Bob!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Dude, you look like a high school sinner!
Do you think you are?
This grumpy star!
Big Bob is no joke!
No joke!
Ha ha ha ha!
Big Bob! It's a pro-
It's Bob Manny!
Give church money.
Bring him here! Come here!
I want to talk to you!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, show's breaking down!
And yet we will still continue talking and blabbing on endlessly.
I just got raped in prison, cause that's the way I'm living.
Yes, the home ministry of SLAT could die right now from a matriculation, brothers and sisters, but we continue on!
We have gone to the toilet, ladies and gentlemen, and it is all ending now.