Through the darkness of future pasts, the magician longs to see.
One chance out between two worlds.
Fire, walk with me.
We lived among the people.
I think you say convenience store.
We lived above it.
I mean it like it is, but it sounds.
I, too, have been touched by the devilish one.
Tattoo on the left shoulder.
But when I saw the faces of the gods, I was changed.
I took the entire arm off.
Mine.
His name is Mike.
His name is Bob.
You may think your husband has never killed a man, but you're wrong.
And before I take an interface with charges, he'll try to kill me.
I'll kill you.
Pity that you're only clean.
I want you to put aside my friends right now if you'reыс owing me
Why did you kill me?
You think into will have overdone him a hundred times and leave from the 968 p Els as family
Carly, you kill to stay free?
Like an American?
You kill to keep America free?
Do you kill? Do you kill for fun?
Do you kill for the love of killing?
Do you kill, Macaulay, do you kill to make America free?
Like a man?
To the ends of the world, ladies and gentlemen.
Come on, come on.
Big fear of sale at Zayner's tonight, folks.
This is how it goes.
There's a sign in the sun and the moon and the stars
that the end of the world will soon be ours.
Bible-beaten maniacs say to repent
and you better hurry up before their money's all spent.
God, he's a common man.
Why?
Why is he a common man?
You better listen up in case there's anything you missed.
The book of Revelation says it's coming real close.
If you need some more fear, well, then here's another dose.
To the ends of the world, and you haven't got time
for fucking and sucking and all of those crimes.
The police are with me.
The name is written in blood
With fires and famines
Diseases and blood
And nuclear bombs
Just waiting to blow
When God finally comes
Where's the first place he'll go?
I wonder.
If he should come, well, what would he see?
The earth run by dogs with us as his fleas.
The shit we've all done and the shit we all think.
It gets up God's nostrils and it's starting to sting.
Let's go.
Hallelujah, hallelujah Allelu
An
A
J
guitar solo
I'm gonna tell you a story about a man
that is out in the woods.
He knowed a little bit about me,
want to be part of the rat race no more. He doesn't want to be part of the business race
no more. He doesn't want to be part of the human race no more. This is the story of the
Lakeview Man.
He called the sheriff and said to come quick. About a broke in the freezer. Stole all my
steaks. Talk was still hot. The sheriff said, man, sounds to me like the Lakeview Man. The
Lakeview Man is a wild man. Lives in the woods outside of town. Howls at the moon. Lures
him if he can.
You might hear him.
The Lakeview Man.
Some say he was a soldier who came home from war. All in one piece with an emotional scar.
We all know the story. Argue about the day. Being out of the war between the states.
The Lakeview Man is a wild man.
Lives in the woods outside of town. Howls at the moon. Lures him if he can. You might
hear the Lakeview Man.
I took the shortcut to the river last night. A beard and a blur in my long beam lies. We
drank a bunch of beer. I drank a bunch of beer. I drank a bunch of beer. I drank a bunch of
beer.
Skipped a bunch of stones and I drove a little faster on the way back home.
Woo-hoo!
A dog disappears. A cow is found dead. Chicken is missing. Mountain missing its head. Shotgun gone. Print in the sand. Two-toed shy. The life of a man is a
lakefuel.
project
I Sharing the
phoena.
You might hear the Lake Fulman
Oh, yes.
Dear friends,
that was the Rainmakers
from a live performance.
I guess that's from the 25 Years On
live show in Kansas City, Missouri.
Lakeview Man.
It's about a yeti, or a crazy guy,
a subgenius, anyway,
that lives out at Lakeview Cemetery in Cleveland.
No, wait, it's a different lake.
It's somewhere in Missouri.
We were at Lakeview Cemetery in Cleveland
just yesterday.
The dog loved it.
Big boneyard.
Beautiful.
Oh, before that,
I've been playing some Dr. Bizarro
and the Disgustos,
that song, End of the World.
How about that?
That was Reverend Jimmy Ryan
playing guitar on that.
Dr. Bizarro did a bunch of albums
in the late 80s, I think.
We used to play on Hour of Slack back then,
and he's remixed them
and put them on CD,
and so that's what that's about.
There was a very brief clip of doctor music.
That was me talking about
Killing for the Love of Killing
with the Doctors for Wotan,
Philo,
but I think that was recorded in San Francisco,
so the other doctors were probably
Paul Mavridis, Doug Wellman,
Jay Kinney,
and in that particular case,
I think Gilbert Shelton.
Goodness.
The guy that,
true to the furry freak brothers.
And the opening sentence
was from the old Twin Peaks show.
Friends, for the next 11 minutes,
we're going back to X-Day
and give the younger generation a chance.
Well, some of them are younger.
Then there's peas.
This coming up is
the sub-ox scene pod crust of 20X Day.
The very beginning of it, I think.
There's about eight more hours of it.
In this case, I believe the lads are
Dr. Argus Fox,
Dr. Danny Shoggoth,
and
peas.
So, peas has problems, folks,
and we need you to get on the Patreon.
Peas has problems.
I don't know that we really want to be
solid.
We're adding a very, very special subscriber tier.
You'll have to email us to get the information.
What could not be fine with peas?
This is shenanigans.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody else took 2-May drugs and had mayhem.
Peas didn't do anything.
Peas is fine.
This is my dose.
I'm comfortable with it.
Working it out.
It's a little intense X-Day-ish.
It has been an intense X-Day.
Yes, it's been a very, very tense.
It adds a professional element to your experience, sure.
We had some new musical entertainment show up this year.
Oh, oh.
Yes.
Yoko Ono cover act, as far as I can tell.
They're not very good.
No, they were not.
See you wrong, dude.
But they're spot on.
They were fucking brilliant.
It was awesome.
It was the most rawest thing I've seen in X-Day.
Raw.
That's one way to put it.
It was raw.
Raw like sewage.
Now, I would like to know who would have the audacity to attempt a...
What's going on here?
In the middle of a radio show, sir.
You can't just drive your vehicle through a radio show.
Slow down.
That's what we say.
Anybody drives anything, you're riding a bike.
Slow down.
Now, speed up.
Speed up really fast.
Now.
Now, slow down again.
Use extreme prejudice.
Someone over there is using a light.
I don't like it.
Turn it off.
Don't slow down.
Oh, he's...
Fragrantly disobeying the laws of the camp.
Fragrantly.
As we set up here.
Arbiters.
I have fragrant disenfranchisement from the law.
Fragrant disenfranchisement.
I know.
I can smell it from over here.
Wisteria.
A town ruled by one man.
Matt Furge.
Is it just me or does natural light taste like bananas?
I find the essence of this microphone tastes like howl.
You could get smarter just by sucking on the sponge.
I've been doing that and I feel like the howl essence is getting deeper in me.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get a good sense of what's going on.
I can't have my $20.
$35.
Can I have my $20 now, Arbit?
You promised.
We don't need money.
You said no one would ever know.
Not where we're going.
Money will just be a hobby, a pleasure out there.
We can collect and spend different currencies for other currencies without ever interacting
with physical commodities.
Here we are.
Now, listen.
Seriously, gentlemen.
We're here in the vaults.
The very bowels of the...
Bulldog of potential pleasures.
Yes, we have a common deer.
We kick...
We lock Stang out of Tarzan's radio station.
Surrounded by the trappings of our church.
Surrounded by pornography of vintage styles from the 70s that may or may not have participants
in this very room actively filmed in.
I've seen your films.
They're disturbing.
But nonetheless, an art form that we have come to express and take on to ourselves as
subgeniuses.
We've watched it be destroyed and bastardized by Ivan Stang.
Or what we now suspect in a detailed investigation that was put into launch by the crack detective
team of it.
That this is no...
No, Ivan Stang is not here at all.
In any way, shape, or form.
This is an evil alien robot Stang.
Named Doug.
Except Doug is an excellent point.
Well, we were given a clue by the clowns earlier.
They said next year...
The clowns knew.
After having...
After having extracted Ivan Stang...
The false Ivan Stang's wallet.
The clowns...
Slippy tried to tell me before he mysteriously disappeared from camp.
Okay?
Beloved Slippy is nowhere to be found in camp.
But he indicated to me that he had a secret to know.
With he...
You know, everybody knows he got Stang's wallet last night, right?
Yeah.
And so...
He was generous with it in an earlier auction today.
He took out the sacred card.
He took it out.
And he saw the holy...
The real, true scribes.
That's his name.
That is yet to be determined.
Because if those bastards can change things...
Nobody...
It's...
It's an acid tan.
You have to talk into the microphone.
I'm not listening to you unless you speak into the microphone.
I can't hear you.
Put your cans on, boys.
Oh, we're doing it professional style?
Is this gonna work?
They're supposed to.
Is it?
Can you hear the show?
It's a huge difference.
Outside.
No, the cans make a huge difference.
Well, some of us are capable of facing directly forward.
This is why Hal uses it.
Who gets to edit this show?
Danny.
Fid.
Let's just ship it to Fid.
No, this is all Fid's fault.
Fid, fix this.
Make it funny.
I'm still not convinced he didn't plan everything.
Dude, he...
This entire X-Day has been one large practical joke planned by Fid Chooley.
Yep.
Too convincingly, Fid Chooley disappeared from the internet.
Fid.
Which means the entire face of the earth is involved with the meth junkie.
And he got teased.
He's so elaborate, dude.
We'll get to how your friend could get to his clinic.
Dude, I got a serious problem.
Professionalism, boys.
This is for the national market.
This is really for the archives.
This is gonna be historic.
See, this is the show.
Shit.
Fid, if you're gonna do a documentary about the Church of the fucking Subgenius,
maybe your film crew should walk around at 2 or 3 o'clock in the fucking morning
and see what really happens.
Instead of like,
okay, we're gonna script a saucer lesson right now.
That's another hot topic.
There was a documentary film crew
working to continue the corruption,
the disinformation of the Church of the Subgenius.
And these...
If there had really been a vision,
there would have been somebody making a documentary
of the documentary.
A documentary?
That they were filming here next day.
That's what they should have done.
I think documentary is one of, uh,
legumes children's stories.
You're filling my cans.
Stop it.
Can I touch your cans?
Well, I'll see if I can.
That's why I gotta sit closer to Danny.
This is why I don't think the three-fucking-person model works
in the Tarzan studio.
It just doesn't work.
You ever watched radio,
T-Shirt?
Radio is one of the...
One of the most brilliant forms
of visual exercise.
I've never seen radio, please.
Let me explain to you how it works, okay?
Step one.
Radio is tiny.
You don't see radio.
That's all you need to know.
Rule two.
There...
No.
No?
Just repeat rule one?
Over and over.
It's like Fight Club.
Over and over again.
Repetition is the soul of wit.
What about eating on the radio?
I've seen that people really want more of that.
In the background,
even a lot of people are talking
just to hear someone
nicely eating a piece of pizza or something.
It's reassuring, I think,
to the subconscious.
If only the fine campers
out in front of our faces
would bring us some of their vittles,
we could provide some of that
good quality audio content,
that ASMR.
One of the writers that I have
is that every groom room
that I have to go in
has to have ambient pizza chewing noise.
Ambient pizza chewing?
Yeah.
Very, very...
You put ambient on your pizza?
No, dude.
I like canned ambience.
Oh.
In olive oil.
I like a case of ambient for moves.
Yeah.
11.
Fine glaze of ambience.
Of condiments.
If you're going to pick one,
that's a good one.
This has been all about ambience
this X day.
It's been about the hypno-lights
and the lasers.
And the stuff and the things.
And the burning, exploding carcasses of deities.
Would you not think, again...
No, I don't think.
I try not to.
But I mean,
you're not going to take everything in
from X day.
Until I actually go into the saucer,
decompress,
analyze everything.
Sleep 12 hours.
Yeah.
I can't wait.
It's just hours away.
All right.
So let's break this down topic by topic.
Topic by topic.
All right.
The major events.
I believe we started with the new revelations
from Legume and Stang, right?
Is that...
It's been planned from the beginning, obviously.
The clues are obvious
when you know what you're looking for.
You're right.
Someone care to recount what that all was?
It was Fidd.
I'm going to put it on you guys.
It was fucking Fidd, man.
I just read it.
Fidd flew people in.
Still not convinced it's not.
Dude, you need to pull this off
because Pease is not going to want to leave X day
to take you to Columbus and back.
So you've really got to pull off this turkey thing.
Yeah, he put on his Discordian costume.
Straight to Pease and he's coming to X day.
Okay.
Before we get...
Before we get Bob,
the little fucking Bob with the little fans.
The little fans that we give people
to cool themselves off
and put in front of his face
and I'm Bob and I fucking fell for it.
I'm sorry, guys.
Craziness.
Crazy, crazy, crazy.
He's a crafty salesman.
What can I say?
What Stang hasn't told you
is it was actually Fidd Chooley
you cast into the fire last night.
I got big troubles, dude.
Tell us about your troubles, Pease.
This trip sponsored by
bailing out on Pease.
Now available in 31 flavors.
This mistake was brought to you by Pease.
31 flavors such as
cold sweats, vomiting,
shivers, headache,
pain,
additional pain.
Why did I come here?
What possessed me to think this was a good idea?
I moved
that we rename this episode
temporarily Suboxone Urine Pot.
I so mentioned.
Yeah.
I'm sorry the rehab center was closed
and your friend had to go home.
Sorry about your drug dealer having withdrawals.
Shut up, dude.
He's not my drug dealer.
He's my friend.
He's my special friend.
There's a difference.
The ability to treat standing up is a gift.
He's just my special friend.
My special male friend.
Yeah, Pease.
I meant like we know each other through the mail,
not like he's gender male.
Like that's how I knew this guy.
You know him through his mail.
Victor Frop Chopula.
He did fucking bit Julie under the Frop Chopula mask.
Oh, man.
So much has happened.
Bit Julie ass Frop Chopula.
I would have got away with it if it wasn't for
bit Julie at the paper cube Friday.
But it was a joke.
Off the top of my head.
Man in the computer.
Just treat me like a maid.
Like a regular joe.
Well I guess that I'd make it
And have something to show
So for now I just guess I'll just fake it
And forget everything that I know
Every bag's always thin words
Twisted inside and out
Could someone please tell me
What the fuck life's about
There ain't no big payoff
At the end of your road
If you think that you're way off
No matter what you've been told
Yeah
If your savior is coming
He won't like what he'll find
Every one of God's children
Driven half out of their mind
Every bag's always thin words
Twisted this way and that
Could someone please tell me
Where it's supposed to be at
Yeah
Well I think the time has come
No matter where you're at in the plot so far
Just put down your script now
Just forget all the stuff you're doing in your life
Yeah you know all the stuff you're doing
You were told you're supposed to do
Now if you were ever in a rock band
And got screwed over by a club owner
Even if you played in a wheeling
No wheeling
Just to ease your troubled consciousness
We brought in at great expense
The Consumer Product Vocal Ensemble
Direct from Seattle
Yeah we know we haven't quite reached Nirvana yet
But we keep trying
We've got Dan Liss over there
Dressed up as John Paul
Doing his impression of Kurt Cobain
You got the hair Dan?
Okay
Now we're going for the big record deal here
We've spared no expense
Rich Poston is going to be having a grunge guitar war
A little bit later over there
We'll even throw in a little Styx
And a little bit of a
Supercat Dirt
Truly inspirational guys
And now for the fake bar room scene
Direct from Maddie's
We're going to duplicate
Right here in the recording studio
The now infamous I Bob Dead Rockstar Costume Contest
Up first for her submission in the semi-finals
Direct from the Crescent City camera crew Elvira
Hi guys ready for the big one?
Yeah
We're ready
Now in an attempt to get more mileage out of this musical vampire
We've got the bar all set up
For any record executive listening
We have Beefeater for a really dry martini
A really dry martini
Here's how to make one
Some Beefeater gin
Plenty of ice
With a twist of lemon
And an olive too
An olive too
Shake it up
And not stirred
Then we'll all get drunk and play the entire song backwards
Singing this song backwards
Oh no we won't play all of the song backwards
We'll pick up on Dave here I hope
Yeah it's Bo Dave alright
Bo Dave
Bo Dave woman Bo Dave-er-y
I was wondering which one of our beautifully Monogrammed signature customized background
Sound's playing in your mind tonight
he what?
Wait a minute
er which Disco?
And that's the same one I always have in mind right now
Us
Poor
High
negotiator
ID
points
I'm
Streaming
From
The
roots
dat
And
Yeah, that's what made me think that what if some, like, Uber man,
not a driving person around in a car or something,
but some sort of, you know, super evil patron of the arts,
some necrophiliac or something like that,
would have the actual stones and underpants to pull off a ploy like that.
You know what I mean?
Well, I lost track of which foil it was by the time you got to the end of it,
but that's okay.
Well, I was thinking that some, like, Uber mastermind
could make everybody have the same soundtrack.
Background soundtrack.
Well, I'm sure that's what the conspiracy is ultimately shooting for.
Yeah.
Maybe the background music soundtrack for all of the New World Order
will be a Muzak version,
a comforting, easy-listening version of Bob Dylan's
The Times They Are.
A changing.
Or perhaps A Hard Rain's Gonna Fall.
Yes.
I've actually heard that.
In the 70s, I got into an elevator,
and this insipid Muzak was on,
and I realized what I was listening to was A Hard Rain's Gonna Fall.
Wow.
And I thought, I guess it's not.
That is so suggestibly horny and deregulation and everything going on there.
You know, the warehouse outing and everything.
Oh, speaking of music, I played that song we just played before you called in
that you didn't hear, Dave,
was called Every Back's Always Thing Words,
and that was Dr. Bizarro and the Disgustos.
Just as you always said it was.
Yeah.
I never once conflicted your arguments that you said that that's who that was
when you were doing your credit role,
especially when you were doing your Sam and your main role.
Well, that wasn't the song that I was going to play that I decided was about me.
Well, then your mind control was in your cinnamon roll.
Mind control in cinnamon roll.
Look into the spiral of the cinnamon roll.
Dr. Sinister is here.
Jays.
And Princess Wee.
Is here.
Well, I'm glad to know that somebody's here because they could be elsewhere.
We could.
Well, we are going to be elsewhere,
because we're moving back to Stang Ranch in Texas before Halloween.
Boo hiss.
Well, we'll be back in the Slacker Mansion of Cleveland Heights next summer,
but the house won't be so cluttered then,
and the Texas house will be terribly cluttered.
And that's even after...
Huh?
It's all full of gypsies in their shiny pink underpants.
I'm trying to find some gypsies in pink underpants to rent our place while we're gone,
but they have to be gypsies that are already our friends that we know.
So friends in Cleveland that we know, you can rent the Slacker Mansion.
It's not haunted anymore, and it's very convenient to shopping and schools.
And, yeah.
And there's a fence now.
Wow.
And it won't be so cluttered.
Like I say, we're moving the equivalent of a six-bedroom house,
only they're not bedrooms.
They're Tarzan's radio station stuff.
And we're going to have to build a shed or buy a shed for Mennonites.
A big shed.
Mennonites.
I love your pronunciation of that word.
It's normally Mennonites.
If you read me it real, real badly, it could be Mennonites.
Well, the shed is a real exciting thing to me.
We already have the plastic letters that go on the outside of the shed,
which will say,
Destructionist Evidence Museum Office.
Because the museum is not actually in the shed.
The shed will be full of metal shelves full of tapes.
Yes, tapes.
Tapes and tapes.
CDRs.
And souls.
All the canisters of souls from our...
But anyway, the shed is so exciting to me.
And I'm going to play a Rainmaker song so you can hear it.
And you'll see that it actually is about us this week.
Even though the song was done in, I think, 2014,
I was listening to the lyrics of it and I couldn't believe it.
It was like, how did they know?
You're needing a parallel life.
We're going to all be quiet for a minute,
but I'm going to play a song.
I'm going to play this song, okay?
I know you can interpret it when it's over.
It's short.
It's only about two and a half minutes.
I can hardly wait.
Here, you won't.
I'm on a red book, a carpet in the red bed room
Cause the movers are a-comin' and they'll be here soon
I'm off to Colorado, there's roadblocks
And the old man's in the oar
Gonna mine me a diamond at a second-hand store
Gonna love my neighbor like the good book said
Put some miles between the quick and the dead
Come on, let's go to the swingin' shed
I was getting back to normal after years of planning
Realizing everybody needs somebody to blame
Still painting with a hammer on my masterpiece
With my waterlust to sit around in a pan of grease
All I'm meant about the books that I never had read
Wondered if my suitcase was still under the bed
Come on, let's go to the swingin' shed
I'm at a loss
carpet when I'm starting to drift.
She once called me sleeping on the midnight shift.
She cried my way when they assumed I'm dead.
The very next word that you're gonna hear said, come on, let's go to the swinging shed.
Come on, let's go to the swinging shed.
It was the new cutting edge of popular music when you were just a wee tot.
Well, yeah, I was gonna say when I was a wee tot, that sounds more like Elvis.
Well, yeah, it sounds like rockabilly.
Yeah, I remember being a little kid and seeing...
Did you know the rockabilly standards and also the honker music of early rock and roll days
actually happened in the late 1940s, not even in the 50s.
But it was considered race music, so it wasn't considered on the variety of guild map.
Swing.
If I can't whoop it, I'll go down.
But I'll go down swinging.
Go down swinging.
You told me the thing.
I think it's so intricately produced as far as, you know, magnet music and stuff like that.
I mean, it's just so wonderful that you can have a hard time focusing on the lyrics,
which are as important as a fat belly button to an artist.
Speaking as a Clevelander, I've always opposed to the notion that it was Alfred who coined the term rock and roll because he didn't.
No.
Long before...
He didn't.
What?
No.
That's funny because we were standing at his tombstone in Lakeview Cemetery yesterday.
Yes, we were.
Just yesterday.
He popularized the use of that word to describe the kind of music that he was popularizing over the radio in the 50s.
But the actual term rock and roll goes back several decades before.
And that...
Yes.
It was part of the African-American vernacular.
And it makes me miss our old caller, Master Sean, who would always say, play sex music.
Oh yeah.
Rock and roll was a term for sex before it was a term for television.
We're still channeling him.
Oh yeah.
Como va?
We thought he was... that it was a mantra.
And we used it as such and it worked.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
We'd get upset about something and we'd just start going, oh yeah.
Especially if you play Bolero.
Well, it's just a short version of that.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Which preachers have been saying forever.
Hey, I've got a final exam for everybody here.
Final exam?
Yeah.
I'm springing this on you.
We don't have to sit up and put our socks on the strippers or the stirrups, do we?
No, it's real easy.
There's no essay questions.
Although, if I know you...
There we go.
Will be.
Pop quiz.
Yeah.
It's a ha-ha.
Pop quiz in the rocket factory.
Yeah, our friend Roger, the good Reverend Roger, put this together.
It's, are you ready for the finals?
It's an end times final exam.
The first question is, there'll be four choices.
One, when you wake up screaming, it's because, A.
I don't even need four choices.
Donald Trump really is president.
B. Nazis really are walking around in broad daylight.
C. Weasels ran off with your spouse.
Or D. All of the above.
I'd say D.
No, it's E.
I wake up screaming because of what I ate the night before.
Okay, so I knew there'd be a lot of E's on this.
Donald Trump is not a demomantic spirit.
Just because he's a multibarrel, a brahmin or something, or a fat cat.
You know.
Okay, here's another one.
The collection cup for date night is now collecting, A. Vomit.
B. Blood.
C. Your fingernail clippings.
D. Someone else's fingernails.
D again for me.
E again for me, man.
I mean, actually, maybe it's a mixture.
I mean, I often have boogers underneath my fingernails.
So, like.
A mixture of boogers and fingernail clippings.
Ewww.
It doesn't make you feel inferior, though.
It makes you feel like you've got a big fat full of tummy and you're ready to go.
You just took over the bus.
You're in charge.
It's making me hungry.
Well, that's because you like sodium flatulence and all those different Earth candies.
That you can't really find anymore in the Soviet orbit.
Okay, number three.
You are running because, A. Insane cops.
B. Supersonic Nazi health creatures from beneath the Hollow Earth.
C. More weasels.
Or you are running because, D. You still have legs.
E. Because I feel like torturing myself.
How is anyone meant to abuse their body like running?
F. I'm running because my legs are on fire.
D. C. I mean, B. Weasels again.
R. I'm sorry.
I like the idea of little weasels nipping at your nose like a Santa Claus device used to have.
You think that sounds like fun, don't you?
Well, no, I know it's fun.
I've seen the little children scream and scrunder and run away from Grandpa's plunder.
Especially when the artichokes are on fire.
And they have been mighty meaty lady me laddy.
Now stop crying, Dave.
You're crying because...
A. I'm weeping softly.
You vaguely remember having loved ones.
B. Tear gas.
C. Nobody witnessed you all shiny and chrome.
Or you're crying because, D. Irregardless made it into the dictionary.
Irregardless made it into the dictionary?
Double D.
Is that really true?
I don't know.
I mean, can we vote on that? Or is it just...
Let's make that...
Everything's in the dictionary now.
God dammit, I am such an underman.
I am such an untermensch.
But at least I don't use a word like irregardless.
If that's actually in the dictionary now, then what does that make me?
Then we might as well give up.
I'm just gonna Crimea River.
This is called Gloucester.
No, Crimea is a peninsula, not a river.
Oh, okay.
It's a huge peninsula sticking out of the former Soviet Union's rear end.
Down there by Kiev and all those other parts.
I don't know.
Okay.
And you know why?
Why?
Because I said so.
That's why.
No, I didn't really.
I have a geography book and I know where I'm headed.
Same place we're all going someday soon.
Why won't you eat your pudding?
Because it's caramelized and ugly.
No, that wasn't one of the options.
You didn't eat your pudding.
You won't eat your pudding because A, you didn't eat all your meat.
B, you knew the guy the pudding used to eat.
C, you no longer have the required orifices.
Or D, it's frozen solid like everything else for a hundred miles in any direction.
All right, now hold on.
B, like are we talking about jello pudding or are we talking about like black pudding?
Oh, I don't know.
It's pudding that you knew the guy that the pudding used to be.
Well, that's why I did eat it.
I figured it was the best way to respect his memory.
I don't know.
Ugh.
Many cultures do that.
This is not unusual.
Wow.
I mean, Christians do that to this day.
Yeah, they exonerate the body—
To eat the body of their saviour?
—the body of Christ by eating his flesh every symbolically, ever communionary through
Eucharistic development especially in the Third World countries where the islands are
now as smooth as a baby's forehead.
Scoots take a long, long way, fringe.
Yeah, they did smooth over some of those islands.
Yeah.
I found out my cousin was on St. Martin when that was going on.
Goodness.
Yeah, but she's okay.
That's really fortunate.
I'm sorry, Agent.
Okay, even though the earth is vomiting up the dead and the government hasn't issued any edicts in weeks,
you, A, are safe in your buried storage container, eating your previous relatives, offspring, etc.
Or B, at least still have your guns.
C, managed to save your waifu pillow.
I don't get that.
You don't want to know.
D, all of the above.
Look, when it comes to edicts, okay, if you still have edicts after a major storm,
that means you still have access to internet porn.
Yeah, or, you know, constantly.
It's full of edicts.
The spirit of Dr. Dark just wafted through here.
You don't know what a waifu is?
No.
All right, so a waifu is a phenomenon that you see amongst the Weebo community,
which is a subset of the neckbeard community.
The waifu is a female anime character that,
a male Weebo neckbeard will worship as if it were an actual person and actually his wife.
The word itself is derived from the rough Japanese approximation of the pronunciation of the English word wife.
A lot of them will have body-sized pillows.
Not a blow-up doll, but a body-sized pillow with some anime girl painted on it, and that's the waifu.
I've been missing out once again.
You really have not been missing anything.
Uh-oh, we're back to the weasels again.
Your neighbors are all raptured, leaving you behind with the weasels.
You, A, help yourself to their stuff.
B, console yourself that at least that crooked Hillary didn't win.
C, run to the nearest church and explain to God that he has overlooked your exceptionalism.
Or D, run to the nearest church and explain to God that he has overlooked your exceptionalism.
Dance while the weasels rip your flesh.
I dance while I rip the flesh of weasels. I don't know about you.
Yeah, I remember that was a song in the Soviet Union under Frank Sinatra's reign.
You remember Frank Sinatra or was it Sinatra?
You know, Zelio Polis, one of them guys like that, used to run the gyros place.
So that's why I think that because it's a revolution code, it's often called revolutionary consummation.
Meaning you just reach a certain point.
Or you just go and urinate on some policeman's shoes just to get your head banged in.
You know, just to get something going and like to take pictures of and stuff.
That's what's trending right now.
You first.
Well, I already got my, took my lumps and my applesauce, so to speak.
That's what you boomers are always saying.
And everything's your fault.
Everything is the boomers fault.
I always thought it was my parents' generation's fault.
They were pre-World War II.
You know, depression people.
It was all their fault.
The greatest generation.
Yeah, the people with three eyeballs and three nostrils.
Well, especially now, these churches, so geez, with three nostrils, which are very important to,
just to getting around the elderly assisted living facility.
You gotta know which way to go.
And, you know, smell-wise, so to speak.
That's why dogs are so popular there.
Some of them even have bands.
You know, all-dog bands.
And I know sometimes a little keyboard work.
It's a little gamey, so to speak.
And so does, like, a guitar lead.
But there's some pretty hot dog bands.
I know the Bonzo Dog Band, but I don't know about these other dog bands.
I hate the Chihuahuas.
Well, you know, they were meant to be food.
And so, since the days of Bonzoomers, curse everybody knows it.
If you eat enough carnivore, carnivorous, you know what I'm talking about.
The Chihuahua vows hurt my ears.
What do you got against Chihuahua?
Hurt my ears.
Yeah.
Piercing, loud yipping.
They're not dogs.
There's a really tasty cheese called, you know, called Chihuahua cheese.
Yeah.
It's the state that borders.
From Chihuahua.
But it's also a location.
It's not just a dog.
That's where Ciudad Juarez is.
It's the happiest place on Earth.
The state of Chihuahua.
Well, everybody knew that from Emiliano Zapata to Pancho Vila.
They knew that.
But when they were talking about queso con crema or queso blanco, they were talking Chihuahua.
Now, if you really want to insult a person from Chihuahua, you call them a Chihuahuaño.
That's the dog.
Person from Chihuahua is Chihuahuancy.
Ah.
Unless I got that backwards, in which case I'm going to make a whole bunch of enemies.
They're small and yippy people.
Yeah.
Okay, you are placed in charge of morale.
A, fallout is the new confetti.
B, whiteboard your optimized personal demise.
C, weasels are just fun with fangs.
Or your new slogan is, D, I'm not crying.
Well, I mean, you're talking about morale, and I'm just immediately thinking that the beatings will continue until morale improves.
Right.
Who's that a quote from?
I saw that on a bumper sticker.
At X Day, the last time I was there.
About five years ago.
Pop goes the weasel.
Your house is surrounded by zombies.
You, A, don't notice.
B, don't care.
C, are green with envy.
Or D, are a member of the zombie horde.
You could answer those all of the above a lot of times.
Are we back to E and E digs?
It's just another trick question.
E-butts.
The doctrine's been by October 5th or something.
You know, I have to say.
To get student loans and to have your forehead blowed.
I have to say I am jealous and envious of the zombies.
They have a certain clarity of purpose that I will never have in my life.
That's true.
It's pretty simple.
They know what they want.
And they know how to get it.
I'm not so sure if they know how to get it.
I think a lot of that's Hollywood Transylvania or transliteration.
When they try.
To portray some objective form of humor as a spiritual epithet, so to speak.
You know, are you calling somebody a demonic form or a space cadet?
Hey, are you making fun of the church or the subgenius?
Of course.
It's part of the religious life.
That's the one thing we don't allow.
Meaning the religious life is allowed.
F them if they can't take a joke unless they're a high E-butt.
Here's the very last.
What did you just say?
I said F them if they can't take a joke unless they're a high E-butt.
In which case, you know, you shouldn't have to.
Here's the last question.
And you better get this one right because you've gotten all the rest of them wrong.
Starvation has given you visions.
You realize, A, the Mormons, of all people, had it right.
You scream your rage to the universe.
It doesn't care.
B.
You have run out of relatives and your storage container's air is getting pretty manky.
C.
That tickling sensation?
Weasels.
D.
Starvation has given you visions.
You realize, D, you're late for work again.
D.
You, okay.
I also see in B, too, because Frank's app is reasonable.
My flesh is obviously the incognition for this literature that we're listening to right now.
It's not like, you know, Balzac or, uh, on our radio, Balzac or Chekhov or somebody.
Or Edix.
Yeah, or Edix and...
Use a fine film, you know.
Well, it's the end of the show and we gotta go back to Texas.
I alphabetized and boxed all of the fiction novel paperbacks that I have.
And they take up nine cubic feet.
So is that three by three by three?
One by one by one foot box and there's nine boxes.
Okay.
Of paperback books.
A was big because of Asimov.
B was big because of Baxter.
C was big because of Arthur C. Clark.
You can see what kind of a nerd I am.
Isn't it Baxter, Bear and Arthur like...
And Brynn.
Yeah, there's like...
Three, yeah.
Yeah, there are.
My favorites were all there.
That actually took up four boxes.
Anyway, we're going back to the goat farm.
So goat bless America.
Goat.
My holy mother of goat.
Goat, damn it.
We're going back.
Oh, goat.
Uh, to, well, it actually is a goat ranch.
It's a stang ranch.
While it is the new headquarters of the Church of the Subgenius.
And has been before in certain ways.
It's also a goat ranch.
Yep, that's the goat's truth.
At least that's what you tell the tax man.
Oh, that was cute.
In goat we trust.
My goat in himmel.
Oh, for goat's sake.
That's terrible.
Oh, goat.
Where's Dr. Dark when we need him?
He was truly goat's gift to man.
Yes.
When it came to horrible, horrible.
Horrible puns.
Indeed.
Goat.
You haven't heard the worst of my puns.
Psychopath finder was also equally.
Just made you want to strangle him until he showed up.
Goat mittens.
Everybody was somebody else's name with a,
with three parts that were somehow sexual orientation.
And each one of them fell out of the window one time,
I think, because it was like the,
um, oh, did not Descartes.
What's that guy's name?
Friends, you've been listening to the horse.
Subgenius radio minister.
History hour of slack.
Number 1641.
That's it.
We got, we got two done last week.
His doctor sinister wasn't here, but we're going to get two done this week.
His doctor sinister is here.
Yeah.
So Dave, you should call back.
When, when, what should he do?
ASAP.
Should he just hang on?
Might as well.
Okay.
I'm going to put on some something.
Oh, oh, I know what I'll put on.
I'll put on everybody listening to this show.
Oh yeah.
Well, you should credit who came up with that wonderful vehicle and device that,
um, remember the questionnaire we just did.
No, that was, uh, the good Reverend Roger, but, uh, you are.
Oh, and if you want to know more about the church, the subgenius and anything else,
subgenius.com.
But now we're going to end the show with this song by the psycho skeletons,
an instrumental with the name of pitch war.
Good night, Dave.
.
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
Thank you.