And, okay, well, so this is an hour of slack right now.
A peaceful hour of slack after a scary morning of having to go back to get up early and go back to sleep again.
Are we going to get to see Stan looking like the dreamer or the dud?
One minute. One minute.
You know, I almost, I'm almost going to miss this place.
I'm going to miss worrying about money constantly.
I'm going to miss the gnawing anxiety about whether I'm going to make it through the next day.
I'm going to really, really miss the arthritis and making subgenius membership packs.
And you know what I'm going to miss most of all?
Changing the number a hundred times every time I put a new hour of slack out.
All these, oh, okay, I better quit whining.
I'll be stuck in here.
You know, if you're whining about your existence,
you'll be stuck there.
You'll be stuck there forever.
God damn it.
Right, I'll be stuck here in this spot with a bunch of people staring at me.
Is it?
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
I blame the dubstep.
Yes, the fury of the elements a few moments ago made itself known.
Now we're in a lulled period of relaxation and contemplation.
What did Bob or the exes mean when they either changed the schedule or handed us the wrong date or lied or were wrong?
What did they mean?
What did they mean by being, by someone being wrong?
You are convinced that they meant well.
Well, no, not at all.
I don't, you know, the funny thing is we've all for 20 years now, we've been anxious to go,
well, everyone assumes that we're somehow going to Planet X with the exes.
But do we really?
Is there any doctrinal?
spot in the pamphlets or the books that says where we're going?
Yes, there's an extensive diagram.
Oh, that's right.
But what about Planet X itself?
I mean, we have all of our own...
No, that's the subgenius afterlife, isn't it?
Yes, the subgenius afterlife.
The saucers take you to the port authority building
from where you begin the long progression into the many subgenius afterlives.
And one can assume it has to be a rocky Earth-like world
with our same or less gravity, but certainly no more.
In the Goldilocks zone, they call it.
Yes, exactly.
A planet that's just right.
No, you can have a just right planet in the Goldilocks zone
with gravity four times that of Earth, can't you?
Yes.
And in fact, I believe that the nearest happy-looking planet
is indeed four times the gravity of Earth.
So if we were to...
Oh, say the Xs never show up.
We have to build our own ships and go to the nearest planet.
At light speed, it would still take us 22 years,
and when we got there, I would weigh 600 pounds.
Yes, forget that.
We don't need a heavy-gravity world.
If anything, we need a light one.
We need a planet of female human breasts
so that Mr. Sister's dream of the sea of titties can come true.
His and our crumbs.
Oh, really?
Oh, you didn't see that cartoon?
I thought that was a sea of keisters.
Well, you got that, too.
And then there's the Hal Robbins 50-mile road of knives.
That wasn't...
That wasn't a good thing.
No.
No, not any more than Dr. Legume's planet of broken glass,
which I'm sure he'd like to send us all to just for fun.
Well, you have to ask Dr. Legume about that.
Well, I guess we don't have to worry about planning our rupture for another year.
We are far away from having to plan that than we will be later on in the year.
So, uh...
The year...
The human mind is always circled around knowledge of such things,
but has never attained it.
Well, it sure scares the hell out of me.
Should we do a traditional second countdown?
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Hey, guys! Welcome to the...
Oh, they don't count in base ten. That's the problem.
Oh, it's always something.
The hell?
Well, I'm Junior Whispero Baptist.
He faced us.
I'm Junior Heaven's Gate?
Same difference.
Well, smoke if you got them.
Well...
Damn.
Now, remember, folks, don't look at me and don't blame Bob.
It was the men from Planet X that made that whole...
I want triple my money back.
Not yet.
Although...
We did that already.
There's one thing that we haven't publicly announced,
and I guess this would be the time to mention it.
You know the original handwritten note that says,
the world ends July 5th...
7 a.m. July 5th, 1998.
And you know there was the little mix-up with the 1998
where it appeared that it had somehow been written upside down
and then turned back over, and so we weren't sure.
Well, we did a carbon dating on the note.
And everything was fine,
except that it's...
It seemed that the words...
The letters L-Y had been added to the J-U years later.
Like, most of the note dated from around 1953,
which would make sense.
But then the L-Y was added carefully
with a very similar ballpoint pen,
but not quite the same ink.
And that was where the FBI detected the little discrepancy.
So it...
Could have said June 5th.
Just to let everybody know, this is new information.
It could be June.
There was somebody added the lie.
I don't understand. I don't get it.
Now, we have a spare microphone up here.
Yes, we can call for another yakker.
One more.
Fat Mandy is waving her hand.
She might just be the one to save this so-called show.
Well, she wasn't up at 7 a.m. this morning, and we were...
Oh, no, Fat Mandy. Do we have a chair?
Oh, um, no. All the chairs...
Here.
We will, in just a moment.
We have a chair and a cherub for Fat Mandy.
No, we have the chair.
We have the chair and the cherub.
Can you get a seat?
And that cherub is yours.
Test your microphone there.
Now, see, there's somebody who knows how to use a mic.
Yes, you put your lips right near it instead of being way back here.
For some reason, we couldn't get our other ranters to perform basic radio maneuvers like putting the lips near the mic.
But at least we have one that does now.
I like putting my lips near a mic.
Next to you, putting your lips near a mic.
Next to Ivan, putting his lips near a mic.
And we all three are putting our lips near a mic together.
The triumvirate of hovering lips.
I'm in love, baby. Let's get married.
Can such...
Can we all get married later?
...closed lips perceive?
We can all get married now.
We can all get married now?
By the power invested in me, I now pronounce us all man, wife, thing, it, and wallet.
Irrevocably married.
Okay, that's done. We're all married.
Yay!
Oh, I don't know.
I can't wait to consummate it.
You are all forgiven for any sins, and you can do anything you want to from now on.
That's it. Easy, wasn't it?
Well, that's worth the price of salvation right there, I'll tell you what.
I have to put in a slight warning. There is a qualification.
The police can still also do whatever they want as well.
Ah, Senator Speck is here.
That means we'll have the beat. The beat.
Right.
The thing that makes the kids go wild. The beat.
Is it gonna be a dance party?
Yeah, there is gonna be a... There'll be a dance party as soon as I can get to it.
I like dancing.
A dance party in my pants.
Where are we dancing?
At... actually, the...
Right here.
...the ball. I don't know where the ball is.
I thought it was here.
We don't know yet.
We don't... You know, and that's the mystery.
At this time, we haven't been told.
The beauty...
The search of the subgenius, we don't know yet.
But unlike most of the bullshit religions, we admit it.
...don't know where the ball is.
Oh, what about...
We don't know a damn thing.
We don't know where the hell the ball is.
Except...
We know we can trust in Bob.
Praise Bob.
We can trust Bob to screw us.
But he'll probably do it the good way. Some ways are fun.
As G. Gordon Gordon once said.
He said a lot of things, that G. Gordon Gordon.
I quote...
Well, you know, the early doctors were fed a lot of Bob's garbage.
He would flush his thoughts directly into the heads of whoever he could find.
And there weren't that many subgeniuses in 1980.
And all of them have their...
They're on the board of directors now.
Every single one of them.
We...
You know, to some of us, Dr. Legume is a new kid.
Well, it's a pity.
G. Gordon Gordon couldn't be among us at this X-Day.
But we have every confidence that in the fullness of time, he shall return.
Not this year.
You sure have a pretty mouth fat, Mandy.
I'll put some glitter on it for you later if you're lucky.
Is that where all that glitter came?
I keep finding...
I'm still finding glitter all over me.
It's pervasive.
It never goes away.
Does it just grow at outdoor festivals, glitter?
It gets in your eyes and cuts tiny little cuts into your cornea?
The animals that try to eat each other...
Glitter causes eye butthurt.
Eye flutter?
Eye butthurt.
Oh, eye butthurt.
Glitter causes eye butthurt.
Eye butthurt New York.
How would you spell that in glyphs?
I don't know.
I've got a great idea.
Somebody made a shirt that's Eye Dobbshead New York.
It's my second favorite to the one with Eye King Kong New York.
Well, first you have to get to New York.
Yeah, right.
Then you need your giant monster or to become a giant monster.
To channel or unleash your own inner giant monster.
I thought I was going to be a giant monster by now.
Honestly, I thought we were going to get aboard those saucers at seven.
I'd be a giant monster tearing up Tokyo or Dallas.
There will be other times.
Dallas has never been destroyed by a giant monster.
Not yet.
Yeah.
Yes, and what kind of giant monster?
Perhaps grasshoppers.
Huge grasshoppers like at the beginning of the end.
They were in Chicago.
With wings of flame.
Huge grasshoppers invaded Chicago.
I don't know if anything ever invaded Dallas though.
They were so powerful.
They were so powerful that they could leave their shadows on the sky.
As they crawled up buildings, they would keep crawling, go off the building onto the sky.
And it would just die the sky with a giant flying, flaming cricket shadow?
Well, it was an easy special effect.
They had a photograph of buildings on a...
With grasshoppers crawling on them.
But we shouldn't really destroy the magic by telling how it's done.
And then Las Vegas was invaded by the amazing colossal man, you know.
You know, he'd have to be a lot more colossal to invade Las Vegas now because it's much
bigger than it was in the amazing colossal.
We could bring locusts.
I brought locusts to a gig once, a puppet show.
Puppet show locusts during the trials and tribulations of Dirty Santa.
Locusts.
Did people freak out to have insects in the room?
Well, not so much because we made them out of paper and rice inside.
And we shook them and they made...
And another locust came and carried away a grain of wheat.
I hate it when my wheat's missing.
Until finally, Pharaoh was bankrupt, as you know.
I may have mentioned this, Dr. Legume made a pinata filled with locusts just to scare the girls.
But the girl who broke the pinata happened to be an insectologist.
So she loved it when Legume's insect legions showered down on her.
Yeah, you can...
Locust failed.
So, Fat Mandy, are you going to be performing tonight with your new cherub?
I'm going to be performing tonight.
I hadn't worked a number out with the cherub yet, but she could come to rehearsal.
We have to have rehearsal.
Do we still have time for rehearsal?
Dr. Hal and Princess Weed, do we still have time?
Well, I don't know.
We're going to have to make some time.
Maybe.
I wanted to play...
I wanted to do the...
I wanted to debut...
Dr. Hal's hit single, X Day, My Subgenius Home.
I thought we rehearsed that in Pittsburgh.
Yeah, but Hal wasn't there.
We wandered into some bar and just took over and rehearsed for X Day.
We did.
It was like a dress rehearsal that we charged people to come to.
And we made tens and tens of dollars.
Then I awoke.
It was just a dream.
My thirst for Slatnot in pain I find.
I wrote out a check to Ivan Stang and signed the bottom line.
Oh Bob, won't you let me live?
And all that is mine, I, John, surely will give.
Oh lift me away in your great shining ship To my Subgenius home.
Oh wear me away in your great shining ship To my Subgenius home.
Vamos a effectivement.
This stage is quiet, though invite the audience.
It's good.
Reverend Angry Larry, do you know if the slot rods are going to be playing tonight?
Oh, good. Okay, so that's three extra things on the...
This will be a packed night.
It'll be a marathon, epic night.
We want as many girls dancing on stage as possible.
Oh, that's good. I'm wearing my mermaid costume.
Did you hear that, everyone?
It's a surf beach party.
Enough preaching. I want to hear Tommy Amoeba.
Enough. Enough.
Reverend Angry Larry wants a beach party tonight.
He wants girls in swimsuits dancing on stage during the performance.
I want girls in swimsuits dancing on stage during the slot rod set as well.
Well, you just have to make it known, and then it can happen.
But who brings a swimsuit to a clothing optional campground?
Well, a bikini thing is a surf thing.
Production needed to send out a memo about this.
¶¶
guitar solo
Anyway, that's all part of the beach party.
It will crown the evening's entertainment.
I think there's going to be crowning?
It will be the summit of the whole Fandango.
Therein we supply our own Annette Funicello.
Stick was telling us he's going to dress up as Annette Funicello.
Nice.
Yes, Annette Funicello.
Yes.
Star of stage screenplay.
And other important notes.
There's this stuff out there that seems to try to capture your feet called mud.
I don't know if you're familiar with mud.
It has a consistency not unlike the Play-Doh you ate as a child.
The romance of mud.
Please be careful in the mud because unlike the Play-Doh you ate as a child, it is very slippery.
You can't hurt mud.
You can stomp on it.
No, I'm more worried about them, not the mud.
Oh, okay.
I trust the mud can take care of itself.
That's right.
The mud does quite a fine job taking care of itself.
And in fact, apparently it's very prolific in reproduction, I've noticed.
It'll try and kill you.
It will.
It will try to kill you.
But now we have the sunshine and the mud will be busily melting away until the next down blast from the heavens.
And since the Exist didn't show up again.
Occupied as they were by their own concerns.
And we won't even worry about who to blame, Stang.
But I now that the planet isn't going to be destroyed today.
It actually was.
As far as we know.
It was.
We're all on the same pleasure dome because I got a text message and apparently the rupture happened and we just didn't notice.
Well, whatever.
Whatever planet we're on.
It's ours for now.
So please clean up your crap.
Huh?
Thank you.
You know, I mean, we're stuck with this one for at least another year.
Okay.
So could you please pick up the crap you left out?
Leave no trace.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Could you please organize your crap into neat orderly piles?
And the crap that you wish to no longer.
Keep.
There's an organized pile called a trash can.
Just throw the crap pile.
Thank you.
Well, I mean, not to be all Mama Pisces and all.
You don't throw your beer bottles down the pooper scoopers.
You know, Mandy, I think you may be part and I'm not sure, but I've been informed that any any subgenius that has boobs.
Boobs.
Or.
And or a vagina is part of something called the matriarchy.
The matriarchy.
Yes.
Apparently, the matriarchy is some is different than the hierarchy.
We are some other group who are secretly controlling everything, including we and Petal and all of the other and the other females in the church are apparently I was informed are taking over.
Oh.
And the matriarchy is.
Well, just let me know when the meeting over.
Good.
They can take over all the responsibility and do all the work.
It's about time.
You know, we get credit.
Been too unequal for so long.
Yes.
You're the maniarchs.
The maniarchs versus the matriarchs.
Friends.
Roman.
Subgeni.
Yeti.
Please.
When playing with your purse, would you so with safety?
I got a brand new two tone dad.
Do I got it just for you?
You know, I can do with my friend.
You do.
Don't die.
Do I simply hope the hairs do not hide away?
Then you might.
Don't that.
Do this.
They already think.
So I'll show it to you anyway.
I can't.
You.
We are.
I mean, I'm not.
Yeah.
I'm not.
You don't need to go all the way into town and try to find out and find a laundry mat.
No, no, no.
You don't need to do that.
You can go over to that merchandise table and buy with cash money.
New clean mud.
Beer and sweat free clothing for you to wear.
And you can anoint it yourself with your own mud, beer and sweat while performing a good
service and donating to the home for slackless children.
So please pay attention to priestess Pisces admonition.
Wow.
We have a wonderful T-shirt showing an egg is growing a chicken for the bulldog auction.
Just a preview of the.
Bulldog auction.
It's kind of a small size that we might need it for a small person like Mickey.
Large small.
Large.
It's a small large.
Large ain't as large as it used to be.
I thought shirts came in small, medium XL, extra large, elephantine and circus tent.
Well, anyway, it's it'll fit most people apparently.
Small, large for large, small.
Small.
Oh, okay.
Well, you know, the bigger they are, the nicer they are.
Why is there poo poo on this table?
I thought Reverend Stang had given up poo poo.
No, not at all.
Those were brought up as a gift.
And unfortunately, the octopus inside that can is dead.
He was chewing on that octopus the other day.
And I think we all partook of it in some degree.
Perhaps taking into ourselves some of the life.
The likeness of the octopus.
It's insortado.
They're just so smart.
And that's really the thing that freaks me out about eating them.
It's not the squeakiness of their flesh and the suckers as they grasp at my gums so much
as the fact that I know it's really intelligent.
And it's full of proteenas.
It is full of proteenas.
You see, the primitive believes that by consuming something, one gains its attributes.
And so perhaps we can be similarly similar.
Primitive.
Or just let Stang have all the octopus for himself.
Give me that poo poo.
Now all this stuff is going to be filtered and organized and then appear in some form on the radio at some future time.
Just as the poo poo is filtered and organized after Stang consumes it and appears in...
Never mind.
Well, you can carry that analogy along, certainly.
I saw a man make pasta out of squid once.
It doesn't say very nice things about our broadcast, but as soon as our broadcast is flushed out into the greater world, it can have some effect.
Can you make squid out of pasta?
Squid pasta.
He pureed the squid and he formed it like through a...
We were talking about the Play-Doh earlier.
Oh, okay.
Kind of like a culinary Play-Doh machine that shot out all the crushed little squidlet bits into this long, strong...
It's stringy pasta, so it's like squid pasta.
But isn't squid kind of long and stringy anyway?
It sort of seems like...
It's long, but not necessarily stringy.
It has a nice al dente resilience.
I can tell you, as one who lives in San Francisco and has eaten plenty of squid...
Yeah, squid has always seemed to me like the bagel of the sea.
You bite into it and it fights back a little.
It bounces back.
Good bagels and it's not very sore.
It tests the temper of your teeth.
Well, and the amazing thing is if you look out in the audience, there are people who are really awestruck by the concept of actually eating squid.
They were doing something totally different with the squid than eating it.
You can see the sort of shocked expressions that you would actually eat a squid and not do other things with the squid.
A Squidly Diddley cartoon.
Yes, Diddley Diddley Squidly.
Some squids are for...
Wow, that's a beautiful pie you got there.
So what about that...
That pie that was inspired by Pisces dream that Princess We made last night.
That pie was an endless key lime pie.
It was. It was incredible.
And practically everybody here had some...
There might even be more.
It was a god pie.
There might even be more of the endless god pie.
A goddess pie. It was a pie of the goddess.
It was as if we had become sort of like Jesus with the loaves and the fishes, but instead it was with key lime pie.
A family key lime god pie.
It's coming man.
Actually the Greek gods used to do that.
But that's why it was key lime pie.
Jesus had been...
He wasn't very creative.
Jesus had been a girl.
He would have absolutely multiplied pie and not fish.
I know. I mean it was the best he came up with at the time.
It was a very male thing.
You know what I mean?
These crusty old peasants didn't eat a lot of pie in Jerusalem in the first century.
Speak for your ancestors.
Well, at any event, these pie eating prophets couldn't realize the culinary ambitions of today.
Because with our greater equipment, we have the ability to produce finer and larger pies.
I've dreamed about your greater equipment for so many years, Dr. Hal.
Yes, in today's scientific world.
I wake up sweating in the night wondering about your greater equipment and princess Weedle.
Oh, Bob.
Well, it's hard to keep everything in mind.
To keep all these mental plates in the air as one juggles them and compartmentalizes.
Always with the circus analogy.
But as subgeniuses, we're good at it.
The mental plates of mine tend to be metal plates and they clang a lot against each other.
Metal plates on the end of poles or broom handles.
Yes, yes, yes.
They crash a lot and they clank.
Stacked by greater equipment.
And they reflect light and blind my vision.
I'm not sure if you're a fan of metal plates.
Yes, it's thinner than normal.
They flash upon the inner eye when the sun hits them.
They flash upon that inner eye that is the bliss of solitude.
I get blinded a lot in my...
Mine's eye.
I don't think it's my third eye.
On the inside of mine.
I think it's my sixth or seventh eye and...
Painfully dry is the inside of mine inner eye.
And then I've got that other eye.
I think it's the fourth eye that is the one that has the cross-eyed problem.
Like the angels that the prophet Ezekiel saw that had multitudinous eyeballs.
My third eye has a horrible stigmatism.
I'm sorry to hear it.
A wandering, lazy eye, eh?
No, I have a Dobbs head on my left retina.
I think it's my left retina.
You know, these days they can make
those things that fit in your eyes,
you know, what are they called?
Contact lenses.
Yes, with little Dobbs heads on them
and other things on them.
If you want to go that far,
they'll put anything on a contact lens.
So you can have slit reptile eyes
or eyes with little faces or whatever.
There's a company that does it.
There are crazy, crazy pinks
who will actually tattoo their eyeballs.
Oh, they tattoo their eyes.
I've seen the tattooed eyes.
They will tattoo their eyeballs.
I think it guarantees blindness
in like seven to ten years, I think.
I don't know nothing about that.
I recently discovered something else
that was quite interesting,
which is that lightning,
when it strikes some individuals,
in some cases produces not a fatality,
but a beautiful tattoo that looks artificial,
but goes down the arm with all sorts of curlicues
and twists, but it's actually subcutaneous damage
from a lightning strike.
Has anybody ever seen or heard of this?
Pretty amazing, huh?
No, but could you do it like,
do you think the tattoo parlors of the future
will have mini Tesla coils?
No, because only God can produce this.
You can't get this tattoo and you might just get fried.
You have no idea whether you're going to get
a lightning tattoo or not,
but you can see pictures of lightning tattooed individuals
on the internet and they've got fairly cool marks
that just come from being struck by lightning.
But they'll try anyway.
They'll go to the tattoo parlor
and they'll demand that they be electrocuted.
If they're cheapskates
and don't want to pay for an artist to do it.
And they'll try anyway.
It's the sad thing that us,
this is, have you noticed,
Dr. Hal, that more and more
you look around and you realize
that there's a huge problem
because the subgenius is the smartest,
most responsible person in the room?
That can't be.
That's a terrible comment.
It is an utterly frightening situation
where you look around
and it's like, that just can't be.
Why am I, the subgenius,
the most intelligent
and responsible person in this room?
And that's why I love X-Day
because, you know,
because I'm not.
I'm not.
You're saying there's something unpatriotic in people's minds
about singing the Star Spangled Banner with your fist down your throat?
Well, that wasn't what it was.
Oh.
I can't remember what I did.
Was I tap dancing?
You were.
Was it the tap dance?
Just the hat tap dance?
Because Mimi does the Star Spangled Banner with her fist in her mouth.
I consider myself a very patriotic person.
I do.
What it was, was she was.
I love my country.
She was singing and jumping up and down with Uncle Sam's eyes on her breasts
and Uncle Sam's face painted on her body and a giant Uncle Sam hat.
And it was.
It was a tribute to 9-11.
And perhaps you were tap dancing.
They just hate boobs.
I was in the back, but the management took it all wrong.
I meant it with sincerity.
No, they just hate boobs.
They're boob haters.
You have to deal with these Philistines.
They're not artistic souls with an artistic temperament.
They're bigoted towards boobs.
If they hate boobs, they probably hate Bob.
Because as Reverend Angry Larry said, the only difference between Bob and boob is 1-0.
1-0?
1-0.
And everybody likes boobs.
So, to summarize, tonight there are all sorts of things packed into the evening.
Involving boobs.
So much that no one person can hardly hope to attend them all.
You're going to have to check what act you want to see.
But they will follow in dizzying, bewildering succession,
making this the greatest X-Day variety show act night of all time.
I forgot how many O's.
Bob.
Bar none.
It's going to be good.
And we can keep it moving because we still have that big shepherd's crook that Reverend 808 made.
The hook.
It's big enough to pull a whole band off of the stuff.
Yes, if you're grandstanding, you might see that hook coming your way.
But just to keep things happening.
Was it a band band?
Such as in SF, Ed Holmes uses on Michael Pepe all the time.
The shepherd's crook of a hook.
The shepherd's crook.
But let's throw the discussion open to new things and new business.
I'll bet you have some new topics for us, Mandy.
I was still thinking about booze.
It was a band band, the date rapists.
Because one of them was a...
Who banned the date rapists?
Well, one of them crapped in the hot tub.
All right, crapping in the hot tub.
Crapping in the hot tub is well worth banning.
You should be banned for that.
I have no sympathy.
I was wondering if there was a band band.
Yeah, that...
I mean, you can be banned for a legitimate reason.
You can be an asshole, and that's why they ban you.
But, of course, we're talking about martyrs who were banned for their art.
Right, right.
That's what I was thinking.
Did you hear about that girl in Pittsburgh at the CMU who got banned?
She was dressed as the Pope from the waist up,
and she was naked from the waist down,
and she'd shaved her pubic hair in the shape of a cross.
That sounds holy, holy.
And, yeah, I can't...
I remember she got...
It was in the Carnegie Mellon University Art Parade
for their annual tech fair,
their little nerdy carnival that they throw.
It's a pretty cool event.
And, yeah, there was an art parade,
and she dressed as the Pope,
and I can't remember exactly what she was protesting.
Lord knows it's an awful lot to protest in the Catholic Church.
Even with this new Pope who's all humble
and washes people's feet and so on?
I didn't know the new Pope gave pedicures.
He washes your feet, just like Jesus,
only he doesn't dry them with his hair because he hasn't got any.
But he's as humble as can be.
Wow, old Pope.
Yeah, I've heard the new Pope is a little cooler than the old Pope.
And they're terrified.
They're terrified of this Pope
because he's threatening to give away the store.
He came out and said that
it really doesn't matter if you're a Catholic.
As long as you're good, you'll come to God.
What?
Yes, and so the church fathers immediately put out a press release saying,
well, of course, the only way to God
to God is through his revealed church.
And the only way to the saucers
is $35.
To add to the confusion, there's still the old Pope wandering around.
The Pope Emeritus.
It's like the Middle Ages when there were two Popes.
We've got that again.
Although one is not the official guy.
So anything could happen
in these end times.
And you can, as a subgenius,
be a Pope if you'd like.
Or a Popess, or a Priestess,
or a Bishop.
And I would imagine
there's hundreds of subgenius Popes
running around.
Raise your hand out in the
live studio audience
if you are a Pope.
Do we have any Popes?
There is a Pope there.
You have a Pope card.
You're a Pope.
They're a Pope.
Everyone a Pope.
Oh, and lovely Joy has decided
that she would like to be a Pope today as well.
There's another Pope over there.
A father.
We definitely have more Popes
than the Catholic Church.
I certainly know we have more Bishops.
And I think that gives us
a one-up on them, honestly.
I think that definitely proves that
while we may not have gilded thrones
and
written boy apartments
above the hierarchy
trailers and
none of that, but we do have
many more Popes.
And Bishops.
And they have a power that the Pope
of the Vatican would kill
for, which is the power to fail.
We have fallible Popes
based on the great fallibility
of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
who makes a million bucks
every time he screws up.
Yes, and then he never shares it
with his friends.
That extra power.
I appreciate the power to fail.
It makes me feel so much better
that if something's not working out,
I can just say, fuck it.
But you don't have that
chicken John fail to win thing
where...
Oh, I got that book.
That's a good slogan.
Fail to win.
That's his slogan.
That's why there's that mural
of him sitting on a tree limb
sawing it off.
He believes somehow that there's a good thing
about failing, or claims that he does.
I preferred his previous
pronouncements.
He used to say,
we who have done so little
for so long
for absolutely no reason.
I'm messing it up.
We who have done so much
with so little for so long
are now completely qualified
to do anything at any time
for any reason.
Okay, enough free publicity
for chicken John.
He really doesn't need it.
He's a meaning well soul.
Oh, he's okay.
He's fine.
He doesn't need help
He's not as hot as you are, though.
That's for sure.
He's busy with his wonderful,
notable wonders and undertaking.
Hal has such a sexy brain.
Hal has a sexy everything.
We should also be creating
new subgenius developments
all the time.
I think you and I should create
some new subgeniuses right now.
We're not going to rest
in the old forms,
but come up with new stuff
all the time.
We're malleable.
It's frothy.
It's frothy and churning.
Bob himself takes his
mystical, large,
strong hands
and squeezes
and molds up
us.
Whoa.
He shall mold thy spirit
and by giving,
make it ask.
Make it ask?
Make it ask.
It's a rhythmic, gentle
tugging that moves us
towards
sleep,
somnolence, unconsciousness,
blissful
oblivion.
I usually roll over and sleep afterwards.
Yeah, I will agree.
Well, I suppose we,
we can roll that over
and continue.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm getting bigger.
Widened by more than a third.
PR's report says
the Army sought tax-exempt status.
IRS senior officials have testified
that the agency's actions
were inappropriate.
They were driven by
illegal political bias.
Vladimir Putin says
weakness reflects strength
and sophisticated
air defense activity.
Russia says
Vladimir is backing
Walmart's hands.
Walmart says
this is PR.
it will cut out PR news.
Everything will happen.
It's just a matter of when.
And can,
and, and that's okay.
We'll just yell really loud
and say it's right now.
That thing that you wanted to happen
will happen.
That thing.
That thing is going on right now.
Are the movies gonna happen?
The movies are gone.
The movies happen all the time.
The movies left.
The movies,
the movies took a nap.
What about Grindhouse?
Grindhouse runs 24 hours.
Oh, oh, there's the,
those movies are on.
Yes.
Any time.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I meant to say
you can take a nap.
There'll be one in progress.
There's an always,
you know,
Monster movies?
There'll be always
a place to sit
and watch the monster movies.
And we were,
we dropped in on
From Beyond the other night
on the all-HP Lovecraft night.
There's always something
entertaining running
down at the Grindhouse.
And last year,
Jehovah One tried to stop
the Grindhouse
by hurling a lightning bolt
while we were broadcasting,
which traveled down the hill
into the grotto,
but didn't reach
the Grindhouse.
It sounds like a tattoo attempt.
It sounds like somebody
had an appointment.
Yeah, Reverend Feitzee Todd
saw the lightning bolt
coming and threw himself
in its path,
shielding his equipment.
We saw it.
We were sitting right here
and it blasted right out there
during the day.
I'll make room on this office.
It's the one.
Holy head shit.
We have just...
Don't worry, bro.
I'm going to interrupt briefly
for a point of business.
You have 15 minutes
to buy clean...
I'm aware.
...T-shirts with no mud,
no beer,
no vomit,
no urine,
no sweat.
You won't have to do laundry.
There are clean T-shirts
over there.
There may still be
a beer koozie or two.
And of course,
as we talked about,
the rare printings
of Revelation X.
Revelation X, yes.
Bumper stickers
and a number of other things.
You have 15 minutes.
Bumper stickers,
but collectible.
15 minutes left
to go get off your butt
and buy things.
If they want to do that.
Yes, these bumper stickers
are so obsolete
they have the Dallas
post office box on them.
They are intact.
Intensely collectible.
And we can't recommend
them too much.
And what about
the little grinning
Dobbs head pin?
Don't you want to wear this
during your non-subgenius
downtime the rest of your life?
When that mafia dude
is about to blow your brains out,
if he notices that pin
at the last second,
that could save you.
Because as we know,
criminals are a cowardly
and superstitious lot.
Are they afraid of
cloisonnier?
Aren't those cloisonnier?
Is that how you pronounce it?
They were.
I don't really know.
The cloisonnier.
They used to be.
They used to be cloisonnier.
They're made by tiny children
in the People's Republic of China
these days.
I love them.
They have to paint every dot
on that Dobbs head
just right.
That's right.
They are forced to
beating the shell and suit.
Takes away their cigarettes.
These are powerful objects.
Also,
Dobbs cufflinks.
I mentioned these the other day.
For all of you
I see out there
wearing French cuffs.
But they could be
conversation.
conversation starters,
conversation enders,
conversation pieces.
Are there any
Dobbs head pasties yet?
Do we have Dobbs head pasties?
We've got to answer
these things in advance.
You have to cut them out.
You have to cut the Dobbs head
out yourself.
And then you stick it on.
We should get some nice
Dobbs head pasties.
Well,
don't let me keep you back.
Prepare them during the year
before X-Day.
And then we will ascend
to glory in the saucers.
Perfectly accoutered
in the saucers.
All our Dobbs head knick-knacks.
Last time you and I
got accoutered
there was a dust storm
and we couldn't see
anything for miles.
I picked a large tick
off myself at the pond
but that's all the
accoutering I got this year.
I thought accouter
means turtle
in the language
I was raised on.
Well, it can
because of the incredible
flexibility of
American colloquialism.
It can be a turtle
or a fish
or a louse.
Even.
Well, a lot of people
use the word cooter
to describe a
vagina.
Like, as in
I sure would like to
sniff that bicycle seat
after her cooter's been on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At last I have control
of your radio tubes.
And I do too.
Good.
This is Ren Hoack.
And this is Stimson J. Catt
of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening
to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall kill you.
You know, I put together
a book of subgenius history
that's much like that
only it costs $150
and it takes the form
of an online class
that goes on for eight weeks.
Not a successful business model.
That's how long it takes
just to download
the material offered
in the eight weeks.
The history of Church of the Subgenius.
I am weary
and what it takes
to run your own
cult.
I thought you did that
as a webinar series
where you take questions
and answers.
You don't do that?
Oh, no, no.
I just make a lot of...
We have chat.
We have to
online chat things
two or three times a week.
I need to learn
how to run my own cult.
Do you have a scholarship program?
We have less than ten minutes
to continue
the so-called broadcast.
Most people who take the course
decide after taking it
that running their own cult
looks like too much trouble.
The word cult
comes from the Latin word colo
meaning
to join together
as in collation.
You know,
you're collating things,
you're joining together.
If you are in a cult,
you're joined together
with the other members
and that is all.
The whole pejorative thing
about being a brainwashed robot
is only characteristic
of some cults,
not all cults.
Well, our Bob
is not a jealous Bob.
No, our Bob
is quite ecumenical
and in fact,
the Church of the Subgenius
is yoked.
It's not.
Ecumenically,
with many other
religious groups
like Bishop Joey's
First Church of the Last Laugh.
Yeah.
Right, Stan?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, absolutely.
And the Church of the
Living Bull.
Yes.
Dennis and Linda Murphy's cult.
Not the Church of the Bronze Bull.
There's a Church of the Living Bull?
Yeah.
Is it related to the Bronze Bull?
I thought it was a golden calf.
And the Church of the
what looked like
it dropped out
of a tall cow's ass.
You know who we've had
almost no contact with?
The one we've had
contact with, though,
is the Flying Spaghetti Monster people.
I was just about to ask
if the Pastafarians
had anything to do with it.
No, there's a whole lot
of crossover with it.
Flying Spaghetti Monster
has a kind of
Lovecraftian appearance,
you know?
It has some potential.
He looks so happy, though.
There's no hate in those people.
And he sticks to the wall.
These days,
the Lovecraft Monster Cthulhu,
which was supposed to be
so hideous
that it's literally indescribable
and can drive people mad
just by looking at it,
is now a plush toy.
I have a question.
What's a bunny Cthulhu?
And not only that,
but it's a damn plush toy
that you see everywhere.
That's a pink version of Cthulhu.
Cthulhu is never properly...
People don't read the text.
They don't describe it properly.
Just how beautifully horrible
he really may be.
There's tentacles.
There's some kind of a face.
A metal idol
which depicts it properly.
Somewhere along the line,
it became a logo Cthulhu.
A logo Elder God.
That's just wrong.
I have a handmade bunny Cthulhu
The girl that runs the bookstore
in Pittsburgh,
I want you to come and do a thing at.
She made me a little
crocheted green
zombie bunny Cthulhu.
Well, that's just adorable.
Yeah, it is.
Sweet little thing.
Now, the actual...
You're saying the actual Cthulhu is...
The actual Cthulhu
does not have two little
cute button bright eyes.
It has multiple bulging pulpy eyes
all over the front of its head.
And eyes around the sides, too.
Pulp.
Its body is grotesquely obese.
And it's got long...
Obesity is a disease.
...claws on four feet and hind feet.
It's different from all these
cutie pie Cthulhus
that people are coming out with
who don't even bother
to go back and read the text.
And Cthulhu in the Lovecraft pantheon
is the marine god
who is comparable to Poseidon
or Neptune.
Then there is Nearthar-la-Tohep
who is the messenger
comparable to Mercury
and, of course,
the black goat of the woods
with a thousand young
Shub-Niggurath,
the Aphrodite,
so-called,
of the Lovecraft pantheon.
And the old boy,
the Zeus,
otherwise called
Yog-Sothoth.
Or Jehovah-One.
I never knew that.
And Jehovah-One is the one
who sent the lightning bolt
to try and kill
Fightsy-Thor.
And he's a great attache
at last year's Grindhouse.
He's crotchety
for the last few million years.
He's in his dotage
in his old age
but may still be propitiated.
And you may remember
if you read your Bible
there's nothing he likes more
than the taste and smell of blood.
That's why he turned down
the sacrifice of Cain
and accepted the sacrifice of Abel.
God was not a vegetarian.
He liked it if you killed things
and cut them up
and put them on his altar.
And he disdained
the sacrifice of fruits
and nuts
and oats
and groats
and so forth.
Now all he just wants money.
Money is now so covered with blood
that he's satisfied
to get money.
Or blood diamonds.
Anything that has caused
blood.
And what's interesting about that
is that the delight of demons
is the anguish of human souls.
This makes God
a sort of giant demon.
Just as the devil is.
The delight of imps
is the irritation
and frustration
of human souls
in minor matters.
Give me that for me.
It was good for me.
Give me that.
Give me that for me.
It was good for me.
It was for me.
Give me that.
Give me that for me.
So now we are bringing our...
Well, no.
Reverend Angry Larry just joined us
so we can blabber on
for a few more minutes.
I'm for blabbering on
as long as I can.
As long as possible,
but Pisces is cracking the whip
on the new schedule
and we don't have
all the time in the world to burn.
I don't see any whip cracking.
Well, you may not see it.
Whip crap?
Never mind any of that.
Let's hear from Reverend Angry Larry.
Whip's crack.
No, let's not hear from Reverend Angry Larry.
Because he has an important announcement
about tonight's show.
Oh, do I?
Subgenius Beach Party.
Oh, well, the Subgenius Beach Party.
We just need as many
girls up there on the stage
dancing with or without clothes.
They're very skimpy,
whatnots, that sort of thing.
Aren't bikinis preferred
for your AIP-type beach party?
Yeah.
So there you have it.
Things like frisbees
and things like that,
people end up taking them,
which is fine with me.
So we'll see how the Subgenius version
of that pans out.
We're hoping.
There's enough water around
where it's more like a beach.
Well, there may be,
but right now we've got sun.
The sun has chosen
to pay us a visit.
It's not all rain and gloom
here at X-Town.
It's a day.
I'm going to make a shameless plug
that August 3rd,
the Amino Acids new record
will be out.
And if you're not in Detroit
on August 3rd,
you can go to my store's website,
which is weirdsvillerecords.com,
and you can order it there.
It's a seven-inch,
all-white vinyl
with six songs on it.
Plus there'll be a digital download
of when the Amino Acids
first arrived here
in 1936.
In 1965,
they played at a bowling alley
in Allen Park, Michigan,
and someone found a tape
of them playing
in a bowling alley in 1965,
and that will be included
on the digital download.
Hot damn.
Yes.
Hey, Groovy Cats,
we are back,
and this is Buster Buttons
from CKLW
coming live from
Thunder Bowl Lanes
right here in Allen Park.
Now, tonight,
we have a very special treat.
These guys,
well, they're a long way
from home,
and I have to tell you kids
that their getup
is out of this world.
Now, they call themselves
the Amino Acids,
and they're going to be...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
They're the Amino Acids,
and tonight,
they're going to play a tune
for you all called
Connie.
Take it away, fellas.
¶¶
© BF-WATCH TV 2021