I think it's working now.
You said that speed of answer is measured mechanically.
Courtesy, however, is not measured mechanically.
It's done by a person known as a service observer.
I'm here.
Hi, Henry. This is the hottest piece of manpower in the world.
Scary, scary, puzzling evidence show.
Keep the phone on the amplifier.
The power comes so in-quiet.
You sound like him.
I don't even look like him.
Yes, I do feel like him.
But I'm not him, you understand?
Papa wasn't so desperate.
What are you desperate for, money?
Power?
Are you reading the bottom line?
There becomes time.
You are a man.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Soul Genius Hour of Sight.
What?
The Soul Genius Hour of Sight
And the Reverend will be discussing how he came up with a religion and household...
What?
How he came up with his own religion.
It's about how Bob...
Uh...
Tuned into the very aethers of the underverse.
You know, and all that's like that there.
Hey, what...
Who was that lovely voice I just heard giggling and laughing over the collar well?
I would like to take my pleasure with it.
Oh my God, I...
You wanted to take...
Since you walked in here, you've attempted to take your pleasure with five pieces of furniture...
Two Pepsi cans...
Those are music.
One real flesh and blood woman...
Three guys...
And a console.
Could you please...
No, it was three...
But let's get these...
Two of those furniture pieces were musical instruments.
They were Chaz's experimental classical...
Zop twangers?
Yeah, it's twangers.
And... But still, they're laden with sperm and pieces of other flotsam which come from the insides of your body.
Are you any less guilty, lonesome cowboy Dave?
Step now before the board of judgment.
Is it not true that you, lonesome cowboy Dave, on a night in 1994, made jokes about religion?
Play the tape.
So God is like this big stupid vacuum thing, don't even really exist.
Ma'am, I bet if I said that in front of some fundamentalists...
Play that again, wait a minute, play that.
I could get into a mess of hell.
No, no, no, no, no.
What was that?
Oh boy, God is just like a really big vacuum, it's a bunch of mashed and stuff.
It's a bunch of flammable...
Wait, once again, I heard it.
There, right there.
There.
It's a bunch of fundamentalists here.
Right there.
Cease playing the tape.
We've seen enough.
You, lonesome cowboy Dave, knowingly made satires of organized religion in your brief stay on Earth.
And you missed church several Sundays during your life.
Do you have anything to say for yourself before the judgment is passed?
I didn't mean to mangle the person in my briefs.
I tried to do, I didn't know if it was...
Enough!
Recording angels, does his name appear in the book of humans?
Nay, Lord.
Then the judgment is passed.
Cast him into the lake of naked women.
No, no, wait a minute.
Wait, no, wait.
Naked women.
Oh, wait, okay, alright.
Ah, so that is what he wanted.
Now we know the truth.
Toss him into the lake of fire and be done with it.
No, wait a minute, please.
Call the next lost soul.
No, you have no more repentance now, Dave.
And you're married now to that hideous demon.
That bewarted, three-teeted demon.
You're a monstrous toad-like abhorrence.
I'm so happy.
Robbing and hopping fitfully in the dank pit for eternity.
Oh, thank you.
I'm so happy.
I now pronounce you tormented in hell eternally, soul and wife.
Oh, thank you, Reverend.
I smell bad, sir.
Could I please?
Could I please requisition the fellowship for a small order of requisite to something
that smells better than all this stuff?
We'll put you on the waiting list.
Well, I guess we'll just see y'all next week.
That's gonna be it for another week's show, kids.
I'd like to thank my guests, Reverend Ivan Stang, the Princess We Are Doe, Lonesome Cowboy
Dave, Psychopath Finder, and my apprentice for doing the first half hour of the show,
Keith.
So, um, I guess we'll see y'all next week.
You guys can babble the rest of the show away, so go right ahead.
Come back next week for the show.
I'm gonna watch Bob Chow for a lucky radio comedy.
It'll tickle your funny bones.
Next week?
Oh, boy.
It'll be more fun than a barrel full of monkeys.
My kneecaps are crushed.
Die.
Oh, boy.
No gets it
charm.
You can launch these.
Oh, I don't have the
script. I
I think
they're 50 cents.
They're all
a bunch of fakes.
I've had enough of this.
They're all a bunch of fakes.
Wait a minute.
You forgot your briefcase,
man.
Hey, man.
What about these heads?
Rush.
I send greetings from Chepuchescu, from fascist heaven where he earned his wings.
They say there's still lots of room here for Bill Clinton and his highness, Dung Chow Ying.
Many blessings from Chepuchescu.
May your bloodbath be complete.
Let's bow down to the new world order where oppression and fantasy meet.
I'm sending greetings from Chepuchescu.
Bartles. Actually, Bartles and Arpad.
There's the credit on that song there.
Greetings from Chepuchescu.
Wonderful new tape from John Bartles.
I think we may actually be able to play most of it over the next few hours of Slack.
Despite the language.
And before that, of course, some brain rot.
On ESO radio.
On WCSB Cleveland.
Starring, in this case, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And Chaz Smith mixing.
And it's always fun to take Lonesome Cowboy Dave to hell.
He's such a simpleton.
He's such a sap.
He's such an easy mark.
You know what I mean?
And we'll get back to that.
There's some...
Some just frolicking fun and games on those tapes.
I did want to mention a couple of things.
Oh, this background sound is from a CD that was sent to us by Chris Korda.
It's called Demons in My Head by Chris Korda.
And where is the letter he sent with it that explained that it really did have demons on it?
It really is about demons.
But for right now, I don't want to talk about demons.
No.
But about video cameras in cop cars.
Apparently, since Texas started putting video cameras in our cop cars.
Maybe it was Dallas.
I don't know.
It's now become very common.
And the police all over the place are putting video cameras there.
So that they can get a good record of what actually happened.
And you'd think it would.
It would be a good idea.
And it certainly is.
I mean, if you think about it.
There's...
Cameras on Cops is big time showbiz now, folks.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That background music was not supposed to happen that way.
Okay.
That's queued up enough.
It was supposed to be this background music.
Nerd Twins.
There.
Yeah.
Cameras on Cops.
It's...
All these TV shows.
And you know, in the science fiction world.
They've always had the ultra-violence channel.
If you know what I mean.
Like in THX 1138.
And Clockwork Orange.
And World of the Future.
And just about any proper dystopian sci-fi movie.
The people always have a sex channel and a violence channel.
Well, um...
Channel 21?
27?
33?
In the evening?
You know, turn it on any day.
You'll get one of those cop or rescue shows.
Which means the camera strapped to the helmet.
It's my daughter's favorite shows.
It's...
You know, strap that camera on the cop.
And go in there after a boy's kicking doors down.
Hauling the drug dealers out of bed.
Breaking up the Pobucker family fights and all that.
All the poor drunken Pobuckers who you know sign a release.
Those idiots sign a release.
It's their big chance.
You know, they're thinking about...
I guess when they sign it, they're thinking about Geraldo.
Burying their sins.
It's their 15 minutes of fame.
But it's part of that ultra-violence channel.
And...
I don't know, friends.
I think I've been reading too many science fiction books.
Um...
I've read about 4 or 5 in a row now that were written only recently.
Like 5 or 10 years ago.
And they're supposed to detect now.
The 1990s.
Those are really fun ones to read.
Because the horrible thing is, they really do depict now.
They're pretty accurate.
And they're supposed to be real scary.
You're supposed to read them and just react with disgust and dread.
And instead, you just kind of go, huh.
Well, gosh, that science fiction writer was right.
Funny.
You know, now that all that terrible stuff is happening, it just seems kind of normal.
Um...
I've read End of the World News by Anthony Burgess.
And also The Wanting Sea by Anthony Burgess.
Who's famous for Clockwork Orange.
John Bruner has several of those 1990s, more or less, sci-fi books.
Written on some of them 20 years ago.
Children of Thunder.
Stand on Zanzibar.
And The Sheep Look Up.
Are all kind of old classics now.
What else?
Um...
Nature's End by Whitley Stryber.
And War Day.
And you read these.
I end up saying to myself, yeah, well, I know this is supposed to be dystopian science fiction warning about the perils to come.
If we continue in this ridiculous, greedy path humanity is taking.
And we did continue.
And now we're right in the middle of those perils to come.
And we're perfectly used to them.
I mean, there is a terrible ecological or human disaster on the news every day.
Several every day.
And thousands of new laws designed to cramp your personal freedoms bit by bit.
So you don't even notice when they're gone.
And it all comes off as boring current affairs.
You know, or at best, a techno-thriller sort of a setting.
And it's supposed to be terrifying sci-fi of awful things that just might possibly come true.
Were the human race stupid enough to let those things happen even after reading those sci-fi?
I mean, you know, there's a lot of sci-fi books.
And, um, oh, J.R. Bob Dobbs used to write sci-fi as a hobby.
Um, Dobbstown University Press.
They're pretty hard to get a hold of.
But, uh, and a lot of my friends write near-future sci-fi, you know.
And does that mean that the absurd baloney that we come up with thinking, oh, it's going to be so funny and satirical.
But kind of grisly and scary.
At the same time.
Oh, boy.
I mean, friends.
Think about it.
What if, what if the Yakatisma do get here before the Axis?
Just think about that, my friend.
And, uh.
Oh, here's one last, um.
Before we go to any deeper, I think.
Into, um.
The, the hilarious comedic thing.
We'll do one more piece of, uh.
Oh, socially relevant.
Yeah, this is socially relevant music.
It really is.
Applies to subgeniuses.
This is, uh.
Lost Souls Incorporated.
Who, by the way, they're a Dallas band.
They're going to be playing at Commerce Street Bar on April 1st.
Really.
April 1st.
They really will be there.
Uh-huh.
The District Attorney in Abilene
Found the First Amendment a little obscene
So he burnt the Constitution
To meet his prime.
And, um.
Last week, he gave back
to the West
Uh-huh.
That's a Hands-Up.
So.
Well, uh.
It's gonna be a complete mess 1300 on April 1st.
about
and I don't know if I'm more angry
or scared when my father says
son these days you gotta take care
you gotta watch what you say
who you say it to and this world
was never fair
so don't ask me where I
stand am I
trying to change this
world
the huddled masses
in Hymie town been up to their
necks in shit so long they never
sit down and you can't walk
the streets without bodyguards around
it's a problem
yeah
so some anal retentives
on prudent committees stated
these so called artists and those who
pen ditties are the cause of this
violence despite their insistence
that those songs are merely
symptoms
well we'll round them up next week to teach
them a lesson we'll read them Miranda
let them know that they're messing with
the toughest God fearing Christian
upstanding people in the world
yeah let's get them
and I quiver with anger
as I watch the news and I
worry if Dan rather share
in their views and I grow very
quiet till I hardly
utter a word
of it
when you
ask me where I stand
am I trying to change this
world
do you wanna have to teach your children
to self censor all they say
and will I
still be trying to read Solzhenitsyn
when they
throw the key away
unless I
pack my bags for the relative liberty
of where had been East Berlin
and is there
really only so much freedom to go around
we had to forfeit ours for them
do you think so
I don't think so
no oh no
but the irony
cannot escape me so
whatever you do
don't ask me where I stand
am I trying to
change the world
don't ask me where I stand
am I trying
to change this
If I knew what there was going to be
ibilitating your future
that I tried
without fear
we would never rebuild
I must lose my head
There's one thing exciting me a year
YES!
HAHAHAHAHA!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Done as if by order.
Heathen men sacked God's church at Lindisfarne.
Thomas is dead.
Ha, ha, laugh, curtain old boy.
It's a great joke played on us by the Lord or fate or nature,
whatever you prefer, on whoever, whatever brain is,
certainly in a sense of humor.
There was also a nun there, Prioresse,
that of his smiling was full simple and coy.
Her greatest ooth was but by center loy.
The first around Tampico, wait for it.
Watch your ears.
And this is the country where the nuggets of gold
are just crying for you to take them out of the ground.
Gosh, spam sandwich eating man,
it seems like we've been waiting for our kids here forever.
So have you seen any of the Olympics?
I've seen them.
I saw the thing when Bob was dressed as a woman
and did it a routine.
I thought I saw Bob doing the aerial flipping thing.
Twist flips with the skis on and stuff.
That was something to behold, that cute little dress,
that cute little skirt and those flashy legs and hyper buttocks
and that silly ass stupid pipe smoking face.
No wonder.
It took all the judges by surprise.
What a routine.
I was.
I was kind of thrilled and inspired.
Well, you know why they gave him that high score
was when he skated around and that little parasol he had
that he had like tucked up in his tutu part of the time.
I like that.
And he pulled out the parasol and twirled it a couple of times
and then it turned like into a hammer
and he went over there to Tonya Harding
and hit her forcefully on the knee with that hammer.
You know, and then God Bless America played
and they brought out the Olympics.
I cried.
Killed her and then they fined him.
Yeah, it was.
It made my nipples awful hard, I'll tell you.
Of course, my nipples are always awfully hard.
Yeah, but they're not very big.
I know, but they're.
Come on now, admit it.
They're dinky.
They're like men's nipples.
Well, they're like raisins.
Of course, they're very small.
I'm not bragging.
I'm just talking.
They're like teats on a hog.
Teats on a hog.
It's quite poignant, actually.
Hello?
That's a beautiful illusion.
I like teats on a prairie squid.
I think they would be much, much, much, much tastier.
No, because teats on a prairie squid have a function.
Whereas teats on a male hog are useless.
That's the origin of the old southern metaphor.
Now, a prairie squid.
Well, what would you say, a bull hog?
A prairie squid without teats.
I don't know what the hell you do with them.
Millions and thousands of tiny teats,
like little rupturing cups surrounding our foreheads
in the middle of the night.
Sometimes we can't wake up because of it.
Oh, okay.
What you do is you pet the squid.
You take it and you tickle it and pet it and squeeze.
And it starts to ooze from those little tiny teats,
the stuff that looks like rubber cement.
Oh, yeah.
You take a glass slide or something
and you scrape it along the little teats.
And you let it dry for like a couple hours.
And then you can roll it up in little balls.
Tasty, tasty.
And you put it in the little pipe
and you can smoke the prairie squid toxic teat secretion.
So the lactic expressions of that squid monster
are actually smokable from?
Yeah, that actually made the papers.
I learn something every day.
That made the papers, but they used toads instead.
They said it was toads instead of prairie squids.
Now, what's the difference, though, actually,
between a toad and a prairie squid?
I've heard as a southern anachronistic euphemism
that a toad and a prairie squid are just the same thing
as one of them big old bullfrog toads.
That's what a prairie squid is.
I lied, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
I forget sometimes that I'm in a big city.
You know, you sophisticated people know everything about...
That's like saying,
oh, what's the difference between a beautiful woman and a...
Donut?
Yeah, donut.
Well, no, there's not all...
More like an old, stinky, broken ironing board in a junk pile.
That's like the difference
between those two.
I'm cracks flustered, though.
Which side is it on?
Now, I know it was amphibian, but a prairie squid...
No, a prairie squid is a cephalopod.
Oh, I thought it was a hydropod.
A toad is an amphibian,
and a prairie squid is just like a regular ocean-going squid.
Only...
You kiss the squid enough, it will turn into a toad.
Yeah, you kiss the squid enough...
Well, see, then there you've got the idea of the original succubus
and the original incubus,
because when the great fairies came down from the Beyond Realm kingdom
and suckled all the maidens...
You want to fancy it up with all that big, highfalutin scientific terminology,
sure, but that takes all the spontaneity out of it.
What about plain old prairie squid?
Is nothing more than a plain old prairie squid?
There's nothing wrong with a young man or a young lady
taking their favorite pet prairie squid up in the hayloft
and with some big red straps and a little tactical nuclear weapon
and having just a good old-fashioned romp in the hay
with their little shaved cephalopod.
You know...
Now, have you ever done slugs?
You know, slugs are attracted to beer,
and what you do is you dip it...
Oh, Christ, no wonder they're...
I'm not going to get into too much detail,
but basically you dip it in the beer
and then you drop it through a hole in the back porch or something
and just wait for them slugs, and they love beer.
Well, I...
I...
You just lay there about half an hour before, you know,
you'll be covered with them.
That's what I noticed while my belly was covered with slugs.
I wondered what had happened,
if there'd been maybe some kind of metabiological change in my body,
if something had...
It was some dribbling beer down on your belly,
and those little slugs come up.
Well, I think some of the beer was, like,
was expanding through my pores,
was actually coming out of me,
and I think that's what the slugs got onto.
They got a whiff of that, and they came running for miles, buddy.
I'll tell you.
You just dropped your beer bottle.
I was like, don't do that.
I can't keep my...
I told you about this.
Oh, man.
You heard the aphorism about the man with the withered...
I'm sorry.
If I can have one more, I promise I won't drop it.
Don't drop the bottles around.
I won't drop...
Oh, dang.
That's not me.
I'm sorry about what I did to your radio station, you guys.
I...
I hope that they...
Man, this is pretty unprofessional.
I hope you don't get in trouble
for having a...
Oh, Dave, be careful.
I fell down.
Liquid frog.
My legs.
Lick it up.
My knees feel all rubbery.
Can you lick up your guitar, dude?
I'll try.
I'll try and help you.
Stop on the slugs.
They're my friends.
He's in a peri-squid.
They're my little friends, my slugs.
Chef Lepaud...
I love them.
...gave birth to the tiny, tiny microworlds.
Millions and billions of microworlds expanding.
It was a cephalopod who did it first.
A shrimpy-shrimper, a shrimpy-shrimper or a mollusk.
Or maybe a one-celled uniquag.
Uniquag.
Saigon!
I am this world on this planet Earth.
This is a top secret tape.
I am the man, Jesus Christ, and God, as the late President John F. Kennedy said,
as referred to by shouting out loud, that we have control of the mind, shaking all over.
That's us, friends! We got it, finally!
Uh, there was a Jane-er Nguyen, and...
Now take Mr. Crawfish right in your hand...
Oh, take that crawfish.
Dear friends, and take some potatoes.
This is the potatoes from right here in lovely Dallas, Texas.
Thank you.
Hey, man, your underwear is showing!
One, two, three, four!
And five.
The rampaging line of Judah.
.
I and I
Rastaman
Not the big man
The big
Oh yeah
Rastaman
Thank you very much ladies and gentlemen
Here are the potatoes from Dallas
Can we get five more
Fine Richard Dobbs
Made out of that good
Miss Honey
You're on your way north
I reckon we can't blame him too much
What do you mean
I mean he's not a real killer as killers go
I think he's on as the next fella
Almost
He's not only going to get me a whole lot of time
And you ain't going
But we'll be up to it
We need money too
How much is the pay
You pay shows
Oh
Hey, did I know you from someplace?
Nobody respects me except for those slugs.
Well, you're a dick.
Look at this.
Look at the shape you're in.
Where's my little conservative body?
Well, for crying out loud, you just vomit stained and your hair's all mushed up.
Why could anybody respect you anyway?
That's pretty funny, isn't it?
No, that's not funny.
Gigi Allen was my friend.
I married Gigi Allen.
I love Gigi.
And Jane-er.
Jane-er and Gigi.
They were anything for a lady.
They were a laugh trio.
If Jane-er could see you now with your pants all urine-stained and your stubbly beard,
I don't think anybody would be proud of you then.
Oh, screw Bob.
I'm not afraid of Bob.
Chance, could you get in here?
This guy's losing it right in here right now.
I'm not going to preach.
All right, we've got some more questions here.
I've been preaching long enough.
I'm a farce.
It's a stupid joke.
I'm tired.
Okay, Doug.
I mean, Reverend.
I'm tired of it.
Could you please put your shirt back on for crying out loud?
Hey, Bob, you can take a bite out of this.
Don't go by the window, please.
Could somebody get him away from the window?
He's a friend.
Go ahead.
Try to stop me.
Just please come back here from the window a little bit.
You're getting a lot of people very nervous.
Bob's a smart, fine words.
You listeners, Bob's a fat.
I've seen it.
Princess, we are going.
Do you want to help me get this guy away from the window?
The rabbit was already in the hat.
The rabbit was already in the hat, Bob.
I'm full of it.
Stick it in, pull it out.
Don't start crying now.
Don't get all mottled on.
Just come on back to the microphone.
I'm sorry, Bob.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Bob.
I hope you didn't hear me.
I'm sorry.
We'll get something going again.
Listen to this.
I get very emotional.
I get very emotional when I am on Bob.
Excuse me.
I feel very bad right now.
Well, I think I've seen a personal self-defrocking happen right here in our studio.
I don't know if we should go to some calls right now.
If we should just kind of lose the ref for a second.
He looks pretty bad.
No, that's okay.
I'm ready to preach the word of God now.
I mean, Bob, what the hell with you?
Okay.
Wait, what are you doing?
Wow.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
員!
All right, you sound başlangigy.
Myiu.
You guys have no moreт
you do.
THAT's what you got don in希望.
That's not so very big of a deal.
Yeah.
He is.
You get a 19-year qualifications.
blabber Incorrect.
Blabber Incorrect.
You think one of them is nothing but ch commands, but you think it's not so şey or something?
Which one?
Little one.
Oh!
allies okay, BTW.
time. Bob said that. Bob said that you were a genius sometime. Oh, come on now, Rev. Let's
just, let's just calm down. I know you're all worked up. You've been flying and your
arms are tired and all that other bull crap and everything like that. You're trying to
wind down a little bit before you do your thing. Don't you think it's, it's a little
bit absurd for you to behave this way? Connie's a slut too. I don't mind saying it. So you
can prove it. I have had experiences with Connie Dobbs and I don't think Mr. Bob Dobbs
would be so happy to hear about. Would you Bob? How's your pipe smoking tobacco face?
Is Smiling an idiot? He looks like an idiot. I'm sorry, Bob. I'm sorry. I've been working
too hard.
Well, I should say you should be sorry. You humiliated a pregnant woman on the radio and
you cursed all the, all of the elder gods in one mighty sentence.
I did?
I, oh, I think you might have.
I don't remember.
Well, I think you're in one hell of a load of trouble right now, buddy.
I'm sorry. I'm, I'm sorry. I don't usually get like this.
Well, is there something in his contract that says we have to go on with this? If the guy's
blasted, can't we go to something else for a minute?
And maybe you'll get him a coffee, coffee, coffee, coffee, coffee, coffee, coffee, carrot.
I think we must look towards Mecca.
I don't know what that's going to do for us.
That big rocket Mecca is nothing but a chunk of hash that fell out of space. Bob told me.
It's a big black chunk of hash and they smoke it, they seep God.
Pull it up.
They seep God.
Well, we have some musclemen here and listeners, and I don't think they would like you referring
to the Kaaba stone or the sacred rock which fell and was witnessed by Fatima's veil of
tear bombs as a piece of hash.
Bob was there. He tried it with the Sultan.
Come on, Reverend Stang, you're just, you're, you're, you're so out of whack tonight. You're
just saying anything that comes to your mind. You know, what are you going to give up this
shtick and quit the drinking too, by the way?
Right, Bob? It's the sacred doctrine of verisability. I didn't do it. I wasn't here. You didn't
hear that.
Okay, I don't want to be harsh with you, but how long?
I did not say that.
How long can you?
I am not here.
A recovering alcoholic like yourself. Oh, recovering indeed. How long can you, you
expect to spread the gospel, the mission of Bob Dobbs, if you can't even stand on your
own two feet?
Pay no attention to the man behind the curtain.
Jesus was the savior that was pure, but he couldn't understand the sinners. And David
Koresh, lonesome cowboy David Koresh said to me, son, the new Messiah is a sinner. And
then Bob shot him and plugged him good. And then the feds gave him the bag of money. I swear
Are you there, caller?
I didn't have anything to do with it.
Listen there for a second.
Oh, oh, I, whoa. Somebody.
Hello?
Are we on the air?
Yes.
I'm sorry. I go ahead.
Hello?
Yes. Hello?
Yes, you are on the air.
Yes, please be so sweet.
I'm on the air?
You're all fierce.
Who's that?
Who's all down there?
Get him out of here. Get him out of here. Get him out of here.
Hello?
You're all just a bunch of damn humans.
What?
How dare you? How dare you? A human? What do you mean, human?
Were you guys linked by some kind of Smith genetic wavelength or something? Some kind
of brain fusion?
Yes? Yes, caller.
It's all right.
Your breath smells like pus.
That's all you wanted to tell us.
I just wanted to say what's up.
Oh, but it's not all right.
It's all right.
It's not all right at all.
Call the police.
Not since the beginning of the days of the egg has it been all right.
No, no, it's never been all right.
The sacred egg.
The sacred holy smoking egg.
They had the sacred egg.
The giant smooth-brained subgenius egg.
At the opening of the Winter Olympics, they had the sacred egg came out and the sacred
bird came out of the sacred egg.
And we...
And then the sacred cook came out and wrung the sacred bird's neck and made the sacred
fried chicken...
On the torch.
And beat them until bored.
The Olympic torch.
The Olympic flame.
The Olympic flamer.
What are they going to add torturing to the Olympics?
That's what I'm about ready to see.
Olympic-style torture.
And it looks like Garry Fasswell, the tiny little dwarf from Minnesota, has gone three
and a half long hours...
Dwarf throwing is, I think, soon going to be in it.
Each country gets to start a new sport when they get to host the Olympics.
We're talking about actual duration of pain.
It's Sydney, Australia.
It'll be a long time.
It'll be the dwarf tossing.
Are we on dwarf tossing again?
The last time I was in town, you guys were talking about that.
This part's been deleted right now.
Thank you.
Oh, one of the discarnate ones trying to make their way back to the ether.
That was an inorganic being, I'm sure.
A bean.
I've heard that...
Those have a low level of flatulence and productivity.
They do.
They're spiritual beings.
They're not.
The more spiritual you are, the less flatulence you are.
They make a spiritual exhalation from your body.
It's like a wave, a waft of spearmint.
It's like a holy myrrh and frankincense smell.
There's no Alpo gravy sauce or any kind of other diseased moment.
It's the kind bob cuts.
Like roses.
And wouldn't we all love to smell the kind bob cuts in our own homes?
And now for limited time only.
We can get the kind bob cuts in this little tiny can at any time we open, Reverend, just
like so.
And we have the aromas of Bob's flatulences.
Now, how'd you come up with a brilliant product like this?
What gave you the idea for this marketing thing?
Well, we were sitting around one day and Philo, well, he led a Philo, if you know what
I mean.
And Janer said, hey, Bob's out.
And I said, well, I'm not going to do that.
And what are you going to do about that?
They said, well, if you hadn't, you could produce a heart Thought we'd like you to use
liquid yUM Fest.
When you they said you couldn't do it, they went home and just ran away.
God bless you and thank you.
You won't have the chance.
Now this whole thing is a family, so I'm everywhere you would even go to, here we go.
for it, but they're the cause you know, we're gonna name this little dog purse, which I
have them for that.
Look, people came and asked me what the heck does Jill's top hat look like, and I said,
that's real.
The他 is from the classic fray we have out there.
the drippings from the enlightened holy men and holy actresses.
Holy actresses actually contributed to the Guru Pitta?
Yes, Hypatia Lee.
Hypatia Lee?
We have Kita Natividad bottled, and the young one, Tracy Lord, retired.
Oh, my, that would be a pungent, that would be a rather pungent people.
Negative land is stupid.
Christianity is good.
You're anti-Bob.
Anti-Bob?
I am the Reverend Nicodemus.
Why don't you speak to me? Speak to me with your dire knowledge.
What do you got to say? You ain't got no words to speak to me?
Are you a type?
Am I Italian?
No.
Or are you real?
This is a real phone call.
Am I real?
I think, I don't think, I think he's a type.
A type?
I think you're just a loop.
That's your asshole?
You're one of Chaz's loops, aren't you?
I'm the Reverend Nicodemus.
You shall speak to me with respect, young man.
That's pretty clever, Chaz.
Having it sound like he's responding.
We saw the parts go in there perfectly.
You used the multi-index memory bank to pull up a random caller voice.
Are you guys fakies?
Oh, look, he typed a different one in there.
Are you fakies?
Are you a fakie?
A fakie.
He said it twice.
That must be the loop.
Are you a fakie?
I think our Reverend Ivan Stang is the lead fakie.
Yeah.
No, no.
I'm just work.
For the lead fakie.
Why don't you guys talk some knowledge?
Some knowledge?
Yes, the knowledge of the ages.
Some silent knowledge.
This man thirsts for knowledge.
How come, how come if you spell Bob backwards, it spells Bob?
Get him off the air.
We are about to impart to you the ultimate knowledge.
Your knowledge.
Is there a reason for spelling Bob backwards?
Silent knowledge.
Now you have three dollars, and you are enlightened.
Silent.
That will be twenty dollars.
But all I got is three dollars.
Oh, here we are now.
Why don't you hold the headphones and I'm gonna go check the tape.
Okay, I really can't expect this to be a new one.
salvation for only $20.
There's got to be more to it than that.
Dave, you haven't been in the same room with a female
in about, what, 30 years now?
No, I think it's like 24.
And there's one sitting right on the other side of that microphone.
Yep, that's right.
I'm in a room with an actual female now.
And she's crazy.
Listen to that voice.
I know those are the kind you like, though.
Well, I enjoy laughing as much as the next person
if you know what I mean.
Did you know that Stimpy was the originator
of bottled secretions?
No, I did not know that Stimpy was your orangutan
of bottled secretions.
Yes, yes, it was Stimpy himself, yes.
And when did this occur?
Or a crap, whichever you willed.
This was in the Curseful Lucy universe?
Yeah.
Yes, yes, this is the origin of the bottled effluence
that we have been...
Incoming.
...formally incarnating, yes.
I thought somebody was tapping on my drill helmet.
Oh, wait a minute, this is the wrong one.
I'm wearing the wrong one right now.
Now get the signals better on this one.
The tapping is coming from within.
B-O-R-B.
Down, my leg.
Spotty.
You know, I was wondering,
if I could ask you a question, Princess Weiradon.
Yes?
Yes.
Um, since...
Since none of these questions like
the ephemeral nature of radio performance
or Stimpy or any of that make any...
or Bob as a woman describe...
No, I don't like that.
I'd like to know what, if you may,
is the diet of the exes?
And also, how come yetis can't move their scapulas
because they have a different shoulder blade?
Oh.
Have you read about that or heard about that?
Yes.
That when they turn to a side,
they have to turn their whole torsos?
Yes.
It's quite complex, actually, yes.
It's a...
I'm not sure that I'd actually want to broach a subject such as that.
Now, diet of the exes,
that is another quite interesting...
Well, what did I live on?
Like rotisserie gold chicken and stuff like that, or...
Parasitic growth...
Syndrome.
Okay, now, I understand now the work you've been doing
for the Church of the Subgenies for last year,
as a doctor and dietitian, and also as a loose canon,
that you've studied the exes' diet for quite a while now,
and you're quite an expert.
This...
They're not flatulent, as the Reverend said,
because they are spiritual,
or are the exes unspiritual and therefore flatulent?
No, I believe the former.
They are not spiritual, and therefore they are not flatulent.
So they neither reap nor do they sow,
and they don't...
Neither do they fart.
This is all true.
I...
This is all true, yes.
So then they don't...
What kind of diet would create such a condition?
As I said, parasitic growths, mostly parasitic growths, yes.
Now, are these parasitic growths,
is there something that you and I could have?
Or, like, say, you and I would go out for dinner
or something like that, and spend an evening,
and, like, there'd be parasitic growths on us
or something like that?
No.
It's actually not available to us.
We...
Because the things that these...
Parasites grow on are things that we don't have around us.
Jeez, that's something, because, you know...
In our mundane world.
So it's not...
In the Munda Organ, it's not available right now.
Actually, no.
I...
See, because, like, all this yuppie, you know,
so many things, Ethiopian restaurants, you know,
and just all this different stuff,
I was wondering if I could get these parasitic growths somewhere.
No.
They're just simply not available.
How about the, like, say, for instance, the hacha?
Of my panties.
Or some other grievous misshapen article on my body.
Would that perhaps hold them?
Or, like, contain them for...
They might be tempted by that, yes.
But I'm not sure that it would quite sustain them.
So, there you have it.
The particular parasitic growths.
That one growth.
Yes.
Well, that's just amazing.
Now, I understand the Reverend Stinkish went to go on duty
or had to blow his bathroom or something like that,
laid down on floor four?
Something like that, yes.
Yes.
He was from...
But why is he...
Now, I know we should talk about this on the air
because he's a lovely man and everything,
but now, don't you think he's drinking too much?
Well, you see,
there is an instrument that's being played
that is a trance-inducing instrument,
and listeners actually may find themselves,
without knowing it,
falling into a deep and very mesmerizing trance.
And this is what has brought on the drunken behavior,
Reverend Stank.
Contrary to what may appear to be a simple alcoholic feeling,
it's actually a trance.
So, he hears his bootlet rumbling
and then just as soon as it passed into his auditory canals,
he became imbibed as if he'd been drinking.
Exact amount.
Oh, crikes, oh, plenty.
Jesus, Lord.
So, are we going to become imbibed by hearing this sound, too?
Because I don't feel no different right now.
Well, you have to relax and just let it happen,
and it will happen.
Well, I suppose I could take a big, deep breath
in this bottled green area.
Yes, just take several deep breaths.
Yes, just let it go.
Let it flow.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
It's fragrant.
Starting to feel anything, Dave?
Starting to feel anything, listener?
We certainly hope so.
And if you have entered into that deep trance
that we try to induce with this show,
then you will write for the free information
at the post office box number I'm about to give.
Ah, yes.
Yes.
That number to write, dear friends, of course,
is, uh...
Just write to Bob at Post Office Box 140306
in Dallas, Texas
at zip code 75214.
That's right.
You can get the free information
from the Church of the Subgenius
that explains everything.
How to come down from that trance
that has been induced during the last few minutes.
Uh, once again, that number is...
Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
A-7-5-2-1-4.
And, uh...
Well, it's getting down late in the show,
and with, uh, John Bartles to take us away,
I think we've got to run.
We've got to run.
We've got to get out.
They won't shut up.
They won't shut their mouth.
I'm getting claustrophobic,
hypertension, anaerobic.
I'm going nuts.
I'm drinking like a freaking alcoholic.
I've drank myself to death,
so quit the freaking crap.
I'd stop and kick your ass,
but I need another drink.
I've got to run.
I've got to take off.
You've got to shut your mouth
before I pour your head off.
I'd like to stop and kill you,
but I haven't got the time.
You are the freaking reason
that I lost my freaking mind.
My friends all say I look like I am in a freaking trance.
I'll come back and kill you
when I get a freaking chance.
I've got to run.
I've got to get out.
You're driving me crazy.
Shut your freaking mouth.
I'm going to come back to get you
until it's nice and freaking dark.
I'll chop you up in pieces
and I'll feed you to the car.
Your body, it will disappear
without a freaking trace.
I'll be doing a big favor
for the freaking human race.
Oh, I hate having to appear like that.
It really is the most tart
and the noisiest manifestation.
It's a great joke,
Palomus, for the Lord
or fate or nature.
Get down.
Dead?
No excuse for laying off work.
Evil turned out rather well.
Mm-hmm.
Punish!
erhögeally so that he Please more or less
no need to launching
When the
That wooden
Professor
© BF-WATCH TV 2021