I am just a dog.
20 million men have had abnormal sex.
Find out how.
The Self Genius Power of Sweat.
Specifically designed to target mouth constipation for a full hour.
I was a nun.
I was married to God.
Then I asked for a divorce.
And he gave me the world.
That surprise winning poem by our little girl here, Rosie Rottenkrotch.
You thought I wasn't going to introduce her, didn't you?
I thought we'd never see her again.
We bring her up here for her last visit.
She's going over to the school later today.
They're taking her in the Woody station wagon that's outside with Woody the Woodpecker on the outside.
To the little Woody, Woody, Woody, Woody, Woody, Woody Woodpecker school.
Just down the road where she'll be okay again.
A little while before she's gone.
But first, before that, let's introduce her to the crowd.
Here she is, little Rosie Rottenkrotch.
Thank you, thank you, boys.
Thank you very much.
Rosie, as you know, is the multiple...
Let's take that again, all right?
Yes, all right.
Rosie, as you know, is the...
Can we take that again?
Rosie, as you know, is the multiple identity poster girl.
Multiple identity poster girl.
For 1970, 62.
Thank you, boys.
Rosie, as you know, is the multiple identity poster child
for the...
For the 1967 weekend.
Thank you, boys.
Rosie, you know, is the multiple identity poster girl for this region of the...
Please give everything you've got to me or my family.
Just send it care of this address.
155, 155, 1555.
Just call it 1555.
That's 1515515.
Thank you, boys.
Just send everything you've got care of me or my family.
This is little Rosie Rottenkrotch.
The multiple identity poster girl for...
This week.
For this week.
Send to this address.
15151555.
That's 15151555.
15155555.
In Mexico.
Thank you, boys.
1-5-5-0-5-5-1-0-5-5.
Aura más música.
All my friends.
Comrades...
1515151515.
Aura más música.
45153.
кожa okay.
Here's all I've got.
And-a-long- представlamento реб Sequ glitter baby们
All right, google movieini
No show, which Doug Wellman loves.
I love you, no show.
The government totally sucks, you mother of a...
Yeah, if you're in North Korea, the government totally sucked.
Ben Franklin was a rebel indeed.
He liked to get naked while he smoked on the scene.
He was the kingiest, but if he was here today,
the government would buttercup his right to your day.
Hey, let me tell you something about the government.
What?
Blowing up the environment.
Hey, what?
Taking all the freaking beautiful animals, yeah.
And making them freaking extinct.
Oh, no!
The government totally sucks, you mother trucker.
The government totally sucks.
In North Korea.
Because the land of love and freedom
is just a baby's breath away.
And if we hold hands together,
we can bring back the USA.
The USA.
Bring back the USA.
Not the NPRK.
No, the USA.
Here on KPFA.
94.1.
KPFA in Berkeley, 88.1.
Bring back the USA.
Oh, yeah.
KFS, KC, KF, KF, KF.
And remember, the government totally sucks.
Wherever you are.
Was that the D?
Yeah.
The government totally sucks.
I've never heard that song by the D.
I thought it was Conspiracy Rock for a second.
Oh, that was a great band, Conspiracy Rock.
Yeah, they got that.
I want to more of rock.
Then there's Turok.
We were talking about Turok.
Turok, yeah.
Turok, Son of Stone.
Then there's Turok.
Deadly Spell.
Decimons.
That's my new goth band, Deadly Spell.
Oh, I bet there's 20 D.
You better Google that one and see if there's somebody that doesn't already have that name.
Oh, yeah, there is.
I looked up.
I was trying to contact Sister Decadence.
For some reason, I Googled Sister Decadence and discovered that there were something like
a hundred different bands out there named Decadence.
Yeah, it's like poor K-Rob.
You know, one day we went and looked for K-Rob.
And there were 100.
100 K-Rob.
50 of them in each city in America.
Well, you get on Facebook and there's something more Bob.
There's so many Bob Dobbs that your finger gets tired scrolling down.
I'm tired of scrolling.
So stupid.
Yeah, there's thousands and thousands of them.
Every now and then, one of them shows a different guy and it's probably someone whose name is
Robert Dobbs.
James Robert Dobbs or something.
So here we are on the show.
I feel sorry for those guys.
And you can call the November 4th Bureau of P.I.V.D. area code to find us.
I'm Robert Dobbs.
You're listening to KFAB and the Positive Evidence Show.
Or as heard on Hour of Slack, calls get lost, missed, knuckles up, dressed up, and what.
So you can leave that part in because the angels were carrying him while he said that.
I hate to put your number out on my show because it doesn't make any sense.
When some poor guy here is going to get a call.
Once a month.
What?
At midnight.
The KFAB.
The calls from Cleveland are coming.
They are.
They're rolling in.
Rolling, rolling, rolling.
Trolling, trolling, trolling.
Keep trolling, trolling, trolling.
Keep those niggas trolling, trolling.
Yep, the heat's gone back up so the calls, but the calls don't sound bad now so maybe
that's not related.
Before the internet, Dr. Drummond, remember how we used to troll people on CB radio?
We had the urge to troll.
But then we didn't have the means of the internet.
We could only troll within about a 19 mile radius.
You know, that proves that trolling is genetic to the human.
All humans need to troll.
Well, all subgeniuses need to troll.
I thought he said he was a subgenius butt.
I wouldn't say all subgeniuses.
Okay.
Did you say a subgenius butt?
She said that we're trolls under the bridge.
When we were singing it, I thought he said he's a subgenius butt, but he says he's
a genius butt.
It's an album put out without the bad words, you see.
It's a genius of those guys.
It's the actual CD of the Pick of Destiny.
My copy of the Pick of Destiny was simply copied from a movie.
Copy.
Oh, that worked?
And this song, I don't remember that song being on in the movie.
Yeah, I haven't seen the movie.
It totally sucks.
Yeah, that wasn't in the movie.
That's in North Korea, not here.
I don't know.
I don't remember either.
Right, yeah.
And here comes the...
No, I didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
Mr. Gingrich will be seeing you when you get home from the show.
Here is police escort.
Pulls up in front of you and asks, Governor Rhodes will get me.
Which state is he?
He's the one...
He sends the National Guard to shoot the students at Kent State.
He did though, right?
And they name the radio station after him.
WCSB used to be located in Rhodes Tower, named after Governor Rhodes, who told the National
Guard...
That's something about them hippies.
That's still...
People up there get big heartache every...
What if you were on top of her, dead on the ground?
Yeah, they...
What if you were?
I know people who did see her dead on the ground.
Well, there you go.
One of them formed a band called The Diva.
That's right.
Yeah.
What do you want to be...
Because he...
Yeah, I think about that all the time.
It's just a second.
I can't get it out of my mind.
The sense of seeing that and then going and starting Diva, because that's the...
That's the only place you can go with that energy.
Well...
But there is a movie called Troll.
It's an Norwegian movie.
Troll Hunter.
Yeah, I have the Norwegian copy on my face.
Yeah.
I mean, my YouTube thing.
Because somebody's putting up movies, movies and movies.
I've got that one with subtitles.
I want somebody to look great in that.
They look like real fairytale trolls.
They kind of look like the old radio station.
Well, they're more outlandish looking on that though.
They're...
I think we should call the president about it.
They're cartoonish, yet photo real.
That's what I liked about them.
They were like a crazy cartoon drawing that they rendered photo realistically with shaky
cam and fake night vision and everything.
I heard that they're American Hollywood mom and pop multi-conglomerate conspiracy is going
to make a Hollywood...
Hollywood version of Troll Hunter.
Well, maybe the Canadian chief will hear you this time.
Oh my God.
Which they'll probably change the title to Bigfoot Hunter.
I think they should keep Troll.
Well, yeah, but then it needs...
Yeah, but they're already Troll, I guess.
It's like, why remake it?
It's so...
The weirdness of it is that it's so Norwegian to begin with.
Oh, well.
It's Norwegian.
And I really like the fact that the trolls could smell the blood of a Christian man.
Yeah.
You couldn't bring...
It's okay if you're an atheist.
You could go troll hunting, but if you were a Christian man, you'd draw their attention.
They could smell you.
And they wanted to eat you real bad on account of your religion.
They wanted to eat you.
I smell the blood of a subgenius wallet.
Yeah.
I'm in the middle of the ocean time
And the feeling's laid back
All trees grow and rain's still low
But you know I keep thinking about
Making my way back
I'm New York City born and raised
Now that I'm lost between two shores
Here I'll show you
Knock on the door
LH family home
New York's home
We'll never find no more
Now
I, I have given
Red corpuscles enough to fill a frigate
I am myself
To no one there
And they, they keep me alive
And no one but them
Oh not even the child
I am a cry
I am survived
I am alive
And I have lost me
And can't even survive
Leaving me lonely still
So supply will never drop off
You understand?
Did you ever read about a frog who dreamed of being a king?
And then became one?
He's too hideous
Well except for the names and few other changes if you talk about me
The story's the same one
I got an evidence deep inside
I've tried it, won't let me go
You understand?
I'm not a man who likes to swear
But I never cared for the sound of being alone
I am myself
To no one there
And they, they keep me alive
And no one but them
Oh not even the child
I am myself
I am survived
And I have lost me
I have given Red Corpuscles enough to fill the frigate.
You understand?
I understand.
The Rudy Schwartz Project, covering a beloved Neil Diamond hit from the album Sunshine Supers
Hits.
And now, back to puzzling evidence with caller thing Phineas Narco.
And I saw a documentary on the making of the thing.
Which the thing?
The 1982 or 84.
The thing.
I was on July 31 with John Carpenter.
Because as we were driving down Highway 10 here, I kept seeing billboards to, Do you
dare to see the thing?
Oh, yes, that's a different...
The thing seemed to be a gift shop.
It was on the other side of the highway, so we didn't pull over, but...
The thing, can you take it?
The thing.
How'd you like it?
Well, can you take it now that you've seen it?
Maybe.
I may have mentioned this last week.
But one time when I was a kid, my family stopped on the highway to see the thing.
And it was an abused, aged chimpanzee.
Where's my father?
A hairless chimpanzee that picked all its own, scratched all its own hair off and lived in insanity.
Yeah, it was awful.
That was the thing.
I don't think anyone dares to see that thing anymore.
You know where that was, Phineas?
It was like 50 cents then.
I'm talking about in the middle of the previous century.
You know what highway that was, Phineas?
666?
Yep.
Aha.
Lucky guess.
Yep.
The thing.
The thing ones I saw were all on highway Interstate 10.
Dr. Hall was familiar with it.
He knew about the Interstate 10 thing.
He said that one is a mummy.
The one I saw was a live abused chimpanzee and the one he saw was a mummy.
Ah.
There's also a mummy in Portland that's kind of a thing.
Down by the park in Portland there's a museum of Goldado with a cool...
No, it's a prospector mummy, I think.
Is it near the mystery hole?
Uh, it's in the same town as the mystery hole.
Have you been to the mystery hole?
I've been to the mystery hole.
Man.
Did you get the vapors of encouragement?
No.
Or was it vapors of enthusiasm?
You got a little jar of these vapors and you signed a liability thing before you went down into the mystery hole.
And then it was...
It's like the whole world got tinier and tinier as you went down the ladder.
Yeah, okay.
To the point where you couldn't even use the ladder if it got so tiny.
And there were tiny doors at the bottom of the ladder.
And then you had to go through them with tiny things on the other side of the tiny door.
Thing one and thing two.
I just remember everything being really tiny.
Yeah.
Well, but do you remember everything?
Do you remember all the things?
No, I don't.
That's the weird thing about it.
I just remember...
Why?
Things!
See?
It's one of those thing things.
That's right.
Well, doctors, uh, I'm going to go to the mystery hole.
I shall bid you adieu.
I shall bid you a do-do.
A do-do.
Oui, oui.
Monseigneur.
A do-do.
Keep up the good work and, uh...
Do you know who shot Liberty Valance?
No, I don't.
The man.
Well, that's...
It was the man who shot Liberty Valance.
If anybody can actually successfully answer the question of the night, who shot Liberty Valance, please call us now at 510-
But also...
I just gave the answer a little bit.
Alfredo Garcia.
You have...
I...
Was that por...
Was that a porno movie?
Oh.
Give some head to Alfredo Garcia?
No, from.
Oh, get some head from Alfredo Garcia.
Yeah.
I think that was a porno.
From the head of...
Alfreda.
Yeah.
Alqueda Garcia.
See, there's the porno movie.
There's a porno movie.
There's a porno title in there somewhere.
Yeah, there is.
Yeah, get the head of...
Alqueda Garcia.
Yeah.
Give, like, Machete versus Osama Bin Laden.
Porno movie.
From PR News in Washington, I'm struck down for helping to bring North Korea to South Korea, and the damage is severe.
And that...
Um...
To...
He...
Uh...
That's PR's Lucas.
On Wall Street 25, the National Weather Service now confirms this is PR News.
Or PR News Washington.
And it's reported that this is PR.
Hi, I'm the Everly Brothers, and in our business we hear a lot of talk about drugs.
The heavy message now is that speed kills.
It refers to a group of drugs called antipetamins, including Ops, Pep Pills, Math Dex, even many.
You see what speed drugs can do?
They're dangerous.
The?!
Personally, I think drugs currently
can be helpful in 여기에 r
So just watch the video used in this directed.
OR
WATCH.
Paul comported drugsaultếu procedure
Thank you.
Yeah.
There's not often that
in the movies, I've also heard
mentioned that
Stanley Kubrick's movies
always have a
bathroom scene.
That's right. 2001.
And The Shining.
2001.
And Black or Orange.
And uh
What's the last one he did?
I shut that back.
Yeah.
But United went on
for about half a show and was trying to figure out why we liked it.
I did. I don't know why.
What about Paths of Glory?
No bad... Yeah, probably.
Latrine.
1957 or something.
Of course, we don't know.
We have to check in the unknown pile right now.
How come subgenius shows
turn into film history shows
for 20 minutes every time?
Because instead of having a life, we all watch movies.
Yeah, old movies.
My latest location I have
to go visit is
Goblin State Park in Green River, Utah.
I saw it in Galaxy Quest.
I was thinking,
some of this is painted in, but some of this is real.
I want to climb around on those real rocks.
On the big old round golf ball rocks.
Yeah, it's alien land.
Is that where Kurt Voskes
went to Gorn?
No, that's at Voskes Rocks.
I was there almost...
Bob Dobbs was almost busted there
a month ago, but I don't want to tell that story
anymore.
No, you told that story
on the last two shows.
The old blind ball.
The Voskes Rocks is where
Kurt walked and fought the Gorn.
And where
Planet of the Dinosaurs was shot
with music in there.
And they did some catch-up parts
of Jesus Christ Superstar there.
Most of it's filmed in Negev.
They run over to Voskes.
Sometimes you've got to do those extra shots.
I used to have a little Gorn action figure
when I was a kid.
Wow.
How much?
No, I'm not going to say that.
It had to be explained to me
two or three years ago
what a Gorn was because I had
forgotten. I was such a
bad nerd that I'd
forgotten the Star Trek character
of the Gorn and how
stupid looking it was.
Really? I understand the modern
day version is all ugly.
In fact, there is one in that movie.
There's a Gorn
in that modern day Star Wars remake.
The Gorn was a lizard-headed
costume man.
Oh, yeah.
In the fourth episode or something.
And it was really terrible
costume. Lizard-head man.
That was what made him so famous.
I didn't notice him because I'm always looking for the fake
caves made out of real nice thick aluminum.
Black painted aluminum they have in
Hollywood. You couldn't see that
when I was 12 years old.
But now you can see that.
You can see what everything
is made of. On Day Job Orchestra.
He's running around with a very
phallic stalactite.
There's that devil
in the dark.
I don't remember.
There's phallic stalactites
everywhere. That'd be a good band
named Phallic Stalactite.
The Petrified Penis
Forest.
There was a place
that was like that. It's called the City
of Rocks.
It looked like pagans had spent
millennia carving
giant phallic symbols
in the rock. But actually they were all
natural.
What about that spooky forest
that everyone goes to kill themselves
in Japan?
Yeah. I don't want to go there.
Suicide forest. I don't want to have
X Day there again.
It was a bad place
to have X Day.
We didn't make any money
either.
I can do anything on Google now.
You can go places on Google.
Except as long as it's not
real.
I've been doing both.
I'll Google a place and then I'll
go to the place.
The Puzzling Evidence Show.
I'm just so sad. And I'll gargle it.
Very sad now. Why sad?
Because no
queen of UFOs has come.
Enterprise episode.
I think we learned that UFOs
have fallen asleep.
And have Scott Bakula fighting a Gorn.
Is that Ragnar?
It is.
Ragnar's the one who had to explain to me
what a Gorn was again.
Because he was selling a t-shirt for
Magdalene that had a Gorn.
I honestly had been so
far from Captain Kirk
and Spock that I'd
forgotten.
I'm trying to relearn everything.
The CGI Gorn that they had in the Enterprise.
Episode.
Right.
Oh, okay.
Well, Ragnar, I want to tell you.
I don't, I don't.
The Gorn.
The Gorn porn.
Now you're talking, man.
Now see, up until this point, I was thinking this is pretty nerdy.
The Gorn porn.
They're reptilians, right?
And they're very slow.
They're Gorn reptilian creatures.
Yeah, they're like sleazestacks.
They're like doing it.
Yeah, like doing it with a dinosaur.
Yeah, they're really slow.
They're really slow.
They're really slow. Super slow.
They have dual
peni reptiles do.
I don't know about dinosaurs.
They may be different.
They're not reptiles.
But neither are Gorns.
Gorns aren't dinosaurs either.
They're different.
Dr. Hal, would a Gorn porn eventually end in a snub film?
Why, yes, it would.
Everything.
Everything would end in a snub film.
I'm surprised Hal's not listening and trying to call in right now.
As Dr. Leguim said,
nobody's biography
has a happy ending.
There was a fine garden that Antonio Carozzi kept.
There were tall, aggressive beanstalks,
jungles of cotton and tomato vines,
ears of corn like golden footballs,
and out front, placed there to conceal the tempting vegetables,
300 spindly marijuana plants.
I didn't even know it could be smoked,
Carozzi said, when North Tarrytown, New York police
harvested the offending shoots
and planted a drug charge on the 57-year-old Italian immigrant,
which was later discharged.
He visited his native village, Carmonda,
in the Arbruzzi mountains,
and brought back a packet of canapa seeds.
Camardans, he recalled from his youth,
used canapa fibers to make thread and cloth.
Its seeds are used in soups and candies.
The kids, Carozzi recalled,
used to carry them in their pockets
and eat them like peanuts.
Ironically, only the leaves are thrown away.
Always I wondered why in America,
where they have everything,
they did not have canapa seeds.
I look everywhere for them,
even in the bird seed.
How come, I wonder, they do not have?
Now I know.
Only the who of knows.
Those were the words of Harry,
the hash hedge, Carozzi, right?
Right.
The biggest dealer in the Italian section.
The biggest and the best.
Yeah, they used to eat these things, officer,
when I was a little kid.
Sure.
We don't do anything with the leaves,
we burn them.
They burn the leaves.
We burn them.
You burn whole books of them at one time.
You can make books on the burnings.
Yeah, you're right.
You can get 5 to 1, 6 to 1,
you can get 10 to life if you're not careful.
But you can get really stung, too.
And badly burned, man.
Yeah, man, some of it's sugared.
It sure is, baby.
Some of it is so sweet,
I put it in my coffee and that's how we use it.
So, smoke it.
That's for the crazy white guys
like Sir Walter Raleigh, you know, man.
We turned him on before he went back to England, you know.
Yeah?
Yeah, he went back and got his head chopped off, man.
We also turned him over.
He used to stand on his head.
He did.
He thought he was in China.
That's right.
Thought he'd get along with everybody.
What's weird, man, you ever seen a guy with eyes in his feet?
Yeah, sure I have.
Just like a potato, right?
Sure.
A spud upside down is an American, right?
That's what we used to call him, Spud.
Spud Raleigh, sure, man. I remember Spud Raleigh.
I was in gym class with him.
Yeah, Jim? Everybody else in my class is named Jim, too.
You must have gone to the same school.
Yeah, did you go to Jim High School?
Yeah, I sure did. That's where I had a plan.
Hi, Jim. What's your name, by the way?
Jim. How you doing, man?
What I'd like to know is why,
when you're watching late-night movies on television,
when all the kids are supposed to be in bed,
they take out the word God
from any European movie.
There's no usage whatsoever,
including when somebody says,
God bless you, it's on television.
Bless you.
I know why.
Oh, Jimmy?
All the other Jimmys, sit down.
The Jimmy I'm pointing at, stand up.
Jimmy?
Don't sit down in that.
Okay, Jimmy, come up to the microphone and tell me.
It's because God stays up late,
and it's Him who's watching.
That's right.
They don't want to offend Him.
You gotta get four fenders, right,
for God the four-wheeled man, right?
Sit down, Jimmy.
Sit down on what?
Sit down on Jimmy over there.
Okay, excuse me, Jimmy.
Ow!
Excuse me, can I borrow your Jimmy?
Yeah, but Jimmy over there, he's caught, right?
Just a second, Jim, I'll be right with you.
Get me out of here.
Anybody got any Jack?
I got some Jimson weed, though.
Jackson High School.
That's everybody named Jackson.
That's right.
Night in Jail Junior High School.
Solid geometry, Jackson.
Was that what yours was called?
That's just around the corner from us.
That's where Tiny went, right? Night in Jail?
I went to the Pink Penitentiary.
That's the baddest junior high school in Los Angeles.
The baddest, man?
The baddest, man, is Night in Jail Junior High School.
They still throw oil at each other there, man.
It's in Highland Park. Very heavy.
Brian Highland Park, isn't it?
I don't know. I can't keep up with him.
I'm dying.
The kind that goes on is,
And they lived happily ever after.
Forever and ever.
Those are my favorite kind of endings.
They lived forever in a century of bliss.
And then a decade.
And then another century.
And then an eon.
And then you get into the crow that comes to the mountain,
sharpens its beak.
and you know.
And the computer in the background.
Are you printing this out?
Open the bathroom door, please, Hal.
The script's printed like 30 seconds before we get there.
Open, Hal, the bathroom door.
Quick.
I can't do that, Dave.
It's stuck.
Take it.
Must reach.
Oxygen switch.
Must reach. Toilet paper.
Must talk like William Shatner.
The History Channel presents Rest Stops of America.
With your hosts,
Dr. Philo Drummond, Buzzing Evidence,
and Reverend Ivan Stagg.
And I'll tell you about the best restrooms
on your drive across America.
The best public restrooms you can get to,
private restrooms that are sometimes
hard to get to, but
just as rewarding in those
times of trouble
when nature's call
is most urgent.
What about rest stops?
My favorite
rest stop is in Arizona
and it's called Texas Valley.
It's just past
Wilcox, Arizona.
Near Chiricahua
National Park.
And it is as good that rest stop is as cool looking as the five dollar national park.
Not that I would discourage people from supporting our national park.
But the state of Arizona, I suppose, the rocks around it were beckoning me.
But we basically just stopped for the rest stop.
Yeah, but it's the most scenic rest stop I've ever seen.
That's what's cool about Arizona.
Well, well kept.
When we got to California, the first rest stop we came to was closed.
And I thought, man, this is a bad sign.
If they're closed all the way to L.A., then we'll know that government is collapsing.
But the next one was open.
Not for long.
And there were signs everywhere saying, if you see anyone smoking, call this number.
Be a fink for America.
Report smoking in national parks.
And rest stops.
I understand fire danger.
Only you can prevent forest fires.
Yeah, I'm not sure if it's that as much as just the encouragement of finkery among Americans.
The sub-juniors, junior slack squad, when we take our campers out into the forest,
we've always taught them how to put their forest fires out when they were finished.
It's not out until you can lower your belly under the cold, wet ashes.
When they were finished warming themselves on the forest fire,
we always tried to teach them how to put the forest fire out if they had time.
Before they had to go back to civilization.
Turn in your parents in some sort of jack-chick-in nightmare.
Clean up your forest fire, boys.
I want you to stir that forest two times.
Report your neighbor.
Remember, Smokey the Bear says,
only you can turn in your neighbor.
Only me?
I'm under pressure.
Oh, God.
Oh, thank God.
It was a nightmare about the communist takeover of America.
My opinion, traitors.
Smokey Bear didn't actually say that himself.
Those words were put into his mouth by a marketing PR firm.
Smokey was exploited.
The only bipedal...
Fully bipedal, clothes-wearing bear.
Yogi was just a legend.
But Smokey was real, and they used him.
They took him to government laboratories in the desert
and programmed him to talk about forest fires.
I hear some noodling going on there.
Poor Smokey.
What did they do to you, Smokey?
Help me.
I die now, my son.
But soon there will come on the mountain a sacred fire from a pipe.
His name shall be J.
A man will come among you with one sandal and one pipe.
Followed by a man with one testicle.
And one morsel of froth.
And followed by another man with one...
One ear in the middle of his forehead.
Now you're getting into the long...
How come all these guys only have one thing where they ought to have two?
What about the people who only have one when they should have dozens?
What about a guy with only one nostril?
Think about that.
One nostril.
In the center of his forehead.
Full of red hair.
Yeah.
Nice...
Matted red hair.
Matted red...
Curly pubis.
Public hair.
In a nostril.
That's all wrong, Dr. Drummond.
And silly and juvenile.
And I think it's...
It lowers the general common denominator of public discourse.
You made the show hurt, doctor.
Yeah.
Look at that.
I'm sorry.
You should rub some homeopathic ointment on his chest.
I'm gonna rub some salve into the...
Yeah.
Show's show...
No.
Oh, I forgot.
The bag bomb.
You have to use bag bomb.
I'm gonna rub some bag bomb on the show's bag.
Not that kind of bomb.
Hey, man.
That's not funny.
It's terrible.
The show's...
Okay.
I'm palpating the show's bag right now with this bag bomb.
The show seems...
This is one I didn't get.
I didn't get it.
Responder.
Just a few Index Another .
wie
I give Steve and I give-
And a
Should we check to the truck we take?
I'm sure we'll take a ride.
Well, I go off and check in the truck first.
It's going way faster than I thought they would put the X in the motor.
Kind of, I got leading reading.
It doesn't make any sense.
was a drone, she was a drag, paper and wire killed my brother and my sister too, and if
you don't watch out, you know they're gonna get you, and if I don't watch out, you know
they're gonna get me too, telephone, telephone, telephone, and I strangled, and I ripped the
cord, and I saw the bone, and I heard these tweeting things, and twinkling lights, and
there was nobody home, well now those nerve endings coming out of the bone, telephone,
telephone, telephone, well I ripped the cord right out of the bone, and I saw the bone,
the other gleaming white bone, telephone, paper and wire killed my brother and my sister
too, and if you don't watch out, you know they're gonna get you, and if I don't watch
out, you know they're gonna get me too, telephone, telephone, and I can't get away, and I can't
get away, it's like a greyhound at the end of the hall, it's like a plastic horned devil.
Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, a song called Telephone from Duck at the Radar Station,
oh so paranoid, only one thing left to do, build your own Amsterdam.
Well, Guido's here in the house, but he seems like he's in a garage or something.
He's built his own Amsterdam.
That's the look I got, he's got one eye pointed skyward and one to the ground.
Perhaps we must build our own.
Those ships, but in the meantime, since those ships are so dangerous, complicated and expensive,
you can build your own Amsterdam.
Of course, if they catch you doing it, they'll throw you in prison for 99 years.
Yeah, they don't like that very much.
But, people are doing it all the time.
Yeah, man, everybody's building like their own private Amsterdam, see, you know, that's
what the mind is for, you control your mind, you control your own private Amsterdam.
Well, actually, I was more like thinking about your backyard or your garage.
Oh, you control your back?
Yeah, you can control your muscles in your lumbago, you can also control your cesspool
and everything back there too, you know.
If a yogi can control his lumbago, then make it into a whole separate, almost like another
mind.
A yogi can control his lumbago and give himself instant healing, but he can't eat a lousy
piece of fried chicken or some, you know, spaghetti with meat sauce.
You know what I'm saying?
The guy can probably make himself fly, but he can't find a pair of shoes that actually
fit.
What?
Well, that's the thing about being a holy man, you have to be not of this world, which
usually means you don't have a job and you have to depend on handouts, that's what I
do.
Yes, but you are so unholy, I mean, if there ever was a word...
Well, I'm a holy man of unholiness, you know, I mean, there's a tradition of that, it's
legitimate.
Not the fuck here.
There's conventions, I mean, you know, I go to conventions with other holy men of unholiness,
unfortunately.
Yeah.
Like Anton LaVey or somebody?
Well, unfortunately, some of the best ones are dead.
Anton LaVey is dead, isn't he?
Anton's dead.
Koresh is dead.
Now, do you think he went to hell or purgatory or heaven or Lumbago or any of those places?
Disney Land.
Guido said it best.
He went to Disney Land.
Can't you see the Church of the Satanist guy in one of those weird teacup rides, you know,
like the Mad Hatter teacup ride or going maybe through Pirates of the Caribbean?
Actually, I'm sure there was a time when Anton LaVey went through Disney Land.
Yeah.
I've been to Disney Land.
That's before.
I mean, lots of people go to Disney Land sooner or later.
Well, Chaz.
I thought it was really kind of boring and pink.
Well, you've got to go.
Epcot Center was cool.
You've got to take the mystic tour.
Like, Chaz, you know, if you want to be a real Satanist or a craft worshiper, Chaz went to the Crossroads.
Chaz went to the Crossroads.
You don't go to Europe.
You've got to go down.
You're going to the Mississippi Delta.
Well, I wasn't trying to suck that mud.
Suck that mud and suck the brain right out of that mud bug.
Well, that's fine, but I just wanted to get high.
What the hell was that thing about?
What is this?
I've been handed a soundtrack of the movie Constantine with Johnny.
Keanu Reeves.
Yeah, with Keanu Reeves.
Yeah.
Didn't our friend, Piss Baptist, John Shirley, write like a CD?
Yeah, he wrote a...
He wrote a...
He wrote the second Constantine novel.
I don't know if he actually read his novel.
Or did he write the novel of that?
He just wrote a...
It was a comic book, then a movie.
And then he wrote like an imagining of other events and things that happened.
First, it was a subgenius gag on the show.
Then it was a novel or comic book.
Then a novel, then a movie, then a novel of the movie.
And then a trailer.
Then a comic book of the novel.
Then a trailer.
Then a theater poster.
No, actually, the poster and the trailer came first.
Yeah, that's right.
Before the show joke, actually.
We're not giving credit where credit's due.
It's kind of like Machete.
Yeah.
They made a musical out of it.
And it was a pinball machine.
And a Mattel toy set at McDonald's.
Yeah.
The little baby Machete and his baby villains and baby hookers.
They were able to buy the Queen of UFOs special seat on the sex goddess thing
with those little...
With 103 little baby Machete things from McDonald's.
You never know what's going to be valuable later.
Exactly.
Think if you still had that Pee Wee Herman talking doll.
The wind up, the pull the string and he talks Pee Wee doll.
Like the one Paul has in handcuffed facing the corner.
That's funny.
Potter Nostril has one that's being serviced by the Little Mermaid.
A marionette Pee Wee.
Pee Wee Herman is being taken care of by the Little Mermaid.
I think we should redo Men in Black with Pee Wee Herman as the young guy.
But Machete is now badass.
Now Machete played by Paul Rubens.
That would be interesting.
That would be different.
I mean the guy's done 30 Rock.
He should be able to do Machete.
Did I tell you I saw that in a theater?
I went to see the...
I think the Develettes.
Yeah.
Young ladies.
Very funny.
That's what I'm talking about.
And then yeah it was those two movies played on a big old screen.
So when I saw Planet of Terror, whatever it was, the first movie was.
It has Machete afterwards as a commercial.
It was quite an experience because it was like sitting in the theater in 1970s again
with big splices and cigarette burns in the corner and all that stuff that movies have.
The soundtrack it was off.
And then...
leap with the raw Mexican.
Yeah.
Machete.
And things missing.
Coming to theaters near you.
They should have had, like,
the smell of old cigarettes
and cheap wine.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, true.
That comes with the $150 DVD set.
It's funny.
There was one thing
that he had to shorten.
In real life,
it took a lot longer.
It's when the film
would get caught up
and the bulb would burn
through the frame.
And in the movie,
in the fake version,
it's all fixed
in a second or two.
And in real life, folks,
you used to have to sit there
in the theater
and yell at the poor people.
Right, throw popcorn at people.
I've saved the best for last.
The climax of this episode
of Hour of Slack,
if you will,
it's the Firesign Theater's
absolute masterpiece
of social and media criticism.
The pinnacle.
It's eight minutes long,
but by the time you get to the end,
your jaw will be on the floor
in amazement
at how much information
they were able to put
into that mere eight minutes.
The Firesign Theater.
Thank you, Mr. Mullins.
We're very fortunate indeed
to have with us this evening
Mr. William P. Bundy,
who's staff director
of the President's Commission
on National Goals.
Now, you will wonder
the way I have
what that commission is,
and I will address myself
to Mr. Bundy in a minute
with the question
of what exactly this is.
But before we go into
the heart of the matter,
and that is the national purpose,
Mr. Bundy,
I'd like you to tell our audience
about your work
as staff director
of the President's Commission
on National Goals.
What is the commission?
Well, I'm afraid our time
is up now, Mr. Bundy.
We're looking forward
to continuing.
It's been a privilege,
Mrs. Carey.
No, no, we really should go.
All right.
Unless you have a question
right up your sleeve.
Well, let's stop on that.
Well, I'll cut that out.
I couldn't resist that.
Would you like to ask a question,
Mr. Rose?
I would make a comment on that.
Would you like to comment on this?
Yes, I would like to comment on it.
Would you like to comment briefly?
Oh, yes.
Would you have any comment on...
Well, yes.
I'd like to comment on that briefly, too,
if I might.
How much time do I have?
You have to leave here.
No, I say this.
But he would always say,
well, from the beginning,
they...
I think this is...
So many people think...
No, I'm not for a minute saying...
We always...
We...
Yes.
Well, that's very, very interesting indeed.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Go on.
And go on,
because I'm afraid we did interrupt you.
Well, it was a very polite interruption,
and my statement, as I now recall,
it sounds...
It sounds very pompous, but...
I don't really believe you.
Sorry, I interrupted you.
No, no, I was just...
It's running.
That's all right.
Oh.
Uh...
Well, go ahead, Professor McDougall.
Now you can help me on something.
You know...
I don't quite know.
I think it's...
Do you have sex?
Uh...
I don't...
I certainly don't condone it.
No.
I'm not interested.
I get terribly, um...
sort of, um...
bound up, as it were,
in, um...
in knowing whether...
when one spends a lot of time,
you know how it is.
I think that answers it.
That's the trick.
How to handle it.
It has serious dangers.
Serious dangers.
Politics makes strange bedfellows,
and...
and, uh...
your policy, I know,
as a...
as a faithful patriotic, uh...
man, is...
No, no.
At the very opening meeting...
But in response...
In response, uh...
it's...
we have...
the, uh...
the communists, uh...
that, uh...
the...
that there are liberal...
I don't know...
the...
whether anybody else does it or not.
And I have a feeling this may be happening.
I mean...
Perhaps artificially, but anyway,
uh...
it has been...
it has been the, uh...
it is the...
the...
uh...
I think when...
the...
where...
Precisely.
I mean, uh...
It's terribly tiresome for Indians,
and I'll tell you why.
You know, because they have extreme...
uh...
um...
problems there.
It's an absolutely colossal question.
I have nothing but praise.
Well, I suppose that we could spend the rest of our...
our time here talking about white collar workers.
There is no other organization which can perform that function.
There's no alternative.
Yes.
And there are others, too.
Uh...
There are examples to, uh...
to show almost, uh...
uh...
limited kinds of effects which can be...
Neil, in the...
in the course of this study of ours,
this isn't quantitative,
but it's a kind of report.
They wrote out of the...
their very deepest experience...
Anything that would...
Anything that would invite, uh...
interference.
All right, but these all reflect...
They reflect not only that, but, uh...
drain, uh...
Mm, yes.
Mm-hmm.
Sort of, just kind of...
You know, yes, it's hard to, uh...
to...
to lump them together, as we were saying.
Well, uh...
Uh...
Then...
Then where do we fit in?
The...
He calls it...
Uh...
Now, this struck me as rather symbolic, eloquent, uh...
Mm-hmm.
Well, that sort of fits.
I'm sure you all will agree.
I want to cite something that I, uh...
got over...
I...
I received by mail just the other day.
Well, I...
I was wondering, could I cut in on...
before...
before you do that, uh...
Yes.
...that simply to...
As it were, um...
It's difficult to put this without being offensive.
Um...
So...
Let me...
There were...
You know, then...
You know, the important thing, you know, is to be...
But, um...
This, um...
You know, that...
It, um...
I suppose it...
It's the, um...
But the, um...
The sort of, um...
Stream of literature.
But I'm sorry I interrupted you.
When you...
That was an exceedingly long answer.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Would you agree with Stephen Spender, who said at a party in Wheaton that D. H. Lawrence
was the last poet to write English poetry?
Isn't he?
No, no, and...
And, uh...
Mm-hmm.
Shall we take, uh, D. H. Lawrence as a focal or a pivotal figure around which we might
have some conversation?
No.
I have no more questions.
He says no.
I...
Well, all right.
Supposing...
Excuse me.
Go ahead, Mr. Westfield.
Ah...
Well, Mr. Dahl...
Excuse me.
Ah...
Well, Mr. Dahl...
Instead, it's not...
Crash, brother.
Well, do you want to go on with anything else?
Do we have time for one more question, Mrs. Huff?
Yes.
Oh, thank you, Mrs. Huff.
You're welcome.
That's right.
Well, I feel the same way.
I do agree.
They...
We were popular in a popular...
And it was not, for example...
Yeah, I...
I don't believe...
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I don't...
Um...
Uh...
I see.
And, in effect, if I follow your thinking correctly, and I would be inclined to say
that I'm inclined to agree with it if I do...
Uh...
No.
Well, it pains me to agree with Steven Spender, but I think that there may be something in
this.
I'm wondering, since our time is limited...
Well, I think that we've probably run out of time anyway, so thank you very much for being
with us on Yale Reports this evening.
Very enough.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Uh...
And since we don't know what time it is, maybe the sun is standing.
If you could do that with this newspaper that was already held from theグ дан位
Aladdin Squadron, or even before that like The Hymn to Tomorrow, it could sell gas.
сам stump feminine
people. You have to, what, dial up a little envelope there to P.O. Box. Friend, all you
got to do is just look at the sub-site on the web. Oh, www.subgenius.com. Or just say,
just to peel back your skull. We're not trying to get money out of radio listeners on this
college station. All you need to do, shut up, Dave, is write P.O. Box. 807 Glen Rose,
Texas. 76043. Go, Dave, go! No. I ruined it. Oh, I'm sorry. I had to do the P.O. Box
and I was imitating Chaz. It's so funny when Chaz goes, shut up, Dave. I think it's one
of the funniest things I ever hear. I wait to hear that all the time. Well, it gets chaotic.
People are talking over each other. You can't hear either one. What can I do to make up
for it, Dave?
Shut up and let me talk the next ten minutes, both you guys.
All right. All right. We'll just give it to you.
No, he just said, he said, what can I do to make up for it?
Okay. Now turn off his mic, too. Now turn off my mic.
Oh, here.
Okay, turn off my mic.
Now isn't that better?
Than what?
Man, it's like...
Bergman knew how to use silence.
Oh, I bought it.