We broadcast during the hours when the mind's grip on what it knows is at its weakest.
The day hours of the morning between 4.30 and 6 o'clock.
This is the time when ancient superstitions and night fears have the greatest hold on human thoughts.
The time when those who sleep are deep in their dreams.
And this is the hour when on the church of the subgenius radio show the doctors of the air operate without warning.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius hour of black.
We inhabit a twilight world.
A world which feels the rising sun.
Long life.
After nightfall.
When the witching hour has been dead for three and a half hours.
We rise from our coffins and go forth to stalk our living victims.
You, our beloved audience.
Good hunting brothers.
Howl.
This is Dr. Howl.
Wailing in the night.
For that which lived, which is dead.
And for that which is dead.
Was dead.
And in fact was never alive.
So we're moving.
We get back to Bob.
Oh, hello boys and girls.
We're back again with the Reverend Ivan Stang.
The tape will last another 45 minutes or so.
I'm Mr. Froelich and I'm your host today, boys and girls.
And this is the Reverend Ivan Stang to tell us about the church of the subgenius and Bob, his friend.
Before you get on to Bob.
Let me just do one thing.
Show up for the showdown.
You can bleep this out later.
I should have done this when you flipped your tape.
You're listening to...
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
The secret that unlocks flavor.
Diamonds are a girl's best friend.
Everybody say amen.
Amen.
It's not very...
Easy living in here.
Remember that.
Well, in answer to your question, Chaz, the church of the subgenius was started by Bob to reveal the dangers of bug pornography.
And as a matter of fact, you know, I hate to harp on this subject.
But, you know, as a preacher, I have to bring this kind of thing to people's attention.
I feel it's my responsibility.
Now, about a year or two ago, we started making these funny jokes.
About bug porn.
It was actually inspired by some toasterized, psychedelicized versions.
Footage from an old movie called The Hellstrom Chronicle featuring really cool pictures of bugs.
Well, I thought that any, you know, healthy young subgenius would be really turned on by these cute naked, naked bugs.
And we...
It was a big funny joke.
But, friends, I don't know about you.
But I went...
I went to the movies for the first time in about three months tonight.
And, uh...
Well, there was a trailer for this one movie called Starship Troopers.
And it was nothing but ocean and a flood of giant, monstrous bugs sweeping over these soldiers in the future.
They were just blowing the giant ticks.
And so...
So forth with the way...
It was bug porn is what it was.
Bug death porn.
Same thing.
I mean, when you're talking bugs, sex, and death, they're about the...
You know that scene where the female praying mantis chews the head off of her mate right after he has done it with her?
And...
Investigated her eggs and so forth.
But, friends, that's just...
It's just exactly like your relationship.
To your boss.
Now, think about it, ain't it?
Anyway, the point is...
Okay, so Starship Troopers coming out.
Bug porn.
Right.
There's another movie out now, I believe, called Mimic.
Which has something to do with the hideous monster bugs that disguise themselves as people or something like that.
And, of course, I saw all these trailers while going to see the movie Men in Black.
You know, it's odd how every summer...
Every summer...
They come out with a subgenius movie, so to speak.
Where the conspiracy takes what Bob's been saying all along and turns it around on his head.
All of a sudden, the men in black aren't some sort of sinister government group.
There are good friends that save us from knowing the terrible truth.
Because then we just wouldn't be happy if we knew about all those aliens ready to pounce on us and destroy our planet any second.
Why, if we thought the National Enquirer was more true than CNN and NPR...
Why, wouldn't...
That would just destroy our faith in reality.
Now, wouldn't it be?
And, of course, last summer they had to do the movie where the aliens invaded the Earth and the Earth fought back and won.
Well, I guess then, as Dr. Leguim was saying, next year, 1998...
That summer movie will show aliens that come.
Benevolent, wonderful aliens that come and take over the whole world.
And the only ones who fight back against the aliens will be the bad, antisocial people.
They'll be the bad guys in the movie.
Funny how they always seem to turn it around on your friends.
You ever notice how the people in the movies that look like you are always the bad guys?
No.
They're not even the main bad guys.
They're the bad guys' minions.
Right?
Right.
You're talking about me, man.
Watching, and it could be a fiction or non-fiction.
Cops.
It could be, you know, any cop show, any crime show, any bad guy.
I'm one of the guys that get roughed up for the information.
You know, I look at them, I guess I look at myself.
There's a receding hairline that kind of like, hey, maybe, like, might be Italian or something.
You know, it's like, you know, it's like...
You're the one that spills his guts.
Hey, man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because, like, you know, it's Batman, right?
You know?
You spill your guts and are left humiliated.
You get the bad guy that doesn't even get killed.
It's better than spilling your bladder all over Batman's shoes, man.
Yeah.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Bobby.
Bobby Bob.
Bob Bob.
Him and Joe Bob and Billy Bob.
Jesus Bob.
All them Texas Bob types.
Bob Bob.
Isn't that too, Ed Bob?
In between the
Glitz band talk,
this is Lost Straight Jackets
in the background.
If I had a dime
for every time I had my face
buried in a big bowl of
killed...
Well, friends,
you know, I'd have $1.50 now.
Dobbs spelled backwards
is still
Spod.
Wow. That's cosmic.
That's real cosmic.
I can't go there.
That was revealed to us
very recently
that Dobbs
spelled backwards
is still
Spod.
Man.
Spod Bob.
Natas.
With
kids
and
tears.
You also heard from something
from a band called
We
from the album
The Mollusk.
Tell the golden eel.
Was that the back?
Was that the Backmaskers?
That was a great band.
The Backmaskers?
Yeah.
Is that anything like
Batmasterson?
No, no.
No?
Totally different, but similar.
They were Christian rock.
Christian rock.
The Backmaskers.
We like Christian rock.
Bob Larson and the Backmaskers,
I think.
That was a killer
metal band, dude.
Oh.
Oh, Bob,
he don't do metal
like he used to no more.
I don't know what happened
with that.
You don't have the
Pat Boone heavy metal album,
do you?
I've never heard that.
We have it.
I figured you probably
must have it.
We do have it.
I've never heard any
of that Pat Boone
heavy metal.
I understand he covers
Ozzy Osbourne
and Hendrix.
Yeah.
Unfortunately,
I'm not sure whether
it's filed under
pop or heavy metal.
Or comedy.
Comedy.
It's kind of one of
those dichotomies.
You don't know
where to put it.
Bulldada.
You put it in the
Bulldada section.
Unfortunately,
the station is run
by pinks,
so you don't have
a Bulldada.
It magically
appears
from nowhere.
I got no friends
cause they read
the papers.
You know
you can't be seen
with me.
And I'm getting
a shot down
and I'm
feeling mean.
So,
no more
Mr. Nice Guy.
No more
Mr. Pink.
Mr. Nice Guy.
No more
My dog
bit me on
the leg
today.
My cat
clawed
my eyes.
My mom's
been thrown
out of
the society
circle.
My dad
passed
a high.
I'm
the
church
in
Koran.
Yes, dear friends, and this music...
Pardon me, Cthulhu.
This music in the background is Hate.
Hate for a Pink Planet.
Actually, from the tape, Hate for a Pink Planet.
I don't know what the name of the tune is.
Cow Flesh.
Something about cow flesh.
And, friends, we've got lots of backed-up gleet and backed-up tapes
from WMUH in Allentown, Reverend Ed Strange's show,
and WCSB in Cleveland, the Einstein Secret Orchestra show
with Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And so let's just sink right on back down
into...
Before the Dave Man, it was the Ur-Dave and the Ur-Bob
and the Ur-Urs
and the ancient Dave Man
and the Dave Bob
and the Ur-Bob
and his only natural enemy...
The one with the pasty-pasty...
...would nonetheless get together
and strive night after night
to invent the pipe.
For in that day, man had the frop
but yet had not invented the pipe.
Now was there the knowledge to use the frop or the pipe?
The two were confused somehow.
Sometimes one would put the...
in the pipe, other times some would put the pipe in the frop and try to light the pipe
and smoke the frop, it did not work.
The silly, primitive, superstitious Dave men would attempt to pack the frop into openings
in their bodies, under their eyelids, up exit wounds and into trepanation holes.
Or, mistakenly, by the same token, the other tribe, the Dave Bobs, would pack the pipes
into their orifices and their trepanation holes in a silly, superstitious attempt to
see the gods, or see visions of the future, diagnose sicknesses and heal the lovely virgins
of the tribe.
One day, however, the Dave Bobs would be able to see the gods, or see visions of the future,
while blindly stumbling around in a glue-huffing haze, a stupid cave Dave, a Dave man, and a
Dave Bob, bumped into each other.
Hey, said the Dave Bob, your frop fell into my pipe.
Hey, said the Bob Dave, your pipe fell into my exit wound.
Say, if only it suddenly...
A bolt of lightning struck from the sky as a result of an alien spacecraft from Atlantis
flying overhead, and a huge, flat monolith and a bunch of apes throwing bones in slow
motion through the air and so forth.
Altogether, man was enlightened and grew a brain and a thumb.
And with the brain and the thumb, he went on to create mistakes beyond the wildest imagining.
He even thought of the most logical aliens.
And that is why this planet has been slated for extermination.
Or fumigation, we should say.
They're not really trying to exterminate.
They just want to run the bugs out, so to speak.
We friends, as much as we might lust after or despise the little insects and arthropods,
cephalopods and so forth, that crawl beneath the surface of the planet, and that get sucked
our feet. So we too, so-called mankind, are but the bugs. In fact, not even the bugs,
the mere photos of bug pornography of some aliens whose lives and mentalities we could
not imagine in our wildest dreams, who in fact would be more sophisticated than what
we call God. God is a bug, and you must face it. You are his bug, and he will swat you
just as you swat that little fly. Yes, friends, God is a bug, and you are a bug, about to
be swat by a bigger bug. God, in fact, is a tarantula, a hairy-legged tarantula with
eight eyes and hideous drooling fangs. And a hairy appetite.
God, the tarantula, loves you. He loves you with a universal cosmic juicy
papa love. He, she loves you like a rock. He, she, he, she loves you like a rock.
The Dave men circle around the altar.
They have the captured Dave Bob strapped up with a cave bear skull, surrounded by cave
bear skulls.
I've got too many syllables in it, man.
Go away, boy.
That's how I like to run.
You're doing it wrong.
He's grinning like an idiot, happy to be sacrificed to the gods.
Man, this is not right. This is not right at all.
This was the beginning of religion, friends.
This is how...
We're morally made.
How it began.
Confused idiots stumbling around in the dim mists of the ancient past, bumping into trees
because the mist was so thick.
And mistaking those trees for monsters, mistaking the shiny lights up in the sky for angels.
And every time the old lady got sick and then got well again and the medicine man claimed
that he was the one who made her.
Well, everyone believed him.
And friends, you know, back in them days, back in the day, back when even old Reverend
Stang was young, there was hunters and there was gatherers.
That's right.
And mostly it was the men doing the hunting and there's the women doing the gathering.
And some, some fame men and some real horny guys hanging around the women doing the gathering.
Well, and then there was the subgeniuses and they were the ones who, for whatever reason,
sometimes it was merely nearsighted.
Sometimes it was a mutated brain or a lack of an opposable thumb.
Yep.
The subgeniuses were not as good at hunting.
They just couldn't hit as many rabbits with those silly little bow, birch bows.
Mutations, you know.
And they weren't very good warriors because they weren't stupid and they usually fled
from wars.
Yeah.
Thus, they had to, but they didn't want to be gatherers because, well,
it was boring, man.
Yeah.
Come on, let's just fake it.
It's boring to gather stuff.
So, there was nothing left for these type of Dave men but to become medicine men.
Priests, padres, you know, gurus, and mystical lawyers, doctors, you know what I mean?
The guy that doesn't have to go out rabbit hunting gets to ask the cute girls to undress
and then...
Has people bring him all kinds of, you know, bring him rabbits, good food, and so forth.
Never has to leave the comfort of his cave because he happened to know that if he told
a big enough lie, those fools would probably believe it.
Hey, listen to this one, buddy.
I was circling around the canyon a few minutes ago and there was this mastodon there, man.
I'm telling you, this mastodon was a mega mastodon, you know what I'm saying?
I mean, I'm saying this mastodon was as big as the whole canyon.
Right?
So, look up.
What do I do?
Good old yo, yo, yo, what?
Look up.
Look what I do.
I'll get me a rock, man.
One little teeny old rock and I'll fling that thing as hard as I can.
I'll take that mastodon down and...
Hey, yeah, but there ain't nothing left, you see, because I was a powerful man hungry
and so I did that whole mastodon by myself.
Now, ladies, you're looking for a real hunter, man?
Just line up over here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you think that medicine man Dave will come over today?
Oh, I love the way he massages me.
My toe.
Oh, it's so good.
Yeah, we must go out and get the Dave man, his special magic roots and berries that make
him drunk and high so that he will be able to talk to the gods and tell us what the future
holds.
Children, children, listen to me.
I'm the shaman, shaman.
I'm a guru's guru.
I'm a mystic mystic.
Look into my magic eye.
Boys and girls, you've been falsely led.
You're following that Dave.
You're following that stag.
You're following that yes, oh God.
Listen to me.
It's me.
Yeah.
I'm a Dave follower.
I'm a Dave-ophile.
Praise Dave.
Dave has the church of the lone gemus.
I'm a little dreamer like an umbilical needle.
He says cosmic stuff.
I do it up.
It, it, he, he shows us how to hate the man.
I watch them.
The big man.
Walk funny.
The brain man.
I teach the brain who learn about the walk funny.
shows us how to hate and drug.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I'm the brain man who teach the brain man how to
walk funny on the grid.
Damn predictable.
Yeah, burn, baby.
Baby.
boil down on abalm, abalm, abalm, abalm, abalm
Michael for veiled nuts and poverty even
ego.
Really?
So desperate to become a girl, he tried to castrate himself.
Believe it or not, mother and daughter used to be mother and son.
What I believe is that there is one way, God's way.
The soul and the mind and the heart.
A penis does not make a person.
You are so idiotic.
You're trying to tell us what we can and cannot do.
You're trying to arrest us.
You come to my shows and put me in jail for what people pay to see.
And your people are coming and locking me up.
You can't lock me up.
It was beauty who killed the beast.
And the son.
The son.
Keeping him out could make him worse.
After all, he is crazy.
And you can't get through to him.
This organization and the law thing.
The sky and the earth.
This is not a place for a rabbi.
Singular and subgenius harp.
It's funny how they use that phrase, Jews harp.
Because it's here on Earth.
Because we know they won't be able to go to heaven and have a harp.
Not if the Christians have their way.
The Christians have their way, they'll take up where Hitler left off.
Oh, yes.
Especially those Lutherans.
Don't you even talk about Lutherans to me.
Bavarians and krauts.
Oh, God, I married a Lutheran.
My first wife was a Lutheran.
Oh.
Jesus Christ!
You damn Lutheran bastard.
Lutherans would throw you all into an oven.
That's right.
They'd throw all of you into an oven,
and they'd throw all of us into an oven,
and they'd throw those Jews into an oven,
the ones they couldn't make.
Oh, but the Papists would throw the Lutherans into the oven.
That's right.
And the Southern Baptists would throw the Papists
and the Disneyites into the oven.
But I, in the name of Bob,
would throw them all into the oven
and cook up a great batch of gingerbread men,
which I would then sit down and pass out to the children
at Halloween.
Ah, yes.
Dear little children,
there's a bit of God in every bite.
Oh.
But if you're lucky,
you won't eat that one first bite.
Eat of this, for this is my flesh,
and this is my blood.
Hey, kids, next time you take communion,
steal part of the wafer and the blood,
the wine that's been consecrated,
sneak it out,
and send it to us at P.O. Box 14306,
Dallas, Texas, 7 by 214,
because we have cloning devices.
You can't imagine how easy it is
for that man Bob to clone,
an army of Jesuses,
from those little communion wafers
and that fake blood, that wine.
It's not fake.
It really is the blood of Jesus
when those papists are through with it.
And we can take that blood
and make another Jesus,
and another, and another,
until a great army of Jesuses
is marching down I-95,
marching, slouching towards Bethlehem Steel,
and there,
there,
to, to,
all led by Bob,
blindfolded,
as Bob always leads,
he will sack his army of Jesus
onto all your enemies.
Yes, he'll do it for you.
And Jesus will kill for you.
You will have your own personal Jesus clone
killing for you.
Jesus killed for you.
You will be your own sin
if you have faith in Bob.
And the best part,
they'll clone the whole thing,
except for the brain.
We wouldn't want a million Jesuses
with brains.
No, we want the kind of,
we want a subgenius Jesus, friends.
Yeah.
Actually you don't have to.
We have the brainless sub-Jesus
already in Dallas, Texas.
We clone from him.
We don't need,
you don't really have to steal anything
from the Catholic church.
Because yes, friends,
Jesus Christ walks the earth again.
In Dallas, Texas, formerly of Cleveland.
Hi, Jesus.
Hope you're listening to this tape.
Yes.
People, you know, people don't,
they don't take us seriously.
A lot of Christians lately,
you know, it's like I'll be at some booth at a convention,
hawking the goods, preaching the word,
some nice, well-meaning, you know,
Christian will come by and go,
I'm gonna pray for you because you're going to hell.
That, you know, kindly way that they have.
And I try to tell them, it's like,
look, we've got Jesus, what do you mean we don't have,
we've got Jesus, we've got more Jesus
than you ever thought about.
I have to cook dinner for Jesus every night.
It's a big deal.
We don't pay him much else.
But they don't, they don't believe it.
How much is a Jesus really worth?
How much do you really believe?
And if they, if this Jesus came knocking at their door,
do you think they'd let him in?
Oh no, they'd demand some kind of dog and pony show for him.
Well, don't think high and dry.
See, I'm not afraid to die.
And I do it every time you walk by.
It's the power of God.
In the ancient times, before the world was created,
the Dave was enjoying with the gopis and the women cow herders in the lake.
He would bash in the blissful illumination of the Gordoba.
And if one day the Dave demanded,
that the river come and wash him as he enjoyed and was enjoying with the gopis.
I wish all the gopis would wash me up while I'm being engulfed by the river of life.
But the river of life, thinking he was drunk, ignored him and refused to do it.
And so he became angered at the river of life.
Enraged.
Enraged he became.
And he, and he.
He cried.
He pulled from his whip.
He pulled from his toga, his sacred holy toga of heads and tails.
He pulled his great whip of a thousand headed snake.
The thousand headed snake of the Dave from beneath his toga.
And he used it to stir the vast ocean of toxins.
Which had, and from the ocean of toxins he was able to suck one tiny drop of milk.
And when this drop of milk shriveled from his mouth, that formed all of the insects of
the world.
And that is how insects and bugs came to be.
Then the Dave, seeing that they were stupid and no better than a Macintosh and without
a soul, gave them sexual organs of a sort.
They called cloacas or something.
A rhino.
And so these bugs enjoyed themselves, like just as Dave had been enjoying.
Those tiny little bugs.
Isn't religion wonderful, friends, when we are able to explain to you in such concise
terms, the very beginning of the universe, the creation of life and so forth by this
purse, perfect personality of the Godhead.
And so, the Buddha, Krishna, Vishnu, Kali, Kanti, and Kunti, all at once, all mixed together,
personified.
And Reverend Sun Yung Moon.
And L. Ron Hubbard.
And L. Ron.
All reincarnated.
And Jimi Hendrix and Elvis.
All mixed together in one perfect body.
And the perfect Godhead, who people in this foolish world mistake for just another poor,
miserable, bald-headed, struggling writer, guitar player, musician, radio personality,
perfect personification of the Godhead.
Oh, praise the supreme Godhead of Dave!
Man, my mouth tastes like moldy Salisbury steak.
And that bottle of alcohol.
Oh, the Irish are keeping.
Ever wondered why the universe seemed kind of screwed up and imperfect, friends?
I don't know if I'm going to make it one more day.
Well, you're listening to the supreme creator, this guy standing next to me in this college
radio station.
I guess what I ought to do is create me some more worlds.
Now, I created enough worlds.
I got some perfected worlds I already created.
I just keep my mind off things.
I go boy, I'm going to go to the moon.
For a little while, I'll have a few more beers.
Now, I think you're right.
Lord, why don't you just ditch those worlds you've created and just start fresh?
Try something new.
Yeah, start fresh.
Yeah, I'm starting.
Try a silicon-based life form instead of carbon-based.
Okay.
Try a negative universe or something.
My mind is stirring in the void.
I've got to make a pronouncement.
I've got to tell everybody what is currently a carbon-based life form, which is pretty,
you know, kind of countable.
I'm going to keep things going.
I'm going to switch over sometime in the next six months.
That's a mini-cycle.
Okay.
Hey, man, I've got Kai's Power Evolution version 3.2.
That might help you out.
Yeah.
Then you won't have to read the instruction book.
You just push the button.
Yeah.
The button that says create cool as hell worlds.
I'll give them all a call and plant in each one of their minds an idea of a role game.
Yeah.
A role game?
Yeah, a role-playing game.
It's so that way when a transition comes and they all got to go and the new life forms
take over, they won't feel so bad about decapitating their habitations and so forth.
Hey, that's a great idea, Lord.
So when you inundate or destroy the world like you did in Noah's day, you're going to
give them a sort of a consolation prize?
That's right.
A subgenius role-playing game.
Are those rolls like sticky buns?
Big old fireproof boats.
Yeah.
Those sticky buns.
The purple sticky buns they call them?
Yeah.
I know what they'll do.
Once they all climb aboard them fireproof boats, see they get off and stuff like that,
I will save me a few, they'll get all the purple sticky buns.
Yeah, as they're kind of like reward for playing the role game right.
What if they don't take it right?
There's a lot of screwy apples out there I got to deal with.
90% of them look like me.
Hey, an afterlife.
Make an afterlife for them.
Like a big trash can for the ones that you already created.
Got it.
It's just like on your computer.
You still want the stuff, but you know, you're done using it right there and then, and then
so you get rid of the one part of it and keep the other part and encode it and stuff.
That's it, I'll encode all the suckers.
Yeah, I'll encode them.
I'll take their souls and I'll stuff them right back in, just like it was some kind
of bad drug for me.
Yeah.
That's it, I'll make them all like a, yeah, what's that one hallucinogenic that them sweetest
kids are getting off on that they're all committing suicide?
Oh, Puffer, Puffer, the Puffer Blowfish Lord.
Yeah, I'll have them all sucking puffer blowfish on Fugu.
And then, once they discombobulate off into them fireproof ships and they're eating all
the purple sticky buns, I'll have my children's back.
But, it will last forever.
What am I gonna do with them then?
Oh yeah, that's right, I'm gonna encode them.
And then the judgment.
Yeah.
At the end of time.
Remember, Lord?
Yeah.
Pity the poor fallen god who cannot remember his divinity from one minute to the next.
I don't even remember being there.
If he hadn't done so much drugs, he'd be able to remember that he was the god.
If you could be smart, if for once in your life you could be smart enough to remember
that you were god and all things are connected, it wouldn't be a problem.
If for once in your life you could be smart enough to figure that out, then it would all
be taken care of.
You'd have the answer.
Yeah, I got a better idea.
God?
I'll start a new other religion that'll be better than that religion based on encoding
them and stuff.
I'll tell them all somehow they're all god and I'll let them think that they're all god
somehow.
Oh, you can let them make their own religions.
Yeah.
That'd be better, man.
They'd beat you to it.
Oh, man.
Good lord, you've let your creation beat you to it.
Once again.
Once again, I'm on the backslide.
In fact, you're letting one of your creations be right you.
Wait a minute.
Once again, I'm on the downside of evolution.
Once again, I'm descending further and further and further into matter.
Now, wait a minute.
I've done 50,000, 50,000 plants this year.
Once again, the creation turns upon its creator.
And I want to Jesus, or Avatar, or someone, each one of them.
You still are.
I can't.
Get him.
All right.
Cool.
Lets run a little for the goodin' right now, man.
I want to, you know...
It's kLA competitions and I don't think we've done that well, have we, formergy bueno?
Did somebody have the dup plaint on it?
Oh, it came from my grandfather.
We have so many adaoth κα Kritik.
just don't even think about that sort of thing.
But we say, why not just all out declare war on God?
Yes, Reverend, yes.
Join the war on God, friends.
We just thought of that just now.
Unfortunately, God being Lonesome Cowboy Dave here,
it's hardly a very exciting big movement to get behind,
so I don't expect it to be as big as, say, Mormonism,
Lonesome Christianity, or Heaven's Gate.
He's just not nice.
Down with God and down with Satan.
Oh, needless to say.
Up marriage. Up marriage.
Both of them.
Down marriage.
Well, we...
You know, I mean, if God goes down, Satan's certainly going to be...
I mean, that guy's just dead and no...
It's just one of the kids, right?
I don't know, Reverend. I was listening to you.
I thought you had all the answers.
Now you're telling me that...
Well, we're trying to get you to ask...
Ask the right questions.
...the right questions.
That's all.
We are simply trying to train you to think for yourself.
That's right. Yeah, think for yourself.
This isn't like some mind-control cult
where we just feed you a bunch of gobbledygook and mumbo-jumbo.
No, we don't.
This is a legitimate liberation.
Yeah, thought liberation.
That's what we're doing.
Question authority, we say.
We want to help everyone.
Yeah, that's our motto.
Question authority.
Unless it's Bob.
Unless, of course, it is Bob.
Because Bob, as we know, is Reverend Stang.
Bob is.
Yes, that's incorrect.
Of course, I knew you'd move into a much more philosophical area
that I could probably not relate to.
But we have a letter here now from Mrs. Elmo Twardy.
Bob is not the answer, and neither is any.
He certainly is not.
But he could be, couldn't he?
I mean, if I'm taking...
You are your own mistake.
I am.
Listening to apologetics.
Plum out of luck, ain't you?
You're on your own, kid.
With a corncob in your one hand,
and some errant eye pointing downward.
But anyway, I'm sorry.
We do have a letter.
And an offering.
Cielo in la tierra.
We're again.
Yeah, we've had some real long talks about it.
But you do really feel, I mean, everything's natural and completed.
For a while.
We'll be right back.
Cielo in la tierra.
We're waiting for the day.
For the man who demands respect.
Cause he was great.
Come on.
I'm on the one mission.
To give a politician to honor.
Or he's a goner by the time I get to Arizona.
The Sunday night services are nearly come to an end.
Nearly over.
It is up to you to go forth and bringeth your own slack.
For me, we must wander off to our own devices.
Our own herbs.
Our own...
Gleet.
Oh, man.
I got my device all warmed up.
It's Gleet ready.
Ah, yes.
I love to dream of my device.
When I actually start to use the device, I kind of get uptight.
It's not ever as good as I thought it might be, hoped it would be.
But, you know, still, I love that device.
And the Gleet that it makes me feel and discharge.
And the offense that I feel when I Gleet.
In my moon pants.
Ah, yes.
I'm so offended that I refuse to even play the tape.
The love in the room is so thick you could almost cut it with a knife.
I think I cut one.
Jeez.
Wah, wah, bam, bam.
Um...
It has been a show.
It has come full circle.
Yes.
And we...
Back to a beginning that never happened.
We are the jerks who have brought it full circle.
We are the full circle jerks this evening.
But we are off.
The jerks are off.
Soon.
In years.
Very soon.
In about five minutes.
Buried alive.
Are you buried alive, brothers and sisters?
Are you buried alive?
Alive.
In a vast desert of anti-slack.
We're friends.
Bob is the ultimate grave robber.
Grave digger.
He's gonna dig you up.
You know, if you are buried alive and you're listening to us right now,
it's real nice of someone to bury you with a radio.
That's all I can say about that.
But there are many ways of being buried alive.
It's not merely earth.
Why, you could be buried alive in your own bodily fluids.
You could be buried alive in that little...
cubicle tomb that they make you go to every Monday morning.
I'm the old backhoe operator.
And welcome, boys and ghouls, to a new grave.
We're going to backhoe you up out of your old grave and dump you into a new one.
In this creepy story of Prozac Free Radio.
Now, how many of those conspiracy pink stiffs who work in them little...
cubicles even know what the guy working in the next cubicle looks like?
Why, he probably wouldn't even know he was there if he didn't hear him typing eight or nine hours a day.
Is that the kind of life you want to live?
I wish I could quit.
I can't stand listening to that guy typing over in that other sacred scribe typing over in that other church cubicle.
I'm just a cog in a machine.
The church of the subgenius scribe cubicle is located right next to the Mormon.
The Mormon scribe cubicle.
Our listeners are wanting to remind us of that fact.
Yeah, the Mormons got a bigger cubicle than I do.
Yeah.
Damn it.
And they each get their own planet when they die.
Hey, we get our own planet when we die.
But as Dr. Legume pointed out recently,
sure, on X-Day, Bob's going to protect you from the pinks,
and you'll have your own planet.
But who's going to protect you from your fellow subgenius?
Subgeniuses and Bob.
Oh, yeah.
What if my planet declares war on your planet?
Eh?
It's going to be...
That's right.
Mono a mono, buddy.
You might never even get the chance, Reverend Strange.
You might never get the chance to have your own planet.
Hell, you might be like William Burroughs.
You might not be able to get all the saucers come X-Day.
You never get set up.
You haven't been in your 30 bucks, have you?
Oh, yeah, I have.
You have?
Oh, you owe $30.
Yeah, I have.
Oh, praise Bob.
Praise Bob, man.
Hey, that $30 will protect you from the aliens.
Oh, that's right.
I sent the P.O. Box 1403 or 6 down to 75214.
I shouldn't have known that, because you didn't have me.
I already named the rabbi here.
It's all in the new...
I remember you gave me yourself.
Yeah, it's all in there in the new electronic book of life
that's implanted in your skull and the chip at the base of the neck.
It's all in there.
Just access the segment G33 subsection rub routine 4.
Lord.
Right there.
Soul of Reverend Edward Strange.
Does his name appear in the book of life?
Book of life won't boot up, Lord.
We can't get it to boot it up.
The book of life seems to have a corrupted virus or something in it.
Throw them all into the lake of fire, then.
And throw in the disc as well.
You know, it's all well and good.
Church of subgenius, Bob.
Eternal salvation.
Or triple your money back
until you see Bob standing at the gates of hell
with a $90 chip.
I've got a picture of Bob standing at the gates of hell
with a $90 check in his hand.
I just showed Dr. Legume and Mrs. Legume just a little while ago.
Huh? See?
I wish I could whip it out right here on the radio,
but I'm afraid my moon pants are stuck.
You might offend someone.
I might offend somebody,
and I don't want them to see the tape I got in my pants.
Well, at least I was...
I can't.
At least I was smart enough to get a pair of button flyers.
Moon pants.
Oh, Reverend Stang, he got those damn weld fly moon pants.
Now he can't get them off.
But mine have a little flap in the back.
You know what that's for.
Oh.
Johnny pants, they call them.
Johnny pants.
Or can'ts.
I like to call them can'ts.
Why do they call them pants?
It's just one pant.
Or a can't.
I like to call it a can't.
It's the Prozac.
Free radio show.
Special edition on this fine, fine Sunday night.
The night of the Lord.
Signing off.
Yeah, signing off for the last time
because Ed Strange isn't going to be with us anymore.
Oh, yeah, he doesn't know,
but as he walks past the dumpster tonight,
the Samuels brothers are going to be waiting for him.
Yeah, so you won't be seeing...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Red Grange.
I mean, Reverend Ed Strange anymore.
He's going to be in the dumpster instead of behind it.
Thank you, Dr. Lagoon.
Thank you, Reverend Stang.
And we really like coming here.
We thank you for having us, Reverend Strange.
And good night.
We like to talk about...
Good night to all the listeners.
Good night.
Sleep well.
Dream of Bob and his minions.
Good night.
We're talking about...
This should have been done...
A film by...
Thank you.
Holy cow!