No, no, no. How does that start? I can't remember.
I, I, yes, friends. No, I, yes, dear friends.
You're listening, no, uh, radio ministry.
It's the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
Produced here at the beautiful studios of WCSB, Cleveland, the home.
I love that show. It's so iconoclastic.
And, you know, everything is worth a poking at and it's making fun.
And sometimes throwing dirt on the shoes and pulling a knife at it.
Yeah, they're just a mirror that reflects the illness in society.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We may go on. We're going to go on for a long time tonight.
We're going to take over the station.
We might have to share bolts all night.
We're going to disregard any, uh, any attempts to take over the station by...
Stand back. They are killing me.
The next... Oh, no, we won't go. I won't go there.
We're really, we are going to give it over to the next DJ if you're listening.
We were just teasing.
Yeah.
We're just kidding.
That's us. We've got our little cot set up here.
We've got us.
We're going to have a...
Hot chockeys here.
Getting ready for our slumber party.
And Philo and me.
All the kids will be here in a minute.
We each have a little candle here.
Why didn't you get to my hand?
And you got your little nightcap?
Yeah, I do.
Chestnuts are roasting.
Sexy guy show.
The sugar plums are dancing.
Yeah, this is the guy show because this is the last show of the millennium and we're
covering the history of the subgenius church, which is basically a guy church.
We would have a girl on the show, but she didn't show up.
That's the next show.
Next to the last show.
This is the last show.
We paid her.
When was the first...
We paid her and she still didn't show up.
I told you you should have given her that money in advance.
That was back in Jane Eyre's childhood because he had the little...
The little...
I said half now and half when you show up.
He had the original little head and he would watch that thing as a child and make little
songs and say little things and do little stuff.
Oh, you should always do the other half.
Always do the other half.
I have to do the other half now?
Amen.
I did not.
Yes, you did.
Okay.
Let this serve as a warning and a disclaimer.
If you are overly sensitive to vulgar terminology, I strongly advise that you fast forward the
tape.
Like everything I touch, this recording is on the cutting edge of societal evolution.
For example, women in combat.
See, I told you so.
Days in the military.
I may have a nice ring to it.
Universal health care.
I am committed to furthering this goal.
I really get no satisfaction out of saying anal sex.
You need to...
So horny.
Anal sex.
You need...
So horny.
And justify the means.
Well, let's set the record straight right here.
The cure for unemployment equals more taxes.
The cure for the recession equals more taxes.
The cure for the budget deficit equals more taxes.
The cure for illiteracy equals more taxes.
How many times do I have the right to say...
It happens to be the title of this recording.
Federally subsidized abortion.
This is no laughing matter.
This is no laughing matter, my friend.
Legal experimentation.
This is no action.
Anal sex.
Never, folks, in my wildest dreams could I have imagined just how exhilarating, fun, and emotionally rewarding this experience would be.
For example, women in combat.
See, I told you so.
Days in the military.
I may have a nice ring to it.
Universal health care.
I am committed to furthering this goal.
I really get no satisfaction out of saying anal sex.
I'm trying to say it.
Anal sex.
Me so horny.
And justify the means.
Well, let's set the record straight right here.
The cure for unemployment equals anal sex.
The cure for the recession equals anal sex.
The cure for the budget deficit equals anal sex.
The cure for illiteracy equals anal sex.
How many times do I have the right to say...
It happens to be the title of this recording.
Federally subsidized abortion.
This is no laughing matter, my friend.
Needle experimentation.
This is no accident.
Anal sex.
Never, folks, in my wildest dreams could I have imagined just how exhilarating, fun, and emotionally rewarding this experience would be.
That's it, folks.
Those are all things that I have said, and they are true.
Tell them, Russ.
So what do you think, Russ?
Excitement in the butt, I think is what EIB stands for now.
Excitement in the butt.
I honor you, Stangford.
Give me the money.
You know that, hey, Reverend Stang, you remember back there in Fort Worth and that boy named Patches?
Patches, he was a poor boy, but he was a great tap dancer.
All his britches were made out of patches.
You know, they wouldn't let him into the church, the regular church.
They said, get out of here with them Patches britches on.
Patches.
Get out of here, Patch britch boy.
But the bitches in the subgenius church.
That's what they said.
They liked the way he dangled in them patches.
Patches, get out of here with them Patches britches or I'm going to make you my prison bitch.
And so Patches.
They said that at church, too.
They did?
And so Philo scratched Patches' itches.
In churches.
And quit his bitching.
He did a batch of bitching that one night, though.
It is a new, not only a new year.
Some batching scratching.
Millennium.
It is a whole new millennium coming forth.
Wow.
As we, together.
Look at that, a new millennium.
The subgenii of the Bay Area and the Midwest, Mestern Western, come together.
Do you understand the Mestern Western show?
Ascendancy.
As we go forward.
Into what is now the only millennium that truly exists.
So are the subgeniuses going to be at Burning Man next year?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
We're at Burning Man every year.
Every single year.
We were at Burning Man before it was Burning Man.
That's true.
In fact, you know, it's a little known fact that the subgenius church is part of why Burning Man exists.
It really is.
It's just why I partly believe that Warm Boy should be there.
Did it start with Jainer talking about that burning monk?
I'm sorry, yes, it did start with Jainer.
No, that was actually 1988 or so.
That was when Trelloid still walked upon him.
Wow.
All hail Trelloid.
Yeah, yeah.
We're going over the subgenius history here on KPFA.
Let's rewind now back to 1982.
We're taking 1982 into 2001.
Doug Wellman used the sound effect.
On the air to represent a tape rewinding.
But when was the baby?
Since 1980, you've been getting tapes of me doing it.
And then of course we took the and made it into the West Coast.
Which then degenerated into .
What about Mama?
Where did Mama fit into it?
That was my Mama.
I thought that was Sterno.
Your Mama.
That was Sterno going, your Mama.
I'm the guest.
It's I who honor Sterno.
Frozen Graves.
Oh, I see.
As long as you honor somebody, you can then claim it as yours.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
I always do.
I honor you, Stang, for giving me the money.
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Swag.
Now I really do have to say, I'm a fan of the radio.
Oh, please don't look in the mirror.
You're not going to like what you see there.
Principal.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is Li Li Jing, the Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the Hour of Swag.
Oh, yes, it's so true.
Thank you, Li Jing.
I got a call from China just this morning.
The high priestess of all Asia.
You know, friends, if you had joined up.
If you'd been the first person on your continent to join up with the church, you'd be the pope
of this continent.
I know.
Dr. G. Gordon Gordon here.
I am the pope of South America.
The entire continent of South America.
It's mine.
When those souls.
Ah, the harvest, friends.
When we start collecting those souls, you know who's going to get to skim, to skim that
fine, fine layer off the top out of the soul rendering vat, don't you, friend?
Oh, and they're trying to keep them from selling any kind of soul.
They're trying to keep the soul down there nowadays.
Oh, yeah.
They don't.
Used to be in the old days, you couldn't give it away.
And now it's against the law to sell it.
So what are you going to do?
And all the religions want to have your soul, friends.
Bob wants your soul, but just temporarily.
He'll give it back after he's took the squeezes.
And he only uses it a little bit while he's got it, friends.
That's something to think about.
He doesn't dry you out.
That's right.
I'm going to go to the church.
If I stay in that slowing and
Jesus walking in the sky, walking in, walking out.
One day a shiny silver psychedelic spaceship
took a long trip from the outskirts of heaven to the 7-Eleven.
They had a funeral going in the parking lot for the second going of Jesus.
And if he ever comes around again, I'll be the first to stick the spike in.
And I get occupied with those lost things she can't even leave me.
And what is this spaceship doing?
Let's hope, let's hope now.
Let's hope now.
Yes, my dear, dear, dear friends.
That was the great, groovy Neptune.
With the song, Parameds on Mars, from his new CD.
groovy gravy, man.
Well, actually, it's just called groovy gravy.
You can contact the great groovy Neptune
or see its website at
Neptune.itgo.com
That's Neptune.itgo.com
And tonight, friends, it's a show battle
between the sub-shows of the ancient past,
like the KPFA Berkeley show of last Christmas
or just before New Year's
with Dr. Philodrum and guesting on Cuzzling Evidence's show.
And, of course, Einstein's Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio
hosted by Dr. Chaz Smith
and starring Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
a broadcaster from WCSB in Cleveland
and also with yours truly,
as a guest.
And, friends, at least it ain't reruns of Hour of Slack.
I've had to trip through four hours of Slack
in the last couple of days
to get things done ahead of time
because of our upcoming subgenius church field trip
to Amsterdam.
And the main reason we go to Amsterdam in a group
is so that we can come back and irritate our friends
by regaling them with tales of our ripping
and fripping times.
I get tired of people telling me
that they're tripping all the time
when it's so obvious.
Their faces have changed,
like blue and red things are coming out,
you know, wearing green.
And one eye is dribbling down the side of their face.
And they've got this kind of ripping.
And they're giggling.
It's cute.
You can tell they're high on something.
You know, the wall behind them is kind of like melting.
Yeah.
And all the black light posters around them
are fountaining.
Yeah.
I find them very disturbing to the environment.
Try and get them in your car
and have the windshield start melting
and have the radio playing.
It looks like toothpaste is coming out of the radio.
Man, you want to throw them right out of your car
and they still laugh as they roll down the freeway.
It seemed like everybody I looked at was tripping
because they were all just melting.
And they're, you know, they put on this music
that tasted like ice cream.
The air was tripping.
Hey, Mom.
Um.
One of the crackers.
Is that what you called them?
I thought it was...
Okay.
Hey, man.
Am I still sweating?
Hey, hey, I heard...
No, you're in New York, man.
You're in the Greenwich Village.
I heard that you had shrooms.
Shrooms.
They wanted a pound of flesh.
They wanted that which makes you alive.
They wanted your soul.
That's what they do want, the trippies.
They want a piece.
Could you make some coffee for us, man?
We've been walking out of the rain.
It's cold, I think.
Yeah, yeah, sit down.
Sure.
How did you get up?
Um, I don't know.
It was like, I think it was yesterday,
but this one kid died.
I think he died.
Um.
He was in the woods.
Well, yeah, that's where we found him first.
Down by the lake.
He almost got ran over by a pontoon boat.
He came to study consciousness,
but he ended up with his pants around his ankles
down by the lake,
freezing at dawn,
wondering what had happened.
Where, where, where?
My name is St. Andrew KSC
of Chicago, Illinois,
and I'm here to tell all of you
about the wonders and the truth
that is behind J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Can I hear an amen, brothers and sisters?
That is right.
Let me tell you right off the bat,
I was here earlier today.
I saw three fine young women here
who have not been ordained
in the Church of the Subgenius
because they didn't have the money.
$30 for salvation.
The only $30,
you can't even get a good hand job
in Chicago for $30.
But in this church,
if you pay your $30 from the body,
you will have more sex, more slack,
more fuck, more booze,
more anything that you want,
anything that you could ever dream about.
And it all comes with a money-back guarantee.
If you foof off yourself dead
and in the pits of hell,
with the flames of Satan licking your ass,
you will get a signed $90 check
from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Can I hear another amen?
Your people are not stoked up enough for this shit.
You are not in the mood in order to be saved.
You need to get down on yourself,
get jiggy with it even if you have to,
because you know Will Smith is getting more pussy than you
because you haven't saved $30 to Bob.
No!
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back,
flackin' whartin' Philip Duncan Burton,
purgaluma Burton,
dirtin' bostonite,
whacker-frazz,
whack-a-flaughtin' back-car,
and that kind of back-wrack-a-lattle.
Oof!
Ah, yes, dear friends,
St. Andrew at the Tampa Defifle.
And now, friends, let's go back to
Dr. Wood,
Dr. Philo Trumman,
and puzzling evidence with some more subgenius history
to be followed by some new non-music by New Monet.
I'm gonna be at an old person's convention that day.
Because the show will have been retired.
I'll be at a place where there's a lot of old people.
Oh, work?
They'll be having fun.
So is this gonna be the 20th anniversary?
I'll be whacking them on the head with this big long board.
20th anniversary of what?
It's got floppy appendages hanging over it.
This show?
This show started in June of 1982.
Was it that long ago?
Yeah, when it was, uh, Rob Nelson.
June of 1982?
Yeah.
I'll remember that for sure.
Yeah, because it was Ivan Stang and Lies and myself.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Get your stinking paws off me, you damn dirty ape!
You want to touch my monkey?
I don't make monkeys, I just train them!
No more monkey business!
No!
Birds and the bees and the monkey babies.
I've seen them all!
All right, Bob's Banda!
Uh, uh.
Uh, uh, what does this have to do with Bob Slack and the conspiracy, the great themes which has driven the church?
Well, I'll ask you a question.
Well, just decide that...
Should we be concerned with George Bush being in the White House a fundamentalist Christian?
Or is this all part of Bob's plan?
All I know is that what language did Jesus speak on the cross?
Mayan
Yeah
It wasn't Aramaic, it was Mayan
Eli, Eli, Eli, Sabahana
Well you can just ask him, he's probably not awake right now
Everybody knows this, classic Mayan
It means
Mu, sad-eyed and bearded
Come down with your fierce temper
Wow
That's what it means
Because he was actually asking for revenge
On all those people
He's been misquoted because they thought he was speaking Aramaic
Hey dude, where's my car?
In Aramaic it means something like
Father, father, why hast thou forsaken me?
Oh, father, father
Where's my tandoori chicken?
In Mayan it means move
Come down and release your fierce temper
Thank you, thank you
In English it means
Please pass the
Kefeltifish
Oh
It's luminous blue
What is the next great frontier
Lonesome cowboy Dave?
The next great frontier
Is the frontier of the human mind
Delineated and demarcated
Sans frontiers
By only its only
Limited imagination
Imagination
Okay, alright, then I'll just forget about it
Can I get
The mind has been completely mapped and explored
And I'm not going to
The mind is still a vast frontier
Where very few have ever truly tried
Your mind maybe
The mind is still a place filled with cavernous muscles
And tiny little tissues which no one can reach
Except for their own cerebellum
The human or normal mind
Has been completely worked out by marketing companies
And conspiracy medical science
The last hundred years
They've had it down
Down, down
What the ancient Reese's have told us
That by properly using our minds
We can even fly as if gossamer on wings of felt
Is that what the ancient Reese's monkeys told you?
Not the Reese's monkeys
The Reese's of ancient India
You gotta lose your shit in order to fly
Anybody who finds himself that far off the ground
Without knowing why
Loses their shit
And that's a truism
And a falsehood
Tish, tish, tish
And it's nice to hear your show return
To a slower, more deliberate pacing
But of course that's the edited version
Over here we're doing the unedited version
Of the last show on the balloon
Yes, yes
But don't let it be forgot
That ere there was a spot
For one brief shining moment
Known as Camelot
In short, there's simply not a more congenial spot
Than happy ever aftering here in Camelot
Okay, I got it
I think that now that the bushes are back in
I think it's gonna be like Camelot
It is a lot like Camelot
Oh, certainly dad bush
I like that
I like the bushes
Now see, this is kind of like
This is really George Bush's second term
Yeah, exactly
Oh, no lie
It's like, uh
It's like the
We're rolling now, folks
Line
You know, it's like the emperor
Bush dynasty
We'll be rolling our way
I meant to bring my new
My new mix
Mixotology tape
That's low, I know
We didn't get the new mixotology
Actually, I have it on a CD in the car
But I'd have to go out there in the cold and rain
We should get it
So we can play the
See, there is your car driving away
Because you said that
Hey, come back here
So do you think that the news will be more entertaining now
In the next four years?
No, I think so
Because at least for those of us on the left
Or where we call ourselves the left
You know, you gotta have a target
I feel now like those right-wingers did
When Clinton was president
I always believed that
A vote against your conscience
Is a vote against boredom
I just wish Jesse Ventura had won
Me too
I really want him to win
I think so
You know, that made me so happy
When he was governor
And I thought that he should be president
Because he's stronger than those other guys
I think he should
No kidding
He kicked
But, you know, he's gonna be in the XFL now
He's got a new job in the XFL
Working for Vince McMahon
Really?
Yeah
When you lose it out there
You're in a world of hurt
Oh, you're doing Dennis Miller now?
You're out of control
Sure
Thanks for watching!
Subscribe to Alan Dickman!
We hope to see you guys soon!
We're out of here
See ya
Bye
Thanks for watching
Gun or a job.
Copyright 1983 by the band that dare not speak its name.
Palmer Reedy's on vocals.
Thank you.
Good evening, my fellow Americans.
Hey, how you doing?
I appreciate you very much for the opportunity to speak with you tonight.
Oh, you know, it's our president, too.
And we are rolling, folks.
I'm rolling.
Getting ready for the second Bush dynasty.
Rolling, rolling.
Keeps them takes dicks rolling.
The Soptynia Show.
Rolling.
Oh, hi.
We'll be in the picture.
And then you'll see it on the air.
And then they'll be.
We knock down with the presidential election special.
Oh, my God, what is that?
So funny it's just some guys saying I'm rolling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Auto Democrats roll.
That's up in broken here.
Yeah, we're on the field.
Wow.
From the cradle to the grave
Someone got their eye on you
Because that blanket hating of abstract concepts is exactly the main conspiracy construct.
We must hate individual Christians and Republicans and Democrats and individual, you know, people.
Because the group, the them that you start hating, that's just a conspiracy defined sub-conspiracy.
I don't mean sub-conspiracy.
It's there to lull and lure certain especially frustrated sub-geniuses into thinking that there's a simple answer to everything.
And this us versus them crap is in fact the very sort of mass fuzzy thinking that the conspiracy invented.
Not Bob, there's no us and there's no them.
There's just you, me, and everybody else.
But then you go, but what if the alternative conspiracies?
Can't I believe in anything?
Any of those?
Can't, you know, aren't some of them at least cool?
You know, the jokers, the deformed people, the outcasts, the trans and sexuals, you know, the mutants, the retards, and the hideous super geniuses in wheelchairs.
You know, what of, what of, what of them?
What of the bonobos, onobos, and monobos?
What of these once beloved minorities?
Must we distrust and hate them too and slay them?
Instead of worshipping them as we sub-genii always used to worship those weirdos and geeks?
In other words, can't we just kill without hating?
You know, it's enough that we're slowly, that on X-Day we're going to slowly dismember entire cities full of ignorant, disbelieving normals.
Do we have to drag hate into it?
Do we have to dirty up our clean killing with hate?
Friends, I don't, I don't feel that that's necessary.
I don't feel we need to lower ourselves to that kind of behavior.
Hating while killing.
We'll kill them!
Let's have the internet shut down.
I want them off the internet tomorrow.
If the Scientologists can do it, we can do it.
Stop the bandwidth.
I'm calling, I'm calling Ma Bell tomorrow.
And he can do it.
He can do it too. He knows the Bells.
I know Mrs. Bell. I'm going to give her a call and I'm going to ream her out.
And the crowd goes crazy.
Not much of a crowd.
Well, it's early in the morning.
It's early out here.
We have a last sub-genius show.
Yeah.
There's probably 20, 30 people there.
How many people can't be the last sub-genius show?
And how many people will come to the one on Flash's property?
Are we going to be able to do that on Flash's property?
The scariest thing in the world.
Why would we do anything on Flash's property if he doesn't have a hot tub?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Because he's got two big legs.
Well, legs, great.
To throw Ivan Stang into, get it?
Yeah, it's like shooting Bob.
I know, exactly.
They did produce some amazing photographs, though, just like shooting Bob.
Yeah, just like shooting Bob.
Done there, been that.
Yeah.
Hey, if either one of you guys ended up at X-Day, you know, you'd see the next ones in line to get roasted.
I'll be there.
I can't wait to get roasted.
Bob would love to get his revenge on puzzling evidence.
I know that for a fact.
Bob just wants to pay me back the money he owes me.
Yeah, oh, Byron has that money, Philo.
Yeah, it's been...
A guy gave it to Byron.
Along with your frock.
What's the matter?
Haven't you ever seen a man with throat cancer before?
I understand Byron still has your frock.
Is that right?
Thank you, yeah, thank you.
No, you have Byron's frock, and you need to give that back to him.
I couldn't remember who had it, but I knew one of us had it.
You have it, and you need to give it back to him.
I don't have it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Something happened to it.
It was in my possession for a long time, but little by little, it's just kind of flickered away somehow.
I don't know how it disappeared on its own like that.
It started out about a pound, and then little by little over the years...
Yeah, it was a pound of really good frock.
It dwindled down to nothing on its own.
It's sort of like it just...
Like the will of the wisps, or like the...
It was so beautiful.
The, um...
It was...
The legendary manna from heaven.
It sort of just dwindled away in the sunlight over the years.
The very manna of...
Manners of heaven.
And this was the gift of the subgeniuses.
If you go out in the street right now, you'll see the streets covered with haverfrop ziplocks.
They were talking about manna.
They were talking about banana.
Brought to you by the subgeniuses.
The subgenius church.
I got a banana from heaven.
I remember that.
I remember when I was eight years old, I saw Bob on night flight.
It changed my life.
And you let me down, man.
You let me down.
Come on, caller.
Be brave.
Poor Bob.
Light your own pipe.
He's gotten the brunt of all of our jokes.
Brody Culpepper just came back on Christmas Day from Laos,
and he said the entire population near Dobbstown, Malaysia...
walks around with little bob pipes.
Everybody.
Well, they were doing that back in the 60s.
Yeah, but no people were going there to look at it, so it wasn't really happening.
Wink, wink.
Oh, yeah.
I'll see you again, old scratch.
What are those funny things sticking out of your head?
Those are our antenna.
Are you a television set?
What in the ding-dong heck-a-madoodle hell is that?
Let's see if you bleed clean.
Chlorophyll.
Plants.
And the most cunning and savage of all life forms.
I was following up on a lead to what some might consider just another New York City massacre.
A pretty woman thrown out of a high-rise window, her Japanese husband disemboweled,
and their two kids turned into shredded wheat.
Do you know what it's like to be violated by a 300-pound Filipino skinhead named Gunther?
It ain't no picnic.
Stop living in dreams.
No woman can travel the world without a man to defend her.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm a woman of wealth and taste.
I've been around for long, long years.
Seen many men go to waste.
I was round when Jesus Christ had his moments of doubt and pain.
Made damn sure the pilot washed his hands and sealed his fate.
Pleased to meet you.
Hope you guessed my name.
I'm a woman of wealth and taste.
I'm not so good at shoutin' and makein' up excuses.
It's the nature of my game.
I hung around St. Petersburg till I saw it was time for a change.
I killed the Tsar and the ministers.
Anastasia screamed in vain.
I joined the ranks in the General's tent as the Blitzkrieg raged and the bodies stank.
And I shouted, who killed the Kennedys?
Well, after all, it was you and me.
Please, teacher, hope you guessed my name.
That thing that's puzzling to you.
It's the nature of my game.
Now, just as every cough is a thrill, and every sink a scent,
heads or tails just call me Lucifer, cause I'm in the middle of some restraint.
If you need me, have some courtesy, have some sympathy, and some taste.
Accept your well-earned apologies, or I'll lay your soul to waste.
Please, teacher, hope you guessed my name.
Who?
Lucifer?
joining in.
Uh, Earth
back to Mars.
But friends,
as we sort of start to wrap
up here, I want to leave you with
a thought
or several.
Consider these
alternate titles.
Earth Needs
Women.
Angry Blue
Planet.
Robinson Crusoe
on Earth.
Mission to Earth.
Uh,
Abin Costello Go to Earth.
Earth Attacks.
The Earth Chronicles.
Or even Reproduction Cycle
Among Lower Lifeforms Under the Rocks
of Earth. Now think of these alternate
titles. The Day
Mars Stood Still.
20 Million Miles to Mars.
Mars Versus
the Flying Saucers.
Now,
why do those somehow
ring true?
Maybe some of you, they didn't ring
true. You said, what? What the hell
is he talking about?
Well, friends, some of us, and I think
I think you
some of us have felt
for a long time that we're on the
wrong planet. As Susie
the Floozy put it, right hemisphere,
wrong planet.
Well,
you know, we always assumed, well, that's
because we're subgenius descendants of the
Yeti. We don't have pure blood
human genes, you know. We're, of course
we feel a little left out, but
you know, we begin, we've begun to
suspect because of certain
clues Bob left, mostly in
cheesy B-grade science fiction
movies.
Now,
this sounds, again, this sounds ridiculous.
Ludicrous to the
polished ears of the modernist, perhaps.
But, you know, it's
theoretically possible to bump a planet
out of its orbit.
Totally out of its orbit.
Put it into a new orbit. It might even
be possible to switch the orbit
of one planet with another one
that was a similar size.
Could it be
that the reason some of us
do not feel at home is because
we were native to the
planet now called by us
Mars, but which was originally
the one true Earth, and
in which, in fact, we,
the Martians, are in fact the only
true Earth people, and the
conspiracy of the normals,
in fact, the ones who, oddly
enough, seem to be trying to turn this
planet into a
place with a poisonous
atmosphere, a dry
desert covered with
just rock and concrete.
Maybe
somebody's pulled a trick
on us somewhere. Well, of course, now
at this point you're thinking, yes, that
all makes perfect sense. Earth was
switched with Mars. The true Martians
are us, and no wonder we
feel out of place, and the
true, the false Martians
are trying to turn this planet into a false
Mars with, you know,
carbon dioxide atmosphere and so
forth. Now,
and you all agree with that, right? That
makes sense. Here's the tricky part.
It happened in 1953,
and no one noticed.
I'm going to
leave you, I'm
going to charge you with thinking,
about that. How did they switch
planets in 1953
without any of us ever noticing?
Could
we be that
totally out of it? Could
perhaps the reason that X-Day hasn't
happened yet be that
1998 hasn't happened yet,
and that they kept it
1943 for 10 years
or something like that, and no one
even knew the difference.
Everybody cuff now.
It's time to be carnivorous,
with your friends and family.
Everybody cuff down
and pull out a paring knife, because we're going to
remove the sockets around Grandma and Grandpa's
eyes. They made a delectable
treat for afternoons.
Summer of pickles,
sitting by the old patio,
maybe talking to the fire.
It's time to go back.
We must get it off.
Talking to the fire.
It is time to get it off.
Shut up.
The boom is calling you now.
You can feel it for miles
and miles. Back to Mars.
The boom is calling you now.
Back to Mars.
The aroma is in the air.
You can sniff the aroma.
You can feel it.
It is talking to you.
The boom is talking
to you now.
How the hell?
It is
later
than
now.
You think
as we descend upon the minds
of the members of the Cabinet of the United States
Government and the Senate, the Congress
and the other representatives,
the representatives of the governments of the world,
we shall find in each one of them
the chip is completely unaltered.
The plan is now
in stage go.
The green light is lit and everyone is
smoking. The lamp
is at your feet, old Buddha.
Please, please,
put that back on.
I can't stand the sight of it.
It's dead.
The exhibitionist Buddha.
Little mentioned
in ancient texts.
Slathering Siddhartha,
he was called for his bow-legged
appurtenance and the strange
way he made the women in Gopi's cry
as they ran from the villages in fright.
For this is a matter
of life or death.
Your lives,
the lives of everyone,
everyone on Earth.
At one o'clock on July 24th,
Zyra,
a new planet, will pass so close
to the Earth, it will cause
vast destruction.
Never before in the history
of the world has humanity
felt so close to God.
As Zyra inexorably rushes
toward us, perhaps to destroy
the Earth, men and women
of all races and streams
pause to think, to pray,
and to atone.
As the evacuation of coastal cities
progressed, tales of individual acts
of heroism and sacrifice
poured into newspaper offices.
So that's what's happening.
How can we get out of here on a broken...
The planet Zyra is heading
towards Earth.
We must not tell the people.
As inexplicably as life itself,
the planet Zyra hurtles closer
and closer to Stang's head, you know.
Stang's head equipped with a special
antenna. 19-year-olds today are so
stupid, you could probably play that.
on the radio and they'd believe it.
No, no, they would not believe
that the planet Zyra is actually
approaching us. That's exactly why they
let us play it on the radio.
Just think if you were one of those skanks
who had enough dough. Only those
teenagers would believe it.
Only the sub... and the subgenius
would believe in anything.
Praise God.
Please check our website at
www.subgenius.com
Subgenius is spelled
without an O.
Although we do have a decoy one
there for the real subgeniuses
so they won't get lost.
And you
can write for free information
or more
at
powerofslack
at postofficebox
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Now if you want to send your tapes or CDs or videos to me, Reverend Ivan Stang,
my actual production studio is here at the Cleveland branch.
And you can send that to me at post office box 19355 in lovely Cleveland, Ohio 44.
One one nine.
And if that's too confusing, I'm Stang at subgenius.com friends.
You can also, uh,
you might want to get in touch with Einstein secret orchestra who's doing this
music in the background and who has the show on WCSB on Thursday nights from
which this show is scavenged like a Frankenstein's monster from the parts of
dead shows.
That's Einstein secret orchestra,
ESO,
at post office box 8 1 5 5 5.
That's PO box 8 1 5 5 5 Cleveland,
Ohio 44181.
Yes,
friends.
The church of the subgenius was born out of Bob in Dallas in the 19 in
actually January 1st,
1980.
The pamphlet number one was first released,
but my friends,
it was never limited to Dallas,
Dallas.
We,
it was a good place to begin the operations because it is a sterile town,
a sterile city full of sterile pinks.
Most of whom don't even come from Texas and,
friends.
I have gotten out.
And of course,
the church is in the hearts and minds of every subgenius everywhere.
Uh,
some find it on the internet.
Some find it in the bookstore.
Some find it in the junkyard.
Uh,
but the luckiest ones find it in the gutter at the bottom of a bottle of
muscatel because friends,
those are the ones that have reached the bottom that have yet achieved total
slack through slacklessness and now can reverse their evolution as under Bob
to become slackless millionaires who give all their money to Bob at post
office box 1 4 0 3 0 6 Dallas,
Texas 7 5 2 1 4 praise Bob.
Hail Connie.
And,
uh,
yes,
let there be slack.
Listen.
MMM.
Music.
Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Hello?
Pardon me?
Goldie?
Uh, no, Goldie's not here.
Yelda, you were talking to Mr. Miracle Man.
Would you like to pump the obscenity?
or would you just like to have your feet shaven?
Well, I'm sorry you're going to have to wait
because we're on wait mode, as you know, right now.
As Scott and Mona have told us,
we've been waiting here for the last 45 days
and still there's no sign of it.
We're calling it now Day 45.
Can you tell us a little bit about where we stand right now, Riven?
Well, yeah, that's exactly right.
Day 45 and counting.
Forty-five days until it is released.
And it appears it will finally happen.
And if tomorrow things go as the way they have been going
and it's not likely to get much better,
it'll probably be Day 46.
It will be Day 46.
It will be forever after Day 45.
I'm going to say the wing.
It will be it.
For me and my family.
It will be the world.
I've been excruciating.
My little dog, Norris, left me something in the mail.
And the rest of my family just broke up.
As it were, they didn't even bother to call me.
They just, and it files a little splitter.
I saw those horrible little melting pieces.
We've had calls like this from everyone in town.
In fact, everybody called at one time to tell us that everything is collapsing.
It is, and it's time to go.
Back to our original component parts.
Keep your head on tight.
Back to the wing.
You're sacked in the saddle.
Try to keep from bleeding.
This is ESO Radio.
ESO Radio, kids.
We'll be back next Thursday night.
Taking air.
After we go and sweep the Freetown Music Awards.
Obscene thoughts and the big nasty from croaking up your throat and going into your head.
I can't say it.
Using the use of family as a barrier, let us catch one full surface of ,
let me support you on another mission with dash Renaissance and Fits you're already contact Untranspective.
Looking for trouble in any particular relation of our vehicles you may contact iceicient ERIC,
Sbrachter, of half age to point us to ESO Nitro.
Because ESO mania, it's 186.
How with all these fun facts is music?
Because ESO is small.
Thank you.