No, he's trying to...
He can't make them shut up.
Ready? Here we go.
Will you be...
He'll never make them shut up.
Somebody gag the cowboy.
All right, here we go.
Five, four, three, two...
One.
And now it's that time you've been waiting for, kids.
Your hero, my lonesome cowboy name,
just rode in on his automatic horse bucket.
Howdy, kids.
I had a terrible ride here tonight.
I was threatened and accosted by three young bullies,
one of whom had a rancid, arid eye
that kept on staring downwards while he beat me for my boots.
After being stabbed in the night several times
about the head in Buttocks area,
I began to scream and chased a 13RTA bus
all the way down Chester Avenue.
Once I got to the dumpster next to Mary Lou's,
I had visions of her in my head.
Oh, Mary Lou.
I had visions of school patrol
and visions of French bunny girls
wearing little parkas
and little teeny, teeny, teeny tiny critterments
you couldn't even imagine.
I couldn't even call clothing.
And he kept me, kept me going
as the oil was slickering up around my feet
and the fires were raging,
making the air on my ears burn down.
All I could do was think of
the soul genius.
So you, uh,
you go to prostitutes, huh?
Good, good.
This is Hour of Slight,
number 1,708,
but it's also Hour of Slight,
number 776 from 2001.
We have lots of new stuff to share,
but if I stop to edit that now,
I won't get anything else done.
So it's rerun time again,
but that's good
because our old shows are sometimes very different
from our newer shows,
and this one is certainly refreshing
because it comes from 18 years ago
when we were all still alive.
I'll see you next week.
Hit me!
And I still can see blue velvet through my tears.
Do you like it when I talk that way, honey?
Are you a big boy?
Do you want to do bad things, Dave?
Stop getting so excited.
Every time you get him sexually excited, his nuts go up inside him and he gets that female voice.
Well, more like a little boy.
He's like little Dave.
He gets scared.
That's why he's so lonesome.
Haven't you ever heard the gelding sound, Stang?
That's when a yearling is frightened by larger males.
He's of his own type or kind.
We call that the forgot-to-debeat-the-prairie-squid voice.
But a squid proboscis is more than just a proboscis.
It's a hiding place for a metaphor.
A metaphor for the pleasures of the universe.
Tuck it inside out and it works both ways.
Yes, Dr. Wang.
Take out the green skeleton of nature now and remove it.
That's a good idea.
I'm going to take my clothes off.
I'm going to take my pants off.
I'm going to do this show with no pants on.
No pants.
The gun is good.
The penis is evil.
The penis shoots seeds.
Jesus Christ, no, it's still coming.
It hasn't even been touched.
It's shooting lightning bolts from inside.
The flames are being blown from the sky one by one.
Friends, last night I was showing...
Somebody told me they found my gold.
I had a plastic subgenius minister's card at a party I'd been at last week.
And I was going through my wallet and going,
Oh yeah, it's gone. I guess so.
And I found my Universal Life Church preachers.
How many here are members of the Universal Life Church?
Look at that. I knew it.
Praise Bishop Hensley.
He was the man who decided that he didn't want to help subsidize religions he might not believe in.
Since religions didn't have to pay taxes.
So he started ordaining everyone he knew.
Much like the Discordians do.
Ordaining popes right and left.
So you're all ministers now.
You don't have to pay taxes.
But as I was going through that wallet,
I also came upon my oldest original subgenius membership card.
The person looking over my shoulder went...
They saw the Universal Life Church card and said,
Oh, I want one of those.
I said, Oh, I'll send a self-addressed stamped envelope to Modesto, California.
But then she saw the subgenius.
membership card and said,
Oh, I don't want one of those.
Now,
I didn't...
I woke up this morning thinking about that.
And I thought, okay, we know what she doesn't want.
What does this say she does want?
Friends, when you say you don't want a subgenius membership card,
you don't want to be a subgenius minister doling out the slack of Bob's.
What it says you do want is that you do want to do something.
Take yourself seriously.
And friends, as a subgenius, I do not take myself seriously.
I don't take you seriously.
I don't take her seriously.
I don't even take that man J.R. Bob Dobbs seriously.
The only thing I take seriously is the one serious law that the Church of the Subgenius has
that Bob passed down.
And that one rule is,
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
I see somebody's been reading their...
scriptures here.
I don't even take the news, what you people call the news,
I don't...
I take that least seriously of all.
So you think you're in America, do you?
Last time I checked.
Well, you're not.
You're in high school.
Now take that thing and bury it where it belongs.
Look at this thing.
It wasn't even human.
Do you think it's healthy for a 13-year-old boy to imagine his teacher naked?
Absolutely.
Mommy, let me go.
I don't want to get breast.
This is strange, but there are four people in the hospital who nearly suffocated in here.
There has to be a reason for this.
What do you think?
I'll run tests on all the main electrical circuits.
I might find something there.
You're wearing black underwear.
Did you go in there and write that on the mirror while I was taking a shower?
Yes.
Well, enough is enough, young man.
Do I make myself clear?
It's like a plague or something.
People disappearing right and left.
Old ladies, little girls, young women.
I'm sorry.
School boys.
I don't call it a mendacity.
I call it anti-slack.
This is Ivan Stank's version.
Watch this.
He starts crying right here.
It's really neat.
Lord, please forgive me.
I have sinned.
Is he laughing there?
Yes.
I don't want him to get to you, Bob.
Here on the last show of the month.
The Millennium.
How many last shows have we done, Doug?
Give me a break.
We never did a last show of the Millennium, though.
The last show of the Millennium.
Yeah, we never did a last show.
In 1998, there was a last show.
We never did one of the Millennium.
We never thought we would be at the Millennium.
I always thought I'd be at some pleasure saucer in space on Planet X by now.
I mean, I'm kind of pissed off that that ever came through.
Well, that's the thing.
Dr. Drummond.
Have you not heeded Bob's new word, build your own ship?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bob's new word?
Is that like Bible with a little N?
Ain't quite the same as getting that eternity on the escape vessels with a ...
Hey, you know, I'm a flexible guy.
You know, he changes the rules.
I can change.
I can move.
I can understand it.
You know, I understand the way that the upper management operates.
Hobos, right?
After years of being in middle management in this cult, I'm a little more of a ...
Well, I understand that, you know, upper management changes their mind at a whim, and the whole strategic direction can change.
You know, it doesn't matter if 20 years you've been predicting that the Earth was going to end on 1998 and we would be off in the present.
If Connie has a headache ...
You know, yeah, if Connie has a headache, four-fifths of the dogma suddenly goes away.
You know?
That's when I don't get it.
These bimbos come in here.
They start changing the rules.
And, you know, Connie's the queen of them.
I'll say it right out loud in front of Bob and everybody.
She's the queen of the bimbos.
Oh, well, hey, is that ... So that's news?
So that's not news.
All right, all right.
I understand that.
But Connie might stick over here.
But I mean that in a ...
What, 84 or something?
The minute Bob was killed.
But I mean it in a malicious way.
I don't mean it in a loving way like most people do.
The minute Mr. Liberate the Women there shot Bob dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet he's gay.
He ain't ...
He's gay.
He's not gay.
I know he's not gay.
Don't be Doug Wellman.
What's that?
He rue the day you shot Bob, because that was when them bitches took over.
I rule the day.
If you left Bob hanging and swinging, why, it'd be as if Confucius had never come along.
Dr. Stang, have they upped your prescription of Halcyon?
Is that what's going on here?
No, no.
I started this diatribe into the bowels of the things that are wrong.
The philosophy.
The philosophy itself is like ...
So you're talking about church point two?
I didn't really mean to cast any dispersion on any of our previous dogmatic points, because
they are still all valid, all still true, as true as truth is, you know, but perhaps
I wandered too far into my own ...
Oh, give me a break, Dr. Drummond.
You were the one that made it a ... wanted it to be a men's club.
I still think it should be a men's club.
God, if only it had remained the way it is.
If only it had been the way it is.
If only it had been the father church that I had promised to be.
It was a polygamous kingdom at one time.
The purity, the purity was there.
And now I feel like a stud on a stud farm with all those women I have to manage.
Can you guys play the Savage Revenge of Helen Keller in Reprovision?
What?
Hell yeah.
The Savage Revenge of Helen Keller in Retrovision?
That is a real actual tract written by Dr. Mars, I believe.
It's a visionary piece.
It also involves performance, and it is quite visionary, except for the fact that they duct
tape your eyes shut, and you're supposed to experience through your nasal cortex most
of the experiences.
Exactly.
You express that so well.
The long knitting needles, believe me ...
Express yourself.
It's a kind of a clean feeling.
You get, you know, like you've all been ...
Clean yourself.
Clean.
Fresh.
Clean it out.
Wipe yourself.
Find refreshment where you ...
Ream yourself.
You peppermint douche.
Ream again in a clean body.
A brand new body.
Lighten up.
Manhole.
Yourself.
Ramrod.
Salus.
Yourself.
I will sit for you.
What's he doing?
By accident.
Stallion.
Oh boy, nice.
Brass cannonball.
Then a brick shithouse.
Ah, there he is.
And you just put this right on his head.
Oh my God.
I've never seen anything like that.
He's got a head condom.
It's really a condom.
Dave has just put a condom over his complete head.
He's ready to dive right in.
Okay, dream.
I'm ready.
Let's do it.
Oh my God.
That's obscene.
It's lubricated and I'm drowning.
He's getting into it now.
Ladies and gentlemen, you should see what's going on in the studio.
It's lubricated, man.
You've got to help me get this off.
I can't breathe.
I've never seen performance art quite like that.
Eat your heart out, Howard Stern.
Ow.
It's clean.
Calm, calm, calm.
Subgenius.com.
And it's a ...
It's a ...
A calm moment, friends, a briefly calm moment because I was putting together last week's
show and I suddenly realized that with the Amsterdam subgenius field trip coming up,
I'm going to have to somehow crank out three shows in advance because I ain't going to
be around to do them damn shows.
Now, I could run some old reruns and things, but we don't have to do that yet.
Friends, because there's been so much going on.
I have this wonderful recording of a KPFA Berkeley more than an hour, less than a show,
show, the original The Show, by the way, with a special guest, Dr. Philo Drummond and host
Puzzling Evidence and caller Phineas Narco.
I've got tons of recordings from Winterstar.
It's a winterstar symposium sponsored by Ace here in Cleveland.
You're hearing some of the recordings from that in the background, Einstein Secret Orchestra
and Ron Slade, but I preach there.
Now, maybe I can ... Maybe by ... At some point, I can find some tapes of Robert Anton
Wilson who also preached there and was really funny.
Friends, of course, we always have tons of ESO Swamp Radio originally broadcast live
on WCSB in Cleveland on Thursday.
Thursday nights at 11 to 1 in the Eastern time in the evenings.
You can call that station at WCSB.org and call in.
Hell, why not?
Friends, I've got this incredible recording of Booger 9000, the legendary subgenius band,
the super group composed of Sphinx Drummond from the Swinging Love Corpses and President
William Howard Taft from Homicidal Briefcase.
Yes, shows.
Joe Newman from the Rudy Schwartz Project.
An incredible recording from an Austin revival in the 90s captured by our friend, Pater Nostril.
Friends, as always, every hour of Slack recently has been partly programmed by the artists
of alt.binaries.slack where, along with artwork, lately the Sabinis have been posting sounds.
We have all been doing that.
All these little clips and bits and mixes from New Monet, Artemia Salina, Dr. Phineas
Narco, Puzzling Primates for Bob, Jupiter Research, and Mr. Sister.
And friends, we got the Bran Flakes new album is in here.
We've got old Meteor Barrage stuff as always, which I bet you've been better on the website.
You better check that stuff out.
I've got the revival recordings coming in.
Better ones than I've had.
From Tucson Revival.
And of course, the sample, the Tampa revival samples did have not hardly been touched.
Oh yes, friends.
And finally, I may end up having to, you know, as I said, I have to do three shows in a week
to get a catch up ahead.
And finally, the final show, number 778, might be nothing but outtakes with no explanations
at all.
I don't know.
Because we've got to move in a hurry, friends.
We've got to move fast because this is the church of the subgenius.
And we know because of the word Bob that the end times are so, so very nigh.
The time is ripe for their arisals.
And XXXX day is coming, friends.
4X day.
We'll see you there at that campground come July 5th, 2001, when the aliens shall meet
with those who are worthy.
And have achieved their ministershiphood in the church of the subgenius under the slackmaster
Bob.
Oh yes, praise Bob.
We didn't want to play this gig.
But when Jesus told us we had to, we couldn't say no to that.
Do you want to hear some Schoenberg or some Neil Diamond?
Okay, I think it's pretty clear.
Everybody here would like a Neil Diamond.
Let's make it.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
You too.
You and you.
Raquel and Rosie get on board.
We gonna ride till there ain't no more to go.
Taking it slow.
Lord, don't you know, I'll have me a time with the poor man's lady hitching on a twilight
train.
Ain't nothing here that's not going to help me.
But I'd care to take along, maybe a song
To sing what I want
No need to say please to no man for a happy tune
Oh, I love my Rosie child
You and me we're going in style
Crackling Rosie, just a lulled woman
But you make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Hang on to me girl, the song keeps running
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Ahh...
Play it now
Play it now my baby
Crackling Rosie make me smile
Girl if it lasts for an hour, well that's alright
We got all night
To set the world right
Hang on to me and then fuck my asshole babe
Ahh...
Oh, I love my Rosie child
She got the way to make me happy
You and me we're going in style
Crackling Rosie, just a lulled woman
You make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Hang on to me girl, the song keeps running
Ahh...
guitar solo
Don't you go dancing with your blue jeans on
You better wear leather or maybe nylon
guitar solo
You won't have to wonder if it just got a stand
You're looking at the phones in your underwear
Excuse me, mom, I was really back this morning
I didn't lock the room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
Need some place where I can hide
Cause if you're going in, I'm pushing, I'm pushing from inside
I feel it getting bigger, it's about to rip
The jeans of my jeans are throwing a fit
Excuse me, mom, I was really back this morning
I didn't lock the room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
That's pretty, boy
guitar solo
Need a better place where I can hide
That's right, I'll tell you why
It's a-growing and a-pushing and a-pushing from inside
guitar solo
I feel it getting bigger, it's about to rip
The jeans of my jeans are throwing a fit
guitar solo
Excuse me, mom, I was really back this morning
I didn't lock the room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
guitar solo
Dancing with a hard-on
Houston, Missouri
I got a diamond cutter
Dancing with a hard-on
Make way for the
That's a little hard on
Yeah that's right
That knows how it feels
When you've been dancing with a hard on
That's a little hard on
Lords of Acid is just about nothing but
That kind of
Richard and Kitty Cat
Well how about a pronuncement
Of earth squashing impertinence
Somebody told me that people have group sex
At Lords of Acid concerts
I said
Now I've been to a
5X Days and a Thrill Kill concert
I've seen them all
Just about
But
And this
Young lady
That was explaining this to me
Said well I had my first three way
At a Lords of Acid concert
Well everybody had a three way there
But they're talking about
Long sliking dogs
They're talking about three way hits
No I think they were talking about
Three way
Sexual activities
With a prairie squid
A man on one end
A woman on the other
And a squid in the middle
You better believe it baby
And sometimes you can get another guy
Or a girl in there
Depending on how
If it's a large enough
And willing enough
Depending on how
And cute enough
The ink sack is on the squid
That's right
You can always use the ink sack
Once it's been de-inked
Can you put them together
Like a little pioneer toy
When you were 75 years old
We've got those de-inking
Suction cup pad machines
At Subgenius Foundation
Huh?
Or I mean just if you had three squid
Not three squids
I'm of course an erudite person
Three squid
Could you just snap
Them together like blocks
And they would serve the same purpose
Of perhaps a hundred just clear
Army
The South American army squid
Oh they're
Will do that
They will actually form bridges
Of their own bodies
Across rivers
So that their horny squid mates
Can get across
You know at the
Cost of thousands of lives
Yet thousands more will live
The reason for the psychic experiments
Look here
The army squid are not only growing in size
To conjugate
And multiplying
But they have one mind
One heart
One mind
Much like you
Dr.
If you cut off the head
It just grows another one
If you pull a beak
Another beak appears
If you shave an eyebrow
Another thing laughs at you
And cries at you
If you pull out its fangs
It grows twice as many
If you pull its ears
It wants you to rub its belly
If you give it milk
It will suck your blood
All these things and more can be yours
At Squidtown
Prairie Town, USA
My
Miles and miles of furrowed dirt
And squid flipping and undulating
In each and every patch
I thought I'd died and gone to heaven
Rose, poor rose
I never thought I'd die
I never believed there could be such a squid farm
I'm fine
Squids as far as I can see
They're sluppin' and sluttin'
I think they're ready to be picked
I got my Viagra
I'm all greased up and ready to go
Look, look I got one of them fake beauty marks
I'm sorry it's a melanoma
But look, I got a tear
Tight, tight, tight pants
I got a tight squid here
Yeah
Retired here
Little bit of that sorrel soul
Sausage sorcery there, eh?
That's right
I like to get down in them furrows and just plow
You know what I mean?
Just plow my way
Use one squid as a condom
For the use of another squid
Yep
And then use a bigger one atop them
We were the ones who invented them things
Back in the dome
You know, back in the dome
Well, back under the dome
You could take one of them
And it would shave your eyebrow for you
You wouldn't have to even sit in a chair
You could just sit there and lecture it
I tried to get a patent on those things
But it turns out you can't patent a formula
That's right
But that didn't matter back in the day
And that's all you really need to create that
We just sit there witless and having the squid
Witless and having
Mammy didn't know nothing
We did all kinds of songs
Knowing and having
Happy was none the worse
Remember the squid songs we used to make up
When we had nothing else to do
But just try and recharge our depleted accordion
Knowing the squids
Yep
Getting to know them real personal
Loving the squid
Having the squids
Plowing the squid
Squidding around on the squid
Squid cake
I like to just take it in my hand
Squid soup
Squid sandwiches
Squid bed
Cream of squids
Squid flags
Squid pudding
Squid beach furniture
Squid cream of era
There's nothing like squid pudding though
All that stuff
Everybody's grandmother made squid pudding
Out of their own orifices
And squid strudel is good too
When you had a dry, dry old granny
Not like the rest of us
We used to dry out the grannies
I remember that
We'd take the grannies and we'd string them up
Smoke them
And for a long time
Two, three, four weeks
We would be cured but we would never get high off it
Church
Grannies
Nope, wasn't right
Besides, Grandpa didn't like that
No, he wanted all of it for himself
He wanted to do his own jerking
He walked 50 miles a day to go to a squid
And then Grandma, she walked
Until she quit squid
She'd walk about 25 miles a day
And they just keep telling the same story
Everybody knows you took the squid bus
You and the old days
That prairie squid merkin
I remember that old song
Grandpa
Alien's coming
We're gonna get her to get our beef jerking
Did you know that Hitler owned 8,960 acres of land in Colorado?
What?
Hitler?
No
Yes, he did
He owned 8,960 acres of land in Colorado
Why, no American citizen would do business with Adolf Hitler
I'm optimistic this can happen
That's nothing, though
Mata Hari was making
You know how much he's making?
He's making $7,500 a throw
That must have been some poon there, boy
And so as we begin the work of healing our nation
God's gonna strike you down
Who's healing our nation now?
In a big thunder storm
Hey, something happened to that thing, Doug
I feel up your pain
And I feel like me, feel like I'm dead
Alive or still alive
God the heathen
What's wrong?
Are you crying right now
Are you insane is that what you're doing?
Because you're mine
There's nothing to do
Oh, I, I
I can't stand
The roads around, I can't stand
The woods down, I put a spell on you
Because you're mine
I can't stand
The roads around, I can't stand
The woods down, I put a spell on you
Oh, because you're mine
Because you're mine
How the, you know, how the hell did you ever survive the last seven years without your, your trunk?
I'm sorry, I like it.
Well, what happens is if you've been around enough squid, well they get into you.
And they just start reproducing and hollering and carrying on.
Gene.
Before you know it, you're just a vessel for squid intelligence.
And then you gotta send them to college.
Exactly.
Start all over again.
Yeah, you're gonna get done with the little peckers.
Keep you young.
Keep you young and quick.
My feet have gone to sleep while we're talking about this.
And I think my hemorrhoids come back.
So if we could maybe change the subject a little bit.
No.
All right.
I know that's the only thing you ever want to really talk about in depth.
But for crying out loud, we've been talking about it for six weeks now.
I know.
Deep dark secrets.
And they don't have to look.
Has Mojo come out in New Zealand the way he did at X Day?
I don't know.
It's a good question.
The emanations of the Connieites kind of turned him.
First, it made him want women.
But then it made him want women so bad that he wanted to turn into a woman.
It feels like.
And then he wanted to make out with, you know, the regular guys that he had just been, you
know, running around making explosives, shooting off bombs with.
That's all he was doing.
Bomb making.
He was rocket butt sniffing.
As long as it can be distinguished that man is man and woman is woman.
I think you're just a big bully.
What makes these men want to wear circles?
Those who can be changed.
They're the easy ones.
What are those who so desperately want to be of the opposite sex yet can't change their
sex?
Perfect.
Ordinary people.
Keep back.
Girls have alkenes.
Guys with limbs and men with muscles.
The classic dude in a.
One is a man, but you feel that you're really a woman.
Correct.
And you are going through the process of actually surgically becoming a woman.
Sure.
Very good.
We have a winner here.
I hope you don't freak out at the last second when they get out the pinkie shears for you.
I don't care if you like us.
Because we don't like you.
And we don't give a flying what you think.
I thought you were trying to French kiss me.
You're better.
Nice.
Boys have alkenes.
Girls have china.
Girls have alkenes.
Man is woman and woman is man.
Guys with limbs and men with muscles.
Hummin' a, humming a, humming a.
A woman pretending to be a man pretending to be a woman?
Ridiculous.
It's preposterous.
In fact, it's so preposterous no one would ever believe it.
I find it very mind-bending.
There is going to be hell.
Medically impossible.
It's not really hard to believe.
It's just hard for you to accept.
Medically impossible.
God.
Just castrate him.
Good heavens.
Jesus.
God.
You can hit me while I whip this out.
Ah.
Guard.
Castrate him.
No.
Guard.
Castrate him.
Ah.
This is not a haphazard maneuver.
Careful planning for it started months back.
Well, the joke's on you.
Be there.
I'm not even a real blonde.
The big green dragon that sits on your doorstep.
He eats little boys.
Boys have cut my Snakes.
Babby dovetails and big fat snakes.
Eggs!
Connie's Spewing 2 by Reverend Protectrix Amazonia.
Bob said it, so you better pick up on it.
If Bob says that traffic light is green, but it looks red to you, floor it!
Floor that!
Close your eyes and gas it to the max!
Do what Bob said, not what your mind said.
Who do you trust, friends?
Who do you trust?
Your mind or Bob Dobbs?
Get that part straight first.
But people are afraid to trust.
You know, I don't blame them.
We've all been burned at one point because we trusted the conspiracy,
or we wouldn't be so screwed up as we are.
We wouldn't be in this room right now.
But, you know, you go, well, if I can't trust Bob,
who can I trust?
Friends, you cannot trust Bob to do what's right for you.
Okay?
That's in your hands.
That's entirely in your hands.
But you can trust Bob to do what's right for Bob,
which you can't even trust yourself about.
So, friends, Bob is real, and yet some people don't believe in Bob
because either he's too good to be true or they fear Bob, you know,
just as some people do.
Well, normal humans sometimes fear, well, actually, it's the old-timey,
I know a lot of old-time subgeniuses that fear computers and the Internet.
There's always resistance to anything new, and Bob Dobbs is always new and improved.
So there's always going to be somebody scared of him.
Isn't a boy named Sue...
He cannot leave the bathroom.
...on the back of the EMS vehicle,
singing to the various crippled victims of the gerbling problems.
I guess we want to call them problems.
Somebody was clearly at fault and didn't want to take credit.
Well, if you don't feed the gerbil, what do you think's going to happen?
Soon, the gerbil becomes very hungry.
As his belly becomes hollow and his skin becomes slick,
as the hair falls out and his eyes grow weak, he will bite it.
He will bite it.
Anything.
At the last minute, I will substitute the starving gerbil for the healthy one.
Or just about ready now.
The master won't suspect until it's too late.
He humiliates you.
This is the only...
reste en yard  woven ab.
Nothing wrong with that.
Just the downfall of this snack-tw trata session.
But why?
There's a positive message I could partners and working brothers share.
I'm sorry.
I have a mission to perform.
Give me some more.
Very well.
I will recalculate.
Human movement is the bringer of human life.
You must be an end to your race.
I want to see the girl Alice again.
Beautiful face, monsieur.
Oh, yes, of course, you remember, huh?
She drove everyone crazy.
Ah, the woman was for herself.
Oh, Dave.
She was at the oyster bar one time,
and she was clipping the cathedral, as we used to call it.
She was making time with a one-eyed man.
There they were, exchanging spit in the middle of the barbecue hall.
No man blinded me.
She was no good.
She was no bad, either.
She looks like one of the Stepford Stepmothers.
I bet you can see the Latin side of her
when you turn her upside down.
I bet she's got one of those little fuzzy monkeys, eh?
Ha ha ha!
Oh, no, you shaker.
And then he goes all the way up to her belly button, huh?
Bob?
You don't even know who he is, and you might miss him.
If you didn't have a real good look at him,
you wouldn't even know who he looked like.
They don't believe in Christ, do they?
If we get a stopper, they're gonna kill us all!
No.
You gonna feel blame?
Are you mad?
I will pull your goddamn tongue out of your mouth!
On the rope!
If you didn't have a real good look at him,
you wouldn't even know who he looked like.
You really haven't got any excuse,
but I've done all kinds of things.
No need for your goddamn tongue out of the rope!
On the rope!
I'll give you no excuse!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
And do you remember when you were a little girl, perhaps,
and your father gave you a beating?
Well, I mean, you know, I don't know.
And get ready for a shock.
The music that they're planning to use
to crumble them all
in the boroughs of America
is this rotten, filthy, dirty, lewd, lascivious junk
called rock and roll.
It isn't just the lyrics and the music.
It's called Satan.
Though they dwell among the stars,
they make millions of trips to planet Earth daily,
traveling faster than the speed of light.
By an increase in swearing with language that withstands a sailor's hand on end.
They attempt to depress, possess, and oppress their victims.
Psychiatrists and psychologists are no match for these ETs.
Mob?
M-M-M-M-Mob?
I think of Bob as a proteus.
A sex gland, often.
When I think of myself ensconced in a little home,
a little domicile,
on the pipe, on the ring,
Saturn's moon.
I can see...
Little flocks of pastures of green sheep floating by,
and what do they call those?
Hillocks?
Like a little cottage with smoke curling out of it.
And each one resembles a pipe.
And I can see myself there with my own little Connie.
A Connie of my own design, perhaps.
Hairy-footed, perhaps with a face much bigger than the rest of her body.
But still...
I like that kind, too.
I thought you did, and that's why I brought her up.
She's been calling you again, Stang.
That big head girl?
The big head girl?
From space?
She's been calling you, Stang.
You think I hear her?
I think all I ever get is your machine.
I know you've been thinking of me.
I went back to the carnival again,
and went on the ferris wheel,
and rode the merry-go-round,
and all I could do was think of you.
Of course, it was very hard to fit my head in.
The merry-go-round was a low ceiling.
But still, I was alone.
And I thought of you.
I ate a loaf of bread,
and then I played with myself and cried again.
Then I went on the ferris wheel.
I had to be restrained because my head was disturbing the other passengers.
And I thought of you again.
I went down to the boardwalk and looked at the scene.
And all I could see was your reference.
Why you don't call me back sometime?
Well, it's Lady,
a huge little ice cream lady,
the woman from space girl calling you back again,
hoping sometime you'll return my call.
Bye.
It's so strange.
You know, they...
All those groupies.
Yeah, I remember.
All they needed to do was to just send their $30 to Bob.
And I know that's all they're trying to do is get close to Bob.
They think I know Bob's phone number.
And I do.
You do.
But they think I can give it to them, and I can't.
I just can't.
And instead of giving you their $30,
I deny them Bob's essence.
What do they do?
They come up to you, and in time, they say something stupid.
I don't know.
They play with your hairy feet.
They talk backwards to you, try and trick you.
When time is right, listen to the words.
Time, yes.
How many times has this happened at Divi-Val?
Every time.
Every damn one.
I remember the last time I was playing with Einstein's secret orchestra at a Divi-Val
for the Reverend Ivan Stang of the Church of the Subgenius.
We just finished a song, and a rush of about 11 women.
No, it's always 15-year-old guys with glasses.
Scangly clothes.
If only it was women.
Yeah, if only it was women who didn't look like kind of fat guys in those weird, you know,
Pendleston shirts with like...
With a Bob shirt.
With real thick glasses.
That's too tight.
Guys that kind of look like us, you know, and only...
I thought that was really good.
The only part I enjoy was saying, you know, they're real smart and everything.
Yeah, but you know what?
You missed this one note.
I saw where you missed this note.
Yeah, it looks smart and shit.
And there's a link on your website.
It's dead.
I wanted to make sure you knew about that.
And you know what's wrong with those CDs?
That's where they go skipping.
No, man.
We don't want that.
That's the coding problem.
Hi.
How have you been?
I'm watching you tonight.
Are you all right?
Are you hungry?
Can I get you anything?
A cup of coffee, perhaps?
A sandwich?
A ham?
I'd like some guineas and some crackers.
A bee job?
Maybe some...
Knotted nylons?
Oh, yes, bees.
Yes.
I can bring you bees.
Would you like some bees, honey?
I can make honey for you.
Oh.
No, they don't talk that way.
The hot Yoo-hoo bottle?
No, they don't wear Hulu skin.
They don't wear a hat.
But, Mr. Mitch, they don't talk funny languages for our pleasure.
No, they just say, Price Bob.
None of them have hair on their faces either.
I found my copy of Book of the Subgenius for a dollar at the cutout bin.
Would you sign it?
Some of them do have the little lines, the dotted lines for the cranial lymph lines
and the place where they took off the top of their head.
I like that.
She's pretty, don't you think?
You creeped her out.
Actually, to be quite honest, there's been
times when I've thought, maybe this has gone too far. I would get frustrated with the sheer
nerdliness of some subgeniuses, you know, because it just seemed like,
God, I didn't know they were going to be so dysfunctional and messed up. Well, duh! Duh!
It finally sunk in. That is what this is. That's what the Church of the Subgenius is all about.
Of course they're fucked up and dysfunctional, because there really is a conspiracy of normal
people sapping away their slack. And of course they're fucked up, and of course that's why Bob
is their God. Now, friends, when X-Day didn't happen in 1998, we were so sad. We're going,
oh man, we could have had a new government that was no government at all. That, you know,
Bob would be the leader, and he never showed.
We'd have a new church where you didn't have to get up at seven in the morning. You could
worship it drunk until midnight Saturday night in bars. We'd have a new coolness where, you know,
coolness was completely defined by each individual uncool weirdo. Friends, so X-Day didn't happen.
What are we waiting for? Do we really have to depend on some pipe-smoking dot-faced
salesman or a bunch of aliens from outer space?
Or a bunch of invisible monsters to make our own slack? Hell no, friends. Bob is not the answer,
and neither is anything else. We must learn to think for ourselves, although only Bob can show
us how. And we must, all of you had better, you must question authority. Or else, we've got
somebody here who's been reading their pre-scriptures. There.
One who dares to really question authority. And friends, really, honestly, I think that
as bad as things are, if you can just, the scientific basis of slack is this.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke! Even if they help, fuck them if they can't tell a joke.
Yo, yeah, I know what time it is.
Write to this address I'm about to give. That's Bob at Post Office Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.
www.subgenius.com and praise Bob.
We pulled off to the side
We just knew they wanted to ride
The sweetest squid you'll ever know
Blow you right through the door
They'll blow you right through the bar door
Three squid falling from the sky
Three squid and they get real hot
Every three squid, well they're falling on now
Every three squid
I got a tentacle
Oh no, there's a tooth
Oh my God, oh no, there's a tooth
They're still suction cups
Oh my God, I feel the
It hurts when they peel the suction cups off
But I like it so much
Oh yeah, ooh-ooh, baby
Yeah, so
Oh
Oh, if you're ever out of your life
Don't think you have to run high
When you see some hairy pink, pink snow
Falling down, oh no
Hairy pink snow
Falling down right from the sky
From the sky
Just pull on over them on the inside
Pull on over, open your mouth
All the hairy squid with the best, best eyes
And use some genius and joy to ride them
Maybe three big squid
Falling from the sky
Eighty-three-d squid
And they're dripping salt
Well, they're falling on gold
Eighty-three-d squid
That's right, the Lord
Fell from the sky in front of my car
While I was driving down the high note
I pulled over, I opened my car door
And they were blowing my mind through the car door
Placed all the hairy squid
Ah, yeah
Yeah
Three?
Ah!
I gotta make a stand
You gotta make a stand
Cause we really love to make a stand
Mr. High Keeper don't make me touch your mind
Back in the day, there was a kid I placed it on