Yes, I believe I'm gonna be
I think I'm gonna be alright
Alright, right, right, right, right, right
Splash!
I tell you I'm gonna be alright
Hey, Will, alright, baby, yeah
Splash!
I'm playing
I'm gonna be alright
What a voice, what a voice.
As the man said, the legendary Screaming Jay Hawkins.
And our very good thanks to the Fuzz Tones for doing a very able job on the back in there.
Let's hear it.
This is Gary Gubrod's band.
This is the only thing that's going to be on the record.
It's pretty unmistakable.
This is Arch Pope's Sternodonts.
This is the last few minutes of the live foundation.
Hi Palmer.
And this is the Pope of all New York.
This is Dr.
Howell.
Now I didn't understand the meaning of it.
This is not viral murder.
I got to hear lots and lots of these tapes and it's fine editing.
Now, you can relax and enjoy this quality product.
Secure in the knowledge that it has been specially created for the lover of fine things and the man of good taste.
Oh, sorry.
You can edit that out, can't you?
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah.
All right.
mag pawer onå…’
You got UV light, can we pull up here.
Hello.
All right.
Good evening, nice to talk to everyone.
Welcome to the Farm Shim Lee Fettre dor.
Thank you.
My name is muchã‚’
Sh mean you.
We love you.
Take care.
life.
Feel the heat.
Nancy, get down.
Get down.
We're over.
Nancy.
Well, here we are.
Where are we?
Here we are.
In the kingdom
of Noxt.
Where all
Noxts begin.
Behind every Noxt
is an infinite number
of Noxts.
A pyramid of Noxts.
Noxt isn't in the
dictionary yet.
But it will be.
Just as sure
as Noxt is now.
Because tomorrow
or maybe the day after
you and I
will start saying
what's Noxt.
And of course
we'll know
it's a historical
kind of understanding
of what
Noxt was
before it became Noxt.
One side of the teeter totter is next.
And the other side is Noxt.
And of course the center,
the fulcrum,
is just now.
So you have Noxt next to now.
And next, Noxt to now.
Doesn't that make sense?
Yes it does.
It does.
I think so.
I think so too.
What's Noxt?
Well, let's see.
It's very difficult
to get a good
nice rest
here inside this
alarm clock.
I don't know.
I try to curl up in the bottom of the curve here.
With a little...
Projections are to keep it from rolling off the nightstand.
Right above me, the gears.
Time sure is noisy.
It should lubricate these gears.
Now is the time.
You said that.
Did you hear that?
Now is the time, Monday's child.
I thought time was continuous.
Yes, that Tuesday's child.
Time is the movement of the first heavenly bodies full of grace.
This is the Shuffler's radio ministry.
Hour of slack on KNON 90.9 and all FXFs.
Praise God.
I'll be...
Turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
My name is Franz Ivanovich Hagen.
And this is the news.
Wake up, puppet boy.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
Somehow, Bob's making...
No trouble. Just get set and get going.
Hear me. Recording. Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Chapter 13.
Verse 11.
And I beheld another beast
coming up out of the earth
and he had two horns like a lamb
and he spoke like a dragon.
And he exercised all the power of the first beast before him
and caused the earth and them who dwell on it
to worship the first beast
whose deadly wound was healed.
And he doeth great wonders
so that he maketh fire come down from heaven
on the earth.
And he doth not let the earth
and the sight of men.
And he deceiveth them that dwell on the earth
by the means of those miracles
which he had power to do in the sight of the beast
saying to them that dwell on the earth
that they should make an image to the beast.
Mob?
Let there be light.
You may shoot your guns and that will split.
That's right, they gonna split all three.
And you know when your guns split
when they clip down over the land and escape
oh, let the spirit of fire blowin' in again.
Let the spirit of fire blowin' all over the country time.
Let the spirit of fire blowin' out of here.
Oh friends.
We want mob!
And have you ever wondered about your neighbors,
maybe wondered about the weird thumps and bumps,
or chants emanating from their apartment?
Well, they may be followers of Bob.
That's the fastest-growing cult here in the Southwest.
Channel 4's Kelly Lane has the story.
...worked up way, but I'll tell you, you'll never get to...
It's Bob.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about Slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
And now, the subgenius.
Our own.
Slack.
The subgenius hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station...
K-N-O-N.
...and only.
...only.
In the city of...
Dallas, Texas.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show,
the listener is advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials
in the event of any material from this radio or other listening device being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed to the ultra-high or ultra-low shocks and brain frequencies
constantly scanned throughout our program should seek shelter in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you...
...that the
...and special guest...
...M. Ilkman.
Ah, yes, dear friends, we're...
I know some of you have had a Jones for the show, the hour of Slack.
You wish it was a week of Slack, don't you?
I don't blame you a bit.
Dave Slack, at least.
Oh, yes, friends, it's caller time again.
Yes, we're going to speak to you on hour of Slack radio ministry tonight.
Hi, I'm Pastor Bucknick, your call-in host, and we're going to take some calls tonight
on signs of the conspiracy.
We want your calls, the actual signs of the conspiracy.
Like, how can you tell if the conspiracy is active in your life?
You know...
...men in black...
...sitting in the back seat...
...in your car...
...while you're on your way to work.
Work itself, friends.
Work itself.
That's all the proof you need.
The conspiracy has got a hold of you where it hurts.
But we want actual physical signs, cattle mutilation, but real things that happen to you.
Cattle mutilations that happen to you.
Or worse.
Or worse, dear friends.
And also, last week's topic, we're going to take a few passages...
...from any of your holy texts, your Tibetan Book of the Dead, your Old Testaments, your New Testaments, your Revised Testaments,
your tests, the old tests from school, or any Bibles that you've written yourselves.
We'll take a few of your calls with those things, and I'll be reading some of my own Uncle Buck's Bible time tonight, too.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
And listen to this drippy music.
This is...
God, dude.
Well, here's a sign of the conspiracy.
We've got one more line open at 823.
823-8801.
So...
Standing next to me on the practice tee is Arnold Palmer, the winner of every major open title in golf,
including the United States Open, the British Open, and the Masters Tournament.
Arnold is going to teach you how to play golf in a new and easy and enjoyable manner,
in the comfort of your own living room.
Are the feet, Arnie, the only part of the stance that need to be in position for that good swing we're talking about?
Well, no, Chris.
I would say that the head position is also very important.
The head is probably as important as the feet in the stance.
And keeping the head in a good, comfortable position over the ball is very important.
Now, you don't want to move the head up or down or to either side during the swing.
No, wait a minute.
I love that area.
And I...
For now, I show thee signs in the heavens and signs in the earth.
Blood benches from the earth.
My lights in the sky rebuke thee.
The children of heaven and the angels from hell are among thee, spreading lies and deception.
Black umbrella skate, go walking around.
Um...
I do things that are different.
Yeah, someone with a lot of energy.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay, your code number once more?
37.
It's a man.
Glorify me, Bob, that I may be glorified through you.
Glorify me that I may glorify you, Bob.
Who tithes his money to the subgenius church, his name will be registered in the cash register of life.
Bob, can you see me?
Subgenius beach party.
My mind is my own and nobody's gonna change it.
I'm not going into that room!
Nobody is, come on.
Wake out of that glass box.
And join the church of the subgenius.
Oh my God.
Is this for real?
No, no, no.
This is just a tape.
Relax.
It is not the day before or the week between.
It's just the show.
The show that, yes, was thrown into the bay three weeks ago and...
They're not actors.
...and struggled free of its chains and floated up, swam back to the studio here, climbed up the antenna, and is now running all the way down those little air wires right into your ears.
Hiya, hiya, you're still on the air.
We'll be at test on Sunday, so...
Stay tuned.
You never know when you're here or not on this show because there are so many doctors.
Just a few dugs, sprinkle a few Gary's, drop a few Bob's over here.
A few Bob's.
Yes, I'm sorry, listener.
You've got a real problem now.
They're live all the time.
I'll be right back.
Be right back.
Let's go for a commercial.
We're living in a terrible, perilous, chaotic time.
Oh, yes.
Chaotic time.
Yeah.
friends and most chaotic oftentimes on the telephone line.
Yes, and we're about to share something with Billy.
What happened?
We're about to share something with Billy.
Hello, Billy?
Billy?
I've seen the conspiracy.
Well, let's hear about it quick.
You're on the air, Bo.
I was cruising westward along Walnut Hill Lane when I took a ride onto Preston Road heading
north towards LBJ.
I was passing the first residential street.
I looked over to my right and happened to spy a Christmas tree shown through a window
of a fashionable corner house.
Right.
The Christmas tree was white frosted and it was decorated exclusively, no pun intended
yet, with white light bulbs.
Again, on the very night...
How do you know that's a sign of the conspiracy, Billy?
Because every street, the eight out of ten streets from Walnut Hill to LBJ, the Christmas
trees were white.
So this is patternology and color coordination conspiracy?
Oh, definitely.
Try it.
It was during the Christmas season.
Every tree...
Okay, we're going to punch this into our computer now.
We're going to get confirmation to you later on.
M. Ilkman is here.
Billy, Billy, listen.
We're going to get confirmation on whether that's an actual conspiracy code.
So go ahead and tell the rest of it now, the other side.
I see.
Okay.
Where was I?
I don't know.
I was cruising on Preston Road.
Anyway, the Christmas tree was white frosted and it was decorated exclusively in white.
Gotcha.
Okay, thank you very much.
And thanks for sharing that with me.
Our Slack Radio Ministry, Billy.
And later on, we're going to get the soul sucker out and we're going to let you...
Okay.
Now, we've got another caller here, I think.
Hello?
Hello, is this Ronald?
What's wrong?
Somebody's messing up here and it's not me.
Oh, listen to that scary wind outside.
Yes, friends.
That's the soul sucker that works with this show, waiting to catch your calls before they get to us.
Are all phones down out there?
We joke around about it a lot, friends, but it's really pretty serious.
I mean, the paranormal isn't something you want to mess with a lot.
We're trying to get that caller in here.
Caller, don't give up.
Here, you got a...
Caller?
I don't like that caller.
Just take it down.
Caller?
Hello?
Is this the caller?
Here he is.
Here's our caller.
Caller?
Are you alive?
Are you in there, caller?
Caller, you need to talk real loud.
Let's hear your problem, caller.
What did you call our Slack Radio Ministry for tonight?
Okay, yeah.
A scientific conspiracy.
It's my own theory.
I'll admit it, but...
You have a spiritual problem?
Yeah.
It has proof.
I have proof that it's serious.
In your navel?
Yeah.
Cigarette smoking causes pregnancy.
Cigarette smoking causes pregnancy?
Yeah, I can prove it.
That's true.
My mother had me, so that's...
Thanks for sharing that with us and the radio ministry and our radio family out there.
Oh, yes, friends.
So we've got some sort of a communistic ad coming up here that we have to put on the hour of Slack rather than...
I've got another caller here.
Oh, you do?
All right.
Spirit voice, what is your problem?
Yeah, okay.
You know, when people burn their hands, they don't ever do that.
They don't ever do that again.
So, like, when people die, they don't ever do that again either.
So it must be an equally bad experience.
That's right.
That's proof of the conspiracy.
You do it once, you can't make the same mistake again.
I can't believe that they do that.
Well, just remember this.
How do you think that relates to the supersonic Nazi hell creatures from the hollow earth that are waiting to get us?
I don't know, but I think it's like a pre-shock wave after fabrication.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
Thanks for sharing that with us, caller.
All right, we got another caller.
Hello, caller.
Oh, yeah, about that theory.
I was hung up on her something.
I guess a pink boy...
Gee.
Oh, I don't know what's wrong.
There's something's happened to the sound control.
Caller, are you still there, caller?
I lost him.
Caller, there he is.
The soul sucker is eating him up.
Caller, can you hear me?
Oh, okay, do it.
Okay, the world's greatest toys are all around the world, right?
Yeah, right.
Right.
You don't even need a stamp.
Just drop that into my body.
Press it to your forehead.
It will come.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
It'll get your car again.
And soon that Bob energy will start feeding out through the airways, and it'll catch you in your car.
It'll lift you out, and your car will be D-man, and you'll be flying right with Bob.
And you don't have to get up early on Sunday morning and wear tight shoes to be saved.
Hello?
I'd like to speak to all of our callers.
We're about to get the soul sucker out, and I'd like to say to you that if it hurts, remember to scream,
because it's a very powerful unit, and it has actually stripped the souls of five callers who called last week,
have not gotten out of their catatonia yet.
So if it hurts at all, I want to hear you yell loud when we put the soul sucker on, okay?
So now we're going to play a tape.
This is called Dallas Police Unfair to Youth by Kate Griffin.
Is it 12?
Twilight Room.
Instead of simply closing the doors, eight police cars surrounded the parking lot.
Everyone in the parking lot was patted down and frisked.
No one was allowed to take their hands off the nearest car.
People who asked why were pushed or beaten.
I saw blood.
Then the police got in their cars and raided the other youth clubs.
What are we going to do about it?
Will we have to stand outside Reunion Arena with signs saying,
Dallas Police Unfair to Youth?
Things were fine.
We've been in this business for years.
Let's stop brutal searches and intimidation tactics.
We've seen people get into Bob and their business picks up 10,000 percent.
Or they get into Bob and all of a sudden they're whining with the gutter, but finally they're happy.
They're loose again.
They can feel free and think their own thoughts and not be feeling the conspiracy breathing down the back of their necks.
They could dance in the Mecham fountain and have a free heart while they did it.
Oh, praise Bob.
Bob Dobbs, he's no slob.
Bob Dobbs, he's no fool.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
And that's why he's super cool like glass.
He's Bob Dobbs, he's no slob.
Bob Dobbs, he's no fool.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
Those numbers are 823-7490 and 823-8801.
Give us a call on the hour of slack.
I either want a Bible quotation or I want signs of the conspiracy.
Or both.
This is Kano.
Kano and 94.9.
Welcome to the subgenius devotional hour here before the normal scary time.
As the smoke of that burning goeth up forever.
That was a stinkle.
But it had lots of prophecy involved.
You heard it right here on the subgenius hour.
And lots of few words.
Wonder why Fido came home with his wazoo missing.
Or wonder why those beefs like Buster and Deer on the parlor and the pasture are lying out there with their throats and half their rectums missing.
Well, it's because of those exists who came down to this earth.
One Christmas day many millennia ago.
To forge a new link.
One might call it a hot link.
Between the aliens and man.
A giant sausage of knowledge from the center of the universe.
The galactic center.
Those little tykes will be able to carry on for us.
Every one of those little kids is a potential Lee Majors.
And I hope you're pleased with what we've done.
The rising generations shall have reason to praise us.
To pour out libations on our smoking altars.
And we should know.
This is a non-smoking section.
The book of the subgenius.
Lunatic prophecies for the coming weird times.
Out now and on your stand.
From McGraw Hill.
If you don't see the book on your stand.
Complain.
Loudly agitate and tell the store if necessary.
They are crazy.
It's a question of bull dada.
And it's application of course in the society surrounding the bull dada.
We apply it from a little disposable tube.
That's right.
Using the power shell.
And using the spirit code.
The Yucateezum matrix applies the bull dada to the normals and pinks.
This is classified information.
Do you want to let this out on the air?
Take the sludge.
Proof of the conspiracy.
Right here.
Conspiracy proof.
Caller.
Hello.
Say it.
Proof of the conspiracy.
Proof they don't have slack.
They use conspiracy street drugs so they have no slack.
Thank you caller.
Thanks for sharing that with our radio ministry.
Okay.
The AIDS town benefit series.
We're playing a benefit for AIDS town.
At the step ladder.
Just a step south of Lemon.
On McKinney.
3406 McKinney.
Remember that.
I'd like all those folks who just called in to come and see us at 3406 McKinney.
Saturday April 19th.
That's next Saturday night.
At the step ladder club.
That's free right?
Free.
Free to the public.
But it's a benefit.
Because the bar is going to contribute to AIDS town to send them away.
Okay.
Also.
A little quotation.
Bible here.
Matthew 1032 to 1039.
This is the words of Jesus now friends.
This is not my words.
And this is you know your family's words.
This is the family Jesus saying this.
Okay.
Whoever acknowledges me before men.
I will also acknowledge him before my father in heaven.
But whoever disowns me before men.
I will disown him before my father in heaven.
Do not suppose that I have come to bring peace to the earth.
I did not come to bring peace but a sword.
For I have come to turn.
A man against his father.
A daughter against her mother.
A daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law.
A man's enemies will be the members of his own household.
Anyone who loves his father or mother more than me.
Is not worthy of me.
Anyone who loves his son or daughter more than me.
And anyone who does not take his cross and follow me.
Is not worthy of me.
Whoever finds his life will lose it.
And whoever loses his life for my sake will find it.
Translation.
This is my personal translation.
Matthew 1032 to 1039.
You can cut this Prince of Peace crap right here.
I'm in charge now so learn to kick butt.
I'll set up sons against fathers.
Daughters against mothers, etc.
And screw up all your other relationships.
Think of death as life and life as death.
Just remember I'm the boss.
If you get in my way I'll slice your head open with this here sword.
On the other hand if you do your job.
Don't ask questions.
I'll get you a good deal in the afterlife.
They're starting to shoot at us now, friends.
Okay.
Yep, that's right.
We just heard gunshots outside.
Absolutely for real.
That's either the pizza on the way or else the pizza thing was a ruse.
It's the pizza bandits on the road.
This Western street.
Huh?
I'm seeing a lot of Vaqueros shooting at each other these days, aren't you?
Uh-huh.
A lot of that.
Okay, well the numbers are 823-7490 or 823-8801.
We're gonna have the soul sucker and that young lady's just telling how the soul sucker really feels.
That's right, dear man.
We're gonna play tapes about 10 or 15 and come on back.
Bye-bye.
My friend hakans
is here.
Pizza for Bob, that's all right.
It is a donation to the subgenius radio ministry.
Thanks, Bob.
Ng-ng.
Finger lickin' good.
And who is this pizza courtesy of?
Doctor Dean.
Dr. Dean, oh, you have to pray.
It's another doctor for Bob, friends.
It's just kid Bob.
Oh, smell that.
Smell that church air coming off of that pizza.
Oh, yeah.
Bucky got the first slice.
Yep, and Buck's not putting it in the orifice that most people put food in.
Nay, nay.
This is a church for mutants, friends.
A mutant church.
Church. Oh, did you have a message, Reverend Dr. DDT agent?
Yes.
All you uninitiates who know me as Eric Kosick, you just don't know!
Oh, there went the needle.
So call the station to find out what it's all about.
Call or die, friends.
And here's what it's all about.
I think here's a song for the person who called to say that people who don't have slack end up using conspiracy street.
It's true.
That conspiracy street drugs are, in fact, a sort of a form of false slack.
A stopgap, scapegoat form of slack.
But, you know, all some people get.
Well, this song here coming up, not the one that's on now, which is by Professor Mother's Bob, Music for Insomniacs.
Some of the voices, by the way, this show you've been hearing was from, of course,
those of you who don't know,
don't recognize it, the amazing more than an hour, less than a show show from Berkeley with puzzling evidence,
Dr. Howell, Gary Gubrog, friend and so forth.
But here is the answer to the question of the conspiracy street.
Bob loves you.
Getting stoned.
Don't sunshine.
Getting high on air.
Getting to it naturally.
Really getting there.
Getting such a high on loving what I do.
I'm so full of happiness.
Hooked on something new.
Life is such a trippy thing.
Hello birdies, hello spring.
Each day on earth is a day that's worth remembering.
And I mean just what I sing.
Life is such a groovy thing.
Don't pity me.
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling.
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling.
My pot is filled with flowers.
My grass is bright and green.
My tea is brewing in my cup.
And still I make the scene.
So just don't try to change me.
I love the world I've found.
I've got to fly my own speed.
I've got to make it my own sweet way.
Don't you shoot me down.
Life is such a trippy thing.
Hello birdies, hello spring.
Each day on earth is a day that's worth remembering.
And I mean just what I sing.
Life is such a groovy thing.
Don't pity me.
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling.
Ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling.
Boy, folks.
That was Frank Sinatra Jr.
And Nancy Steele.
Nancy Sinatra.
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hi, girls.
Hey, we got another caller here.
And I bet you know what he sounds like because he's been on our show before.
And here is our great caller.
Hello, caller, are you there?
Yes, I would like to know what is the difference between a emergent pal,
rewardious, and a video creeper?
What's the difference between an ...
What's the difference between an emergent pal, a rewardion, and a mediocrity?
And actually, that's not a bad question.
Not a bad question.
Too bad he fell prey to the soul sucker.
I don't think ... I think he passed out because he soon as touched him.
I don't detect the pulse over the phone.
No.
But I'll tell you, we might ought to talk about that.
Actually, this is KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
The emergent pal, according to church, subgenius church dogma,
the emergentile is the type of subgenius for whom it's always an emergency.
And I'm the worst sufferer of that community.
They wait until the last minute.
They create their own emergencies because they live off that intensity.
Yeah, they're constantly in an emergency.
They really ... their idea of slack is constant activity.
Now, in the church, we give them ... there's two states of rewardionism.
One is the classic rewardion that simply rewards themselves.
Right.
Those are the opposite of the emergentile.
And they promise us to the ...?
They promise to themselves so that they can continue to function.
The other kind is the rogue rewardion that actually wallows in the rewards
and becomes a total pig and sells out, which is like almost everybody in America.
And then the mediocritan is just the hoi polloi that just kind of shuffle along
in tune with the groove and make very little ... very little, well, difference.
I guess is the big way to say it.
And yet they create ... take up a lot of space, but they make very little difference.
That's the mediocritans?
No, that's the mediocritans, right.
Yeah.
Well, most ...
The hoi polloi.
Most people are mediocritans.
Yeah.
We're talking about the pink boys, them, the Barbies and Cans, the somnambulax, the its,
the mere food tubes who go through life for ...
I'd say that most ... most of you, not us, but most of you are simple mediocritans who
wish that you were rogue rewardions.
Every ... well, yeah.
That's exactly right.
But your rewards are so paltry that you get very little out of it.
And we've got a caller on the phone.
Question number three.
Hello, test, caller.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, you're on.
Say it.
Say it or the soul sucker.
Okay, I have a quote, a quatrain from Nostradamus.
Uh-huh, make it quick.
It says, like the great king of Algo-Moid, the year 1999, seventh month, the great king
of terror will descend from the sky.
At this time, Mars will reign for the good cause.
That was excellent, caller.
I would like to give you the four-month award.
For the best call we've had on our Slack.
That's right.
Yeah, this man has found a key that unlocks the prophecy of J.R. Bob Dobbs back in the
1500s.
This guy here ... now, I think you're tough enough to handle the soul sucker.
We're gonna give it to you and just howl a little bit.
I had it last week as well, so ...
Ready?
Okay.
Are you still there, caller?
You still there?
Yeah.
Now, why in the world would I be going ...
Wait a minute.
Oh, well.
I heard ...
There was a pulse.
I have to play this again.
Listen, this is really important.
Do it.
Listen to this little bit of tape.
This is one of the funniest moments.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
I can't really explain this.
I have to listen to it over and over again.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
There must be that.
Now, why in the world would I be going ... there, the dog?
Yeah, yeah.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
8-2-3-8-8-0-1.
Yeah, yeah.
This is a tune.
Isn't that a pretty little tune?
That was sexy.
This is ... here.
Does Odan do that?
No, that's Mark.
Mother's book?
Yeah.
It's my ... my ...
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, not everybody can do the salute, friends.
And many of you out there in subgenius land do not ... still do not know how to do the
salute by which you raise your ...
Put your left hand towards the heavens.
Put your right index finger right up against your Adam's apple and forcefully, with the
vibrations that will attract the attention of the gods, go ...
Praise Bob.
Come on, help me somebody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Down you go.
Oh, yes.
Hello?
Caller.
What?
You ...
Oh, you can't say that over the ...
I'm sorry.
Your air, you darn fool.
That was ...
That was sick.
Bob.
Well, friends, before that gets any further ...
Are you in there?
Yeah.
I'd like to know what anyone thinks about Oral Roberts teaming up with Dick Army.
I'd like to know ...
There he went, friends.
It's sad, sad ...
Oh, you know what?
I want to put on just a hairy little bit of a record here.
I think if we go like this.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
This is for you to all the dogs out there.
The conspiracy fans out there.
This is for you.
Okay.
Last weekend I listened to the show there.
No, not that one.
I think it was called Damage Incorporated.
What's that?
Anything else?
I was wanting to know
is that being played now?
The answer to all three of your questions
is yes, no, no,
and yes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for sharing that with us.
And now,
M. Elkman.
Yes, friends, this is the
Deacon M. Elkman, the
Deacon of hate, hate, hate, hate.
But I've got a little
something else to talk about, friends.
Tonight, yes, you know how
they were talking about
it's been signs of the conspiracy.
Well, you must realize, oh, there's that
soul sucker, he's just sucking you.
Uh-oh.
That was bad, my friends.
You know how they say
the signs of the conspiracy.
Yes.
I'm so irate at this moment,
I'm having trouble getting my thoughts together.
Hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.
But my friends, with the conspiracy,
the sign is that all them Nazi concentration camps
were just a training ground.
They killed you pretty quick there.
I mean, it seemed slow at the time,
but it was quick because now they've got
those 80 story concentration camps going up
where slowly, little by little,
they're sucking your souls out
and all your money for the conspiracy.
And that kind of stuff,
that kind of stuff just makes me feel so mad.
I just have to hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.
You must draw your own conclusions.
You've got to believe me.
Oops.
Where am I?
And what is putting this intersection?
The intersection?
In the Isle of Mar ideas,
å› Ğ±Ğ¾Ğ»ĞµĞµada.
I said it prior,
democratizing the former
and now-
Thank you, Bob
For cleansing my memory
For helping me sleep
And, Bob
I'll follow you always
That's right, Bob
Until that next day
Thank you, Bob
For sending them pills
For finding me willing
Teenage girls
And, Bob
I'll follow you always
That's right, Bob
Until that next day
And now McGraw-Hill has printed 15,000 copies of the collected teachings of Bob.
More?
More book.
You are absolutely amazing.
Yeah, I know.
Want some more book?
I don't know.
It's got some nice big fat places you can just blast your fist right into it.
Oh, my God.
Julie!
Yeah, we paid for them bombs.
Why couldn't we get the thrill of pushing the button?
Now we paid for the schools.
That's right.
If I paid for that school, I'd blow it up.
What if I go anyway and I can pretend?
Because, you know, after something's happened, all you have left is the memories so you can
just pretend and convince yourself.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about the memories none.
But then I won't have the Kodak.
No one has the Polaroid.
It was just a bad dream that, you know, you never went to school.
The past memories of my life that I no longer live.
That would be awful.
I don't want to go to school.
And let's have an awful little...
Your memories.
I think you didn't expect me to be listening tonight.
Your memories are fading.
Just by chance, I heard you guys came along.
Oh, your memories are fading.
I've got to wake up tomorrow.
Even as you speak, your memories are fading.
Oh, your thoughts are gone.
There are people floating about unregulated, you know.
They're not your own.
Everybody's floating around now here in the morning.
Oh, your memories are fading.
After the blast of the bomb.
But you're still going your own way.
Where do I come from?
You come from the shirt.
You've got to come from the shirt.
What is my name?
What am I doing here?
The nuclear bomb.
You've come from the shirt.
All right, come on.
What color is your hair?
Here I am, hippie.
Well, this must be a tree.
Or a little tiny bomb.
Our first time seeing you.
Yeah, your beverage bomb.
Was it real at all?
You have a mission.
Hot Silhouette's in the Convertible Converter.
Or did you get to the Convertible Converter?
You gave this applause.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob is a rock and Bob is a tree.
Bob is a bear and Bob is a bee.
Bob is truth and Bob is lies.
Bob is cakes and fruits and pies.
Bob's my hat, Bob's my watch.
Bob's my sandwich, Bob's my crotch.
Bob is my hat.
Bob's my toothpick, Bob's my brain, Bob's an ugly yellow stain, Bob's a cactus, Bob's an itch, Bob is taking off every stitch.
Bob's my master, Bob's my slave, Bob will rob me, Bob will save, Bob's my toaster, Bob's my fridge, Bob's my little sister Mitch.
Bob will cost you, Bob is free, Bob's a watch, and Bob's the key.
In short, Bob Dobbs is the man who used your leg as a frying pan.
If your mind is a jar, you can pour it out of the sink, and the subgenius church is the missing link.
Ah, yes, dear friend.
Dear caller, is this Gary?
Yeah.
Gary, what were you going to ask?
It's about an hour of slack radio ministry.
What would you like to share with our radio ministry?
The end of this one long passage goes,
And again, there is seen that this occurred in the entrance of the Messiah in this period, 1998.
This is from Edgar Cayce, and I was wondering, what's it referring to?
Oh, now say that one again.
It's at the end of a long passage.
Uh-huh.
And again, is there seen that this occurs in the entrance of the Messiah in this period, 1998.
Well, what occurs?
You can give us a little hint.
There's something about the rebuilding of the pyramid of ESA.
Rebuilding the pyramid of ESA.
And it's from Edgar Cayce's origin and destiny.
Well, I...
That's the fact that we're going to have a series of rocket launches out of, in the late 90s, out of Egypt,
because they've got a good desert there, and everything falls into the Red Sea.
So, that's what they're referring to when they say, builded the pyramid of ESA, because what it really means is NASA.
Also...
NASA. That's how it got pronounced in the Egyptian, NASA.
Well, but you're...
NASA. That's how it got pronounced in the Egyptian, NASA. Well, but you're...
NASA. That's how it got pronounced in the Egyptian, NASA.
We're missing over a main point of subgenius doctrine that many, many listeners out there may not understand,
that the whole basis for this church is to warn you about the arrival in 1998 of what we call the men from Planet X,
if men they really be.
That's what I thought Nostradamus was referring to.
That's exactly right.
The great king of terror that will come from the sky, and you see...
I didn't forget that. That's part of my very being.
Bob is not...
Bob is a bobber in my glands, dang it.
I can't forget it. It's just that sometimes I don't even sort it out. It's just all part of me.
Well, you gotta use the...
It's in me.
Let go of that part, and, you know...
Give them the other part.
But, friends, it's true. That's the whole point of this church, is those who are saved, friends, will wave goodbye to the ones who fry down below as cities, whole cities, are pulverized by those men from Planet X.
by those men from Planet X.
Unless, unless, friends, Bob Dobbs can swing the right kind of deal.
And see, Bob is a salesman. The guru of our cult is the greatest salesman who has ever lived.
And he's got to do his greatest sales job to make sure, friends, that Earth does not get sold.
Because if the conspiracy controls this planet on X-Day 1998, my friends,
why, the X-ists will take one look at this planet and decide that it's like a dog's been hit by a car on the side of the road.
They'll put it out of its misery, friends.
Speaking of which, speaking of putting people out of their misery, Gary, I understand we have already tried the soul sucker on you, and you'd like to tell us how it felt.
Uh, kind of like a great rush, sort of.
A rush?
Kind of indescribable. I can't really put it into words.
Did it hurt?
Kind of, but not...
Because here it is again.
No.
That's a... over there.
I think that Nostradamus stuff is great. I think Gary's a fantastic caller.
It's true proof of Bob.
Hey, that's true.
That's what I say.
Hey, true, man.
True.
Baby.
This is Jimi Hendrix on the hour of slack.
Hello, dear caller.
Uh, hello. I've got, uh, about three things that are, uh, conspiracy...
Squirt them out. It's a squirting universe.
Okay. Uh, the first one?
Yeah.
You know, like, uh, can't get any good praise anymore, it's all dry-freezed, you know?
Okay. Next thing?
And, uh, you know how, uh, you buy your, uh, hot dogs and they come in packs of ten?
Wait a minute. Your packs of hot dogs and packs of ten?
Yeah.
Oh, oh.
And then you buy hot dog buns and they're eight.
Right.
Hot dog buns is eight. Okay. And then what?
And then, uh, how the candle end doesn't have a metro line.
A metro line?
Yeah.
Because you didn't send enough money, friend.
I sent my money.
Maybe he's right.
Huh.
Well, we can't talk about that on the air.
Friends, this is, this is not a comedy show.
Absolutely. Thanks for sharing that with us, caller. I, I'm even afraid to put that guy on the Soul Sucker. He might sue us.
Oh.
We got another caller.
Listen to the swinging love corpses in the background here.
Hello, caller. Hello?
Uh, yes, uh, Augustine in City of the Gods, uh, Chapter 8, Line 22.
Okay.
I said no credit is whatever, whatever is to be given to you.
Listen to the opinion that demons act as messengers and interpreters between gods and men to carry all petitions from us to the gods, and to bring us back, uh, to bring back to us the help of the gods.
On the contrary, we must believe them to be spirits most...
Friends, you know, the, it's, what he was saying is true. You gotta watch out.
You gotta watch out.
Watch out.
Hold on.
I think Bob's just a guy with a pipe.
Oh, that's crazy talk.
They're not emotional.
Angels don't have any emotions.
Gentlemen, the situation at this time is so serious that it's the worst in human history.
The fate of the entire Earth is in our hands.
Every hour, we are getting news that our factories and our refineries and schools are being attacked
with a lot of bale and ash.
race of unknown origin. They haven't been analyzed so far. Professor, I know you've
been in this book line study for many years. You know more about them than we
do. Tell us, what should we do? Don't go up there at night. Stay in sunlight. Keep
yourself safe and secure, and in the daylight, we'll draw you out of there.
You've got to use all your power to knock them out. All your power... Laser guns?
Laser guns. Not only laser guns, but your crew. Get them up there and knock them out.
When you knock them out... But we're gonna have trouble with the launch pad.
Well, the launch will be all right as soon as I can get there. We know we've
been behind it for years.
It's been a long time.
It's been my research staff that came up with the initial evidence.
Dr. Moore, can your staff come up with a weapon to stop the Nazi hell creatures in time?
I can't say for sure, but we've got the physiological providers for the answers.
A man? Is he a captain?
What is he?
Everybody's got love on the planet Everybody's got love on the planet
The girls have all five tips on the planet
Well friends, that was the swinging love corpses, which you may not know about. To begin with,
with Love Planet.
That's a fantasy world
they dwell in, I think.
Love Planet.
What's wrong?
It's sad, friends.
But, what's...
I don't know.
I can't hear myself.
You're on.
Oh, well, we got a caller
and this fella named Walter,
in quotes,
wants to give proof
of the conspiracy
and I think we need
a little proof of the conspiracy
from Walter.
Walter.
Are you there, Walter?
Yes.
I am with you.
I have proof...
You better talk real loud, Walt.
Talk loud, Walt.
Okay, I have proof
of the conspiracy
that the phone company
is in on it.
Hurry.
Every time that I call somebody
at four in the morning
to share the word of Bob
and start to tell them
about Slack,
the line goes dead.
That is proof
of the conspiracy.
You score.
Anything else?
That's it for right now.
Here you go.
persà¸„à¸£ Parent883
undesí°
unsъє Tú
way
plá
Coronavirus
ID
altos
Addis
fonction
It's a birthday present for your mother.
New York, New York.
New York is a state of mind.
We've got elkwood.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
We're right here.
It feels so good.
This is DK Jones.
And I'm Pastor Buck Naked, and I'd like to say hi, girls.
Well, also, I'd like to tell that guy that I do have a birthday present for his mother.
No, we've been having fun with this rock and roller who's been calling us up and cussing us out.
But that's okay because it's a free country and Bob lives, but, you know.
Okay, friends, we've only got five minutes left to go on the show, and I'll tell you what.
Every show I get down to the time where I'm in the show.
I want to play the credits of the...
What?
And the sickening conviction that the man from Planet X...
You can't say that out of the air.
...had Enid powerless in his grasp.
The man from Planet X?
If she was to be saved, I had to think calmly.
No, Bob.
I checked off my resources.
Where was Enid?
Where was the man from Planet X?
On a skateboard, on a skateboard.
That's right.
Uh, alright.
To attempt an understanding of Bob without understanding his mortal enemies, the men from X,
is to attempt seeing truth without knowing falsehood.
It's the attempt to see light without knowing darkness.
It cannot be.
That was so sexy.
The men from X?
Are you ready for the soul sucker?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Here it is.
No!
Ah!
Cole, are you alright?
Yeah.
You alright?
I...
Ah...
Wow.
I was gyrating.
Here's a little more.
No!
Ah!
Oh, here he is.
I hear that guy's soul.
All right, friend.
Ben, your soul is black.
Your soul is black.
You know that?
Hello?
The voices, faces, music, and editing you've been listening to come from Flippo Abernathy,
Buck, Naked, and the Jaybirds, Dr. Conan Canobite, G. Gordon Gordon, Killer for Bob,
Doctors for Bob
Dr. Philo Drummond
Overman First Degree
Reverend Cleve Donut Duncan
Dr. Snavely Eklund
Dr. Ahmed Fishmark
This is Glass Madness
This is Herr Dr. Chris Gross
And this is Negative Land
These are the fantastic swinging love corpses