Oh, friends, I have this new dog, and he's been sitting across from me in this studio
watching me while I was getting the equipment ready to do the show, and I've been pondering
what must that animal think, you know, when he watches us do, what do the dogs think when
they watch us do all these things that we do?
Are they thinking, gosh, if I had hands, I'd, you know, I think what, if they think like
that at all, they'd go, if I had hands, I'd use them all the time, too, but I sure wouldn't
be using them for that.
That looks pretty boring.
But, friends, it isn't boring anymore, and nor ever again, because it is this show.
Hi.
Very funny.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Now we're heading into the sexual or gonadial area of the Doug Smith brain.
No, not that brain, not his.
As you can see, it has some similarity to the previous portions of the brain and the typewriter.
But the enormous stamina of this human.
Saying, hey, hey.
Yes, that's all the trigger the Smith brain needs to get an enormous rise.
Can I say something?
This show is our only method of communication.
Communicating with you Earth people.
In hopes that in the storm of Babel, you will understand the basic reality of our method.
And apprehend that we are not simply a comedy group or a humorous exercise.
But actually the emissaries of a distant civilization which only wishes to confer its own understanding upon the citizens of your rather backward planet.
We thank you for listening.
How do they do it?
Well, like this.
Put that in like this.
Oh, no, not like that.
And like this.
Ouch, that hurts.
No, cut it out.
And like this.
Oh, hey.
Yes, you'll see us.
The Boeing.
Inflamed in glory.
Trailing clouds of glory.
When you hear that Boeing, friends, that means it's time for the show to begin.
Yes, that's our aura.
What, radio guys?
Yes, I think so.
You can relax and enjoy this quality product.
Secure in the knowledge that it has been specially designed.
Specially created for the lover of fine things and the man of good taste.
Oh, sorry.
You can edit that out, can't you?
Anything.
As the final day grows closer,
you may...
you may find yourself changing.
Not just your mind, but your body, too.
You may find hair growing in strange places.
Between your teeth.
Under your fingernails.
Yes.
Even from your face.
You may find things other than hair growing out of your body.
You may start to develop new orifices and senses.
Eyes may sprout from inside your ears.
And you may learn to listen with your tongue.
It's all part of the all.
One sense, one pipe, one grin.
And Bob is coming or kill me.
Just accept.
Just accept it.
Glory in the new flesh.
The new flesh of Bob.
Yeah, that's made from the infinity tree.
They cut that tree down once.
And every time you use any piece of wood from the infinity tree,
you can just use it over and over and over again.
I think Bob's pipe is actually made from that tree.
It is the very center shaft of the tree
was made into the shank of Bob's one true pipe.
Oh, my God.
Which then took root in the upper part of the tree.
Which is part of Bob's mouth and grown in with mighty roots
that go all the way down to Bob's toes
and deep to the back of his brain to yank that pipe loose from Bob's mouth
would be to pull all of his entrails, his head, his brains, everything out of his mouth.
What I find interesting is the most interesting about Bob.
Superstructure is how his bones are really more like Lincoln logs.
Well, you know, they said that while he was doing his gig, doing the presidential papers,
as Mr. Lincoln when he was doing that three-week scene on Broadway and stuff like that.
They said that parts of his body actually came, just started coming off of him on stage.
Bob partakes of the Lincoln log.
He is like the Mr. Potato Head of America.
He is, and his house is like Candyland.
And his business is like Monopoly.
And his sex acts are like Twister.
And his backyard is like Fort Apache.
I like that bathroom he's got that's like Parcheesi.
His bathroom is like the Flintstones Village kit.
And his face is like an old football turned inside out.
What about his kitchen?
Oh, that's Connie's kitchen.
It's like a creepy crawler set.
Ooh.
You know that infinite tree?
Connie's kitchen is like Barbie's dream kitchen house.
And does the infinite tree grow in their backyard?
The great tree of Gnosis.
The tree Ouroboros which bites its own root and grows in an ever circular pattern as Bob smokes himself.
A tree of infinity grows inside a tree of infinity.
And that's where the hoop snakes dance and sing their song around that tree.
Exactly.
And they dance around and roll around Bob as he sets his foot into his pipe.
And kills.
And sets fire to his shoe and begins to smoke.
Die!
Until his foot is smoked.
And then his stump of his leg.
And then his other leg he smokes.
And soon he's down up to his chest inside his own pipe.
Smoking himself away.
Finally only his lips are left to suck until even they are sucked by themselves into themselves through the pipe.
And only...
There's nothing left but the smoke of Bob and the pipe.
And on that moment the show will end.
They call a clown, they call a sandman.
But what about Bob's evil twin Jesse?
Did you go to chop that tree of infinity down?
It's right because then the pipe becomes not unlike a pencil sharpener.
And the pipe can actually expand and cover the head.
And twist around and around and around.
And actually sculpt.
Living...
Living sculpture out of the head of the bad Bob.
And make the bad Bob back into a good Bob.
It can be done with just a little bit of willpower.
If only everyone in the radio audience would clap their hands and believe in the good Bob.
And the bad Bob...
I love the bad Bob.
I love the good Bob.
I really believe.
Make the pipe spin like a razor.
And carve the...
Carve the face back.
And it happens.
It happens every time, friends.
Friends.
But it won't happen again unless you call.
If you can hear the voice here of Bleepo, of Ivan, of Princess Wee, of Lonesome, and myself.
You need to be calling to keep this ministry on the air.
It's your last chance.
Share your love.
Share your hate.
But share it.
Whatever you got, share it with us.
You want to speed?
All of us.
We love this to you every Thursday night.
Don't be like one of them lonely old Mexican fellows dipping his hand down that pumpkin for them sheets he's going to roast up to eat with his tequilas.
And find a rabid squirrel there.
A sex god waits your call at 687.
And as you talk to these gods, you will become as the gods.
6900.
For your generous contribution helps to keep this ministry on the air.
And keep the gods rolling.
As unto a god.
As gods.
Are born and reborn and die.
So will you be on Valhalla.
With a baseball hat of black.
And a hat of black and green.
You can be as unto a god.
You may be god number one.
You are as close to a god as you will ever be.
On WCSB.
Out of this world.
One.
Own.
Beauty.
The baby.
CHAR conjugate for Cileca.
Dis überhaupt au point.
All па firmly и anticlimax,
нич eg по PI والьюț ağ案 عل ego,
ни vendo pas
Who killed Bob?
By, uh, Anus Presley.
Yes, uh, from Denmark.
Actually, the late Anus Presley.
The late Sphere Christensen.
Also known as Reverend Godzilla Bloat.
Oop!
He died.
They do that.
You know, them subgeniuses do.
Cary Thornley died.
The founder of Discordianism.
One of the co-founders of Discordianism died about a week ago.
A week and a half ago.
My time.
Twelve.
I don't know.
I'll, I'll...
Hmm.
Friends, we'll, uh,
we'll say more about that presently here.
What else were we listening to?
There at the beginning, a, uh,
a long intro barrage,
mega intro of some old Hour of Slack and KPFA,
the Puzzling Evidence Dr. Howell,
Gary DeBrogfran stuff.
Sort of a mega intro.
Uh, Friday Jones,
Long Live Bob's New Flesh
with Joe Satriani in the background.
And then the rest of that, of course,
was all Einstein's Secret Orchestra radio,
uh, from, uh, November 13th.
They play the Infinity,
the Tree of Bob,
and I think there were, uh, credits on that.
And here are the Jeffros,
they're in the background honking away here on We Be Kings.
Uh, and, uh,
uh,
is it, uh,
is it still Christmas?
Or, uh,
The doll that stands up.
She's new.
From Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys.
We have to buy,
the marketing scheme for children's toys.
Skull Farmers.
Little wind-up bobs.
Hundreds of little bobs.
Each whispering their messages
in the night.
Death of little children as they sleep.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Instagram search
Or add to youropinion
all my goodness
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
All rights reserved
This video was made possible
Thank you for watching
should Zak was saying
goodbye
and on your U come back
and on your vr
ALILY
GPS
live
with music
Uh, yeah, street friends... I better back off... Sorry about that mean...
to Yukon Jack, dear friends.
Yukon Jack there in the background.
And let's get everything all set here, friends.
So I have a question, Mr. and Mrs. America.
Did you ever lie about cheating on your spouse?
Now, I'm asking you personally, okay?
You, the listener, the individual listener,
who I trust is a fellow American citizen.
Did you ever lie about cheating on your spouse?
Before you answer, it is my duty to inform you
that if you lie about it, we're going to find out
and you're going to lose your job and probably go to jail.
And if you tell the truth about your lie
and we find out that you lied to us
about cheating on your spouse,
you're going to lose your job and probably go to jail.
That said, now please feel quite free to answer the question.
A simple yes.
Yes or no would suffice.
Friends, so is Christmas over yet?
Well, it is.
It is after this Christmas, dear friends,
because this is Earth's last Christmas before...
It's Earth's last X-mas before X-est-mas, my friends.
It's X-est-mas, July 5th, 1999.
It's X-day.
Dos Equis.
Call us religious nuts, man.
Hell yeah.
Go ahead.
We're nuts about Bob.
And before it's all said and done,
I promise you we'll make the Jehovah's Witnesses
and the Scientologists and the Branch Davidians
look sane, normal, and laid back by comparison.
Praise, praise, praise that man, Bob.
And, oh, I guess I better...
Well, I guess it's the last Christmas for...
Carrie Thornley, too.
Here's the news of genius news here, dear friends.
This was posted on alt.slack by Reverend P. Kitty
of the Order of Malkavian-Dobzian.
And this is not a joke, by the way.
Carrie Thornley, also known as Omar Kayam Ravenhurst
and Ho Chi Zin, co-author of the Principia Discordia,
died Saturday.
He went into cardiac arrest after an extended illness
at Crawford Long Hospital in Atlanta, Georgia.
Services will be private.
By the way, this was dated November 30th.
So I guess that would mean that Carrie died in late November.
Visiting with friends not long before the end,
he said he felt, quote,
like a tired child home from a very wild circus, unquote,
alluding to his favorite passage
from the Principia penned by his co-author,
Malaclips the Younger, Greg Hill.
Quote,
And so it is that we, as men, do not exist until we do.
And then it is that we play with our world of existent things
and order and disorder them.
And so it shall be that nonexistence
shall take us back from existence
and that nameless spirituality shall return to void
like a...
tired child home from a very wild circus.
There is a Carrie Thornley website that will be maintained
and will soon include the text of his newest book,
Confession to Conspiracy to Assassinate JFK.
That is at...
Oh, this is a long one, friends.
www.sondralondon.com
slash new slash Thornley
slash...
thornley.html
If you have a tape deck, then you got that.
But it's at www.sondralondon.com
S-O-N-D-R-A-L-O-N-D-O-N
One word.
sondralondon.com
And that's the news about Carrie Thornley.
We'll see St. Carrie Thornley on the other side
if somebody there remembers to flip the tape.
Carrie was actually one of the most prolific contributors
to the...
to the subgenius material in the 80s that there was.
If you look at our old stark fists and our books,
there's always one piece by Carrie Thornley.
There was almost...
That was like, you know,
he sent enough stuff for there to be 10.
Anyway, two weeks ago,
Fringeware in Austin, Texas,
sponsored a Robert Anton Wilson rant
and a small subgenius devival.
And I was the A.V. boy.
And take...
I did the intro for Pope Bob.
And Pope Bob Anton Wilson gave a wonderful little history
of the Discordian religion
and of Carrie Thornley,
which I will play after this message on side two.
Thank you.
Incidentally, this music in the background
is from Dawn of the Dead...
No, Day of the Dead.
Okay.
No, Dawn of the Dead, the second one,
by Goblin.
Mm.
So I go around with a little rubber stamp now
that says, uh...
that says, uh, NASA-Soviet...
Racist NASA-Soviet coup.
I've got such a problem in communications anymore
that people think that I'm advocating a racist
NASA-Soviet coup.
Uh-uh.
So how did you find subgenius?
Uh, Camden...
Camden Benares gave me some stuff.
And he says, this is something like
the 12 famous Buddha minds.
And one way or another, he implied that.
I said, all right, far out.
And I went back to Tampa.
Camden lives in Southern California.
He's an author of Zen Without Zen Masters.
I went back to Tampa, and I...
wrote him an insane letter, of course.
And we began an insane correspondence.
And I suggested that we integrate
Discordian theology with subgenius theology.
Subgenius, yes.
So you found a relationship, I'm sure,
between the Discordians.
Is it a church or a foundation?
It can probably be anything,
because to join the Discordian society...
It can be a dinner.
You have to make five copies of your application
and nail one of them to a telephone pole
and throw one of them in a garbage can
and drop another one of them in a mailbox or something.
So there's never been any situation
where anybody had to tell anybody
that they were joining the Discordian society.
Right.
Well, and the number is 84844.
To speak to puzzling evidence.
Mankar Feld, Kerry Thornley, and Bob DeNelson.
Anyway, the Discordian revelation came
by way of two fellows named
Kerry Thornley and Gregory Hill.
Kerry took the religious name Ho Chi Zen,
and Greg took the religious name
Malaklips the Younger.
And when I discovered the way
to become a Discordian pope
was to appoint yourself,
I became a Discordian.
I became Mordecai the Foul.
And then we got Fang the Unwashed
and Anrak the Backwoods
and Lady Yell, Anarchist Bitch.
A title which was given to her by Eldridge Cleaver
during a political discussion.
Really.
And the numbers have been increasing steadily.
Greg Hill had cards printed up
saying the bearer of this card
is a genuine and authorized pope,
so please treat them right.
Good forever guaranteed by the House of Apostles of Arise.
Amen.
On the site of the beautiful future
San Andreas Canyon, San Francisco, California.
And then I moved to Ireland,
and while I was there,
I heard on Irish TV that the pope had announced
that bishops can give indulgences over television,
which is an entirely new diploma
for the Catholic Church.
It shows they're not still stuck
in the 13th century in all respects,
just in 99% of their attitudes.
And this is a very important moment.
There's a lot of controversy in the Irish newspapers.
And one letter writer asked,
if you made a video tape of the bishop giving the indulgence,
and you played it over and over,
would you get perpetual indulgence?
Which is a question worthy seeing.
Irish atheists who have all been educated by Jesuits,
so they think of, nobody but an atheist
who has been educated by Jesuits
would even think of asking such a question.
Like one year when I was living in Ireland,
the bishop sent out a pastoral letter
to be read from all pulpits on God's plan for the family.
And another atheist who'd been educated by Jesuits,
I assume, wrote in a letter asking,
will the bishop clarify with what degree of metaphor
a timeless being can be said to have plans?
There's a great advantage in a Jesuit education.
Just think of some of the great minds produced by Jesuits,
education, the Marquis de Sade,
the old Tertre, Diderot.
Diderot, the great encyclopedist who said,
mankind will be free when the last priest is killed
by the last brick falling from the last church.
Victor Hugo, James Joyce.
Jesuit education has a really great background for
if you really want to have a lot of fun with religion.
Anyway, I decided if bishops can do it,
I'd do it.
And if I could do indulgences over television,
I could do pontifications on the radio.
I appear on radio much more often than I appear on television.
And when Greg was handing out cards,
the number of discordant popes was increasing slowly
from the hundreds to the thousands.
But when I started doing pontifications on the radio,
the numbers started increasing in the millions.
I was on one show in England,
had an estimated listenership of four million.
And I made them all popes.
We had four million popes in one minute.
And whenever I get in front of a radio,
the number of discordant popes now must run to
20 to 30 million at least, probably higher than that.
And we won't stop until every man, woman, child,
and other entity on this planet has become a pope.
Let's imitate Ivan's style for a minute.
Why the fuck should that old queen of the Vatican
be the only pope?
As a matter of fact, I sent the pope a pope card
so he could be a scholar.
I also sent the pope card to the anti-pope in southern France.
So he's both a pope and an anti-pope at the same time.
And if he writes to Douglas Hofstadter,
he'll get into the next book on strange loops.
I'm not an anti-pope at the same time.
I also sent a pope card to Ian Paisley,
the leader of the extremist fringe of the Protestant...
I think it was...
the Ulster Freedom Fighters in Northern Ireland.
His slogan was,
No pope in Northern Ireland.
So I sent him a pope card.
He didn't even have a thesis.
He believed in Northern Ireland.
Somebody else, he died.
Did he die since I sent him that card?
Maybe the card put him in a state of cardiac arrest
and he found out he was a pope, too.
Pardon me while I have a little fruit juice.
Ah, man, that's good fruit juice.
Oh, my God!
Good job!
Could we talk about Einstein?
Can we talk about Einstein?
Do you like talks like that?
Yes, my cat has an important message for us.
Yes.
Yes?
Wait a minute, can you come here?
Listen.
Listen, come here.
Tell the people of Earth
everything that must be known right now.
Okay.
Send one dollar to...
No, no, no.
Don't tell them to send it anywhere.
Just burn one dollar right now.
Burning a dollar, that's right.
For kitties, for all the kitties
suffering in the labs of
DNA.
For all the kitties in the world.
They must think and react faster.
They'll pull out the most furious scams
in the planet's history
and fool nearly all of the people
all of the time.
Build your own rocket ship.
Yeah, well, that's true.
I don't think he will.
I've got it.
What can you do me?
I love you.
I see.
Your twins.
Rain, rain.
Eagle in space.
Go ahead, cake me.
My people will follow you.
On next day, a vanishing race.
Ah, yes.
As you see them running off into the hills,
you can notice the race vanishing off into the hills.
Well, listen, I'm at my friend's house,
and I'm using her phone.
Well, that's nice of her.
Yes, it is.
That's really nice of her.
Well, we gotta cut out of here anyway, Mr. Bleep.
Nuts, we have to bleep out, Bleep rabbit.
Hey, you coming in?
We must get off.
HH, hh, hh, hh, HH.
HH, hh, hh, hh, we must get off.
Hh, hh, hh, hh, we must get off.
The Aussie CrossFit Team
contradicted its words.
I was thinking about,
I was, I gotta do this, I gotta do this.
I mean, I can't take none of this no more.
The fear was justified when he made his next move.
I had come to a conclusion in my mind.
Why should I just keep living like this?
She tried to keep him calm.
I just wanted the police to know, hey, y'all can do what you want to do.
I'm tired.
She had to change his mind.
Fatigue and tension hurt her.
She set in.
So it came down to...
Reality.
It, it, it, it, it.
Help me now!
I, I, I mean, I can't take reality.
Why should I just keep living like this?
I will do it.
Uh.
Yeah.
Uh, I don't have it.
Help!
No more.
I need help.
Save the fire, Ben.
Yeah, baby.
Lucky, lucky.
Oh, God!
Oh.
Shoot some mothers in the head.
Poor Bob.
Gotta be a logical explanation for this.
Shut up!
Brothers in business, I can take this man.
I won't be surprised if I have to.
Let's go. Down the stairs.
Yeah.
Come on, let's talk about it.
What I'm talking about down here.
When the men come home and say they're tired,
wait until they get ready to go pop in the shower or the tub.
Tia.
Um, he wants a woman with boobs so big it's unreal.
I'm not gonna hurt you right now, okay?
Get in there with him.
I need you to calm down.
Ask him to come here.
You like that? Do I have to tell him?
Get in there with him.
Help me.
Pull up there with you.
Help me now.
Get in there with him.
Help me.
Pull up there with you.
You like that? Do I have to tell him?
Help me now.
Go ahead.
Help.
Oh, yeah.
Pull up there with you.
Help.
I need help.
Help me.
You like that dude?
Help me now.
Get in there with him.
Ch-ch-ch-ch.
Help me.
Oh, yeah.
Help.
I need help.
Pull up there with you.
She tried to keep him calm.
I mean, all I was thinking about was...
Ch-ch-ch-ch-chia.
Oh, yeah.
Get in there with him.
Watch it.
So we came down to...
Ch-ch-ch-ch-chia.
Yeah.
Oh.
We don't know.
What?
That hurt.
Build your own rocket ship.
Come in, little ones.
Come swim in the pool of rocket fuel.
Godspeed.
alk sauce
On the first day,
The gods created a just prism.
And on the second day
The gods created malice.
On the third day, the gods created Wally Sherrod.
On the fourth day, the gods created Scott Arpenter.
On the fifth day, the gods created Deke Slayton.
On the sixth day, the gods created Gordon Cooper.
And on the seventh day, the gods created John Glenn.
I have a big spiral galaxy on me.
Hey, man, here I'll show you.
I start at the center or go from the outside inwards.
That's the fun about the spiral galaxies.
The cluster galaxies, you just got to go at it.
Yeah.
But spiral galaxies, yeah.
I like to start on the outer rim and go in towards the center
because then there's that black hole at the very center.
And just when you think you've snorted everything up,
it snorted.
It snorts you.
We used to call that the goofball.
We called it the thunder, thunder.
I can't pronounce the last part of the word on the air.
Yeah, the black hole at the middle.
That's the goofball.
That's where you really go for a ride.
You snort that black hole, man.
The killer death hole.
I've known a lot of people that got those deviated septums
from snorting too many of the goofball black holes.
I know a guy who had to have all of his septums replaced
with titanium.
He had to have titanium steel so he could keep snorting black holes.
Yeah.
Even the neutron matter isn't as heavy, man,
as the black hole at the middle.
Men of science constantly search the infinitesimal corners
of our solar system, seeking new discoveries,
hoping to better understand the laws of the universe.
If it ever occurred to you, you might have totally lost your mind.
There was a rumor about a tumor.
Or was it a transistor?
Yeah, it was a transistor.
It was a subcutaneous spring wave generator.
Well, that of course touches on right, mind control, which is.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Do you think Oswald was a, was it a slice in the pie of mind control?
I think I'm an android.
I think Oswald was an android.
I think we're both mind, we were both mind control victims.
I think there were, I think what happened was like they captured a bunch
of German scientists after the war that were in the mind control.
CIA got a bunch of them and KGB got a bunch of them.
I think they began comparing notes and they began to say, my God, this is,
this is heavier than atomic power.
What are we going to do with it?
No matter where.
I think they began experimenting on selected subjects.
I think I was one of them.
I think Oswald was one of them.
I began to experience audio hallucinations when I was in that outfit with Oswald.
They went on for the rest of my life for about ten years.
I thought they were, I thought they were spiritual.
I thought they were spiritual experiences.
I got into Edgar Cayce and I was always writing down my dreams and they were always coming
true and it was like I just got so much into that world view that I couldn't imagine a
materialist universe any longer.
And then one day I began to find out more and more about mind control.
There's a great book about it, Operation Mind Control by W.H.
Boart.
That, uh, I think it's called, uh, I think it's called, uh, I think it's called, uh,
God, when I got to the chapter in that book about the assassination, about the assassinations,
there were so many connections with my life, so many things that overlapped with people
that I'd met or that I'd somehow had dealings with that it was like I just, the margins
were just crammed full of notes all the way, all the way through.
It was just, I just couldn't stop writing margin notes.
Yeah, I was at David Ferry's house once, et cetera.
It was just, it was, it was just.
The Discordian Society has a rather unique history among religious movements because
one of the two co-founders, Kerry Thornley, who died last week, was indicted by Jim Garrison
as one of the conspirators in the JFK assassination.
And this, this gives us a unique glamour.
What other religion in the world could claim that they may be a religious movement?
religious movement to be in charge of the Kennedy assassination.
As Charlie Manson said recently in an interview, in my day, being crazy meant something.
Now everybody's fucking crazy.
When, when Kerry was, uh, when Kerry was indicted by Garrison, I was convinced Garrison was
an unscrupulous demigod.
And I was convinced he was a good man.
Kerry a lot of encouraging letters, don't lose faith, don't lose hope, you know you're innocent, and so on.
And then after the trial fell apart and there was no evidence against Kerry and Garrison how to let him go,
two years later on an acid trip, Kerry suddenly remembered or imagined that,
well, he served in the, this is the background of the whole case why Garrison indicted him,
he served in the Marine Corps in the same regiment with Lee Harvey Oswald
at the same base in Japan from which the U-2 spy planes were launched out over Russia.
When one of those U-2 spy planes was shot down, Eisenhower personally came on television
and assured the American public it was not an American spy plane,
and then later, two days later, he had admitted he had lied.
I think that was the first time an American president really had to get up in public and admit he had lied.
That may be the beginning of the rise of popularity of conspiracy theories.
Watergate was just...
a much bigger example.
Anyway,
on an acid trip, Kerry remembered or thought he remembered or imagined or hallucinated, you can take the...
I've decided all my writings can be summarized in one sentence, just one simple sentence.
If everybody used the word maybe more often, we might all become startlingly sane.
It's just not right.
Have you ever read a theological work that said maybe Jesus is the Son of God?
Have you ever heard a Muslim say
maybe Allah wants us to kill the Jews?
The trouble is they don't have enough maybes in their vocabulary.
Everything is for sure and certain with them.
For me, everything is unsure and uncertain.
I'm confused about everything.
That's how I make my living.
I get up and share my confusion with other people.
And since almost everybody is confused these days, and since it's one of the three stages of chaos, chaos, discord, confusion, bureaucracy, and international relations, it's part of the divine plan of Our Lady that we should all be confused most of the time.
Anyway, whether Kerry, anyway, Kerry's memory, or pseudo-memory, or whatever it was, was that, well, he was in the Marine Corps.
He and Lee Harvey Oswald and several others volunteered for scientific research.
Now, we know the CIA used a lot of military people for research at that time.
They used other people, too.
This was part of the MKUltra program.
MKUltra was a top-secret program that started in the 50s and wasn't revealed until the Church Committee discovered it in the 1970s.
Senator Church had long hearings in which a lot of people came forth telling how they had their minds warped by various things the CIA did to them.
So, it was a lot of research.
There was one guy whose father committed suicide who sued the CIA and collected.
The CIA got their revenge, though.
Senator Church was not re-elected.
If you read Bob Woodward's book, Veil, you'll find there's a lot of evidence that the CIA participated in the election the next year to make sure that he wouldn't get elected.
James Jesus Angleton was thrown out of the CIA for interfering in American politics.
They're only allowed to interfere in the politics of other countries.
There's a lot of evidence.
They've been interfering in American politics, too.
They don't want us meddling in our own affairs.
How do you think the mind control perspective tied into the assassination itself?
I think that's why they had to shoot Oswald.
Because it was like the CIA didn't want the FBI to realize that they were using a Manchurian candidate to spy on them.
And that's what Oswald seemed to be.
He seemed to be spying on the FBI.
You feel...
On the FBI.
On their anti-Castro activities.
For Kennedy.
Or for the CIA.
It was supposed to be loyal to Kennedy at the time.
So hippie.
Well, that was certainly one of the best theater pieces America's ever done back in 1963.
But I don't want to know, and I don't want to talk about it.
Dig it?
It gets beyond the worry.
And it is beyond talking about it, yes.
So.
Tell us more about the Discordian.
Principalia.
The Discordian society evolved in probably 19...
Probably the summer of 1958 in a bowling alley somewhere in East Whittier, California.
Or in Santa Fe Springs, California.
Where Greg Hill and I were sitting over cups of coffee talking philosophy and talking about order and disorder.
And decided that what was needed was a deity to explain all the chaos in the universe.
And that was sort of the occultism of the early days.
The thing that we figured, I think, is sometimes a lot of people relate to the subgenius foundation the same way.
It was something like, you know, you want to evangelize, but you're not religious.
Right.
Or you want to get militant about something, but you don't feel strongly about anything.
Neonostics, you know, meganostics.
If it ever occurred to you, you might have totally lost your mind.
Bring us into bondage.
He says it straight.
They use a lot of spiritual words.
But.
Behind the scenes, they want you to live in the bondage they're living in.
No thanks.
We sometimes have to question the easy assumptions that we've all grown up with.
And sometimes facts and new information have to come along and make us shake up our thinking.
Cave men.
Cave women.
Neanderthal.
Where I come from, we have universities.
Seeds of great learning.
Where men go to become great thinkers.
And when they come out, they think deep thoughts.
And with no more brains than you have.
Everybody knows that you use many black holes to get around the speed of light.
Right.
Just sidestep it.
What?
Oh, 196,000 miles per second?
I don't think so.
Screw Einstein.
That's like, oh, yeah.
Oh, you think I'm going to slow down for those road bumps?
Yeah.
You think I'm going to follow this rule that Einstein came up with that there's a speed limit out here?
Well, he kept the secret, that one secret of how to.
He had Einstein's secret radar fuzz buster.
Mm-hmm.
So that you could outrun the speed of light.
Well, he didn't tell us.
He knew, but he did not tell us how you can add to the speed of light.
Everyone thinks it's common, you know, knowledge or something that thou shalt not add one's own speed to the speed of light.
Oh, give me a break.
Well, then how, you know, I mean, I've heard Scotty griping about how they can't quite make it to warp nine.
Right.
Which is.
That's like nine times the speed of light.
Right.
They still wouldn't be able to get from star system to star system as fast.
If they were traveling at nine times the speed of light, when they got there, they'd have to wait nine light years for the rest of their body to catch up.
Well, and every time they went back.
To earth, it would be a million years later.
Right.
There's a lot of problems with all of that.
The whole world is waiting for this will decide the fate of civilization.
All humanity, whether we live or die, may depend on what happens here.
Attention, please.
Four minutes to bomb time.
Tired of the everyday routine?
Ever dream of a life of romantic adventure?
Want to get up?
Get away from it all?
I'll buy you a start on your rocket ship.
Do you like dogs like that?
Want to take a ride?
That's what happened with the humans, too.
That many gods, but there could only be one because the reason you have to have only one is because, well, if you have more than one, someone could say, well, one of them's made up.
Well, if one of them's made up, why not all of them?
So that exposes something that they don't want to expose.
So you have to get it down to just one.
Yeah.
I'm not.
Yeah, you can't question one.
Well, it makes people real nervous, too.
And I can understand that.
There must be a God.
But I fear tomorrow I'll be crying.
Einstein's brain in that jar will not lie to you.
No.
Never.
You cannot survive outside of this shower.
Please come back.
We are only here to help you.
And I want to see my way all the way clear because I've got this much in the tank.
But you're the guy who wants us to live, not like Donald would be, but like the trolley.
I always have loved this law.
And I see this thing.
I always have.
I have.
was in fairy wonderland and quantum leap land was like around the corner it's like oh my god
you know get me the hell out of here
war of the worlds 50 foot girls 20 million miles to earth
war of the worlds 50 foot girls 20 million miles to earth friends and that's uh einstein's secret
orchestra playing in the background you're listening to the sub gene
radio ministry hour of slack a little history of the discordians and the roots of subgenius tonight
we're about to tell you how you too can help save the world so stay tuned
for all addresses and important contact information
love is the heart
he's not the answer but neither is
anything else
the human race
oh
the end of time
beginning of the end the end of time
20 million miles to earth
20 million miles
¶¶
at Fox 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That zip code again is 75214.
And trends, of course, it's always slack at subgenius.com
or www.subgenius.com.
Just type that damn word subgenius in there.
It's just all over the internet.
It's crazy stuff, kid stuff.
And we've been listening quite a bit to,
to a historic old radio broadcast,
the KPFA Berkeley subgenius,
less than an hour, more than a,
more than an hour, less than a show
with Doug Wellman, puzzling evidence,
interviewing Carrie Thornley, the late Carrie Thornley.
And also we heard Robert Anton Wilson discussing Thornley
and the CIA and the discordian religion and so forth
in Austin about, what?
Two weeks ago, December 8th, I think, or something like that,
at, sponsored by Fringeware.
And I kind of got to hear,
the only time Pope Bob cussed in that speech
was when he was imitating me.
I was honored though.
And well, friends, I guess, Earth, we must get off now.
We must get off now.
Earth, we must get off.
And you can best take the thought that is your money
and donate it to this radio station.
And then that money will once again
be transformed into thoughts.
Death to vermin.
Thoughts to money.
Money to thoughts.
Death to vermin.
vermin.
Vermin to brains.
Abundance to all.
Vermin to worms.
Worms eating into brains.
Till next week.
Brains creating money.
Keep your hat on tight.
Money creating ideas.
You're back to the wind.
Ideas creating music.
And you're back.
To the wind.
And you're sack.
Sack.
In the?
Saddle.
You're all blistering now.
We'll see you all next week, kids.
Flippo Abernathy, Reverend Ivan Stang, the princess we are doing, Lutzen.
Cowboy Dave, all entertaining.
You hear my name's Chaz.
This is ESO.
A radio.
A medium.
A blister.
Yep, they come around here a lot these days.
Back in the saddle.
Saddle back.
Back saddle.
Anyway.
Components.
I've been fighting them Indians for 900 years.
Before I was one.
Hey-ya!
I was one of them.
Or at least.
I seem to be.
But I read.
And no quotation.
In a book just yesterday.
Says if you beat everyone.
So the debts you make.
You'll have to pay.
Can you get to that?
I want to know.
I want to know if you can get to that.
Can you get to that?
Wait!"
You'll bet.
Right?
Have you been getting the money?
Mm-hmm .
Oh dear Dino's live.
I'm going to spend tomorrow at the dentist.
estas me.
Hello, gosta.
Kisses later come back, side kiss
I uh...