Where's your fish?
I beg your pardon?
Well, I don't have one at the moment.
Okay, okay.
All right, mister, just hold the fish up with your right hand.
Yeah, that's right.
Smile.
Thank you very much.
Official report.
Let me tell you, you're wrong.
You're wrong in feeling that way about...
This is too genius to be a snack.
Hold it!
Dogstown.
Is actually nothing like this.
Unless you want it to be.
This is the Sakeem.
The Sakeem.
Yes.
Sakeem.
Our...
Flack.
National present, Cheese Theater, with two of Hollywood's most distinguished citizens,
Bob and Bob.
And here is that glamorous star of radio and pictures,
Bob.
Bob, thank you, thank you.
It does feel wonderful, Bob.
Don't look now, but I think there's a plug coming.
May I? May I? May I?
Well, Bob, if it'll do you any good, I have an in with Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
I have a lady in the playpen, Doctor.
The best get, the best get, get, get, get, get, get.
Do you know what it means?
To be sure.
And make it homogenous.
Virginized.
Beauty.
Fussing.
And a fighting.
Psych.
A great actor, ladies and gentlemen, is one whose talents range in many directions.
Pretty.
Brass.
Bob and I.
Home.
Same.
Bailey Howard's hot rod beaver.
Most kids her age go for somebody like Bob.
Who's he?
An actor.
Frankly, it evades me.
I don't think...
You're not supposed to, honey.
I'll do the thinking tonight.
Why, it's...
It's...
It's foam.
I thought you were...
You certainly are.
Really?
In just about a minute, you're going to hear Bob, who I'm sure will have a laugh or two
up his sleeve.
So listen.
A pint a day for adults and a quart a day for children.
Finzing.
Carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot,
carrot, carrot.
Thank you, wrecking crew.
And now, folks, here he is, the star of screen, radio, television, vaudeville cafes, personal
appearances, and fat boy for the Cleveland Indians, Bob...
I love that head.
It was a good ship lollipop.
Everyone aboard was a sucker.
Oh.
I wonder what time it is.
My rubber sheep is afloat.
Dab, dab, dab, dab, dab.
Next Thursday night, we'll be back with Dick.
So try and be with us.
Keep listening.
Bob may soon be seen in the new Paramount picture, Paleface.
You want to join the club?
Sure.
Well, you got to get undressed up there on the diving board.
So everybody gets to watch.
I participated in the...
Oh!
...baptism ceremony for the first time this year.
Oh, you hit my knee with that door.
Just to help out Reverend Stang, if you understand.
In previous years, I'd been warned away from it.
They said, don't go there.
Don't have anything to do with that.
I don't know why.
But this time, I thought, I really want to help.
For some reason, I can't remember.
It's all blurry.
I've been the Burning Man since then.
But at any rate, I went there, and we did indeed, with the total immersion, bring many
quivering naked bobbies.
To a full understanding of their new life as subgeniuses.
Many other mammals also show these patterns of aggression, especially when females live
in burrows that are costly to dig.
Edgar Rice Burrow.
Their housing is so valuable, they often pass it along to their daughters and will wound
any unrelated young females that try to establish themselves within the area.
They had a giant object which they continued to fling up into the sky, and as it was practically
isostatic in its weightlessness, they often succeeded.
Yet, aberrant breezes would blow it down to earth again.
But, at Burning Man, on the other hand, there was a perfectly formed flying saucer that
did the same thing.
If you photographed it, and unfortunately, I never had a camera with me, if you photographed
it, it would look like the most realistic flying saucer photo ever taken, because it
was actually there.
It was actually there.
A real flying saucer.
It was inflated, but it was so well-shaped that it was exactly like a science-fictional
flying saucer, of great size and silver, so it would float around.
Okay, let's get ready to leave now.
We've got to get in the car.
We're going to be taking a ride down to the docks, Dr. Howe.
There was a kite that looked like a computer cursor, a computer cursor which appeared to
move around in the sky.
Please ignore the movement of the vehicle.
Not to mention lasers, balloons.
You can...
Other objects.
You can remove the blindfold now.
And the cigarette.
I'll have one of those.
I'll have one of those, too.
I want the one you have, though.
Rewriting the Geneva Convergence.
Can I have the one you already have?
I don't want just any cigarette.
I want the one you have.
That specific one.
From objects which might force the soul to abate her feeling.
Can I have that one now?
Rendered more compassion.
Please give it to me.
Thank you.
If you don't give it to me, I'll step on your toe.
Because occasions rise so often that demand such sacrifice.
So take it.
Here it is.
Thank you.
More skillful.
You get it all slobbery.
It's all wet and slimy on the end.
What happened?
More able to endure.
You seem to...
Okay, look out.
As more endure suffering and distress than...
Oh, Jimmy, what have I let you in for?
Stay where you are.
Don't move, Ellen.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Keep quiet.
Ellen?
Who is it?
Conspiracy.
What's that?
We don't know.
Huh?
His head is still spinning.
He's not responsible for what he says.
Conspiracy to commit...
The Self-Genius.
Power of Swatch.
Right now.
We've got to get out of here.
can't wait for the night!
I love you!
We'll get you back!
keep it down!
We need to help you!
He saved
9-year-olds that kick you in the shin
Toilet bowls with droplets on the rim
Leisure suits with polyester trim
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Pepperoni pizza by the slice
Ronald Reagan's gonads in a vice
Chinese food is nice with a bowl of rice
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Shopping malls on Sunday afternoon
Watching Grandma vomit with a spoon
Margaret Thatcher squatting on a broom
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Puffy skin infections turning red
Making Phyllis Lafley give you head
Hamsters that are dead rotting in your bed
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Let our age equal pumpkin
Flim
Schmegma
Sandwiches with moldy wonder bread
Oral sex with Ellie Mae and James
Telling children that their mother's dead
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Scrambling on your eyeball with a pen
Giving gonorrhea to a friend
Scraping at a scab with a grill of pad
And an orange is nothing but
Yes, an orange is nothing but
Yes, an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
I'm Dexy. I'll be your guide for the next half hour.
Divorce? Divorce?
Um.
White paper.
Human augmentation.
Flesh out this idea.
Excited.
Changing into the cat man.
Titillated. Titillated.
You know, the augmentation of human animals.
I'm looking at the spread.
Reinvent the wheel.
Post-humanist.
Post-biological.
Into that whole
Primate neural grafting.
It's actually out there.
Allow.
Um.
Bonobos.
Bonobo.
They watch television.
There's a little tweak here, a little tweak there,
and suddenly you've got proto-humanish kind of an entity.
Bonobo desires.
So everything from increasing our, um,
Doing.
Wood.
But.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Veil of ignorance.
So there you are.
In the veil of ignorance.
A loosey-goosey.
Maybe even fish.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Loosey-goosey.
Uh, to Bono Persons.
Neural modification could be quite, uh, destructive.
And, and harmful.
Group sex.
Um.
Going to prison quite often.
I don't think so.
Because we are still very little removed from our paleo,
paleolithic ancestry.
Sexy, sexy.
And I hope to meet you in a sexy primate neural grafting.
My baby.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Now that's what I want.
That's right.
Slack bangers, friends.
Uh, uh, well.
Uh, neural primate grafting, uh, was by Nor El Pref.
And Rudy Schwartz Project did.
And orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin.
And now back to, uh, the 9X Day drill, which by the way,
is held at a campground.
There is a raccoon out here who is known
for stealing pornography and liquor.
Oh.
And cigars and things.
It'll leave the occasional sack of sugar.
But, uh, yeah, he's legendary around these parts.
Don't worry about the bears at night.
There are hardly any of them.
And unless they're rabid, they probably won't do any more
than sniff at your feet.
Your feet.
Reverend Rosna at the X Day campground,
recorded these, uh, bullfrogs at the camp pond.
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop,
bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop...
bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop...
bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
Thank you.
How about you?
Yes, yes, yes, friends.
The Leonard Skinner Memorial
Tractor Pull
by the Rudy Schwartz Project
from
schwartztone.com
And before that,
friends, Reverend Norell Preff
of norellpreff.com
captured the Vintage Bob Show.
Our new intro
was by Popes Lilith
von Fraumensch.
Also, thanks to Just John
and Fernanda Nandi-Liemer
for the
openings.
This is Hour of Slack
number 1065.
X-Day meets Burning Man.
Dr. Hal was at both events
and has many tales to tell
and I have recordings to play
from the subgenius event,
the 9X Day Drill.
But before we go into that,
here's Fat Harry White.
Mmm, baby.
Slippin' into my new skin-tight
joppers for you, honey.
And dressin' up for the ladies
for the love.
Come over here, Maureen.
Hey!
I'm talking about dressing up
like it reminds me of when I worked
at Slack's R.O.'s.
You know, right?
Next to Jessop's, the grocer's.
It was the first time I met Foxy Fionna,
my very sexy lady friend.
Never forget it.
She walked up to me at the counter
and in a very sexy voice,
asked me what I had to offer
in the trouser department.
Apparently, she wanted to buy
some flared crimpling slacks
for her long-legged father's birthday.
Very partial to bright colours, it was.
Anyway, I told her I was almost certain
I'd have something with a good length
that would satisfy her
and asked her to follow me upstairs.
Well, after going through me trousers,
she surprised me by saying
that she really fancied
the large pink pair that I had.
Not only did they hang well,
but she thought they looked really attractive.
Particularly the way they swung about loosely
when I walked.
Mind you, she wasn't too sure of the size at first
and had me lay them out on the counter
so she could measure them up.
She also ran her fingers admiringly down the crease.
Well, she decided to go for it,
asked me how much.
I says three and a half quid.
She asked me rather cheekily
if I would go down.
Well, you know, thought about it,
long and hard,
decided to drop them for her,
which I did there and then.
What fun, backwards and forwards,
over the counter.
A good bit of haggling,
and no mistake.
And I was thinking about this, right,
because I've been back to that shop,
because the weather's beginning to change a bit,
getting a bit parker, isn't it?
Well, I tell you what,
I went out the other morning
and me buns was so cold
it started to change colour.
I'm not kidding,
when me very sexy lady friend,
sexy Sam,
saw me coming towards her,
me purple hair sticking out me coat,
she told me to get it covered immediately.
So I said,
I'm going to the shop
to buy a hat, a fur one.
Well, I said,
well, when I got there,
you know,
I asked sexy Salea,
the very sexy lady friend hat assistant,
to show me what she had,
you know, in a fur department.
She said she'd be only too pleased
to show me what she had downstairs,
and led me to the basement,
where I could see everything she had
on full display.
I tell you what,
you wouldn't believe how much she had.
She had every kind of fur
that you could imagine.
I was going to go for a fox fur,
but as soon as sexy Salea said
she had a particularly nice beaver
that I might be interested in,
immediately changed me mind.
Well, you know,
after getting it out for me,
I've got to say,
I've never seen such a big bushy one like it
in all my life.
Well, when I asked her if she could,
you know,
try it on for size,
she said,
I might find it a bit tight at first,
but if I buried my head deep enough,
then it should stretch a little
to accommodate me fully.
Tell you what,
she weren't wrong,
and when I looked at it in the mirror,
you know,
sideways on,
I could see it had slid in perfectly.
Well, you know,
after that,
she then said
she'd summat round the back
that I might be interested in,
led me into the storeroom
to show me a selection of gloves
that had just arrived.
Well, I was obviously interested,
but as I didn't know what size I was,
I had to get
sexist Salea to measure my hand.
Well, after asking me to,
you know,
give her a finger,
which I promptly did,
she then asked me to stick my thumb up,
no problem at all.
Within minutes,
she declared
that she was holding her measuring cup
and the tape
that I was extra,
extra large.
Well, then she had to take a phone call,
but while she was on the mobile,
I took the opportunity
of rummaging in her box
until I found the perfect fit,
and when I withdrew,
sexist Salea nodded
appreciatively
at my great big leathery pair.
Dressing up
for the ladies, yeah.
Am I looking in the mood for love?
A fat, hairy white
can be your friend,
see myspace.com
slash fat hairy white.
What a man.
Speaking of men,
Dr. Howell performed at Burning Man,
as he explains to Governor Rocknar
on Puzzling Evidence.
I think that was Burning Man.
Oh, it burned like you wouldn't believe,
and off went a bunch of firecrackers.
See, they had a special deal
where they built this big, fake,
phony upper Egyptian temple,
and the man was sort of half sunk in it,
but then when the time came,
he rose up on his hydraulic pedestal
higher and higher,
towering over the whole thing
before he burst into flame, yes.
Did people cheer like crazy people?
Cheering like crazy people,
or were they cheering like normal people?
Same crazy people walk widdershins
around the burning wicker man.
And so they were up there doing that.
Listening to this show tonight,
it makes me feel like I've been there.
I've been there,
in a precision bench lathe.
We've all been there.
We'll all be there.
I hope so.
But do you feel like you've been through
57 years of specializing exclusively
in lathe manufacturing?
Incredible special effect.
My gosh, it's incredible what they can do.
I just love it.
At Dobbsco,
it means more value
for their lathe purchasing dollars.
What's going on here?
Which end is open?
There we go.
I know we're trying to push our lathes
on everybody,
but we've got these two left in stock,
and we're trying to do a closeout.
What's new in metalworking,
you might say?
I'm just trying to do a show.
Well, a whole lot of welding.
In Rocknar, where did you go?
I'm right here.
Well, you're just sitting back there.
I'm just daydreaming
that I'm on the volcanic dust desert.
Hail Rocknar.
Yes.
It's not volcanic.
It's the bottom of a lake.
It's one of the worst places humans can go.
Yes, it's a lake bottom,
and the dust is diatomaceous.
Earth.
Yeah, the place is like the...
But you say Earth.
It's so fine.
It's terrible for your lungs,
and it's terrible for your bare feet.
It's terrible for your machinery.
You're walking around in the sunlight,
which is being reflected almost 90% off that plane.
Incredibly destructive.
It's like being in another planet.
It's nice to come back.
That's one of the more interesting things
about the event.
It's the worst place on Earth.
No, it's not that bad,
but it's the worst place
you can have a huge event event.
You should go out there on your birthday.
Unlike X-Day,
where they put on a nice, healthy, wet bean area.
You know, what do you think it's worth it when you do it?
I must say that the ice cold cans of Ale 8,
which I had along with me,
really helped things.
Really came in handy.
Yes, they did,
and even Chicken drank one.
Oh, how did he like it?
I'm afraid not much, but he's a...
He doesn't like much of anything.
Well, perhaps that's so.
Anyway.
Faster than a speeding building.
Look, it's a bird.
And now, the adventures of Super Delicious Cereal.
Say now.
Well, thank God he didn't...
Ah, shut up!
Lemur and then Sawdee made those noises,
but now Dr. Fox,
the phylo-drumming describes married life.
Look at this.
It's the heaviest rack you ever saw.
Hubba hubba.
It has the greatest capacity and the smallest floor space.
Haven't seen a sight like that since I was weaned.
Stay calm now, Dr. Howell.
Stay calm.
What exists in the depths of the earth?
Hold yourself back.
In the chthonic darkness,
some say they come out at night
to wreak hideous vengeance on the living.
Dr. Howell permits at any angle,
at any height,
horizontally or even vertically.
I, Dr. Howell and Owl,
will exorcise these evil spirits from your body.
And there's Dr. Howell as he goes about.
He's breaking down each job into fairly simple components.
If you are a subject...
Yes, he's getting the requirements from all the users,
and he's writing down the sequence to perform the operations.
Each of the steps are operations that Dr. Howell is devising.
The worker will perform,
and accompany each step with a brief notation
of the essential things to be remembered about how to do that next step.
We'll call these key points.
I call them key points in your life.
Dr. Howell's development is available for all new-bile interns who...
And with this breakdown,
we will begin instruction as soon as possible.
Well, as soon as the...
Upon receipt of the appropriate funds.
The facilities have to be available, yes,
and the funds transfer must be made.
The resources have to be available for acquisition...
The waiver is necessary for mutual protection to sign...
Immediately upon implementation and completion...
It is possible that sometimes,
after receiving the treatment...
Of the appropriate paperwork...
The patient is...
Once the budget is approved,
we'll be on our way.
Less than satisfied characters...
We have to have the appropriate signatures...
Mere honesty stimulates us to mention this...
And then we will dispense and implement in three hardness grades,
seven sizes, and two weights...
And thus the presence of the prenup,
or as you might call it, the waiver,
which the young subgenius ed must sign before beginning the treatment.
And now the drama will increase for the next 15 seconds...
And believe me, I had no idea that I would be forced into this role,
but at what you may call it...
Don't say it!
Ivanstock or Doc's Day or whatever it is,
I found that I was required to fill a role I had not thought myself to...
Was that one where you got first night privileges?
And first morning, and first middle of the day.
Ah, yes.
Let me ask you one thing then.
Is female choice of honest male advertisement adaptive
under conditions of promiscuous political...
...homily, polygamy, or...
Boy, I don't know.
...monogamy?
You're driving me crazy.
You're coming and going.
What can I say?
But at Exstock, it was an interesting time,
because new people were being brought in,
and certain ancient rituals had to be revised to accommodate them.
What could be the source of this bizarre sexual behavior?
Well, it's only human.
I mean, why do you call it bizarre?
Because it's like nature taking its course, kind of.
See?
Not bizarre at all.
Now, others, of course, require a certain amount of what we call kink,
because they are atrophied in their imaginations,
and they require special additions to flag their deteriorating...
Now, did you seclude these young women and feed them on raw egg,
eggshell, gulps of Margosa oil, and a dish of steamed rice?
It was a fair idea.
Black Graham, grated coconut and sesame oil?
They insisted upon it.
It was not anything of my doing.
But I will say that we also managed to do broadcasts,
radio broadcasts, right out of the Ex Day main meeting room.
Yes, it was astonishing,
because there we had generated future seeds
for radio shows.
So, our first questioner is asking, Dr. Howell,
when the saucers do come, how long will I have to wait
to exchange this body for another?
Impatient sort, apparently.
Impatient sort is the name of the questioner?
Well, then, in that case, I'll say...
It's not on here. That's an anonymous...
Dear Impatient... Oh, it's anonymous.
Yeah, well, we didn't... Did we specify that they needed to be signed?
No, they don't have to sign.
If they wish to remain hidden in the light of thought,
that is fine with us here at the Ask Dr. Howell Show.
When the saucers do come, how long will I have to wait
to exchange this body for another?
Are you sure you want to be so precipitate
in giving up your beloved fleshly vehicle,
which guided through the confusing mazes of property,
and the providence on this earth?
You know, your other may have more appendages,
it may have the latest in tentacles and maxillipeds,
but it may not have the homely familiarity
of your own anthropoidal body.
However, I think that I'm quite correct in saying
it is subgenius policy that you do go ahead and experiment
as much as you please in this or any other direction
in your endless search for slack.
This question came up once before,
and Governor Ratnar, I believe, said that he intended to keep
his present physical body because he's already used to it.
That is, of course, a pre-see of what I was saying,
but in the near future, space travelers may get to modify
their bodies so they are more comfortable on those long flights.
Soaring through the far reaches of outer planetary space,
fantastic headquarters of that swashbuckling cosmic highwayman
of the 30th century, Bob.
Yes, here comes the one and only Bob,
gliding through galaxies in his search for star-shattering adventure.
The interplanetary villains quiver in their space boots
when they hear the merry ring of his laughter
and feel the blast of his mighty
PONOCROPEC
fun-loving astral wave.
The happy outlaw of outer planetary space,
he's fast with a joyful laugh,
a ready jest,
and the clipper full of futuristic arrows
Bob!
robs from the cosmic rich.
He's firey.
He's fantastic.
Merriest of the merry men
in the astounding year 3000.
Bob Gibbons, the Covid veteran,
Bob Gibbons was born in the interests of America
in BBC之前
all he worries about is compliance with the best existing
So we available back-to-back
Oh!
The mind is the most powerful sex organ.
You're gonna like it when you get left behind on it.
You squeezy weasel.
Listen to me, mister, it's salvation I'm talking about!
Oh!
The blues isn't about feeling better.
It's about making other people feel worse.
Oh!
I will tell you about the fiction and the facts.
This show is brought to you by the Salesmen of Salvation.
Oh!
That's marvelous, that is marvelous!
Somebody help me, Faya.
Oh!
ぐках?'
Because when I got sc busted it was so weird that I just didn't know how hard it was to stop making art.
Oh, that was сказала, no!
You watched the whole thing and you still want to make the whole thing more interesting but also just want to judge it you'll get hurt.
Oh!
You'll get hurt, that's right!
Look, that's it.
You can't be runaways.
or no more of that.
Well we gotta get moving.
Karen, I hope you're okay.
I'll hug you.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
Slack bang the billy.
Now that's what I want, that's right.
Slack bangers.
That's Reverend Bill T. Miller, Brother Cleve, Reverend D.K. Jones, and all of everything, friends, can be downloaded at kingofslack.com.
Except our background music, which is Joe Newman's Rudy Schwartz project from schwartz.com.
Schwartztone.com, that is.
And now, back to 9X Day and the subgenius nude water baptism.
Oh, my.
Time to turn around.
We pick up.
I turn around.
I see myself when I turn around too fast.
Oobah, oobah, oobah.
There I am, and I shouldn't be there in time.
Hey, what are you doing back there?
Get out from behind me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just was looking.
Get behind me, Satan.
It was never you, it was Hal.
I, uh, well, if you say so.
That is, I don't really recall because my memory isn't what it used to be.
Too many lacunae.
I think there's been.
Too much, uh, disc activity.
It's you got every time I turned around.
Too much fragmentation and not enough disc proper optimization taking place.
Somebody was giving me some funny kind of a pill to take.
You should remember to drink your maintenance on your hard drive.
Everything changed.
One day you wake up, you've got all your information distributed.
Seemed to emerge into a strange guest call.
And I couldn't tell whether I was freezing or boiling as I sat on the mobile living room.
And we, as I sat, moved onward through the.
Where do we treat this situation?
Whirling.
Blorp.
Oh, oh.
And then it happens.
Mine doesn't say blorp.
No, I, I.
Bad sectors creep in.
That wasn't me, that was John Elway.
They take over the media service.
He kissed the playa as it worked.
You are, I can only say you're in the state of wash.
And as the mobile living room went along.
W-A-S-S is what you'll be chanting to you and your friends over and over again.
This outriding, this wonderful guy on a special motorcycle scooter.
As you cry and moan about your hideous situation.
With five parallel blue lights on it.
Was sporting and moving around it like a dolphin moving around a ship.
Twisting and turning.
He wore an outsized fireman's hat out of which fireworks spurted and sparkled.
And he flanked us and went before us clearing our way.
And he only wiped out one time when he went through a puddle of piddle.
On the desert floor.
Which had not yet hardened.
And it caused him and his vehicle to wipe out.
But he was all right.
And back up on his feet a moment after it.
Yeah, you can back up your feet.
You can back up your feet.
The miracle of Burning Man.
From Dr. Howell there and Dr. Philo Drummond on KPFA in Berkeley.
And now the miracle of Reverend P. Kitty's sermon at 9X Day.
Friends, standing here tonight.
I'd like to talk to you all about love.
I'd like to talk to you about the love that I feel.
For that man Bob Dobbs.
I'd like to talk to you about the joy.
The love I feel for the joy that slack brings into my heart.
And I'd like to talk about the love.
The camaraderie.
The solidarity.
That I feel with my fellow subgenia here.
I'd like to talk about all those things.
But I can't.
Because I hate.
Yeah!
I hate the conspiracy.
And everything it's done to the world and to us.
Am I alone?
No!
I hate.
I hate this world.
And the mazes that they've crafted in it.
The way they bring us down.
And how everything's designed to turn it around against ourselves.
Who's with me?
I am!
I hate the exes for not showing up.
And Bob for the false promises again and again.
Am I the only one here who hates Bob?
Kill Bob!
And I hate the pinks.
Oh God, I hate the pinks.
Making everything horrible in the world.
Turning society into a weapon against us.
Coming down against anything that stands against their interpretation of how life should be.
Oh God, I hate them.
My finger has more hate than a thousand Hitlers ever did.
Every neuron in my brain is an atom bomb.
Exploding into billions of nuclear blasts with every thought.
Leaving radioactive fallouts in a wake.
Miles across everywhere I go.
What's your point?
Some people would say that means that my hate consumes me.
But they're wrong.
My hate inspires me.
My hate lifts me up on wings of fire.
That I may rise above the pinks.
And escape the normalcy that threatens to engulf me.
That's what my hate does.
My hatred for the pinks is for their small-mindedness.
For their self-loathing.
And for their...
No imagination.
For their lack of imagination.
Oh God, we could be here all night.
For their petty obnoxiousnesses.
For their stupid shoes.
For their horrible shoes.
My God, the pink shoes.
Their socks.
And their complete hatred and lack of comprehension of anything and everything that doesn't fit into their particular world view.
Why they go.
And why they police themselves.
But therefore, I'm going to be magnanimous.
I refuse to become that which I despise.
I let my hatred bring joy to my heart.
Bring slack to my heart.
My hatred is a slackful hatred.
A joyous, wonderful hatred.
One which puts a smile on my face as I go through the day.
I will open the door for that old lady even as I know that she will be burning in the fires of hell afterwards.
I will help that stranded motorist on the railway even if all he deserves is a painful death.
I will wear a slackful smile and offer courtesy to those who would destroy me.
Because I know in the end that Bob will see to it that they will suffer eternal torment.
You're like, Jesus!
And how can I not be happy knowing that?
The conspiracy wants us to turn into what the pinks are.
They want our hatred to burn so wrong that it consumes our slack.
That we're overwhelmed with nothing but anger, gripe, until all we can do is hate how the world is and not slack off.
And enjoy ourselves.
My hate powers my slack.
They want everything to turn into subgeniuses being like pinks pumping out more petty crap.
More obnoxiousness.
More flat out pink hate.
Petty hate.
Little hate.
Well my hate is not petty.
And I will not let the conspiracy turn it for their own devices.
I will use my hate to spread slack and joy to everything around me.
And I will not let the conspiracy be damned.
It's one of the things we hate about this world.
The obnoxiousness.
The stupidity.
The pinkness.
The complete bullshit that they spew into things.
So I will turn it against them.
I will turn my hate into slack.
Turn it into a weapon against the petty crap that they throw at me.
Because you need to take things into your own hands.
Sometimes no one's going to do it for you until you grab the world and fuck it into the shape that it needs to be.
Do you hear me?
Get me out of this one.
Little bitty from OBE called UA.
You seem a little nervous my friend.
You summoned me from beyond.
You'd better be ready to speak your piece.
You called me from beyond.
You disturbed my restful sleep.
With your childish little games.
You don't know what you're playing with.
This is not a game for little boys and girls.
This is your life.
It'd be better.
Listen to your music backwards and reverse.
This isn't just another stupid heavy metal band.
I'm from the hundreds and eight mile metal.
You thought you were going to be cool didn't you?
Get ready for me.
I used to be a nice guy just like you.
Then I found the taking of a soul is the truth that I want.
I will eat you alive and chew you up and spit in your face.
You're a beast.
You better be ready to face the consequences for the boys and girls.
One last chance.
That's all you have.
You rang for me.
Then you rang for me.
There's no escaping the eyes.
You will see them in every dream.
You rang.
You will never escape the eyes of dogs.
The eyes of dogs will follow you wherever you go.
I will not shine in those eyes again.
You rang for me.
You called me from beyond the grave.
You better be ready to face the truth my friend.
We're here for your soul.
Sons of God.
Kill them.
I will stay.
The demon voice of I will stay.
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
You have been driven to the brink of insanity by the conspiracy.
My problem will be out here.
Hope you as a saint shall not die yet.
Will theSenator be where you were then?
I can't.
But I read books you will see in youriseance.
Help me to live like this.
Help me to work,
Thank you.
Everyone's heard quit your job and slack off, right?
Hell yeah.
Right?
Right.
All right.
Well, I'd like to tell you a little something.
I was trapped in a conspiracy job.
Office job.
Dilbert.
Cubicles.
All that crap.
Oh, the pay was great.
But I paid.
Little by little.
Bits of soul.
Day after day.
So, one day, I called in sick.
Not because I was sick, but just because I was sick of working there.
And it felt good.
So I called in the next day.
I called in the next day.
Turned into a week.
Weeks turned into months.
I kept calling in.
I was still on the books.
And their computer was so ass backwards that it kept paying me because the people I was calling into didn't take the effort of marking me off the books.
At the same time, my wife, the Reverend Venus envy.
She was hating her job too.
She took advantage of a layoff option.
She was getting unemployment.
So here we are.
No jobs.
No visible source of income.
And yet the income kept coming in.
The bills were getting paid.
And we were sitting around the house doing nothing, slacking off, and enjoying ourselves and getting paid for it.
Now, do you think someone may have had something to do with that?
You think someone may be behind it?
Well, I'm not saying, I'm not going to jump to conclusions here.
No, I'm not going to jump to conclusions.
Let me just say a little something though.
Eventually the unemployment ran out, as it does.
Things started to look a little tight.
And right when that happened, we got a letter from the unemployment office asking us, would we like another $3,000 gratis?
Of course!
Yeah, we said yes.
Now, I'm not saying what you think I might be saying.
I'm not going to jump to conclusions here.
I just want to say, the person who sent that letter, his initials were JR.
Oh!
So, when Bob says, quit your job and slack off.
Do you think it's a joke?
No!
You think it's a lie?
You think it's yet another false promise from the man who has betrayed us so many times?
No!
Well, actually it might be, you know.
But the question comes down to, do you believe what Bob has to offer you?
Do you believe in Bob?
Yes!
Hello!
Do you believe that you can quit your job, you can slack off, and that Bob will be there to catch you when you fall?
Do you believe in him?
Yes!
Well, let me tell you something.
That doesn't matter.
Yes!
It doesn't matter whether you believe in Bob.
Fuck Bob's job!
It doesn't matter to me.
Sure as hell it doesn't matter to Bob.
All that matters in life is whether Bob believes in you.
Bob believes in my money.
Exactly.
When you quit your job, when you walk away from that asshole you're with, when you leave the life behind that you had, all that matters is will Bob be there to catch you when you fall?
No, probably not.
What have you done for him?
Why should Bob help you?
Have you paid your dues?
Yes!
Have you converted the worthy?
Have you bled for Bob?
Yes!
Have you died for Bob?
No!
Have you killed for Bob?
Yes!
Have you killed Bob for Bob?
This joke that you call existence is nothing more than the pipe dream of the only man who actually defines reality.
And you better pray that he remembers that you're an extra in this little game.
When he lays himself to sleep at night, are you in his thoughts?
Are you in his pipe?
When he lays him down to sleep, will your soul he pray to keep?
Think about it. How confident are you?
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob!
For about ten minutes.
Well, here's the Ask Dr. Howell column.
That's repeated from the publication known as The Southpaw Self-Pleasure.
He was a right-handed man surrounded by nubile willingness, but only his left hand could bring him satisfaction.
That's so, so sad.
Such a sad story.
Which can be purchased right now for $5 each at subgenius.com.
Which is available from the subgenius.
You can go there now.
Spend your money, see.
These are pictures from last year.
This is last year's X-Day.
And here is Dr. Philodrumon and Ivan Stang and Dr. Howell sitting there at the picnic table.
Gibbering and cabbering.
And here is Sister Decadence in her role of
Trottering and frittering.
Kali, the ruthless one at the ball of gods and demons.
This week, the ball was of robots and people in their pajamas.
Now, you know, Quijibo, the subgenius house magazine,
is published by Christopher Lee.
And I have to say, Christopher Lee was the box office magic word for 2005,
appearing in movies that earned a combined $640.1 million.
Did you know that Christopher Lee is like the tallest of all the actors?
That means that...
He's like seven and a half feet tall.
Christopher Lee has beat out Ewan McGregor, Brad Pitt, Morgan Freeman, Samuel Jackson, Gary Oldman,
Vince Vaughn, Liam Neeson, Chris Rock, Ralph Fiennes, and Kerry Washington.
Whoever Kerry Washington is. I don't know who he is.
You mean in terms of earning? Earning power?
He appeared in $341 million worth of millions.
But Christopher Lee in movies makes more.
And he's in his 80s.
He was in Star Wars, Revenge of the Sith, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory,
The Corpse Bride, an accomplished top box office star in 2002,
with Star Wars Episode II, Attack of the Clones,
and Lord of the Rings, The Two Towers.
And so, in addition to all this, he is a subgenius who publishes Cui Cheapo, the famous...
It's amazing how he gets all that work done and still manages to come to XDAY every year.
And he looks so different when he's in XDAY.
You know, normally he's like 6'5", but when he gets to XDAY, he's like 5'6".
Yes, he does change considerably in appearance.
And he has glasses on at XDAY.
And his eyes are perfect for an 89-year-old when he's not at XDAY.
The weirdest thing, he wears a little beanie.
When interviewed, Christopher Lee said this,
I have the slack gene, which just means getting stuff done.
I'm actually starting to feel an affinity for ex-president Gerald Ford.
Through wacky circumstances, he also found himself increasingly appointed to new positions,
inheriting the problems of the previous administrations, and facing them with character and personal decency.
It's a great thing to do that politicians do.
Mr. Ford gave conditional amnesty to Vietnam.
Vietnam drafted Dodgers who had fled the country.
And I rehired our Dodgers who had fled the restaurant where I work.
A great subgenius magazine, friends, QuijiBo is.
It's not put out by me.
You can find out how it is put out by writing to this address,
QuijiBo, that's Q-U-I-J-I-B-O,
at 18 West Main, Greenfield, Indiana, 46140.
Maybe a fiver.
That's 18 West Main, Greenfield, Indiana, 46140.
Before Hal and Dr. Philo Drummond and Puzzling Evidence were talking,
there was Reverend Peaky Preaching Live at 9X Day,
and some Rudy Schwartz Project, also heard in the background.
That's from SchwartzTone.com, S-C-H-W-A-R-T-Z.
And you rang live at the X Day 1998 drill,
turned out to be, performed by Reverend Bill T. Miller, the King of Slack,
and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
I will be teaching a subgenius online course in November and December,
with MaybeLogic.org.
This, you're listening to, is the Subgenius Radio Hour of Slack,
from the church of the subgenius, subgenius.com.
And our mailing address is subgenius, P.O. Box 181417,
at Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
And now, back to 9X Day.
Subgenius Radio Hour.
2 Beans, ladies and gentlemen.
Around the world, thinking about that horny girl.
Thinking about her day and night.
Wishing that she was here tonight.
Singing, loo-ah, loo-ah.
Oh, baby, now we gotta blow.
Right off this planet, baby.
Loo-ah, loo-ah.
Oh, Bob Bob wants us to go.
X Day is here.
Woo!
Well, maybe they've blown a fuse.
Or maybe a small spider crept in and created havoc.
Doesn't take much.
It takes a thousand million slaves to build a pyramid,
and only one tiny little earthquake to destroy it.
Well, we are, of course, at the mercy of our instrumentality here.
Or a spider smeared across the original plans,
making the number look like another number.
Anybody could mistake a fly speck for a decimal point.
Anybody could.
Anyway.
That's how I ended up on this planet, actually.
But that's a long other story.
We know about that.
Or in this time, rather, I should say.
And yet now we go to eat doughnuts.
Yes, doughnut forsake me, oh my darlin'.
Yum.
Yum, little darlin'.
So don't forget.
Tomorrow is your wedding day.
It's you, the caller, and the listener.
On you.
That make the audience.
Yep, that make this show.
Well, it's been fun, kid-roonies.
And we're gonna be back with more cartoon fun next week.
So tune in around this time.
Yippee!
And listen to the puzzling evidence show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And of course, the giant squitter-roonie.
Tell your friends.
So tell Froggy to plunk his magic twanger and keep the giant squitter-roonie at bay.
We'll be back.
Or you're just gonna chase him.
Get on, little doggy.
And marry me.
Duh.
Transfer of files.
Please upload and retweet.
And retweet data.
And retweet.
tekta старą kaplung.
Bye!
Do you know anyfestовор?
Dos entails busleriwhave activeOut-of- jardzy halves.
No ouvracie dolar Dogs esté vite abo'