Are you too stupid to see what's going to happen? I know what's coming. Have I got to beat you to make you understand?
It's the Super Genius Powerball Squadron!
It's going to end more horribly than anything in all history.
That much I know.
Hello, you're on the air.
The show is low.
How low can you go?
You're about to find out because you're here on the Puzzling Evidence Program and this is your moment of challenge.
Zero! We've got one billion! You've got zero!
Number one!
The show rules!
The show rocks!
We're going to whip your butt real good!
Okay, so we'll do that guy.
Yes, the show rocks.
Indeed.
Hello.
And now it's time to relax to the cabana for the cocktail hour.
We're in Washington, D.C. and remain calm, everybody.
All these crazy kids out on the street today, they'll protest anything.
They'll be anthrax.
And you know, I'm kind of behind them. I love those crazy, beautiful bastards.
Yeah, all those people out there trying to fight cancer, I don't get it.
Why do they protest against cancer?
What's wrong with cancer?
I'm sorry.
Because it's unfair.
You're deluded, Mike.
The American spirit revolts against anything.
You've got what we call Michael Pepe.
Michael Pepe is.
Not a square deal.
Where you think that everything is fair and beautiful and nice.
And it is.
But it isn't designed for you.
This is how much you get.
Designed for unknowable purposes.
The little numbers assign the value for your life.
Think of the king cobra, for example.
And the order squamata.
It's a different map of the U.S.
With more little numbers.
Family elapidae of the genus and species Ophiophagus homa.
It's a Bob Nelson.
It is without question.
It's the original.
It's a boing like a snake.
The largest venomous snake in the world.
Growing length of almost 16 feet 5 inches.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob is the man.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob is the man.
Now everybody.
Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob Bob, Bob
Bob Bob Bob, Bob
Bob Bob Bob Bob
Blah
Now everybody
rockin' that beat
What does the book say about that?
Well, follow in your book and repeat after me
as we study our subgenius doctrine and dialogue.
Well, it says,
the pipe in the face forever.
That's all you need to know is that the pipe will remain in the face.
Was that by John Philip Sousa?
And to keep,
smoking. The pipe must keep smoking.
We, the subgenii,
are Bob's tools for keeping the
plan in sync between
the totally fated future events
and events that happen accidentally
in the present.
If one follows the implication of this to its
core, it can, by its non-existence,
teach to those able to
discern it, the true secret of
Dobbs. Only by taking
the most circuitous possible route
can we increase the probability
of the impossible.
Only from the step above can the present
step be seen and understood
in context. At least we know
that much.
Sounds like a little doctrinal purer
than thou, if you ask me.
Well, it's the church, after all.
I'm sorry, that's the way we have to be
when you're going back to the pamphlet.
You know, this is a little bit of a
swing to the right for subgeniuses.
They're not used to it because they spend most of their
time in a state of total slack.
Ah, yes,
that total stream of slack.
I'm off.
Yes.
If you say it really fast, it doesn't really matter.
To the interpretation of the word, you've got to get the word.
Okay, so you've got to straighten that out.
So let's straighten that out right now, right here, tonight.
Okay.
Which they contained in a magnetic bottle.
Had this containment failed,
a possible
catastrophic explosion
might have occurred.
Though this is denied by sweaty scientists.
Yeah, don't worry about it, come on.
It says that he could see like it in no way,
not do anything about it.
Like the end of all time, who cares?
The evil side.
Okay, that's where we're going now.
There we go.
Oh, that's an old hag's tail.
They don't actually do that.
What are they doing, Star Trek?
All last week across the media landscape,
in pod,
blog,
flat screen,
and crunkly old newsprint columns,
fatuous professional observers complained that the occupants,
the high wall street marchers,
have no clear agenda,
or can't articulate their positions.
What impertinent horse shit.
I saw a statement on one wall street occupiers sign that said it all.
$70,000 college debt.
$12,000 medical bills.
I'm 22.
Where's my bailout?
What part of that is under the law?
My daughter is 14 years old.
What part of that does that even mean?
Oh, kom butler what am I even doing here?
I shouldn't be here, I want to,
If I'm unaccompanied,
I feel very ambushed.
I would enjoy spending my time.
Here I come.
This is not the nation I was born in.
I had to cover up for being a girl in with promos.
Excuse my tongueن
I suppose the ad forının
governed, Reverend Martin Luther King, bumped off, and even won U.S. Attorney General, Ramsey
Clark. Today, the entire establishment, is a clueless, hopeless, blob of self-interested,
craven opportunism. Even the arty fringe, the people who pretend to be an avant-garde,
are nothing but narcissistic, self-branding operations, masquerading as culture leaders.
There's so much influence over our government, they will never be held accountable until
the people stand up and beg for justice.
Justice! Justice! Justice!
We can televise, you know, the, um, all of the protests in the Middle East, but we can't,
this is happening in our own backyard, you know, and why is this on TV? Why?
There are a bunch of people basically gambling with all of our futures, and I don't agree
with that. I don't consent to that.
Our politicians no longer represent the people of our country.
They represent us, the people. The voice of the people has not been heard.
These people are out here talking about things that affect everybody. Problems with the banking
system, problems with politics, um, my 401k plan, your 401k plan, problems with how that
all works.
I lost my job, and I lost my health insurance. Um, I'm, I sort of have a social safety net
from the unemployment insurance, which citizens pay for. This is a difficult story to tell.
And that is still an unfolding story. And I think until there's a compelling narrative
of why people have decided to peacefully occupy Zuccotti Park, I think it's very hard
to communicate that story to everyone else.
Eric and Ferrari got that for us. Thank you, Eric.
Continuing now with Michael Moore. I asked Will Bunch this question last time. We have
diversion to you tonight. That's 2,000 or 550 tea partiers there protesting taxes or
protesting stimulus or anything else they don't like on Wall Street. It's on the evening
news, isn't it?
Oh, absolutely. Um, you wouldn't need that many tea partiers there. They're not going
to be there. It would be a top story. Um, and, and same thing a couple of weeks ago
when a thousand environmentalists were arrested at the White House. Uh, imagine a thousand
tea partiers arrested. This, um, I don't, I can't speak for why the networks, uh, have
not covered this. This is really the very first down on Wall Street in the financial
district, the very first attempt since the crash of 08 to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to,
to, to, uh, take a real stand. And, um, it's been powerful. And, and I gotta, I gotta
believe that even though it may only number in the hundreds right now, this is going to
grow not only on Wall Street, but in communities all over America. And I would encourage people
watching the show to think about, okay, you can't make it to New York city, but there's
a branch of Chase Bank in your town. There's a branch of Bank of America and there's nothing
preventing you from organizing a demonstration outside that branch with your bank.
signs, with possibly even civil disobedience, to make your voices heard.
They think they're going to get away with this.
These people who stole the pension funds of the American public, who stole their money,
who stole the future of our kids and grandkids, they think they're kleptomaniacs, and they
think they're going to get away with it.
They have taken our democracy and formed it into a kleptocracy.
And if we don't stand up, if we don't have our voices heard, believe me, they're not
done yet.
There's a reason why corporate America, and I think you've pointed this out before, they're
holding $2 trillion of cash in their bank accounts.
They've never done this before.
Never held on to that much.
They've taken that money out of circulation, and they're waiting.
They know the other shoe's going to drop.
And as Mayor Bloomberg said last week, he said there's going to be riots in the street.
If we don't provide jobs right away, there are going to be riots.
Now, this is Mayor Bloomberg, the billionaire, talking.
This isn't Michael Moore saying this.
This is Mayor Bloomberg.
This is Mayor Bloomberg saying this.
They know, and the smart rich know, they can only build the gates so high.
And sooner or later, history proves that people, when they've had enough, aren't going to take
it anymore.
And it's much better to deal with it nonviolently now, through the political system, than what
could possibly happen in the future.
Well, what's left of America's democratic system if this is the process that has been
cemented in place?
If you think you're a big man.
America will punch you if you're just a little girl.
America will punch you if you like rocks on the beach.
America will punch you.
America will freaking punch you.
If you think you're a big man.
America will punch you if you're just a little girl.
America will punch you if you like rocks on the beach.
America will punch you.
America will freaking punch you!
So punch, America punch!
Punch, America punch!
Paul Revere will punch you!
Jesse James will punch you!
America will freaking punch you!
If you look her in the eye
America will punch you
If you forget to wear a tie
When you're on your way to school
America will punch you
America will freaking punch you!
So punch, America punch!
Punch, America punch!
Kennedy will punch you!
Calvin Klein will punch you!
America will freaking punch you!
Dr. Spock, Carole King, Jerry Lewis, Martin Sheen, Jimmy Stewart, Tiger Woods, Mr. T, Mary Worth, John Wayne, Isaac Hayes, Willard Fillmore, Willie Mays
They're all gonna freaking punch you!
So punch, America punch!
Punch, America punch!
Terry Ford will punch you!
Richard Drew will punch you!
I hope you're ready to get punched!
Ugh!
The first issue I want to speak with you about is the recent clashes that have taken place on Wall Street
between Americans who are turning out to demonstrate and police officers.
From what I read, you recently sent a message to support the campaign
and the activists of this group called Occupy Wall Street.
You've called them courageous and honorable.
Can you talk to me about your take on Occupy Wall Street?
Well, Wall Street was just a shorthand for the financial institutions.
The banks are bigger and richer than before.
Corporate profits are reaching record levels.
And unemployment is about the level of the Great Depression.
Real unemployment.
These people are saying, oh, let's blame the corporate.
And the institutions behind them.
So fiscal policies like taxation, rules of corporate governance, deregulation and so on.
It does set in motion a vicious cycle which is getting worse and worse in New York.
So walk down the streets and you can see it.
Very serious poverty.
On the other hand, phenomenal wealth.
Right side by side.
Very much like a third world country.
It's what you see if you go to sub-Saharan Africa.
Meanwhile, infrastructure is down.
Architecture is collapsing.
Schools are collapsing.
And all of that increases the, keeps the cycle going and in fact rising.
Well, it's about time for some protest.
What may be new in the coming year for the 2012 election is that many, including yourself,
have speculated and assumed that the campaign spending for the U.S. election in 2012
will exceed $1 billion.
For each candidate.
That is a massive amount.
It will probably be much bigger than that.
And where does that come from?
Well, you know, basically a lot of it comes from financial institutions.
In fact, if you look at the 2008 election, what swung Obama, what gave him the election,
was primarily financial institution contributions.
They preferred him to McCain.
They expected to be paid back.
And they were.
And the next one will be even worse.
It's not that they're rich.
It's that they're influencing the system.
They're gaming the system.
That they're fighting against the bigger corporations because they've gamed the regulatory process.
They've gamed the politicians.
They've gamed the system so badly that you can't have competition anymore.
And that's what this is about.
This is not an anti-capitalist movement, per se.
You know?
This is...
This is a movement about equality and democracy and liberty and justice and the rule of law.
Those are deep democratic principles that have been completely forgotten.
I have my problems with the whole system.
I mean, the whole way it's set up.
You have to get the money out of the system.
The message of this group is actually a populist movement.
And it isn't being funded by...
The Koch brothers or Dick Armey.
It doesn't have that kind of political agenda.
This is not the Democrats, okay?
This is not the Republicans.
And so, they don't know what to do with that.
And so, the Democrats are not going to be in power.
They're going to be in power.
And so, the Democrats are going to be in power.
I'm along monitored, it works, it works.
I am onarnish of learning.
I am on-"
If you have to take things to temperature,
The only way to answer is to keep the rest of the everyone list as best as possible.
So, next time I stay at the party, we'll have Dan—
Jeremy Russell, I'll call her.
T temple…
No, that provides...
To keep you free from the franchise.
still in spin
and there's
no telling
who that it's
naming
for the loser
now will be
later to win
cause the times
they are
changing
come senators
congressmen
please heed the call
don't stand in
the doorway
don't block up the hall
for he that
gets hurt will be
he who has
stalled
cause the battle
outside
raging
will soon
shake your windows
and rattle
your walls
for the times
they are
changing
, and we're
out here at the edge
of Bernie Manor
and we are
we are
in the
middle
of nowhere
I've seen
nothing
but nothing
at all
we've got
nothing but
the
do is
no
one
more
talent
we
take
it
over
sudden
combat
was
not
a t valores
we did not save
Tim spoke you! Let Bob know you!
He regularly grooms his eyebrows.
Please!
I'll be loud!
When it's not up to the individual, it's up to the chap.
Please!
He's a god.
He is a god.
He's really not a god.
Bob, he regularly grooms his eyebrows.
Slack! Slack! Slack!
Let's talk about Slack.
What about Slack?
Slack is a group of people who love to talk about their problems.
I'm glad to hear it.
That's what I'm talking about.
I love it.
Thank you.
Yes, dear friends.
This version of Brazil in the background
is a rather unusual piece
considering that it's by the same name
as Psychoskeletons.
They don't usually sound this way.
I was going to do credits over this.
Dave is waiting to get on the line here.
And I still do have credits to go.
In fact, I think what I'll do
is bring that one down.
And that means now we can get to the man Dave.
But you did do the credits, didn't you?
No, actually, I didn't.
That version of Brazil sounded
so good that I decided
to just let it play.
The Psychoskeletons did that.
Here, I'll do the credits real quick, Dave.
Friends, this is our Slack number,
1,331.
There have actually been at least,
well, no, we had some reruns.
But we've had some X-rated ones
that some of you can't hear.
You'd have to go to subgenius.com
for that.
The long collages there
were by
Reverend Phineas Narco,
of National Cynical Radio
podcast, which is,
he does at least weekly, I think.
Usually there's one
right after the hour of Slack.
Live.
And this was from his
one on the
Occupy thing.
Although it had, that's a song
by Bob Dylan and Noam Chomsky
talking. Noam Chomsky?
He sounded like a robot.
Noam Chomsky?
Noam.
Noam Chomsky and other
people on there. What else?
Oh, did you hear, Dave,
that song by the Little Girls,
America Will Punch You?
Well, the Little Girls are, you know,
yes, I did.
I was saddened by it. I almost
wept, but that was because I had
my hand caught in the toaster. But yes,
it's a true,
it's a true, true perception of the
world we live in.
Well, we saw those
two little girls perform.
They're not as little as they were when they
recorded that song, although they did that song.
We saw them at the Northeast Ohio
Witches Ball. Yes, we witnessed
it. Last weekend.
And or known as Con
on the Cob in Hudson,
Ohio. There were some great bands
at that, and I haven't had time to
sort through all the CDs I was
given. Those girls don't have a CD.
They're called Shy Show.
I got that off their website.
The name is spelled S-H-I
S-H-O
Sci Show.
Or Shy Show.
And they're now 14
and 11, respectively.
And they've been playing together for
seven years, and they opened
for them. For seven years!
And they opened for
They Might Be Giants. Can you believe
that? And they're not
micro or macrocephalic like so many
of the indigenous people that we've been using
lately for the, you know, slavery and
especially in Hudson, Ohio.
Yeah. Where they used to mill the rocks
and carry them uphill with one donkey
and about 500 slaves. No, they
didn't have slaves in Hudson. It was abolitionist
all the way. It is.
It was. Oh. Well,
before, we also
heard, well, there was a
lot of National Cynical radio, which
you can catch at NationalCynical.com.
Thanks to Phineas.
Yay, Phineas Narco.
Puzzling Evidence Show was
represented. Thanks to
somebody finally cutting up those two-hour
shows, besides the
large. Bob Nelson,
the guy who actually had that show
first before it was a subgenius show.
And then it got taken over
by Puzzling Evidence, and
Nelson left, and now he just
calls in and listens and cuts in the
parts that he is on.
And that's how I ended up with those.
It's a
drastically valuable resource
for practically everyone in the Bay Area.
If you listen to...
Yeah, if you're up at four or five in the morning.
Exactly. After about
20 beers. And there was a
song at the very beginning,
Bob is the Man, a kind of a
queasy
song. That was by
someone called the
Cryogenic Strawberries.
And I don't... You'd have to look
them up. The Cryogenic Strawberries.
They apparently are a
subgenius band. They sound like
one. And
the intro was one of...
the earliest by
Lemur. So
here we sit, broken-hearted.
Oh, the other band.
I love the name of this band.
Pleasure Leftists.
Yeah, man.
And that's kind of our theme
for tonight.
Obviously, we decided
let's make Mr. Sister tear his
hair out. He's our
conservative friend. Our beloved
conservative friend. Yes. We have many...
We love our conservative friends. And in
many ways, I'm just about as square
as you can get compared to
some
Baptists I know.
Right-wing Baptists. But
actually, the... Huh?
But you still don't believe in the
creditable financial rape of every person
in the United States at the behest of a few
crazy people at the very top.
Perhaps 4,000 now.
A clinical study from Switzerland revealed.
Oh, there's 4,000 rich,
super-rich people that run the world?
Well, they're way beyond our idea
of rich. They're... Right. Right.
Beyond imagining.
Beyond imagining. And we're
the 99%? Is that it?
Actually, some somebody's...
Some subgenius... I may be confused
about this. Some subgenius said,
we subgeniuses are the 615%
of the 99%.
And then somebody else said, no, we're the
666%. But that's
kind of corny, because everybody
makes fun of, you know, the
Antichrist and Jesus. But not that many
people make fun of Bob,
whose number is
999.
He's the anti-Antichrist
or Herman
Cain. Yeah.
Who wants to...
You know, since conservatives are so
into the government staying
out of people's business and fewer laws
and states' rights, he wants
abortion to be illegal
as a federal law under
all circumstances.
Circumstances. Rape, incest, danger
to the mom, all circumstances
in all states.
And of course,
he condones the actual use
of, like, from the song Brazil,
which was played earlier, having
helicopter troops invade your house and
serving you a notice and then leaving and saying
you owe them $45.
And if they
execute you, your family has to pay for
the bullet, just like in China.
Slash stroke.
Now, our friend, Reverend Sue,
Susie the Floozy, who
runs Bob's Slack Time
Funhouse, which will be following this
show in Atlanta on
WREK.
Susie
posted a long, sort of
convincing rant on
Scrub Genius Forum, which is
subgenius members only,
saying that she
intended to vote for Herman Cain
and here's why. And she said, well, I heard him on a lot
of talk shows and he's made
more sense than
other right-wing hosts, which is the only
kind of talk shows there are for the most
part. And that's not saying
very much, considering that this guy
doesn't really make any sense.
But her point was
if Herman Cain
was a president, or
for that matter, really any of those guys,
but especially him,
it would essentially
push things so far.
Most
of us would end up living in shoeboxes
and it would lead to armed revolution.
And eventually a
serious overturning
of the status quo.
And people tend to think,
things don't change that much.
But you know, China was a lot different
before Mao, and Russia
was a lot different before
the Bolsheviks,
and America was a lot different
before the industrial military
complex. And it could become
different again in a way that we can't
even imagine.
Now, my dad
says he's worried about
America because
of that guy
in the White House.
Worried about America, whether they're dead or alive.
I'm worried about America because of my
dad, Pappy. He alone
could destroy America just with
his jokes.
But as
usual in the end, they usually just
America destroys Pappy.
And when we're Pappy
with a capital P, we'll understand what
that means when we go, I just
can't believe now that
the people got them 3D hologram
things implanted in their foreheads,
but everybody knows what everyone's
doing. And furthermore,
what did I just say?
They're competing for Big Brother's
attention.
They want Big Brother to read
their every tweet,
their every Facebook post.
Oh God, what was the theory? I decided,
okay, use that in newsgroup
forums like Scrub Genius
and the
long-lost sad alt-slack, which
by the way, wandered out of its hotel
room and got lost and died of exposure.
Or not its hotel room, it's
old folks' home. It was in
assisted care.
This is the old subgenius newsgroup.
Anyway, newsgroups are for people who
think in multiple
paragraphs.
Okay, Facebook is for
people who can think in a sentence
or two, or maybe a
paragraph. They don't allow you,
much more than a paragraph. About three to four lines.
Right, three or four lines.
Twitter...
Twitter is for people who just can handle
one sentence at a time.
And the next big social
miracle will be
er, which will be for people
only, you know, three words
will be allowed, but that's bad form.
And a typical
round of
conversation would be
user A would type in,
hot.
She, her hot.
User B would say,
ooh, stooped.
Stupid, with an E.
Then
person C would say,
ooh, both
stupid. And
then user A and B would
both say, grammar Nazi,
only they'd spell, it'd be
grammar Nazi
and grammar
Nazi.
Or something, you know.
Exactly.
So it's slowly getting closer
and closer to the point where
people can get their idea across
with one type of grunt.
Because there'll be so few ideas
to get across.
So few crotchety widows and orphans
to bother the mainstream flow.
It's going to be quite a world when
your every thought is pre-programmed by another
source and plugged directly back into the
source. What the hell good will that be?
And you have to pay for it.
Yeah. Top dollar.
An amount that you can't afford.
Yeah, but if you win enough points,
you can type an extra word on
er.
And what purpose
would that serve? Just make everybody mad
at you and call you a grammar not-so
or not-Nazi.
Or a troll with one L.
Yeah, right. A troll.
Well, but Dave,
isn't the Church of the Subgenius
both the world's biggest
troll and
most honest?
Most direct mode of
communication? Both
at the same time?
Definitely.
We understand what it means
to have every
aspect of our bodies controlled
and our minds controlled.
There's like nipple rings and earrings
and different kinds of products you can buy to get the
same results. But once you
listen to the Church of the Subgenius for
25 seconds or whatever
time you can afford, I know it's
very hard for some people
to afford even 25 seconds to
improve their brain. We're going to, we're working
on that. We're actually going to cost,
make the hour of slack cost
accelerate to download. It'll be
free streaming. We'll still, we pity
the poor.
Because we know.
But if we can
get 99 cents a download someday,
that would be fun.
There might be on-site mutilations too. I think that
would be an interesting...
At least if we can afford them for as long
as we can.
WCSB listeners
will be able to get their online mutilation
right at the studio when we have
the open house on November
20th.
By the way, the
Radiothon pledge drive is November
6th. That doesn't
affect other stations unless
they have pledge drives too.
And it'll go for, it goes for
them, although they will have different premiums
offered.
They may not give you the online mutilation
that we can offer in person.
If we're still here November
20th.
According to, it said, one news thing
I read today was that global warming could
exceed safe limits
in our lifetime.
And what they really meant was my grandkids
or my kids' lifetime.
And what they mean by safe, I'm not
sure it, Pappy
doesn't, you know
it's, I can't even repeat
what he said.
He lives in, on a ranch,
the Stang Ranch is in the middle of Stang,
County, which has been suffering
a drought for 10 years
and probably will for 10 years
more. I think it's because of an Indian
curse, personally. But
I said,
just to irritate
Pappy, I said, well now Pappy
why don't you have your governor, Rick Perry
pray for some more rain. That worked real
good last time. And I can't
repeat the four letter expletive
the Nixonian expletive
that he emitted.
And not at me,
the whole thing. At the fact that
I was able to say such a
thing. Because my, Pappy
is not what you'd call a friend
of the super religious. Although
he is a preacher, just like me.
Being an atheist has never stopped
any Stang male from preaching.
It didn't stop Jesus.
No. It didn't stop Moses.
It didn't stop Mohammed.
It didn't stop any of those guys. They were all
atheists as we all know now.
After current studies
released, I think it was in last
April. Jesus wasn't atheist
my friend. He was the son
of God. The son of God.
But he didn't believe in him.
Don't you think that ain't that typical of a teenager?
Well he just made fun of them all the time.
Youth. They just gotta rebel, don't they?
He's the son of God!
And yet he didn't believe in him.
He smoked Chesterfields too, by the way.
Who, Dad?
Jesus. Oh, of course he didn't.
But see, they cut that part. The Council of Nicaea
removed things like that and
women.
Women are equal to men and stuff like that.
They took that out of Christianity
because, well, for obvious reasons.
Well, they weren't using the same
anatomical maps as Leonardo.
That's one thing for sure because when they cut out
those important parts, they left
the worst parts intact and that's what we're
living under. Near
and, well, under.
But those parts taste best if they're
they can taste pretty good if they're all ground up
and mixed together.
We had some, a pan pudding
that you've heard of
scrapple, right? It's made from the parts
of the pig that they won't even...
I used to use it as a consummate dressing for my hair and my body.
Right. But now I know
that Reverend Stank
actually likes liver.
He does not think he likes
liver. Well, I only like liver
if it's in the form
of pan pudding is
liver mixed with
other parts of the pig.
Anus, penis,
the intestines,
jowls.
Now, that's some goody.
Like scrapple, but instead of being mixed
with cornmeal, it's mixed with rice.
And it doesn't have that burnt
hair smell that good scrapple
does. Well, I get all my pork products
from the Borgia plant right
down the street and there's nipples
and oaks and
snouts aplenty. Women don't
like that word nipples. They think that's
anti-woman. They like
the word tilts.
Yeah, curly tails.
Some kind of weird spiritual
or religious artifact. Mr. Sister,
delivered our pork products.
I even have a t-shirt that says,
in Polish, it says, Mr. Sister,
pork products.
In Polish? Yeah, and an
English pervert, Embager,
made that shirt. You see them around
Cleveland every now and then. Several of us
wear them. Although
the famous Mr. Sister
himself doesn't look anything like this shirt
anymore. He's lost
like 4,000 pounds or
something. Yes. And he
used to look like Godzilla.
Now he looks like a little Struthiomimus
or a
smaller, much smaller dinosaur.
Stan, why would you
compare your friends to various dinosaurs?
I love dinosaurs.
You know, Dr. Howell is a
reptococculus of the...
I love dinosaurs.
I never understood that.
Dinosaurs are the next...
Dinosaurs are the next coolest
thing to naked girls.
They might come back the way we're
going if we extinctify ourselves.
Maybe some...
Never mind.
Last night, Princess Weah and I watched
all of Planet
of the Dinosaurs, 1978.
Which is known...
Famous for... It's a pretty good dinosaur
stop motion, and it's
incredibly terrible acting
and costumes.
What a fine, fine specimen
of Bulldada. Yeah, it was.
It's great. And then we
watched Tarzan and the Amazons.
Which, uh... We haven't finished
yet, but I know how it's gonna end.
He'll call the elephants and they'll
come and save the Amazons
from the white men.
I've been sitting around listening to...
Tarzan know like men. Men
bring guns, cause trouble.
Men go away. Tarzan know lead you.
I just had a...
I just had a vision in my mind of
Peter Sellers as Dr. Strangelove
coming in in a wheelchair as
the, you know, the guys with the pith helmets
attack Tarzan, and he's like giving
orders, but I didn't want to...
But I thought I had to share it with you because...
Uh, Steven Spielberg essentially
beat you to that. He didn't
use the word Tarzan, but he... It was
Indiana Jones instead, but...
I was watching that Tarzan movie and thinking,
I think Steven Spielberg owes these guys
an explanation. Especially
in the set design, art design,
glass paintings and stuff.
But we're getting lost in
the dogma of inside
bad film, which I'm sure
some of our listeners really appreciate,
but probably not most
because they're not old.
Well, not... Some of them are
too archivist
and you can be that at a very early
age. In fact, the ones who turn out to be
too archivist at a later age
began at an earlier age
somewhat close to the Cambrian
period, where everybody flossed.
And that was the
obsessive dynamic, cultural dynamic
of the whole society. People
flossed all the time. They were constantly
worried about things being stuck in their
teeth. And it still is with us.
It still is with us
today. Well, and
not only the Cambrian, but the
Devonian, especially
here in Ohio. Yeah, most
importantly.
More artifacts. Never mind. Are we not
ancestors of men?
Barely.
We are not
vying for position
in the cloud for Big
Brothers' attention.
Exactly.
Others.
I'm actually...
Well, I mean, I have to make a living
to some extent, but...
You love Big Brother.
You're saying you
must admit that you do
love Big Brother and you don't like Big
Slimy... Yes, you're right. I must admit
that.
You're right. I must admit that.
And I know exactly how
Winston Smith feels. I know
him and he's a cousin
of mine. And he smokes
like a football.
I'm not a football player. I've got quite a bit of...
I've got some collage artwork, original
Winston Smiths on my bedroom
wall.
He's a subgenius. He's a
friend of ours, Winston Smith.
That's so wild to be a cousin of a cultural icon
rather than one yourself, I suppose.
Well, he not only... This is the
Winston Smith who not only was featured
in Orwell's book,
but he also did all those Dead Kennedy
album covers.
I think I'm going to turn off
Philip Glass there. I'm sure some people
will go, oh, thank God.
Well, it's too...
Turn on the Flying Ryan Brothers.
The Fly-In Ryan Brothers,
I should say. The Flying Ryan
Brothers are subgen...
Reverend Jimmy Ryan is like the
Joe Satriani of subgenius.
He's too... Their music
is almost too normal for us to use
most of the time. It's too good.
It's like, you know, it's
professional.
We use it in our vacation movies.
Yeah.
It looks good in the...
If you look at Google
subgenius family vacation,
you'll see that Princess Wee and I
are not as old as we sound.
We look as old
as we are. Well, you sound much worse
than you seem. Yeah. We're still
able to walk, and there's photographic
proof of that. The point is,
walk where? I mean, where
does any one of your vast wealth
want to go when you don't need to?
All you have to do is flip your
limp wrist in the direction of
some servant.
It comes trotting up immediately and
brings you a dog bowl full of champagne,
I suppose. We had to let
several of the maids and butlers
go. Oh, speaking of walking
and old age, I read
today that somebody's making
GPS shoes for
people with Alzheimer's. Yes.
Yes. And how...
I don't know if we still will
need them. We'll need them ourselves.
I've got a GPS now.
Well, I think we should be
appraised of that, definitely.
We should. You should get one.
Because you've been known to walk around
in the neighborhood and, you know, forget
who you are, where your
address. Well, it occurred to me,
I thought, well, the next obvious
step is, you know how a lot
of certain
subgenius types lose their
glasses, their cell phone, and
their car keys on a daily basis, right?
Now, if certain
objects had GPS
locators in them,
then you could have this little
handheld locator where you push one
and it tells you where you're, you know,
it points you in the direction of your
cell phone. You push two
and it shows you where your car keys are and so forth.
The problem with it is,
by definition, the people who need
a machine like that would lose that machine.
Exactly.
So you'd have to have another, you'd have to have
a GPS locator, locator,
locator.
The pile of technology
needed to complete a human function,
would just become enormous.
I'm patenting that right now.
Trademark, 2011
Reverend
Ivan Stang. But think of the
social consequences, Stang.
Think of what if, you know, this is
allowed to proliferate throughout the land and stuff
and people can't remember what they're doing
to begin with. I forgot
what I was even talking about. Good!
And it really made a lot of sense to me.
It was kind of funny. No wonder you forgot.
The potential use by
zombies, that's what it was. I forgot.
What if, you know,
people go around and all of a sudden it comes up
on the screen that your keys
are at some field somewhere near a
ditch and you didn't even know you'd been there
the night before. And you go out there
and you realize that you are actually
a zombie or perhaps
the zombie might attack you
or at least, you know,
say dirty words to your, you know,
stuff like...
Dave. What?
I have a song that I'm going to play.
Well, I hope it's a
really good and nice song.
I'm going to pull the Flying Ryan Brothers
down for a second. It is a real good
and real nice song.
And it has...
We've been talking about the economic
depression and on
previous shows we've talked about our
own personal
economy and
depressions in our
foreheads.
Someone has used the term occupy
space. Occupy time.
It's about too many.
Craziest place.
Reverend
or rather Popess
Pontiara Ivakovich
made a little
song. She just
sang it acapella
but Reverend Frodus
Suds Pasha
doctored it.
And I'm going to play this song
tonight, right now.
And I'm going to play it again during
Radiothon Pledge Drive.
Okay? Because
well, it's appropriate.
Because you're a rabble-rousing guy.
Yeah. I'm going to
pot us down as we
pot holders say.
Okay, here goes.
Early
each day to
a mysterious stage
the little
old Ivan Stang
drives
in his
own special way.
To the yeti
he calls
come
by my table
of swag
Come feed my
little wife
show her you care
and you'll
be glad if you
do
My
grandkids are hungry
our house is
so bare
all it takes is money
from you
Feed the Stangs
money for swag
money, money
Feed the Stangs
that's what he cries
Come overhead
space ships fill the skies
In Wisteria
campground Bob Dobbs
and his minions
look down at the
yeti hive
and though you can't see it
you know that he's smiling
each day.
They all look like
Paolo from stress
he's not
looking for
likes
someone
he'll
say
love
again
by boys
captain
Money for swag.
Money, money, money for swag.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Dragging your butt through the day?
Time for the hit and all of the guilt?
But none of the sex?
There is a simple answer, dear friend.
And a glowing beacon of slack amidst the turmoil that does.
It's J.R. Bob Donne and his mighty Church of the Subgenius.
Though his words are simple and few,
Listen, listen, he's calling to you.
Be.
The stains.
Money for swag.
Money, money, money for swag.
Repent! Quit your job! Slack off! And praise Bob!
Yeah!
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
How about that?
Isn't that wonderful?
That was like Les Mis meets Bob.
Um, yeah.
I could hear Woody Guthrie in the background.
Oh, man.
And when she says money for slack, it doesn't just describe your ridiculous church.
It describes what everyone needs.
No, it actually describes your local.
Radio station that plays the hour of slack.
Come pledge drive time.
And by the way, she's saying money for swag, not money for slack.
Well, it's a good thing I misunderstood that.
Yeah.
Or, um, but, but, but, but that's what you, if when, when we do the pledge drive in two weeks, um, if we're the earth still exists in two weeks, we will, uh, be having, we'll be asking people for money for the state.
And they will get swag in return station swag and a subgenius premium, but that will.
Whoa.
Well, we've got, we've got, we're going to be a rocking party friends.
It's going to be a, the Halloween masquerade party for WCSB will be rocking.
We'll be there, but you won't know who we are because we'll have masks on.
Of course, if I wear the Bob mask, then you might know who who's wearing.
There's only three of them in Cleveland that I know of left.
So, and I've got all four.
So, um.
And if you see a person in the gorilla suit and the Bob mask, you'll know who it is.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh.
Um, so, uh, yes, uh, that was a feed the stangs by, uh, Popes Ponteary Vakovich with, uh, mixed by, uh, Reverend Frodo Suds Pasha.
What an exquisite piece of music.
Really?
Well, I think it owes an explanation to Mary.
We do a lot of.
I'm crying about everything, especially money for swag.
Fine.
Yes.
But still.
Mary Poppins was involved too, I think.
Speaking of swag, I've been nursing an ill tooth by using my old Bob cup.
They do have value beyond coffee and beating people up.
And, uh, I'm wearing my shirt now one day before it becomes miserably cold in this area.
Poor Dave.
So the Dobbs cup.
Dave has nothing.
That's all Dave has left is a Bob, a Bob coffee mug and a Bob t-shirt that's very, very threadbare.
Oh.
Well, the nipples I did.
I know women hate that word.
How come?
I would like to ask we directly.
Why do women hate the word nipples?
Do they?
I dare not speak for all women.
So I shan't answer.
It was.
We had a little argument.
I had a little argument earlier about, uh, a different word that involves nipples.
Nipples are a subset of the word she didn't want me to say, even though I was saying it
in an admiring fashion.
Buttocks?
Could it have been?
No, no, no.
It's when you can't say on the radio still to this day, believe it or not until until
11, like at midnight, you can't at midnight.
You can say the word, the four letter word.
You can say.
It has nipples on it.
Yes.
And disagree.
Disagreement or perhaps even civil war or neutrino death.
But you can't say, you know, right.
Yeah.
Oh, don't.
Whatever.
Don't say it.
Don't get slack religious.
Let's not be slack religious.
That was Prince of when Princess.
We first heard that song money for stangs or whatever.
Free the stank.
Feed the stank.
The stank.
Her first comment was that is so slack religious.
Followed by my comment.
Where has that word been for the last 33 years?
Really?
Jeez, oh man.
Slack religious?
Who couldn't have sunk that and none but did.
We right now and then.
What I'm afraid of, we both said, Oh, Nan's gonna call us up and go, uh, that's on page
66 of Revelation X.
And I came up with it four, 10 years ago.
But you don't remember because you know.
You're right.
Because you did all that, you know.
Oh by the way, WE now has a week.
Yes, I have a week.
We're, we're, we're members of the modern world.
We have a foundation.
We have a video game set in our home, a console.
Play on it and we go, whee!
You bowl and so forth and then play lawn tennis.
This is the only one I know of that comes with like a foot pad.
So you have to, you can't do it sitting down.
You have to be running and jumping and jogging and sword fighting.
And you actually work up a sweat playing these games.
God forbid you don't plug a ridiculous machine into a wall
or have to go outside and actually walk around and act like that.
That's why they want you to stay at home and do that
so you don't behave that way in public.
And another way you can't behave in public is to let your show go on too long.
And I must say this is the end of this show, Hour of Slack.
The Church of the Subgenius show.
Future shows may be more explanatory of Church of the Subgenius.
Wait until we get to the German, the English computer translation.
The translation of the German article about subgenius.
It will not be difficult, my dear.
Maybe next week.
And if you need more information about this show
and any of the artistes that we play,
like the Flying Ryan Brothers in the background,
in a couple of days, look at subgenius.com if you want.
And there's a radio button.
And if you click on the title of Hour of Slack,
$1,300.
$1,331.
Live.
October whatever, 20-something it is.
23rd.
Hail Eris.
You can find links to like Shy Show and Puzzling Evidence
and the Cryogenic Strawberries.
But not Lonesome Cowboy Dave because he's not on Facebook.
No, I refuse to be because I was told by you that it's a bane of normal existence.
Someone's always pestering who you don't know.
Well.
Well, I only have three.
I've kept my friends down to like, you know, there's six now.
I might make Wee.
He's not even my friend.
Yeah, I'm not even Wee's friend.
But there's a subgenius slack hole that anybody can look at.
And it's actually pretty funny.
But you have to be a Facebook member to see it, I guess.
So you can't win for losing now, can you?
I should officially end this show right now.
Yes, with a fish.
For Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back, flackin' whartin'
Philip Buckaburton, purgaluma-burton,
doesn't wash tonight at all.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slackness,
slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month.
From enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Music
Sound
approaching
A Online
attractive
Don't brode
Bo boo
Bo bo wow
learning the different parts of the alphabet,
rolling their tongues and arguing with each other
on into the hours of the night.
Well, before any more further ado,
let's all give them a big round pat on the forehead
and slap them into the ground and beat them to a merciless pub.
And friends, that's what you can do every Sunday night at 9
on the Hour of Slack, heard only on WCSB in Cleveland.
But don't get in it too hard.
WCSB, Cleveland.
Okay, are we done now?
Dave, you know what we just did?
Something I've needed to do for the station for a long time.
One of the things when you're a DJ here,
you have to provide ads for your show.
And although our show is ended as far as the others
outside of Cleveland will ever hear,
you just did that ad.
You didn't know you were doing it,
but when I put the tail end on it
and did the legal ID at the same time.
Oh.
So then it makes no sense to me whatsoever still.
So now we're free.
It's like the part of the show that will be on the Internet is done.
Radio synesthesia normally would be starting right now,
but I foolishly told Dr. Sinister at the station meeting yesterday
that we were going to be here tonight
so he didn't have to hurry in to spell,
African Abstract God,
because when we're not here,
African Abstract has to stay until Dr. Sinister gets here
while the pre-recorded hour of Slack plays.
So we're kind of a hassle to our fellow,
to the DJs before and after us,
unless we come in and do live shows.
And we will be doing that until we have to switch to reruns
for about two months or three soon.
And now Dave can tread water.
He's going to be better with us in free form
because Rob's not here yet.
Who's Rob?
Oh, Dr. Sinister I meant.
Yeah.
Praise Rob anyway.
Praise Rob, whoever he is.
It's Dr. Sinister who is not here yet.
Oh, here he is.
He's just come running in.
Now we tread water.
I'm sorry.
Friends, welcome to Dr. Sinister's Radio Synesthesia.
Ah, ah, ah.
The radio has never smelled so good.
No pilfering allowed.
Remember, boys and girls.
It's the only radio show that you can see.
That you can eat like candy.
It's the only radio show in color.
That you can protect like a friend.
And tastes like pan pudding.
And it's the only radio station that wears a mustache.
And as a gastronomical extra,
it's the only show that provides a handy wipe.
For after use.
And you'll need it, friends.
Get your deep pens, handy wipes,
and other household cleansers ready.
For Radio Synesthesia.
Which actually I think can be spelled two different ways.
Coming right up right after this brief massage.
It's more for Radio Synesthesia.
Here, I'll just, I'm going to turn the music.
Up.
This is the Flying Ryan Brothers.
Oh, well, of course, their timing is perfect.
I'm out of here.
Well.
All yours.
Why, thank you.
See you, Dave.
There's some music on right now.
See you, girls.
As well as the microphone.
As well as Dave.
Well, hello, Robin.
How are you?
I'll see you soon, perhaps.
Friends, I always bring my own headphones.
It's because they're louder than any of the station ones.
And also because you stole them from the station.
Originally and put your signature on the back.
So, yes, welcome to Synesthesia or Slank Overtime, as it might be.
What I'm going to do here is queue up a couple of PSAs.
And what is this music?
The Flying Ryan Brothers are subgeniuses.
It's to propagate the weird nanovegetables.
Yeah, this doesn't really...
Ryan Nattek.
It's a man who often confused diuretic with diabetic.
It makes the nanotech go.
It's Ryan.
R-Y-A-N.
Ryan Nattek.
A man who often confused diuretic with diabetic.
You know what's really funny?
Back when I was a snake oil salesman, I noticed that there was a lot of herbal supplements
on the market that had names like Nature's Way and Nature's Herbs and Nature's Secret
and stuff like that.
And I thought it would be really cool to make a combination herbal supplement, combination
diuretic and lactic acid.
And I thought that would be a great seller.
I knew it would never.
So, yeah, that having been said, thank you for filling in these last couple of minutes.
And...
Thanks for the escargot.
Yeah, look at that escargot.
That escar is pretty fast.
It was delicious.
Just zipped right by, like...
Man.
I can't believe this is made by a subgenius.
This is...
Yeah, I know.
It's really good.
This is not subgenius music.
This is genius music.
This is stuff that ought to be played on the Friday Fusion show.
Right.
That's why I don't play it very often.
Yeah.
I'm not insulting that.
I do enjoy some wonky music.
But...
That's not the word for it.
It's virtuosity.
Virtuosity.
Not in every aspect, perhaps, but it is certainly virtuosity.
And very virtuous.
To some, perhaps.
I mean...
This makes me want to go on a crusade and storm the world.
I'm not going to storm the castle of the evil villain.
Actually, wait a second.
I'm the evil villain usually, though, so I guess I want to storm my own castle.
Yeah.
But this just...
Like, I just feel this righteousness and this passion for, oh, do it, do it, do it,
right.
Well, what did you just eat recently?
Could it be a gastric, you know, a digestive problem?
Oh, man.
I had some Cambodian food for dinner tonight.
Well, you want to go out and shoot everybody.
There you go.
I'm subgenius.
I'm a subgenius.
Or at least, you know, enough...
No, you didn't.
...teachers and firemen to...
Oh.
...accessuate the problem.
Stick Lars.
I'll remember that going forward, just like the quotation marks around the name Bob.
You always capitalize the G in subgenius.
The old professor himself.
You know, quotation marks are kind of actually right about what's going on on Wall Street
yesterday.
Yeah.
Well, Dave, I want to thank you very much for hanging out with me here for a second,
but I'm going to cue up some music, and that is not this.
And, boy, I would love to hear from you sometime.
If you'd call in during synesthesia, I know foreign service is not cheap, but gosh, it
would be great to hear from you sometime.
Well, thanks, man.
I'll make sure I don't do that.
No, I will.
I will.
No, you should.
All right.
I certainly will.
Well, thank you for hanging out tonight, and hope you'll stay tuned.
Thanks.
All righty.
This is WCSB Cleveland.
The name of the program is Synesthesia.
I'm Dr. Sinister, and I'll be here till midnight.
All right.
Here are some announcements to service the public.
Or not, as the case may be.
Just a second here.
Got to get this cued up.
You know what's really funny?
I'm so used to Charleston leaving the wave cart on all the time.
Usually when I come in, it's on.
So I'm so used to it being on that I actually...
Did I actually turn it off?
You did.
You did what you're supposed to do.
Well done, sir.
Believe me, it was an accident.
WCSB Cleveland.
Come by another tonight.
I will be there again.
No...
Into this room, you little hoşu, regal.