Oh, yeah.
My name is Chaz, and I'm broadcasting you tonight from my little holding cell here.
All quarantined, all strapped in my suit.
Pressure suit's all pressured up.
Yeah.
It's here.
The ship is waiting, hissing away, spewing out its little steam.
Waiting for the moment, the final countdown.
And that's where we're at.
Just hours away from the final hour.
The final minute.
The final second.
X-Day.
Thought I'd never get here.
It's kind of late now.
We're there.
There's nothing else to do.
Just sit, look out the window.
And...
We wait for the lights.
X-Day GORDON THEогh
Current Rules
Is your pleasure-ship hovering above, waiting for the final hours to pass?
Tomorrow Tribes
Whiteisse X-Day O intimidated military exclusion.
goddess waiting for you somewhere in Eurasia blue.
My names. We'll see you. Goodbye mom. Goodbye dad. I gotta go into space.
One two. Hey bleepo. Yeah.
Um, Chaz and I have been planning our, which reruns we're gonna, we're gonna run as since there's only another like week of broadcasting left on the planet.
Oh God.
Yeah, I've done 638 hours of slaps.
Down to a few hours now.
And we're gonna start rerunning number one. I mean, for what radio station?
Right.
And what were you planning, thinking of doing Chaz? Are you just gonna run reruns or like what's your first show after the, after you leave?
Well I was, I, I.
Or is there, are you just gonna blow it off?
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I was under some understanding that they were gonna install some black, black box, black box, black box in the studio here.
I don't know what the technology of this really is. You know, like I say,
You can ask me too, Stan.
I don't understand how a lot of this is gonna, you know, take place. I don't understand how a lot of this happens. I just know that it won't fail because of me.
The vehicle lift weighs, uh, close to six and a half million pounds.
We all are in this together as a team effort. We're gonna make it work. And I don't know how to make it work. I don't know how to do most of this mission.
But I do know that I can assure you that my piece of it is gonna work.
And it won't fail because of me.
Hello, world.
Chaz here.
ESO Radio, broadcasting live from the pleasure ships.
Oh, yeah.
Where you gonna go?
When the sex goddesses come for you.
Gonna go to the place that's the best.
When I lay me down to die.
Going up to the spirit in the sky.
It's where I'm gonna go when I die.
When I die and they lay me to rest.
I'm gonna go to the place that's the best.
And it's so beautiful from out here. It's so pretty. The earth. It's just that little blue and white and little marble hanging there.
Gosh. That's where it all began.
We'll see ya. Goodbye.
Prepare yourself. You know it's a must.
Gonna have a friend in Jesus.
Friend in Bob.
So you know that when you die.
Bob will recommend you to the spirit in the sky.
Swamp Radio.
Be so very lonely.
Your 2008 tears will fall.
Failure is not an option.
I'm so happy.
Happily as I've been going further and further back.
Backwards.
In my career.
As I get better at what I do.
Well at least you got better and were able to get as far as major market broadcast radio.
Bleepo. There are those of us that.
I would say major disappointment might be the word used.
But he is regressing enough to grow an awful lot of body hair.
I mean I don't know if his voice is getting higher because of the operation or.
There was major disappointment and there was General Electric.
Oh there. I thought you were gonna refer to the guy's erection again.
And then there was Admiral Bob.
Oh Bob.
Just like a penguin in bondage boing.
You know on X Day, Neegie will return to us all the greatest tapes that we ever recorded.
Praise the Neegie.
Which he has been keeping.
Oh God that's so good.
Neegie has been keeping all of our lost recordings in a special vault.
You hear that?
Will all be returned to us on X Day.
Oh that's so glorious.
Janer will get his 8mm films back.
Oh.
You know your first show will come back.
Actually I never did lose anything.
Will I get those videos that I erased by accident back?
As long as you saw them Bill.
Things that were mailed to you.
You know that you never got around to looking at.
Uh huh.
Even if I've only seen it for a fraction of a second.
What about events that I next taped that never were taped?
There's a thing called the.
The new program.
The thought that you imagine very vividly doing.
This is too damn confusing.
I'm getting out of here.
Will then be done.
They will have been done.
When you want to do a wonderful new show.
That show will materialize in your hand as it takes.
Yeah the new program.
We.
Have.
Escaped.
From.
Your.
Pants.
The hell.
Escaping.
From.
My.
Deep.
Head.
In.
The.
Are.
Gripping.
But.
They're.
Slipping.
And.
They're.
Clipping.
Cause.
I'm.
Dripping.
Well.
That's.
The.
Yanagi.
Is.
Related to the.
Oshitashi.
Which you often get.
You know.
When served with the wasabi.
Yeah.
And.
It's.
It's in conjunction with the uni.
And the yanagi.
And the hiroshi.
And the inaka.
And the wasabi.
Yeah.
All these things.
You combine them.
These things become combined.
For the normals they become combined in sort of a slurry shop.
We subgeniuses luckily will get the fresh human soul sushi as it were.
Yeah.
On demand.
Sushi on demand.
24 hours a day.
Even in Cleveland.
TOmana
The most popular sushi sushi market here in Minnesota.
And I'm riding alone by my own in a land of sand and stone.
I'm living in Arizona.
I work with my hands in a land born free.
Living in a white house in Canyon Deshaye.
And what I take, I give to living in me.
Oh, when it's scissors-toothed, I'm a man of my word.
And when it's rivers, it's through your eyes, you see that?
No, Jack's right?
And you'll see your state of mind will sow its seed.
And what what what what what what what.
Yeah.
I'm a man.
I work with my hands.
Living in castles made by the sand.
And I'm riding alone.
Out on my own.
In a land of sand and stone
I'm living in Arizona
. . .
. .
.
I'm living in Arizona
. . .
Come on, Mom.
Come on, Dad.
Dad, I got to go into space, Mom.
I got to go into food again.
I got to go into space.
Come on, Mom.
I'm never coming home.
We're going to give you one more little song.
Hey, this year at Starwood,
we are Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
and we'll be playing in the Puffer Dome
from midnight to 3 in the morning tonight.
On Friday night at Starwood this year, yeah.
Friday night.
We'll be puffing it all night in the Domo.
In. Beamed in.
Beamed in.
And from the pleasure ships.
Holographic images only, please.
A lyric little song.
Perhaps maybe a child's nursery rhyme.
Perhaps a little didgeridoo song from an aboriginal.
A little song that a child would sing with me.
Swing his eucalyptus leaves on his head.
And make a crown of thorns for himself
to become the aboriginal messiah.
And save the red rocks from these and that
and this.
And those cars going by.
And that toxic polluted swamp over there.
And those red glowing rocks over there.
And that meteor falling through there.
We can't even comprehend what might have been.
We can't even think about where we might have gone.
It all takes too long.
Just keep your eye on the red rock.
Just keep walking by the river.
Oh, that's so pretty.
I'm sorry.
It made everyone weep.
In the moon.
Meet them sleeping inside.
I'm touched.
You've been touched so many times you're as soiled as a bad pair of underwear at the bus
station.
Please don't touch me again.
I'll try not to.
They make me say things.
They make me do things.
Hit me.
They make me wear the moon pants.
They didn't make you do any of that, man.
Ah, but the moon billies wear the shaggiest moon pants you've ever seen.
They're made for the mean men and they're packed with all kinds of strange ideas.
I'm afraid those shaggy things aren't pants, Dave.
Those are moon dogs.
I thought they were the bad ideas sheeping out of their legs.
The bad.
What are we going to do about all the bad ideas?
We can rebuild him.
We have the technology.
One pill makes you larger.
And one pill makes you stronger.
The world ends Sunday week.
I like the way that sounds.
A big deal.
World ends Sunday week.
End of week.
If we make it we can all suck up to the sound of love.
For more enjoyment and greater efficiency, consumption is being standardized.
Okay, I'm going to look for ways to express concretely love to passion.
Love to passion.
Passion.
You're kind of like the frog and the prince guy.
That you've got this super being inside of you which is imprisoned in this evil flesh.
And you keep struggling with this evil flesh so you can become a god.
But most people don't and they become like kind of petty devils that go from one low
comedy to another with the rats dangling out of their pants.
It's a stinky word because there's no law and order anymore.
It's a stinky word because it lets the young get onto the old.
Oh, thank you God.
Oh, it's no order for an old man any longer.
I think it's the only church I know of where a preacher willingly exploits himself for his own...
I'm doing it for Bob.
For Bob's...
Well, yeah.
We can clear this up really.
It's no different from any other religion in that respect.
We'll cheat anybody.
We can clear this up.
The whole thing is a gigantic...
It's one of the greatest, most gigantic cheats that humanity has ever conceived of.
Praise Bob.
Oh, Princess Wee, did you do your tale and song?
Oh, no.
Yeah, we can play it in three different keys and do it real fast.
Let's do it.
We'll do it right now.
Because it's getting late.
Is it going to be in a key?
The show ends in half an hour forever and ever.
Yeah.
But unfortunately, as you said, it goes on and on and on forever and ever.
On.
And once again, we must remember to keep our focus as we project out there.
After the ball.
I don't know exactly if you'd call it the there.
We got it.
It exists simultaneously in so many different places.
Have you hit Tim?
Yeah.
No, that's the rectal thermometer.
Put that thing down.
Yeah, I need to sing.
Okay.
This is the last one.
Listen to this bleep-up.
Okay, now I made sure I was not in tune.
Beatles songs out the window, huh?
I got a little preview of this earlier.
Oh.
There, we'll start over.
Okay, you better start again because we have to...
Back it up, man.
Back it up.
We have to sing.
Beatles songs out the window, bleep-up.
I heard it.
All right, here we go.
There was the pop record.
Shut up.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Picture yourself afloat in the cosmos in a pleasure ship vessel of your own design.
Somebody calls you, you answer quite slowly because you're not in tune.
You're so incredibly high.
Smell of dangerous officers appear on the shore waiting to take us the next day.
Climb on the deck with our heads in the clouds and we're gone.
Looney's will not die with Simon.
They won't be able to make it.
Their hands are shaking.
Looney's will not die with Simon
Picture yourself in your own private garden
With lobstery trees and fresh figgy pies
I didn't like the figgy, I thought it was a frog
Nobody calls you to answer but dronely
The girl with calliope signs
More pleasure saucers appear on the shore
Waiting to take us on an extra
Climb on the deck without a deck
And we're gone
Looney's will not die with Simon
Why?
Ah
Picture yourself all asleep in a fountain
Where chaco tyrannosaurus' leave kisses behind
Suddenly someone comes by and awaits you
And if all the children fall asleep
Then these neighbours about to catch the man
Looney's will not die with Simon
He'll dream of happily ever after
You just have to figure out for yourself.
Everyone gets the time they deserve.
And everyone gets that destiny they choose.
I know you ordained for genius, and you know exactly what that means.
I know exactly what that means.
But for those of you who are somehow yet unsaved, there are nine more holy and complete days where the post office will be open.
And if you don't know what to do, call one, nine, six, nine, and ask.
Operators are standing by.
But we, we, that's me, are not standing by.
Bye.
We is ready, and we will greet you as you board the pleasure ship.
With both horn lights flashing brightly, we even will place the lei around your neck, kiss you on the cheek, and send you on your merry way into the escape vessel.
But for now, we out.
We out.
P.S.O.
And you get your own free Wee-Bell.
We out.
Oh, wow.
Isn't that weird?
No.
That's not the Wee-Bell.
The Wee-Bell is a wee-bell, honey.
She means wee-bell because, not because...
Oh, man.
So, I always wait because she says, wee-bell.
Right there.
Oh, man.
She always says wee-bell.
Oh, wee.
Simple, simple.
El did, oh, al did, al did, we...
There are hands sticking out of the walls.
When the bush came, we had to hide and think about when Bob would come and liberate us.
And put us in little tiny pleasure ships about the size of this pack of girl right here.
You see, we had to shrink because our heads were so big from staying in the basement.
But he did compress us.
Yes.
Well, I can't wait till the subgenius exhibit opens in the new Disney world.
You know, now, don't start counting your chickens before the hatch, Bleepo.
Well, they promised me a job 50 years ago before I was born.
Well, me too. Me too. Most of us.
But St. Palmer Vredes speculated that, you know, what if on X Day, the exes, you know, the sex goddesses from Planet X arrive?
In saucers.
Saucers.
The size of little tiny shirt butts.
And they fly around hovering like gnats in front of our faces going, well, get on board. Get on board.
And then what do we do?
And then they, you know, get tired of waiting and they fly away and fly away and fly away.
Do not abandon your post. There is no danger of radiation leakage.
Why is it so hard to get out of here?
Why is everything all right down here?
Why are you waiting?
We will pull you to sleep.
That accident over in Red Sector L destroyed another 63 personnel, giving them a total of 242 lost to our 195.
Keep up the good work and prevent accidents.
John and Yoko, Jimmy, Leary, Rosemary, Tommy Smothers, Bobby, Dylan, Tommy, Cooper, Derek, Taylor, Norman, Mailer, Allen, Ginsberg, Hara, Krishna, Hara, Hara, Hara, Krishna.
All we are saying.
Is give me some time.
Now sing it for the Senate.
Oh, God.
All we are saying.
Is give me some time.
Personally, I like to think of myself as the most sweetness and light new age, love oriented subgenius.
And I know that the 33,000.
Saucers of Planet X will line up from North Pole to South Pole across this globe.
Let the world turn under it.
And loonies will not die.
For Simon with Simon.
They will have nothing to do with Simon.
Loonies will fly, arise up, up, up above the atmosphere.
Far, far as they depressurize, their heads will swell.
Even the poor and the weak.
Even the innocent loonies who don't know of Bob.
Like balloons, they will swell as they depressurize, floating ever higher up out into the stratosphere,
the Oana sphere, the DNA-o-sphere, the Devo sphere.
And finally, the most furthest out from the solar system, surrounding like a great bubble
the solar system, the We-o-sphere.
And it's really weird.
It's really weird.
It's really weird out there.
But there can be other creatures in this alien environment, hunters.
Hunters are fast and maneuverable.
They eat the floaters, both for their organic molecules and for their store of pure hydrogen.
But there can't be many hunters, because if they destroy all the floaters, they themselves
will perish.
Give birth to the little onion-headed boys, the little onion-headed boys and girls, with
such pale skin.
Made for hunting.
They've got a tail, 2011.
articulate fish.
Partифor dark-headed physicians.
The faces of civilization.
Activ Chaos, watch stateword woman of science.
Well, he looks like important in his case.
How creating of...?
Why I'm unique.
And do you mislead or becomeandel of it?
Well, I think, I have a sub-dimension.
I'm an hyvinon of technology.
I know the rule of wide environments and gusts of wind.
So I share interests withmetropl aimful digitalaciego.
Pretty simple.
And then you do what, what?
Who knows that I need!
So I've gotten to live and learn the day routine more.
The time you're out of the night
Step into the sun, step into the light
Each day to get more
The most glorious place
On the face of the earth
Or the sky
Hold on to your breath
Hold on to your heart
Hold on to your hope
March up to the gate
And feel it all
Open
Speaking of swinging like carts of stink,
did you get the email and hear about the dreams
of like Toto with a space helmet?
You haven't heard of a lick of a dream like that?
No.
Of dog sex with Judy Garland in a space...
The helmet and everything?
I had that.
I didn't actually have the dream, I had the actual sex.
The dog sex with Judy Garland.
So you were Toto in the space helmet?
Well, actually I was...
Can I say doing?
I was doing
something.
Toto and then Toto was doing Judy.
She was...
It was a little three-way thing.
It was fun.
Little is right.
Well, yeah, I mean...
I'm surprised to hear that about you, Bleepo.
Well, let me tell you, I mean, the dog was never the same after that.
Let's just say he had to wear a special little bag after that.
But I don't...
I use my dog as a special little bag.
I'm not proud of that, you know, because I'm not into animal abuse.
I like that one better.
I use the little dog as a special bag.
Right.
Big dog.
I saw that.
I saw those dogs.
Those dogs are the funniest lawn ornaments I've ever seen.
I got to say that.
Well, especially when I turned the blood spray on.
Yeah, coming out of the derby hat.
I love that.
The first time I saw it, I thought it was like a Laurel and Hardy thing.
And then I...
Instead of chocolate, I thought it was like chocolate, but it was real blood.
I thought, which was wacky?
You know, with the old film holograms with the dog thing.
The nose and the chocolate, it was just too...
I'm sorry.
The devil, Mr. Douglas, I have found is nothing more than a tiresome collection of genes.
And it is with great assurance that I can tell you that Lucifer, son of the morning, is no more.
You mean if I smoke that, it's the same as if, as if I was a colleague?
Plain common sense may tell you that you're caught in a rut of faint or futility.
You mean if I was a colleague?
Do they ever forget or forgive the whippings and the harsh, strict words of command?
I wonder.
How can you forget or forgive those over and above you?
Those tall, silly dictators.
Mommy!
Daddy!
Where are you?
Peekaboo!
Something's going to happen.
And I wanted to say goodbye.
What's going to happen?
Something wonderful.
Do you think time's really going to be shorter?
After X day?
No, it'll be much longer.
Depending on where you are.
But, you know, it's like pretty soon.
I would say by July 6th, several of us will have caught on to the 25-hour day.
Yeah, but this is what I want to talk about.
Why not the 36-hour day?
Why not the 72-hour day?
I haven't heard talk about time control in years.
It's been a long time since anybody talked about it.
Well, that's because we've been using time control on you, bleepo.
Your hands are distended.
Well, chance is right.
We're facing down the barrel of the last five minutes of the last greatest radio moment of Earth Farm 1.
We're four minutes from that orgasm, Stan.
No, we're about seven minutes from that ultimate, final, final, that final, final excommunication.
We're beating up to the countdown.
And the final squirt.
The great ooze.
We're whipping it in a frenzy until it's all gone.
It's coming.
They're coming to get you.
And I don't mean they're coming to take you away.
I mean they're coming for you.
They're coming to join with you, to commingle with you, to become you.
I like that one quote of yours in the magazine there.
When in doubt, eat pussy.
What is your name?
I'm.
Did I say that?
Well, then, pussy.
Pussy.
I think that you can't say that.
Did I say that in that magazine article?
Yeah, and you said something about you can't, an anus, you can't use your anus in a medicinal way anymore.
I didn't say anything about that.
I can easily believe that other quote.
Well, that's the time thing again.
Somebody said that.
I believe Bo said that on the show that your anus can only be used in a medicinal fashion.
And if you laugh at it, you're in some big trouble.
Hey, listen, we've got four minutes left.
And I would reiterate what Chaz just quoted.
If I had much others, I'd say if I had somebody who's going to say, Reverend Stang, what is your final statement to the youth of America, to the humans who've been left behind?
What is what do you have to say as your most?
I think it's a critical.
Your one moment.
And I would have to repeat once again.
Pain.
No more.
When in doubt, eat.
Puss.
We are not men.
But although I felt that the eyes of the departed were upon me, still, I forced myself not to perceive the bitterness of their expression.
And gazing down steadily into the depths of the ebony mirror, sang with a loud and sonorous voice.
The songs of the sun.
I believe they're trying to pray to the exes, but praying is not going to do them a lot of good.
A lot of things can happen.
The vortex gets much bigger.
Stop wondering what happened to me by now.
If you go that far, that fast during the vortex.
A bunch of geometrical.
Bumps are going to start appearing on your skin before you even get there.
And so they have a clean up there as a clean up ritual, I guess, before a lot of the inductees or the young savages will be allowed to have their skin scraped so they can, you know, at least breathe right when they're on the escape fence.
Is this the law?
None shall escape.
That is the law.
Never, never, never, never, never, never.
Never, never, never, never, never.
Never mind.
They are complete.
There's no clothes on the pleasure ships, is there?
If they want them, they grow them.
I guess it's with some of them newer models and stuff,
all you have to do is think of like maybe a nice pair of checkerboard pants.
As soon as they grow them, you could want them to not grow them,
and it would disappear.
It would be this endless cycle of them growing clothes
and themselves willing the clothes and you willing not the clothes.
I guess staying really did kind of help bring about a very awful world for all of us.
It's just this constant fluctuation.
Yeah, between a bunch of different minds wanting their different ego ideas of what they want, you know?
I am here to protect you.
You have nowhere to go.
You are a true believer.
Blessings of the state.
Blessings of the masses.
It could be hell.
Subgenius hell.
There is no hell.
There's just endless, endless lines of more or less pleasure and a lot more pain all the time, really.
There is no Bob.
Well, I happen to know there is a Bob because he's standing right over there.
He's sitting there, smiling.
Just like the smile on the dog's face.
What's interesting to a dog?
To hunt.
To kill.
From all the tales of the West, we'll remember best Corporal Rusty and Private Renton Tim.
Nobody has done this for them or to them.
They have done it to themselves.
They are a slave.
You know what it is?
In short, they are a slave.
They're a slavery.
They need to be free.
They need to be liberated.
Uh, uh, you know.
Bob doesn't care whether you brush your teeth or whether you shave your legs or whether you...
Or whether your dad's the heat.
Yeah.
He doesn't care.
He doesn't care if you're packing a big old colostomy bag from a surprise you had somewhere in a hillbilly bar.
Or a .44 Magnum loaded with big hollow point bullets ready to...
No, sir.
As long as you got...
Take down Africa with one shot from this pleasure ship.
Which can magnify the bullets in the size of the state of Oregon.
But since we're all into drumming, we wouldn't want to take out Africa with one shot.
We'd probably aim for Antarctica.
But, uh, I like penguins.
Ye who read are still among the living.
But I who write shall have long since gone my way into the region of shadows.
For indeed strange things shall happen and secret things be known.
And many centuries shall pass away.
Ere these memorials be seen of men.
At the end of the rainbow, you'll find a pot of gold.
At the end of the story, you'll find it's all been told.
But our love has a treasure our hearts can always spend.
And it has a story.
And it's a story without any end.
Unless we're so stupid as to destroy ourselves, there are going to be people exploring those worlds.
There are going to be human habitations on those worlds.
We're going to be moving out into space in the next century.
We're on a little time delay here.
We're broadcasting live from Brushwood.
And it's airing just a few minutes later via the internet at WCSB in Cleveland.
And, uh, that's what's happening.
Tonight.
Yeah.
Yep.
And we're watching all kinds of people from many, many walks of life.
Every different type of...
They've kind of set up a little booth here for us.
A little window booth like they do at the big TV station.
People are going to hang around the Universal Date Wire.
The invisible date, date, date.
Yeah.
Which is actually going to be hovering right over the jam site for Saturday in the afternoon.
To allow the jammers and the other unfortunate ones...
Which consist of Einstein, Secret Orchestra, again.
And whatever drummers show up.
We're going to be drumming for the Earth.
Saturday is going to be the last, uh...
I'm so sorry.
The last drumming to the Earth.
The last...
We're going to bid farewell to the Earth Saturday afternoon at the, uh...
With a happy, clappy, pounding sound.
The Greek Amphitheater.
We'll be singing the Strophe and the Anastrophe.
We'll be performing Antigone in the afternoon.
Uh, but I don't think any of the players from the Iambic chorus will be there.
Not the Baraka?
No.
Or the Koya Naskatsi.
No, those people will all be taken into, uh, Native American subterranean worlds to have their manicures and toes nails.
The life out of balance is about to be balanced.
Yep, it had to happen someday.
And better that it happened someday than some other day.
Some day.
Some other day.
Next day.
I still get gripped with, uh...
It's a great vibe.
...plasmas, or spasms of fear.
And, uh...
Thinking that, uh...
Convulsions.
Well, I don't know if them ships is really going to be there.
They're going to be able to pull us up.
Now, what if Stan gives us the Kool-Aid and...
Well, he pointed that out.
Yeah, he pointed it out.
You know, Stan could be a black-off guy trying to get a bunch of us, the subgeniuses, so that the, you know, the other bad guys could...
Yeah, delivering us.
Right, to them.
Saying, here, here's the choice ones.
Chomp, chomp.
Or the, uh, the pleasure ships might come down and they're the size of a mosquito.
Yeah.
And there they are hovering right in front of your face going, come on, get on, get on board.
Yeah, I...
And there we are, all paid up, dues-paying members, and there's a little mosquito spaceship going, come on, let's go.
Well, that thought might have been precluded by the infinite worlds theory, wherein some...
There is a galaxy, supposedly, a completely self-contained galaxy the size of a grain of sand.
And since this is possible, it is probably happening.
So, therefore, there could be many, many, uh...
Like Stan predicted also that...
I can't deal with the possible.
It must be happening.
You know.
The possibilities?
Yeah.
There's just so many of them.
I mean, who knows who's gonna show up on X-Day?
And they all happen.
Not just a little teeny bug craft.
Every thought that people have...
What if the big guys show up first and don't even see the planet?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, right.
They're so big.
It's like they look at, they look at, where's the planet?
Yeah, where's Earth?
We're down here, man!
It's supposed to be here somewhere.
The charts say Earth's right here.
And we'll be, we'll be this tiny dust speck.
They won't even...
Yeah, and they...
You know, smaller than a mote of dust.
And they mistake it for like, you know, just a mote of dust.
Yeah.
They don't even see it.
They were expecting some big guys like them, you know.
Right.
They don't even comprehend it.
And there we, yeah, you're right.
There we are down there.
Hey!
We're down here!
And then right in the middle of it, you got the black op guys trying to figure out who's
gonna...
They wanna get on there, see?
They wanna make their own deal.
They wanna get off on time and stuff.
You think a bunch of goons and spies who know this is gonna go on is gonna let it go on
and they're not gonna get on there?
No, no, man.
Oh, they're not gonna get on there?
They're not gonna get on there.
The spooks are definitely here tonight.
Yeah, the spooks wanna get all their people on there.
Yeah.
Sure.
A pure white race probably.
Who knows?
And they think, yeah, they have to do all this other stuff, but all they have to do
is become dues-paying members.
And that's it.
That's it.
They don't have to go around with their surveillance.
They have to make some big conspiracy out of it.
Right.
Yeah.
They're spending...
Look at how much money they're spending in surveillance.
How many gray cars did you see on the edge of the campground this morning when all they
had to do was just walk up with 30 bucks?
Yeah, blow three bucks and...
Have fun.
Yeah.
Smoke some frappie.
That's all it takes.
There's not much to it.
We're not talking rocket science here.
Well, we are, but not in any form that you would understand.
Don't worry about it.
Or even us.
We don't know how this whole thing works.
Like I said before, I don't know how a great amount of this whole endeavor is gonna happen,
but I know my little part of it.
I know how to make my little part of this whole thing, and I know how to make my little
part of this thing work, the whole rupture, and all that, and I guarantee you...
You won't say all this because of me.
It's the latest thing in nuclear fission.
Nothing like this has ever been exploded before, and we're gonna be pretty darn close.
I know you're leaving, babe.
Goodbye, so long.
I hope someday somebody listens to your song.
Those bright lights never ever turn on.
Spell your name, it's true
Maybe a change of scene would be the best for you
So long, babe
When in doubt, eat pussy.
At the center of your pregnancy
Sex
Is another dimension
In another world
I find a power of movement
That's a good one
Long time
Will I have no intention
Sex, not with nobody
Girl
I tried and I tried
I will
I tried
And I didn't
Ah, I'll Daddy
Well, I have no potential
I'm in another dimension
I've been in another dimension
The next day never happened pill
Yeah
That you trip on for 50 years
What if
Dot dot dot
If dot dot dot question
If what
What if what
Were if
If were
At
With
What if
Were
If
Were if
Cave
The beginning was the end
Of everything, my friend
That was a premature ejaculation, though
Awesome
It was before and after
The ape regards his tail
He's stuck on it.
Have I ever had multiple orgasms?
No, not in my recollection.
You will soon, my friend.
Very soon.
All that stuff.
The real X-Day behind the X-Day.
The Sword of Destiny.
It's kind of like the real Mardi Gras behind Mardi Gras.
Yeah, like who's the real Rex?
Where's the real magic happening?
Yeah, it's not happening in the boneyard somewhere down on...
It's not happening in outer space.
On rude apple heart.
The real magic doesn't happen in outer space, kids.
It happens in a little microcosmic world in inner space.
Magic.
Are you...
Let's speak to the Brushwood fans here.
Just randomly...
We're out there practicing their magic right now.
Let's just take...
Forget about the people in Cleveland.
Forget about the people in other parts of the world.
You want to pick us up here as we just roll along?
We'll just walk out there?
Yeah, all right, here, let's go.
Let's take the microphones.
What should we hit first?
You want to go where they're selling all the froth?
Or you want to go...
Where they're selling the magic?
Drums, or...
No, I want to go watch the magic.
Oh, there's people, I guess, off over by those blue tents.
Hey, have you seen Ivan Stang?
Hey, hey, you dressed in that white...
Gosh, look at that outfit.
It's like white polka dot.
The arms are 40 feet long.
That person's arms are 40 feet long.
I want to watch you guys.
Wow.
How you doing, man?
Look at that.
That's pretty cool.
Look at that chick over there.
Yeah, baby.
The day glow paint all over her.
Wow, look at that, dude.
Nice little...
Her little things are...
Yeah, over that way, there's this weird glow coming from just over the hill.
Actually, let's just follow the glow, man.
That's how we said it, you know.
Let's put these mics down.
Not worry about this right in the shot.
Look, it's getting bigger.
There she is, man.
The chick I was telling you about.
Oh, wow.
The one they were tearing.
Wow, she's...
Look at how tall she is now, though.
Man, she's like a 30-foot woman.
Man, one pill makes you smaller.
Yeah, I was...
One pill makes you tall.
She took the tall pill.
I don't want to take no more of these pills.
We all took the small pills.
I took the...
Uh...
I took all the pills.
Oh, man, what's going to happen to me?
You didn't eat the mushroom, too, did you?
Yeah, I took...
Name it, what'd they give me?
I took it all.
The hamburger, the mushrooms on the hamburger...
You better just remember what the doormouse said.
...the green pills, the yellow pills...
Eat the hamburger!
Take your hand!
What if the rockets don't come?
Ah, don't worry, they're coming, all right.
Ain't nothing gonna happen to spoil my plans, baby.
I figured it all out.
It's time we told you, son.
We're not going home.
This is where we'll live from now on.
But what about the rockets?
What about Ohio?
More of what they want will be wherever we are,
because we'll want the same thing, too.
Um, we'll come back.
We'll have misery, son.
Only we'll have bliss this time instead of misery.
Exactly, my friend.
Dave has spoken,
Leepo has spoken,
Chaz has spoken,
Stang has spoken,
and we have spoken.
We have spoken.
This is the end.
And yet, perhaps the end is really a new beginning.
A new beginning for all of us.
Because if we can start again the same way we began,
then it'll all be simple.
We'll have a chance to redo all of those things that we weren't able to do before.
We can get it right this time.
That's right.
Can you imagine what it's like to go back and make it all right again?
It'll be like doing third grade all over again, only knowing everything that you know now.
No more knocks on your head.
No more kids picking on you.
Driving you down and making fun of your funny name.
You will be as unto a god.
A pair of shoes and a new account.
You'll have everything you want.
The water stops its flow.
You'll be safe at the end of a high sea.
You can stop and start again.
There's no place you can go.
You're as close to a god as you will ever be.
Take me, love me, and be what you'll be.
Be there then.
And I'll love me now.
I want to thank everyone who loves me.
Where's my wallet?
I want to thank Reverend Stagg,
and many other chows, and me, and everybody.
We'll see ya!
Goodbye, Mom!
I'll see you on the flip-flop, man!
Goodbye, Dad!
Catch you on the saucer!
I'm out of here!
I'm outta here!
Subscribe here for more fun отп比較
Please, subscribe on YouTube.
vegan.com
tutrtuok
I'm so sorry!
Are we done now?
Not yet.
Earth is finished.
We're going to blow up our rocket and start all over.
See if we can't build a better world up here.
Then he lifted his eyes to the deep ocean sky,
trying once more to see Earth
and the house he had always called home.
But Earth was too far away,
and the house was now only a heap of radioactive rubble.
Only one wall remained standing,
and within the wall a voice spoke again and again and again.
Not one would mind, neither bird nor tree,
if mankind perished utterly,
and spring herself, when she woke at dawn,
would scarcely know that we were gone.
That we were gone.
The whole world is waiting,
for this will decide the fate of civilization,
all humanity.
Whether we live or die may depend on what happens here.
Attention please.
Four minutes to bomb time.
Then close your eyes,
and tap your heels together three times.
And three times.
Think to yourself,
there's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
Stars are my home.
The world of...
...dimension X!
A googolplex is just as far away
from infinity as is one.
Well, infinity, you don't want to argue with infinity.
What?
It's not a number.
It's a state of consciousness.
Isn't it?
What?
Come on now, let's not try to think like three-dimensional beings.
Let's try to think like two-dimensional beings.
What?
In a binary world.
Yes.
Let's...
Ah...
That's what it's going to be.
What's that super excited that is?
Mis하하?
Is it a relaxing atmosphere filled with
rhythm?
What can I do for that?
Because I'm aware of this.
It's another day.
Look for it.
Watch the sky.
And the waves.
Yeah.
The waves of hot jams.
The waves of the molecule atomic.
My tears.
One.
One more.
Until it's tired.
I just don't try to change me.
I love those.
I've got to fly my own sweet way.
Life is.
Such a trippy thing.
Good God.
That I will ever see.
Hello.
Talking about it.
Each day on earth.
Is a day that's worth.
Remembering.
Each day on earth.
Is a day that's worth.
Remembering.
Every little boy.
Life is.
Such a.
Holy thing.
Don't pity me.
I'm glad to be.
A ding-a-ling.
jukin Song
Look up any remark from the
that marry
The
Do not
kiss
get
A
sing
b
ed
You have come to a God that you will ever meet.
It's a close call.
Sister.
You are close to the beginning.
Goodbye.
See you again.
Out here.
I am coming to you.
It's so close.
Out here.
I'm here.
...
O why?
I'm here.