Open your heart, unzip your pants,
close your mind and bend over
cause you're about to receive the word of Bob.
Do you wanna pour it down?
Do you wanna pour it?
Do you wanna?
Do you wanna pour it up?
You should love it!
Oh, yes, dear friends.
We're back.
That wonderful hour.
Friends, that bad hour.
That one-time hour, friends.
That mysterious hour.
That poltergeist-infested hour.
Friends, the poltergeist is working tonight.
Yes, he's working double time.
Because one of these tape decks won't turn off.
Get your finger out of the hole there, Dr. Stang.
You're liable to hurt yourself.
There you go.
There we go.
Well, let's turn on the dampers and see if we can get the nuclear power plant started here, Doctor.
I'm anxious to take off.
Take off.
Oh, wait a minute.
Would you get all those guys out of the other side there, please?
What'd you do, Doctor?
There, central control is on, Doctor.
Good, good.
Okay, you want to close the watertight doors here?
Yeah.
Oh, watch out for that squid, man.
There's a prairie squid right by the door.
What?
Speaking of which.
And inject some of those collar soles, would you, into the retribution chamber?
Primary and secondary circuit tests commencing now.
Well, we really are...
A swine, too, has a prayer request.
Is that so?
Well, friends...
Well, tell them to pray.
That's right.
They're just going to have to pray, friends, because Pastor Naked ain't here.
They've been injected now.
You know, like last week, we...
What?
We had the all-female callers, but...
And we wouldn't let any tool-using primates call in.
Tool-bearing primates, I believe is the proper term.
That's right.
And tonight, not even the tool-bearing ones...
Not even the faithful.
Not even the faithful will talk on the phone tonight, friends.
No, there's enough motor-mouthing going on here in the control room.
We don't need help from outside, because we've got to talk to you tonight about something...
Very, very important.
We're talking about conservation of a natural resource, friends.
Yes.
My dear friends, when was the last time you had you a good old prairie squid, eh?
Yeah, prairie squid.
Now, what sort of evocations does that name bring up to you, friends?
Prairie squid.
It even makes my microphone pop.
Well, we're going to...
Probably half of our audience doesn't even know...
What is that?
Half of our audience...
Our audience has probably never seen...
Well, you left the airlock open.
Yeah, that's...
That's what that is.
Oh, kill the airlock.
Yeah, well...
Okay.
Friends, let me tell you something.
First off...
Let's get serious about this, doctor.
First of all...
Cassette deck two...
Is not working.
And the ports on the starboard side are completely...
That's okay.
We're losing air fast, and we're going to have to try to keep up with it, friends.
We're all going to have to...
Church air over here, doctor.
Ah, yes.
Have a...
Now I feel considerably better.
Ah, yes.
Have a nice church air.
Oh, yes.
Praise God.
I feel that church air now.
Do you feel it?
Friends, can you feel it out there in the radio audience?
I bet you can.
Yes.
Reach out and feel it, friends.
And if you can't reach down and feel it, then you're going to...
You probably don't even know what a prairie squid is.
You probably don't even care what one tastes like.
When you were...
Now, I know about half our audience, Dr. Gordon, probably remember when they were teenage boys and girls out in, you know, West Texas or wherever they're from, going out in the fields and taking off their clothes and spreading some prairie squid bait all over, you know.
Yes, yeah.
What did you used to use?
I used jelly.
Jelly, mostly.
Yeah, I found...
Honey, whatever I could steal from my folks.
Peanut butter with bananas in it worked real well.
Yeah.
Yeah, I found that with...
And those...
Excuse me, I'm still...
Those...
Decompressants and all that trail we're talking.
Squid, would they be...
They'd be crawling out of the woodwork.
Out of the brush.
Out of the weed, so to speak.
You just lay there and wait for them.
And there you were.
And be quiet, because you'd scare them away.
They're very...
And, you know, it's just...
Just to give you an example.
Just like, do you remember back when you were a kid,
there were all those thousands of those little cute horny toads around?
And why do you think they called them horny toads?
Because they counter-exist.
You know, they're part of a symbiotic relationship with that favorite outdoor mollusk of ours.
Yes, and dare we say the name again?
The mighty prairie squid.
Oh, yes.
And, of course, as you know, Dr. Stang, I have just come back from a fact-finding tour
through the Amazonas regions of Brazil.
Yes, friends, just to fill you in exactly on what's going on here,
we have as our special guest tonight Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
Yes, indeed.
The erstwhile head of the Green Hill-Dobstown encampment
and now commandant of Dobstown II just outside Rio de Janeiro, Brazil.
Yes, friends, right on the coast where the surf is high and so is everybody else usually.
Exactly.
And, friends, you know, and this, what you're listening to, dear friends,
is the hour of slack on KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
Now that the uranium has warmed up, the airlock leak has been stopped,
I think it's about time we launched this show, Doctor.
I can feel the mighty thrust of that show lifting us up higher and higher.
Thrust, yeah.
As Dr. Motherspaugh's beautiful hymn, the Bobcata, plays in the background.
And maybe if I hit this tape deck hard enough.
Hit it hard. Here, wait a minute. Let me shoot it for you, Doctor.
Let's go. Hold on.
Please do.
Did it do any good?
I don't think so.
Felt good to me.
Yeah.
Well, look, why don't we just...
Let's kill that deck.
Why don't we just throw it away?
Why don't we just throw it through the plate glass window?
Okay.
Go ahead.
There it goes, friends.
And...
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, we're one tape deck short and four cards loose here, but...
But, friends, this is...
We're going to focus on an endangered species that probably, you know,
half of you who weren't raised in the South probably don't even know what a prairie squid is.
Maybe we ought to identify it, you know, just so people will know
who don't know what a prairie squid is, Doctor.
Perhaps we ought to at first sort of, as best we can,
define our terms and say that a prairie squid is really...
It's sort of a physical metaphor for a lot of things,
and it's probably exactly what you think we're talking about.
Well, it's not a metaphor.
It's an endangered species.
Yes, I know, but...
That used to live on prairies, and the fact that most of these callers don't even know what a prairie squid is.
Well, they don't even know what a prairie is.
It's all been covered up with...
Most of them.
...Los Colinas and all that kind of stuff, right?
Yeah.
Well...
Throw this...
Yeah.
At the same time, it is a metaphor for existence, Doug.
The very struggle of...
Who's Doug?
Of the prairie squid.
Doug, the guy over there.
The struggle...
The struggle of the poor...
Now, friends, you know, you do see prairie squids nowadays.
You can go to the supermarket and buy a dead, cellophane-wrapped...
Plucked.
...shaved prairie squid.
Yeah.
I mean, they...
It's shocking.
To us, to us old-timers, I mean, most of you, you...
That's the only way you're ever going to see it.
They've never seen them alive.
I know.
And a lot of people don't even know that they are actually a wild animal.
And, friends, that's such a waste because, frankly, frankly, what the prairie squid is
best used for is the sexual act, sexual congress.
And I'm, you know, I know this may...
We don't want to offend any radio...
But it's a well-known fact, Dr. Staines.
Yeah, I mean, you can look.
You can look in the encyclopedia under prairie squid.
Under prairie, under squid, sub prairie.
Or subgenius.
Yes.
And it'll say, subgenius, C prairie squid.
Exactly.
And, you know, yes, it is.
That's its best use.
And some people might find that offensive.
But they're the people that don't like to think about things like that because sometimes
they're not sure how to do things like that.
Or they're afraid that somebody will laugh at them if they said that they did something
like that.
Then they...
They have to...
Add them a prairie squid or two.
Oh, most of them think the prairie squid is a myth.
Oh, yeah.
They get real embarrassed if you talk about a prairie squid in polite society.
The polished ears of the rationalists.
Oh, yes.
The modernist...
The politically correct ears of the various groups.
The so-called humanistic.
Yes.
You know, if they were humanists, if they were really concerned about humanity, they'd
free the prairie squid prisoners.
And they'd quit killing prairie squids and make them...
Make in purses and shoes out of them.
Well, I mean, it's worse than killing whales for dog food, Reverend Stang.
I mean, if you think about it, I mean, at least you're benefiting some canines who would
otherwise not have anything else to eat.
But the very idea of killing and tanning prairie squid and turning them into purses and basketball
shoes...
It's repellent.
It's repellent to anyone who's really lived with nature.
Anyone who is really a nature-oriented person who's concerned about the environment would,
despite the stigma, despite the embarrassment...
They would be proud, Doctor.
They would be proud.
Nay, they would find it their Bob-born duty...
Duty.
Duty, my dude.
Duty, yes.
To seek out that prairie squid and protect them.
And nurture.
I mean...
And nurture that prairie squid.
Oh, look at this.
We got a note here.
There's an anti-Bob person online, too.
It's probably somebody who doesn't like this show.
Probably doesn't like to think about prairie squid.
They probably don't.
Let's go ahead and give it a try, shall we?
Well, if they've got nerve...
Get that microphone out of your ear, Doctor.
Hello?
Dear friend, can you hear us?
Nope.
Well, the poltergeists are back in the board again, Doctor.
And I...
Dear friend, are you out there?
They're blinking.
Sort of.
Ah, yes.
Well, the show that no one can talk to.
That's Reverend Ivan Stang and his little button that will not push.
Friends, I just...
I can't...
We can't do it without Buck.
He's the only person left who understands the technology.
That's why we really don't want to take too many phone calls tonight.
Is because next week, Reverend Buck Naked will be here at the controls.
And I think it's probably going to be an all-phone call.
I think it's going to be a phone show or something like that.
Yeah, it'll be another one of those phony shows.
And so, uh...
We're not handling too much of the phony work tonight.
But I know just what to do about this.
Instead of any real...
They said it was an anti-Bob...
They all want to be...
There's a common psychosis.
This anti-Messiah complex.
Well, it's the only way you see...
If you get your name in the paper as an anti-Messiah,
it's in the same size type as if you were the Messiah, you know?
They want to...
They link you to the Messiah by being...
I mean, guys that are saying they're anti-Bobs,
they're just saying that so they can have their name linked with Bob.
You understand?
Exactly.
It's a hate-love relationship.
They know they can't...
They aren't good enough to be Bob or to even serve Bob right.
And they're mostly anti-Squid people.
You know, you see them at these Squid suppression rallies.
Yeah, and...
You know, right...
No right to Squid.
You know, they got the no right to Squid move.
Yeah.
Burning records trying to stamp out Prairie Squid.
And those are the same kind of intolerant people who...
The only way they can react to something is to kill them.
If they don't understand it, they kill it.
They kill...
And if they can't eat it, they make socks or shoes or something like that out of it.
There's people out there that would kill a Playboy magazine
if they saw it crawling around through the bushes like a Prairie Squid.
Especially if they thought it would hurt them.
And since they're good for the same things...
Well, except that, of course, the Playboy magazine,
is by no means a Prairie Squid, Dr. Stang.
I'm sure that you and I know that perhaps a Playboy magazine
might be employed with a Prairie Squid, but certainly no such...
Man, I've never needed a Playboy...
Anything besides just the Squid.
The Squid itself is all one really needs.
Friends, a Prairie Squid, it's like a snail without a shell.
A really large, about a foot long...
They've got a light...
They're differing variations of color of hair and how much hair,
how curly...
Yeah, and where it's distributed,
and whether they're an elongated squid or a small, squamous, flattened-out squid.
And just as a snail is like one just...
It's a pseudopod. It's a big foot.
A Prairie Squid, friends, is a huge erogenous zone.
That's all it is.
A mobile erogenous zone.
And we're not talking about one of them camper conversion kits either.
That's right.
And this isn't some chauvinistic thing,
because I know a lot of country girls...
out there know what we're talking about,
because a Prairie Squid...
Well, it interfaces both ways, right, Doctor?
I mean, that's the beauty.
Without expensive interfaces, you can plug right into this amazing new pest.
I mean, you don't need attachments or rubber washers or anything like that with a...
It just one serves the entire family.
And back in the old pioneer days,
when they first came across this prairie from little towns up the northeast...
It was a family thing.
Yeah, sure.
You had the little Prairie Squid cage right there on the back of the covered wagon.
Everybody had them.
I mean, you nurtured them.
And now they're almost extinct.
Now you could cruise Turtle Creek from one end to the other
and never find an ambulating Prairie Squid.
About five years ago, I saw the first wild Prairie Squid I'd seen since my childhood
running around near Glen Rose, Texas, near the power plant.
So, well, who knows?
Maybe they'll be real big, glowing Prairie Squids in a few years.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe they'll be mutated Prairie Squids, you know?
I mean...
I mean, other things are changing fast,
and people's social habits are changing,
and perhaps one day, Doctor, perhaps one day,
the squid will...
In Bob's time.
The squid, if Dobbs is willing, will return...
After Bob comes again.
And the squid will.
The... Yes, friends.
Yes, after Bob comes the squid.
But I think...
I think now it's...
It's time for a phone call.
We'll go ahead and take a phone call here, friends.
But we're not going to answer.
Blue Mouse, call Johnny Normal's conference line.
And you guys let her talk, or she's nice.
Let her talk, or she's nice.
Okay, we'll be nice if you talk.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, there she is right now.
All right, let's see what she has to say.
Go ahead.
You don't even know why Rue Mouse...
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
I'm sick.
I come in peace, and this happens every damn time you put me on the defensive.
Well, first of all, you're not supposed to say damn.
So let's go...
Let's start that again.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hello, you're...
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Give her a chance.
Okay.
Okay, here's a chance.
This is your chance.
If you blow this...
Okay, I want you to know...
You're going to be in debt forever.
I want you to know that you're all on tape as violating the FCC rules,
so don't be sending people out after me.
I've got tape on you, fool.
Nothing's going to come out of me.
It's going to come back on you.
Dig dog's butt, Johnny.
Nothing will happen to me.
You're nothing but a hypocrite.
You self-righteous hypocrite.
You slug-dabbling...
Hadron of Hastor.
My father is Hadurter.
Hold on.
You're a self-defiling hypocrite.
I'm a surfer.
You know, that's what I am.
But I don't want to get into that.
Let's go to line number one.
Only three more minutes.
I'm sorry that that neurotic woman got on the air,
but you know what happens sometimes.
They get past our...
By all means, let's...
We're sorry.
I just can't believe someone would call in
and have the nerve to say things like that
about Prairie Square.
I know.
Not only that, but they call somebody else's show
using our airtime.
Using...
And our area code, for that matter.
That show that dare not speak,
speak its name.
K-N-O-N.
In Berkeley, out in California.
Oh, they're hip out there in California.
Oh, yeah, but they...
They're so hip, they've got...
Oh, they've got their crack, so to speak.
Yes, yes.
Their drugs and their wild sex.
But have you ever heard a person
from one of these hot tubbers
talking about a prairie squid, friends?
No, you never have.
Never.
They haven't heard about those...
They've never heard of it.
Those organic boys with their avocado dips
and everything.
They're city folks.
Yeah, they don't know about prairie squid.
Oh, they know everything.
They know everything.
But they don't know that.
And if you told them,
if you tried to tell them about it,
they'd think, oh, how quaint.
He's talking with his southern accent.
How folksy that...
Oh, he must be...
He must be near to the earth or something.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
But I'm an artist.
I don't have to lower myself to those...
to those demeaning...
I'm involved with such incredibly cerebral machinations
over the...
I'm politically minded.
I don't have to...
...the politically correct aspect of my art
and how it applies to prairie squid...
Yes, I'm not obsessed with...
...that I don't really have to think about
the humorous side of these things.
If there is a humorous side,
because I'm serious.
I'm from California.
I don't have to do veiled juvenile humor
guising as some sort of...
of highfaluting environmental concern
citizen satire.
Yes.
I'm not that kind of person.
Oh, no, no, no.
Of course not.
That's what they'll tell you every time.
That's the line they'll spring on you.
The sophisticated...
The sophisticated line.
The conspiracy is...
Their bourgeois line.
The conspiracy is insidious, friends.
Incredibly, they make you want what they have.
And they make you feel stupid
because you haven't got it.
Yeah, and they make you think it's better
than what you already have.
That way, once they get your attention
directed at what they have,
they can get your slack.
Your slack, friends.
That's right.
And you're a prairie squid, too.
And if as long...
As long as you're the kind of person
that can still...
You know, if you can find one,
you can go out in the woods
and have a short relationship
with one of these harmless animals...
Or a long relationship.
I mean, you know, like...
It's not...
There's no limited time.
The tantric sex magicians in India
and the ancient cultures of the Earth
have known of...
I mean, these are...
These creatures are not just common
to the continental U.S.
That's right.
And Reverend Stang,
I don't know if you know it or not,
but in Tibet,
they breed in the temples
a special variety.
Oh, the fattened special prairie...
The special prairie squid.
The soft squid, they call it.
Yeah, it's the one
that the Dalai Lama has.
Uh-huh.
And they still breed them there.
Those things eat...
And they have to ship them out to India
where the Dalai Lama is now.
You know, the Chinese let them
because...
They're better fed
than almost anyone in Tibet.
They're better fed...
Any human being.
They're better fed
than most of Tibet put together.
And, uh...
And, friends,
when you become a member
of the Chinese church,
of the subgenius,
you become eligible.
Yes.
Eligible, friends.
We'll give you
your very own
prairie squid direction
and survival package.
Give yourself
to the feeling, friends.
Remember to write
for information.
We don't want...
We don't want you
to send money.
We want you to send
your whole wallet.
That's right.
You can take the money out.
Just send us the rest,
especially those...
those little pictures
that you keep
in the secret compartment
that you don't show anybody.
We'll take the credit cards
and things, too.
Well, we'll take those.
But those little pictures
that no one else knows about,
that's what...
The Bob already knows
about those.
And we can judge
just how...
how...
how highly to rank you
in the great hierarchy
of this church.
And Bob collects them, too,
we might add.
And the better ones...
The better the pictures
that come out of that
little tiny secret
embarrassing compartment
in your wallet,
the higher up
the rungs you move.
Yes, friends.
And we also found
that one person
who sent his wallet in
had a picture
of a prairie squid in it
and didn't even know
what it was.
He thought it was
some curious...
some curious
little...
little life form
or...
or a blow-up
of a bacteria
or something.
And he'd been carrying it
around for years
because he felt
it gave him good luck.
And it did.
It did.
It gave him
incredible good luck
because it brought him
to Bob.
And you see
that just a picture
of a little thing
like a prairie squid
can set you
on the right path.
It'll put you right.
The path to Dobbs
and South.
Bob loves you.
Praise Bob.
And, you know,
if you could just
let go of those hang-ups
that have kept you...
that have kept you
tied down, friends.
You could...
Shackled by your own insecurities
was they might say,
Reverend Stang.
You know?
ignorance, your pathetic
ignorance. Your pathetic pink
ignorance is what it is.
Your ignorance of the subgenius
P.O. box number, which we were about
to forget to give. Oh, can we
do that? You bet we can. We have to.
Oh, well, in that case... Bob said we
had to party. Yes, well, that box
number... Why are you sitting there listening to this
radio show? Why aren't you out
partying? Bob said to
party. Party!
Bob said you had to party.
He didn't say you could. You had to party.
You better party. He didn't say you might
if you felt like it. Yes, indeed,
French. He said to get out there. Where's that
dirt? We want Bob says
to get out there and do it.
Bob says
find the squid.
Yes, friends.
Let's bring those squids back. Well,
well, well, in the meantime, we'll just
step back.
Someone said to Barry McGuire,
you're all the same.
You've all been brainwashed.
And Barry thought for a
moment, he said,
yes, that's true.
But you sinners have been brainwashed
also. The only
difference between you sinners and us Christians
is that us Christians,
we have chosen
to wash our brains.
That's a little rough.
And that doesn't sound
too good to the polished ears
of the liberals and the modernists.
So they soften it
down, you see.
And of course, they would read that verse.
Let God be true in every man.
Be an untruth in a measure to a degree by chance,
in my opinion, they say.
Yeah, let's soften that because somebody might get offended.
Yeah. But the Bible says, let God be true
and let every man be a liar.
Now,
to make these Christians into a political force,
they don't want us involved.
Let's tell them we're not listening to them anymore.
We're going to be involved.
It isn't going to take Ronald Reagan three years to learn about the godless, aggressive nature of communism.
Over the last two or three decades,
the federal government seems to have forgotten both that old time religion and that old time constitution.
I'm a little scared.
Now,
I'm going to tell you a story.
It's been a long time.
It's been 1984 since 1953, friends.
That's right.
That was probably the last time your parents told you about Perry's good.
After that, you know, there was a law.
Yeah, that you weren't even allowed to talk about it until the same law.
J Edgar Hoover passed on.
There was a law.
There's a law, friends on the books.
It says it says this.
No subgenius can do anything.
It wants.
Now, is this a free country?
Yeah.
When they, when they try to repressive.
I mean, now they they talk.
Oh, America, home of the free land of the brave.
Brave, brave enough to are they brave enough to talk about prairie squid?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
And they talk about can they talk about those two dogs we know of?
Oh, no, no.
Can't talk about them either.
But.
Yeah.
You know, and they're saying, oh, well, it's a land where we have free discussions.
But it's a democracy.
But you can only launch a bleeding head of Arnold Palmer on a Thursday night.
And they say, and not if it's a public holiday.
Yeah.
They got a golfer head can only be launched on on Thursdays in your own, you know, in the in the in the home of a consenting person.
You can't just go next door to your neighbors and launch ahead.
And the odds forbid you launch ahead in public like downtown on the.
The main square or something like that.
Friends, I want.
North Little Rock.
You find yourself in trouble with the county law, boy.
Yeah.
That you can tell them.
You can tell them.
Oh, but officer like doctors for Bob did.
You can say officer.
But but but I'm a bold surrealist, sir.
I'm a bold surrealist.
Oh, yeah.
We got bold surrealist.
We got we got 40 men hanging them from telephone poles up in Tucker that like to say they were as bold surrealists.
Yes, friend.
Yeah.
Oh, they'll.
Oh, yeah.
They'll tell you.
Kind of head.
Yeah.
They'll launch a sneed head.
Oh, yeah.
They'll they'll launch a Trevino forearm.
If you want.
Be careful.
Green straps the whole time.
The whole time.
Friends.
Friends, I want you to listen to this tape and I want you to meditate.
Meditate on this.
Moseurize and think about Prairie Squid and listen to this tape.
That's true.
They did.
But the head moved up or down.
And I can recall not too long ago, my father.
Uh.
Said to me while playing around at home, you're moving your head.
And I said, I don't think so.
I said, I'm keeping my eye on the ball.
And he said, well, you're keeping your eye on the ball.
Yes.
But your head is moving up and down.
Which I had worked into this unconsciously.
See Arnold Palmer unconsciously knew that his.
I realized.
And you his head had to be launched.
Yeah.
But that's not the real.
That's not the Arnold Palmer.
That you're thinking of friend.
No, no, no.
You're just not the guy that drives a tractor.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, no, no.
It's not the guy who sells, you know, oil based petroleum products.
This is, this is the, oh, forget it.
You don't even want it.
There's no way.
There's no way they can understand it.
Just, just right to that box number.
Yeah.
That box number friends for the church of the subgenius.
And we'll send you plenty of information about Prairie squids, golfer, head launch in slack,
slack, how to make.
And Reverend staying.
Uh.
You know, the good, the good sex for mutants dating league, I believe, you know, that's
right.
Yeah.
We, that's another church service since.
Since Buck sold the good sex for mutants dating league.
Well, he had to, he was just getting worn out.
You know what he sold it for?
It was, it was getting worn out.
It was wearing him out.
But you know, uh, you know what he sold him for?
All them hot mutants coming.
You know what he sold the franchise for?
No.
What did he sell a franchise for?
A bottle of ripple.
Well, that seems to be value received for value given.
If you ask me.
You can write to P.O.
Box one four oh three oh six in Dallas, Texas, seven five two one four.
You can get information and you don't have to send money.
You'll get lots of printed information.
It'll tell you where to write the good sex for mutants, uh, in salt lake city.
We'll send you, we'll send you the little maps of the, uh, of, of the, the, the known
existing Prairie squid wildlife refuges in your area.
If there are any, if you're fortunate enough to live.
In a part of the country where there are still a few of these precious creatures left where
they're still legal.
Yeah.
Well, they're not.
Oh, Dr. Dool, you just got back from the mutant, uh, beauty contest at the good sex.
I was one of the judges at the good sex for mutants, uh, dating league first annual, uh,
beauty contest in salt lake city just 10 days ago.
A Reverend Stan, those lovely, how were those lovely and disgusting subjeans?
They were, they were some of the most beautifully disgusting.
Mutated sickly creatures that I have ever seen.
Beautiful mutants.
And, uh, there was actually a close runner up.
She was voted miss.
Well, we think she was voted miss congeniality was actually a mutated variation of Prairie
squid.
Praise Bob.
And it was the biggest, the biggest Prairie squid that I have ever seen.
I say it was about 110 pounds.
Prairie squid.
And friends, if you just tuned in late, if you just tuned in late, you're listening to
the hour of slack on KNO and 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas, the, the vocal organ, so to speak of
the church of the subgenius.
And we are serious.
You really can write to us at get that pencil P O box one four Oh three Oh six here in Dallas
seven five two one four.
And uh, and we'll tell you about that good sex for mutants league.
It really is.
It really is a dating service for mutants.
Various minority cults like the Christians have their own special dating service.
God, I forgot to bring the questionnaire for that.
I was going to read it over.
It is hilarious.
Um, but, uh, and so we've got our own mutant dating service friends, and this is a church
for mutants.
This is a church for people who the only thing they have in common is that they have nothing
in common with the.
Constipation.
Friends.
And you know about the conspiracy and if you don't, then you're not a subgenius.
That's why that's it.
And they want to owe half of them out there that send us their, you know, membership,
love offering and get the magazines and the tapes, uh, and so forth.
They, uh, half of them out there aren't really subgenial at all.
Listen to those phones.
They're pathetically trying to reach us.
They have things they have to tell us.
They want to be healed.
They hate us.
They want to, they hate us.
They want to kill us.
They want to love us.
They want to ask us how we do it.
And mostly they want us to loan them money, which is, uh, and they want us to shut up
about prairie squid cause they're not going to embarrassed.
Oh, they turn.
So this is the prairie squid show tonight and we're dedicating, we are taking this valuable
church time to inform you about this very, very, very clear and present danger.
That is to say the extinction of the prairie squid.
Prespo, Prespo.
Oh yes.
Dear friends.
This is the beach, the Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the hour of slack on K and O M in Dallas, Texas.
Oh yes.
It's so true.
Thank you.
Lee Jing.
I got a call from China just this morning in the hot tub.
I'm going to call the high priestess of all Asia.
You know, when friends, if you had joined up, if you'd been the first person on your
continent to join up with the church, you'd be the Pope of this continent.
I know they, they Dr. G Gordon, Gordon, the Pope of South America, the entire continent
of South America.
And when those soul are the harvest friends, when we start collecting those souls, you
know, who's going to get to skim to skim that fine, fine layer off the top, out of the,
the soul rendering vat.
Don't you friend?
Oh, and they're trying to keep them from selling any kind of soul down there nowadays.
Oh yeah.
They, they, they don't used to be in the old days.
You couldn't give it away and now it's against the law to sell it.
So what are you going to do?
And then all the religions want to have your soul friends.
Bob wants your soul, but just temporarily he'll give it back after he's done.
He only uses it a little bit while he's got it friends.
That's something to think about.
He doesn't dry out.
That's right.
Friends as Jane or hyper cleats, uh, uh, the, the, uh, the trance spouter of all time,
Jane or hyper cleats and little rock Arkansas once said they, they said my mind was in this
jar and then they poured it down a sink.
I want you to think about that friends and Dr. Gordon, shall we go to the swing and love
corpses?
This isn't their brand new album that just came out.
It does have a, it does have a beautiful song about Prairie squid, right?
In the middle of it somewhere.
I just remember exactly which, uh, why don't we go ahead and roll that?
And I've got the small Prairie squid right here and we'll take a little, little while
the music's playing.
This is a swing and love courses, friends.
Dr. Philo.
Great song.
Great souls.
Great things.
Thank you.
No, I don't want to suffer.
Poor crazy pony.
She couldn't stop lunatic room.
No, I don't want to suffer.
No, no, she suffered.
So, as the sarcomeres contract,
thin filaments from the opposite ends of a sarcomere,
that is, the filaments extending from different Z disks,
meet at the center of the sarcomere when it's about two micrometers long.
As the sarcomere contracts,
as the sarcomere contracts further,
thin filaments from different Z disks
begin to overlap within the lattice of thick filaments.
The latticework of filaments becomes crowded in such a double overlap state,
and the sarcomere expands laterally.
Its cylindrical shape increases in girth.
This lateral expansion stretches the Z disks and other lateral...
You've got to see this guy for what he is.
He's a maniac, out to rule the world.
What can I do to make you understand him?
I love you.
Flying saucers, man.
No!
Cut!
I won't
I will only your wish.
I'll cut the cai Body of Heaven inanguished
And phrases
Like
No!
There is now increasing evidence that the connective tissue surrounding the individual muscle cells,
as well as the tissue linking the cells, also plays a role.
And I think that about sums up how the prairie squid actually moves, Doctor.
I'm sure, I'm very sure that our audience has been finally, finally so glad to know,
or at least feel like they can go out into the street and feel cool again.
Knowing about, you know, how they work, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what it's all about.
Chicago's youngest mother, an unnamed girl, at the age of 10 years and 8 months,
gave birth naturally in Chicago.
This is the second youngest in the United States when she was delivered of a 6-pound, 4-ounce girl.
Now, friends, you know, at the same time, he described it as pterodactyl-like.
It had a Brahma bull type of hump on the back, like a pelican's pouch at its throat,
and a 5- to 6-foot wingspan.
Not with feathers.
This was a reptilian thing.
And it was seen by a paramedic who worked...
This is for the Harlingen, Texas Emergency Medical Center.
While I was down there on the river and this big bird came down, man, it was tremendous.
Yes, big bird is back.
Probably hunting prairie squid along the edges of the Rio Grande River.
And, friends, somewhere at the edge of your mind is a sort of a tiny cluster of memories
that date back to human prehistory, to a time when every man, or in those days, they weren't men at all.
They were yetis.
Yes.
And the women, even the women, were yetis, too.
And in those days, friend, the prairie squid didn't have to live among horny toads to stay stimulated.
It was able to, let us say, converse physically with the yetis at any time that they wished.
You know, the yetis, friends, your ancestors, those of you who are true subgeniuses.
Except for that one variety of self-stimulating prairie squid.
Yes.
Doctor, which, as you know, became extinct in the late devouring period, I think it was.
Yeah, well, that was, there was, yeah, but that was long after the yetis were extinct themselves,
and that's probably what killed them off.
Now, I'm holding in my hand here a book titled Things You Never Knew Existed.
A very forthright compendium, friends, one might say.
And right here on page 44, there it is.
Squid.
Comma.
Prairie.
And there is an entire summation.
Now, you can get this information on this prairie squid by merely writing to the Church of the Subgenius.
That's right, friend.
And if Reverend Stang would be so kind as to give him that sacred box number really quick one more time,
and I believe we'll, uh, we might get a guest telephone caller as their lights are still on.
Well, no, it looks like he's drifted off again, Doctor.
Oh, we'll, we'll get one.
We'll get one.
Friends, that address to write to.
For more information.
About J.R. Bob Dobbs, the only, only individual who could save your soul and then give it back to you again.
That address for Bob is Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 140306, dear friend.
In Dallas, Texas.
75214.
And, uh, oh, friends, you don't know what.
What?
You don't know what, what could be coming your way in the mail once you sign up with this amazing church with your free information.
Uh, that you can find out the inside story on not, not just things like prairie squid.
You can find out why you've been losing at the races and how to start winning again.
You can find out.
How come you didn't get that big raise at your conspiracy job that you're nailed to?
How come that special date with her didn't work out?
And remember.
Remember that first time you found you couldn't do it for the second time.
Yes, friends.
That's the only almost as scary as the second time you find that you can't do it for the first time.
It's scary friends.
It's a scary, scary world out there.
People.
You won't have to see what you can do.
You won't have these problems if you just let Bob solve them for you.
Get right with Dobbs.
Get right with Bob into your life.
Let Bob into your heart.
You need Bob.
You have to have Bob.
You have to have.
You better have him.
You know, because I'll tell you, friends, when those have it, because when those end times come down, if you're not right with Bob, you're gonna fry.
And you'll probably deserve it.
You will.
You wish you could die.
Friends, you'll wish you could die.
But it'll be worse.
Bobby, he won't let you.
He won't let you die.
You'll be going, Bob, kill me.
Give me a car.
Please, Bob.
You didn't tell me the end times is going to be worse than a Sidney Sheldon miniseries on TV.
Me.
Friends, we're going to take that collar right now.
Where are we going to take it to?
Because our laboratory continues to be shaken under these conditions.
Squick.
It's been a long time since we were trapped by the line.
That's a squid ick for the uninitiated.
Yes, this is the show that continues to be trapped by the tiny corners.
An icky squid is a sticky squid.
We are forced to listen to you.
We always used to say at the academy.
That's right.
An icky squid is one that's actually icky.
And if you were just a collar, you're now listening.
What is ick theology?
What is your wick?
It won't make any sense.
It's a giant ickthyosaur.
No, you're asleep right now, and this is the ugly show.
Is that a squid?
It's all over northern central California at this hour.
And even people in the building refuse to listen to it.
Well, let's hear what that other collar has to say.
Okay.
Oh, he's calling another collar to see what he has to say.
He's calling another collar.
It's a chain reaction.
Call callers and find out what they have to say.
The last person who broke the chain, something terrible happened.
So don't do it.
Do what it says and call the next collar.
Call a collar now.
The last collar.
Disintegrated two U-quarks, a D-quark, and three pybasins.
Now, you can't.
Go ahead.
We let you speak if you're real.
I think all them three collars just pick up the phone and dial in.
They've been called.
There you go.
See?
Yeah.
Somebody else.
Tell us about your basketball game down there at Santa Fe School with all the eight-year-olds today.
Tell us about that.
Squid.
They talk about squid.
They talk about squid out there.
Yeah, they can talk.
They like to act like people who know what a prairie.
Squid is.
But anybody who called in icky squid.
Because they heard about it for months, frankly.
Yeah, of course.
I'll just throw these little wellmen down there.
Yeah.
Yes, that was one of the Hour of Slack shows out there.
Actually, that one's not.
That predates the Hour of Slack.
That's the more than an hour, less than a show show.
It's kind of a cut show, if you know what I mean.
But there's also, we just last week, a new Hour of Slack started up in Boston at the radio station with the MLS.
It's a great show.
We have a lot of people coming up on the MIT campus.
They're praising Bob, Dr. Bleepo Abernathy, and Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger of the Church of Mr. Science.
Praise Bob.
Some of you out there are lucky enough to be in correspondence with these individuals.
And we'll be playing some of their variation.
It's different.
It's a Yankee kind of thing.
But up in Boston, you know, they're a wild bunch.
There's some subgeni up there.
Feisty, feisty.
They're dangerous up there, Doctor.
They have to be.
They have to be because the audience is in Boston.
I have stood in front of, it was like the Alamo Friends, that time at the Spit Club, DeVival in Boston.
You know, we travel around and do DeVivals in other towns, not Dallas.
Dallas apparently isn't ready for, they want to call us a comedy act.
An act.
A joke.
A joke, they said.
Uh-huh.
They said it was a joke.
If that's an act, then those five people who left that club spit in Boston without any legs ought to get,
an Academy Award.
Yes, friends.
Copyrighted by DVD, 6J, or Hyper-V.
And, friends, I want you to think about, let's go to some, I haven't played this version of one of Buck's songs in a long time.
This is Onan.
Well, as Pastor Naked cannot be with us tonight, I think it's only proper that we.
That we not play his version.
But, Onan's, and here, somewhere in here.
Ah, yes.
Ah, yes, friends.
Somewhere in here.
The tapes are running backwards.
Bob's my friend, and he's leading me somewhere.
Let me in.
Is he waiting there for me?
Is that him waiting for me?
Bob's my friend, and he's leading me somewhere.
Leading me around.
What could be waiting there for me?
What's waiting for me?
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Stop them from killing me.
Ah!
Bob can't help me.
He can help.
But will he?
Will he help me?
He can help me.
Bob's my inner guide.
And he's leading my body.
He's my body.
He's even nice to my pets.
Nice is not super.
Bob's that little voice.
And he's not just a dream now.
Not just a dream.
The mightiest guru yet.
The mighty is.
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Not yet.
He can't.
Never put the love's ticket to Bill'so.
Possibly.
.. but said more than I need.
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Total-- Freedom!
And so did Kot nossos tn ca Diabo!
Live
What is waiting there for me?
What is waiting for me?
Help me somebody.
That was Dr. Onan's Wotan Band.
Yes, indeed.
He's the youngest doctor out there from Knoxville, Tennessee.
And a true crib fisherman.
Yeah, he's a crib fisherman.
He'd be fishing out of some cribs, I tell you, Bob.
Yeah, looking for some prairies.
Yeah, he'd be a squid fisherman.
Well, they do have prairie squid in Tennessee
because there is sufficient prairie there, or at least open lake.
Well, they have those gulch squids, they call them.
Yeah, they got some of that delta squid down around New Orleans.
But I don't know about that delta squid.
It kind of tastes muddy.
That's my favorite kind, boy.
Do you like that?
With red beans and rice?
Yeah, after you use them, I'll only eat them after they've been used.
Well, they aren't even good.
That's right.
They're tough.
You've got to soften them up a bit.
You've got to tenderize them a little, as the doctor would say.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
And find squid.
So I'll tell you.
Oh, this little famous piece of music is also by Dr. Onan.
I believe that's part of the Hour of Slack introduction at times, is it not?
Yeah, yeah, right.
He's got a new one on the way, a new digital Bob song.
See, everything's digital.
It's digital here.
We're not live.
That's why we can't take any calls.
This show has been entirely on...
Basically, you have to use the digits of your right or left hand to operate anything on this show.
That includes move the turntable around with your fingertips.
But we don't use turntables.
We only use broken tape decks here on the Hour of Slack.
And friends, praise Bob, a tape deck can be smashed to pieces.
But if it's needed for the Hour of Slack, it will...
Praise Bob and pass the Habifrop Zip-You-Lops, doctor.
Oh, yes.
Let's step into a quick moment.
From a subgenius revival.
This was the last one in L.A.
You were there as security, running security.
And Bob got shot again anyway.
Oh, yes.
But this time it was one of those dispensable Bobs.
Yes.
He was afraid to go out there.
He knew the guy that wore the Bob mask in L.A.
And it was a Bob mask.
I mean, Bob, the real Bob, wouldn't go in L.A. at the Alexandria Hotel.
Yeah, he certainly wouldn't be seen at the Alexandria Hotel.
That's for sure.
In fact, I didn't even want to be seen at the Alexandria.
In fact, nobody wanted to.
The only thing that was really seen was obscene.
And that was that obscene big dead rat that was in the Pope of New York's breakfast table or something like that.
I forget it was.
That's the way popes are treated in L.A., friends.
That last year.
Last year.
Oh, speaking of popes in L.A., doctor, before you play that, I think we ought to...
Most people don't know that the Pope of all Arkansas, who's on temporary combat duty in Los Angeles,
reaffirmed his nuptials.
Yes, he did.
He did.
And he did it the subgenius way, too.
He got...
It wasn't...
He had already gotten a short-duration marriage.
That's right.
From Pastor Naked, the official one.
He already had the paperwork.
He did have the paperwork.
He would have sanctified couplings, friends, for the last few years.
But their short-duration marriage ran out.
And rather than send Buck any more money, they went to Las Vegas and had one of those parlor chapel,
as Norm just told me they're called, a parlor chapel wedding.
Marriage parlor.
Yeah.
When he left the chapel, this acolyte came running in.
You know, it was one of those ten-minute ceremonies.
This guy actually had the gall to come running out going,
Sir, there's supposed to be a $25 tip, quote, tip, unquote,
to which Pope Sterno threw down a dollar and said,
Sir, kill me.
That's right.
But we should say congratulations to Pope Sterno and his faithful ubermatrix,
that is to say, Miss Dottie.
That's right.
And they're creating more little yetis, friends.
Yes, sir.
They are.
They are further contaminating the gene pool.
Sterno's father, the way he became a subgenius was his father was one of the guys who had to stand on the Nevada desert
and face nuclear tests from about half a mile away.
Wearing only goggles and a lead-shielded jockstrap.
Mm-hmm.
Duck and cover, baby.
You betcha.
But they weren't allowed to in those days, and the result is thousands of subgenius children of those selfless servicemen
who gave their genitalia.
Genetic structure.
Gave their genes for...
For nuclear dominance.
There you go.
And rather than...
I was about to play that Hal song from the L.A. Divival,
but I think instead we will, Dr. Dool, dare to play this live report from L.A.
Sterno, we're going to you now.
This is Dr. Sterno Docs and Dr. Byron Verner of Famous Potatoes organization in Los Angeles.
Can you hear Sterno?
Sterno?
Gee, bow.
Bow-gey, bow-gey, bow-gey.
Yep, that's them.
Bow-gey, bow-gey.
I'm having trouble.
I don't think they can hear us.
Sunset Boulevard.
Bow-bow-bow-bow-gee, bow-gey, bow-gey-gee-gee.
At this moment.
Bow-bow-gee.
Eat a bow-bow-gee.
Bubba Gee
Well
I don't really
Bubba Gee
Much
Much out of the limits of
That sounds like Los Angeles
Alright
Better check in that purse might be a snapping turtle in there
A snapping turtle
Did he say doctor
Gotta watch out for the coodles
About going into these
Lesbian snapping turtle bars
Lesbian coodle bars we call them
We told Doug about them yesterday
The other Doug
The famous Doug
That's another place friends
It's not the same thing anymore
Where you can get those
Prairie squid
Drinks you can actually get prairie squid
Drinks
They put them in a blender
With protein powder
And just turn them into a really
It's like
Kind of like a daiquiri
In texture
But it's not the real prairie squid though
It's the flash frozen stuff
I mean nobody
Nobody does it with a live prairie squid
Praise Bob
Well dear friends
It's time
For a moment of
Threadity and melody
Yes if you'll turn to page five in your program
I'm going to lead you in the hymn
Which we call
Bob is a
This is my story
This is a hymn which is usually performed
In moments of extreme stress
And such I judge this to be
It's very easy
And you can support me on the second verse
And the chorus
If you choose
So we'll sing Bob is my story
Page five
I saw a man
With a pipe and a grin
All in my life
A new morning light
Smiling at me
Like a madman
Till he
Made me uptight
I told him
Don't bother me anymore
But he kept on
Just the same
Till I was totally
Brainwashed
Bob is his name
This is the chorus
He is my story
Bob is my song
Bob my amphetamines
All the day long
But I won't tear my poster of dogs down
I'll feel no sadness or shame
Till I rejoin him in dogs town
Bob is his name
I'll feel no sadness or shame
He has no lack of his patented slack
For those of his following four
He is the friend of whoever will send
Green bags or gold
He's growing stronger and stronger
But he keeps redder than flame
I'll be a pig boy no longer
He'll be a pig boy no longer
Bob is his name
Bob is my story
Bob is your story, friend.
And Bob is your fame.
Bob is the glands that keep you feeling the way you do.
Keep your squid juices pumping.
Bob...
Well, that's held by the old digital counter on the wall, Reverend Stang.
Yes, we're coming down. We got three minutes left.
Three minutes of slack time, friends.
And I could play some Burblin background noise,
or I could play the official sign-off tunes and so forth, but...
Well, we could just talk for another three minutes, but...
We easily...
Easily.
Easily, yeah.
We could talk for another three hours, friends.
Or three days, if that's what it takes to get you to write to that sacred post office box.
You've been hearing the learned old scholars of the Church of the Subgenius Society tonight.
That's right.
And learned we are in the dark knowledge and forbidden sciences
of time control, slack extraction...
And the arcane secrets of the prairie squid.
Friends, are you gonna put up with what the gland owners are laying down on you?
I want you to either stand up or shut up, baby.
That's right. Praise Bob.
You gotta hip out to it or die trying not to.
Or just kill me.
That's right. But, Dr. Gordon, I am going to use this last two minutes to play something I...
I always mean to play and rarely do, and that's the credits for the hour of slack.
Yeah.
Even though all of these people weren't...
Being as how that's the only money those people get is the credits, maybe you ought to roll them once in a while, Reverend Stang.
That's right.
Roll those credits.
The problem is they're an hour and a half long, so...
Friends, Norm Ward and the Monday Morning Creatures will shut off this tape at the proper allotted time.
Praise Bob or kill me.
Help me, somebody.
My legs are on fire.
She ain't got no legs.
Pull the lever.
Down you go.
The voices, tapes, music, and editing you've been listening to come from...
...Jalebo Abernathy...
...The Buck, Naked, and the Jaybirds...
...Dr. Odan Canobite...
...G. Gordon Gordon, Killer Fruits...
...The Lion...
Help me, somebody.
She ain't got no legs.
...Doctors for Bob...
...Dr. Philodrummond, Overman, First Degree...
...Reverend Cleve, Donut, Duncan...
...Dr. Snavely Eklund...
Cash in on radio the easy way.
Hey, we're only kidding, too.
We're not even on the air.
We're asleep.
This is the cave.
Now that you have paradigm perspective, let's move on to the shift in paradigm.
This is Dr. Ahmed Fishman.
This is Glass Madness.
This is Herr Dr. Chris Gross.
This is Hell's Mommy Satellite G-Birds.
...compatible with all religions.
And this is Negative Land.
These are those fantastic swinging love corpses.
These are doctors for dinosaurs.
These are doctors for Wotan.
This is Gary Gabrog Fran.
This is Saint St. Amor by Prodigy.
As a whole, Dave Trager okay, about to blow that shit out out.
This is Arch-Pope Sternodoxiog Chexius...
...are we gonna help me up, thought.
This is D.K. Jones.
This is Palmer Readings of the tips of lies foundation.
Hi Palmer.
And this is the Pope of all New York.
You might say to me, Ram Day!
Bob!
Are we on?
Yep, we're just about on.
This mic doesn't work.
You have to turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
My name is Franz Ivanovich Hagen.
And this is the news.
Wake up, Pope boy!
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I am Pope Legend!
No trouble.
Get set.
Get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Chapter 13.