What does that red button over there do?
Go ahead, please.
Once upon a time, in a famous story,
a girl named Alice got very curious about a little white rabbit that passed by.
She followed him, and soon found herself falling down a very deep hole
into a strange place called Wonderland.
This is A Voice of Colossus.
The voice of God.
The choice is yours.
Obey and live, or disobey and die.
Quiet, numbskulls. I'm broadcasting.
The Soul Juice.
Unless they have control of your radio, too.
And I do, too.
Good. This is Ren Hwock.
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall kill you.
Thank you for listening.
I write just for you.
But others hearing this may find
things they would argue.
I do not sing what I believe.
I only give them facts.
If they believe quite otherwise,
it still will have impact.
I do not sing what I believe.
If they believe quite otherwise,
It will still have impact, my friend.
Thank you for listening.
That was L. Ron Hubbard singing,
the founder of Scientology.
And this, dear friends,
is Hour of Slack number 795.
We survived the sixth annual
end of the world drill
and brought back many recordings
of that spirit-filled weekend
at our survivalist campground
in Sherman, New York.
But Sub-G and I the world over
celebrated X-Day,
including this promising new band,
the El Queso All-Stars.
Now check out the show.
Check out this song,
Planet X or Bust
by the El Queso All-Stars.
Planet X or Bust by the El Queso All-Stars.
I cut my finger on a soup can lid.
I got an infection and it spread to my dick.
It swelled up to the size of a human head.
And then a mouth opened on it.
And this is what it said.
It said to kill the pink boys.
Put your job,
mock the world and worship Bob Dobbs.
We'll build a ship and take a trip.
Come on and get up here, write the coordinates.
Three and a half months in my garage,
tearing parts off of old used cars.
My groin at this point,
it was unusual.
I was given occasionally hum
while smoking cigars.
Our project was finished.
This ship would hold 20.
The power source was anything
the crew would think was funny.
We didn't need this lacklustre hapless.
Our merc-group is worth it,
escaping a star fist.
On our way to Planet X for sex,
the next next.
The parries quit and Harry Potter money shot a connie twop.
It's an all-haas hour of bonanza.
It's like a world without Tony Danza.
Or Banza, the pink shit that gets the charts.
In a world of death arc,
simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy.
We take a moment and we pause to reflect.
On the pinks that we killed,
and the planet that they wrecked.
Then we laugh like banshees,
and howl like our manjees.
We're a victory dance,
in our under-roos and panties.
Our fantasy is a reality.
Earth turns to dust.
Planet X are bust for us.
As Bob's pipe is lit,
space and time shift.
A temporal disturbance.
The contents of the flag were
a ten-dimensional split.
Severance forever,
sub-geni for pink shit.
Bob walked in a circle,
and steadily exhaled in the smoke,
I can see why the pink boys fail.
DNA's has con-destruction.
Sick and full of slack with suction.
Pay-per-view alien abduction.
Functioning on source slack.
The money should be painted black.
The leak from space that stole your balls.
Will soon come back and take it all.
Return to slack, return to bars.
Repent slack off and quit your jobs.
The smoke of the BCR.
Bob hungry.
Lick and throbbing,
day to the slave.
Now you're sleeping like a babe.
Bob will be up to keep on the job.
Guys be talking with the UFO in his garage.
I cut my finger on a soup can lid.
I got an infection and it spread to my dick.
It swelled up to the size of a human head.
And then a mouth opened on it.
And this is what it said.
It said to kill the pink boys.
Quit your job.
Mock the world.
And worship Bob Dobbs.
We'll build a ship and take a trip.
Come on and get a pen, write the coordinates.
Three and a half months in my garage.
Tearing parts off of old used cars.
My grind at this point was unusually large.
It would occasionally hum while smoking cigars.
Our project was finished.
The ship would hold twenty.
The power source was anything you could think was funny.
It's lackless, they're hapless.
Our birth proof is worth it.
Escaping a stark mix.
On our way to Planet X for sex and rex next.
The very sweet Harry Potter money shot iconic walk.
It's an all-haas hour of bonanza.
It's like a world without Tony Danza.
A fan to the pink shit that hits the charts.
In a world of dead hearts, I believe in this lobotomy and sodomy.
We take a moment and we pause to reflect on the pinks that we killed in the planet that they wrecked.
We laugh like banshees and howl like Karanjis.
We're victory-digging in our under-oos and canyons.
Our fantasy is a reality.
Earth turns to dust.
Planet X are but for us.
Depress the eddy blood that flows in your veins.
Let the froth-pot-pot breathe slack like rain.
Let Bob control what's left of your brain.
Oh yeah, send all your money to the Reverend Island stand.
Depress the eddy blood that flows in your veins.
Let the froth-pot-pot breathe slack like rain.
Bob control what's left of your brain.
Oh yeah, send all your money to the Reverend Island stand.
Planet X are but for us.
The El Queso All-Stars, my friends.
I love that song, especially the ending.
And there's a lot more of their music at www.mp3.com
slash El Queso All-Stars.
El Queso All-Stars.
But let's get back to X Day.
Dave, what else do you remember?
There were a number of weird sightings and things going on.
As usual, and I even told Reverend Toth as we were walking off to have his friend try and bite my foot.
Or no, to get some oil and stuff.
There was a huge X in the sky.
Again? When?
It was around about an hour before the gig and that Friday night.
Before you guys played?
Right, as I was off to oil land, Toth pointed up the sky and said, look at that X.
And I thought, that's stupid.
And I looked and there was a perfect huge X of two planes crossing.
That was a lot more impressive the first day in 1998 at 7 a.m. when there was a giant X in the sky.
Now, it's like, well, how come there weren't four big X's to match four X days since we've been let down four times in a row on this so-called destruction of all the universe?
Bob!
Why would there be an X at any time, though?
Just think, you know, your synchronicity cabbage is not correctly hued.
Your monster is gone asleep.
I'll tell you why there's an X.
Because the conspiracy jet airplanes make those X's so that the satellites can have a, they have a, that's the way they keep the maps.
The coordinates.
The maps and the coordinates.
Right.
To track the disease germs and so forth that they spray with those big X's.
That's the hit spot then.
In other words, your mark, as they used to say in the final career of sociopathic acting.
What?
Bob!
What's that mean?
paogleæ
There's no way you can trap the world's mostottles and do shit like that about a man, right, or a person, and try to prune a manPoint
You sooner than you've ever done.
You saw the light of him, eh?
I'm just trying to see what you'rehistorykick to it.
I've set up a Bush I can similar Isữa toRIID IELа participant in PubgComic callhumre
When the Nahas start generation of titans helping Ocelan that might complicate This show
live will be an opportunity for you to develop your properly working life for your
society.
Don't, don't, don't, don't you, you, you, you, you believe it
I'm a human man, my balls could fly
Sir, are you about to find a human?
Negative, I am a meat popsicle
Possess me
Dot, dot
Goddamn, the Jehovah's Witnesses can't have a cute guy
That's right
Goddamn, Goddamn
Revenge
We have coffee
We have healthy
Drink Bar
Thank you.
There's a new rule for the pagans this year.
We like to call them pay and pay again.
All pagans must pay twice to get into the subgenius festival.
Please don't feed the pagans.
I like when you're walking by the pagans and they're like peeing or like jacking off in their cage.
Meeeeee.
Even their own shit.
Hi, how are you?
Yeah, I have a question for Reverend Stang.
Yeah?
Okay, I've heard about all these alien sex goddesses that are supposed to service the subgeniuses after the world blows up.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I just have a question about them.
Next year.
That has been delayed just slightly apparently.
It is a riddle darker than it is being discussed right now.
What was the question?
Well, I'm just trying, well, I mean, what if you're a female subgenius?
Do you get an alien sex goddess?
Or what if you're a gay or lesbian subgenius?
What kind of a sexist are you to distinguish between these so-called human genders?
You may have any procreative special you like.
Hey man, it's a goddess.
You may have a cigar in your butt.
It could be a cigar in your butt.
It could be you.
It could be a mirror.
It could be your right hand.
Sometimes I change into all sorts of people for you, baby.
I'm so glad when you do that too, baby.
I know.
When you're the third person from the left is where the way I like it the best.
You don't understand, man.
The subgenius babes are more manly than pink men.
Baby, what kind of question is that?
It's not a question.
It's a demand against us.
You don't question the word of Bob.
You just don't question it.
No question.
What kind of a religion do you think this is?
Some rationalist, humanist, logical thing where two plus two equals four?
I'm sorry.
This ain't that kind of religion because this is the kind of religion that works, damn it.
And you can't use it.
You can't mess it up with logic and your serious so-called sciences and philosophies.
It works all night and you wouldn't understand, man.
No, how could you understand, especially dressed the way you are?
Your mother is ashamed of you and your father has desecrated our own graves.
Hold on a second.
I've got to go drink cranberry juice.
These holy stones which you're standing and defecating on now are the remnants of a past,
past ancient empire.
Ah, my heart throbs in my little teeny tiny bird chest when I think of it.
Of course, my brain says,
Oh, thanks, guys.
The stems are being sucked into me.
And now, friends, Reverend Armand Gettin, live at 4X8 with Saint Anne on the keyboard.
Good day, Harry.
Woo!
Hello, hello, hello.
Where'd you all put your monkeys?
I see them all out there.
Monkeys!
All fucking monkeys!
Woo-hoo!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Ah!
He's a vector fax cop.
What the fuck's a vector fax cop?
Billy!
Willie, are you a veteran?
You know, there were a lot of people who found out Brad Pitt was in the fac- club.
And they—
I hear a lot of people says that, oh, the church of the sub genius, they're just like
escribal .
It's just like a ficlub.
But if not, it's because of ficlub they fucking did something!
Yeah.
I had to go see him-
Oh, my notes are...
You know, I don't know how long it's been since I've seen
a mob spray-painted under a bridge
or on the side of the road or on a high school.
That fucking sucks.
You people, you don't know how to recruit.
Keep recruiting for bobs.
More women!
And more women!
Man, fuck, it's not that hard.
You just gotta do something.
Fuck does not equal laziness.
I mean, how hard is it to go to Kiko's
and print up 100 bobhead flyers and just post them?
I remember the days when old flag ruled Houston.
Everything ended up on old flag.
Not just the old flag.
It's the fuck one.
We should be running the worldwide web.
All in the talk shows.
Start your own TV show.
Do you know how easy it is to start your own TV show
on cable access?
Under $50.
Easy.
Because I like my club.
The first rule of the church of the subgenius is
to always talk about bob.
Yeah!
The second rule.
Is to always fucking talk about bob.
Recruit, recruit, recruit.
I cannot stress that enough.
If only 1% of America were subgenius,
that would be over two and a half million.
That would be over two and a half million.
I'm the most subgenius!
Yeah!
Because, folks, I don't know a little with you here.
We're not about quality, we're about quantity.
It's all about volume, volume, volume.
The more subgenius, the better.
You know that Jesus works a conspiracy job because he fucking has to?
It sucks! I work a fucking conspiracy job!
You are a conspiracy!
You're out of your house, boys.
The fuck do you care?
I swear to God.
X-Day, X-Day, Sidney, bigger than Starwood, bigger than Burning Man, whatever the fuck that is.
Bigger than the fucking Super Bowl!
People make me sick.
I'll tell you why we're still on Earth.
We're still on, we're still on Earth.
Because the fucking crop is not worth reaping yet!
All in one, I don't even want one percent of America, a half a percent, one million subgenius, is that so much?
Is that so much?
No!
It's so...
Listen.
I have a homework assignment for all of you.
Everyone here.
Next X day.
Because there will be a next one.
Hopefully the last, but probably not.
Because you're all a bunch of slackers.
Next X day.
Bring a friend.
Bring a friend who's never been to X day.
It will instantly fill up all the population.
You keep that up.
And what was the percentage of the law there?
We will have one million sub-GAs by 2010.
One million sub-GAs.
We won't need Russia.
We'll need the entire fucking upstate New York.
We'll be a state of sub-GAs.
Can you imagine a Coney Island calendar?
A 52-week Coney Island calendar.
That's all.
52 weeks.
Two for every week.
That's all I have for you.
Not that you're going to pay attention
or all of it, whatever.
Next thing.
You're not going to pay attention.
Look at that!
It's going to be real!
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi!
Hello, everyone.
I talked to you last year
and I yelled.
I screamed.
I'm not going to do that this year.
Last year I was ranting
in favor of stress
against slack.
This year, I'm ranking against sex.
And I'm going to be revealing DNA's plan for you, and you, and you, and all of you.
Not a pretty picture.
Now, you've got to ask, why rank against sex?
Why rank against DNA?
There isn't anything you can do.
It feels good to do it.
It's like a frat boy just giving that good, beefy, pink chuckle.
Yeah, man.
You know, don't go along with it.
Take a look at that gift horse's mouth.
Doesn't it smell like a rat?
Isn't there something there?
Hmm, maybe DNA is not our friend.
I don't know.
Anytime.
I'm being pushed into something.
I get nice and stubborn.
I dig at my feet.
I don't want to go any further.
Until the feedback stops.
I'm going to tell you something.
Some conclusions I've come to about sex.
About DNA.
About the pull.
This is the pull of DNA.
The Pavlovian ring.
The deep animal sound.
Sexy, ain't it?
When the sex surge.
Kicks into gear.
The human polarity.
Switches.
North becomes south.
South becomes north.
When that happens, mental thinking stops here.
Continues in the smaller brain below.
Yes, humans have two brains just like the brontosaurus.
And I don't mean the apatosaurus.
I mean the brontosaurus.
They took away our brontosaurus.
But I know they're still out there.
Various symptoms of this switch in polarity.
Tunnel vision.
The bees in the head.
The red shift in the color.
Sweat.
Steam.
You know, you act like the cartoon wolf in the nightclub.
All the Tex Avery-isms.
The loss of inhibitions.
And the ease with which the money can be extracted from the victim.
The highly suggestible nature.
This is all small brain thinking.
It robs the higher thinking.
This is not necessarily a good thing.
Let's move on.
DNA's plan for you.
DNA isn't concerned about you as an individual.
Doesn't give a damn.
Doesn't give a damn about population explosion.
Doesn't give a damn about anything other than marching forward.
And you only get to make a couple of those footsteps before you're out there.
You're out of the picture.
DNA wants you to be born.
Grow up.
Fuck.
Reproduce.
And die.
Yes, die.
DNA doesn't want you to do anything after you've given birth and raised that kid up a little bit.
You're out of the picture.
DNA turns off the healing in your cells.
So that you can't fight cancer anymore.
You can't fight the infections.
You stop repairing yourself from within.
Does that sound like a good thing to you?
Does that sound like your friend there?
Is DNA your friend?
No.
No, it wants to call that bell that the magnetic forces shift to the little brain.
Oh, gotta get out there.
Gotta get some of that tail.
That poontang.
Excuse my expressions.
This is not something that one would choose.
But we don't have any choices.
We are crack babies on DNA.
We have this tingler inside of each and every cell twisting us to its whims.
This is not a beneficial thing.
This is not progress with an end product in line.
This is just a mad beast stumbling forward.
It doesn't care if the creature it evolves into is any good.
It'll keep going.
And maybe that's the strength here.
DNA loves mutations.
Maybe that is our strength.
Because you, and you and you and you, all you people here, you are mutations.
That's obvious.
Like Reverend Stang was telling you, if you weren't fucked up, you wouldn't be here.
But that is our strength.
So how can we fight DNA?
I mean, how can we disengage this automatic urge?
This animal call to breeding?
Those are all good ideas.
There's self abuse.
There's abstinence.
Purity of essence.
Peace on earth.
All in all, you're just another prick in the hole.
You can turn gay.
Castration.
Heaven's gate.
No.
Terence McKenna and his brothers.
And his brothers.
He used to think that, well, when they were on mushrooms once, they heard this great insect sound of a higher intelligence, they thought.
And it made a certain vibratory sound.
He thought, and they tried to put this into action, that if you could get high enough on mushrooms, bellow out this sound as strongly as you could, it would unlock your DNA and let the mushroom molecules bond with the DNA.
Did it work?
Not yet.
That's not to say that it won't work.
You gotta hit that note just right.
And even so, what then?
What happens when the human being is bonded with a mushroom?
Where do we go from there?
Mushroom god!
Horseshit!
Sounds good to me.
But that's the thing I'm trying to encourage.
We've got to get in there on a cellular level and disengage this thing.
So you can do a little bit of a countdown.
Now, I know, I sound like a crank up here.
Don't believe me, do your own experiments, keep your eyes open.
But I tell ya, I'd rather be a big crank than a little cocky. Thank you.
Say Barnes-Lerner, dear friend!
I'm a frog watcher. I'm gonna be the number one frog watcher around here.
You must be one of the hierarchy, I've heard of them, they're the famous subgeniuses.
Are they naked yet? I heard they were deformed.
Where are the frogs for me to watch? I'm a frog watcher, like Dr. Lagoon said.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, there's not much ammunition for a frog watcher here, Jesus.
There's nothing but naked, ugly men.
Go ahead. Be spectacled, naked men.
Bless the frog watchers.
I pray that he may someday become a tadpole.
Bless the pornographer.
Bless the bootleg pornographer.
Bless the pervert.
You are all unclean.
I'm not touching you without protective garments.
In the presence of the Lord, Reverend Ivan Stang himself, and Ed Strange the Baptist.
You are here to be cleansed of your sins, so that you may sin more.
Reverend John, have you been unclean? Have you sinned against man, God, and nature?
Of course.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
Praise God.
Are you prepared for the preachers to wash away all the sins of the world?
I am.
Do you reject the spares seen all these away?
Absolutely.
.
papers that I'd read. I thought of Arnold Palmer and his bleeding head. I thought of all my
brethren and France that they'd shared. I thought of all these things and wondered if I cared.
I pondered for a while. I pondered through the night. By the next morning, I decided they were
right. We got France elections in a white array.
I felt so relieved. It really was a rush. I am so happy that I'm a subgenius.
I'm tired of playing normal and following the herd. I awoke the next day.
To go and spread the word. The people that I talked to, they acted all afraid.
They won't even listen unless they're getting paid. I really do hate them,
these things of which I speak. They pointed and they laughed. They said I was a freak.
This is I, so socialize. Open up your ears and clean out your eyes.
Who's in the world? Do you want to?
Fight. It's against the system. We should unite.
Fight, fight, fight, fight.
Now I sit here thinking about everything I've said. I really am a folly. My face is turning red.
I thought I was finished. I wondered what to do. Ready to give it up. I didn't have a clue.
Then it all came to me. I really should have known.
There are so many like me.
I'm really not alone.
I found others like me with whom I could convert.
One thing that's so genius will rule this universe.
No!
Yes, I am a body. I don't care if it's true.
Yes, I am a body. There's nothing you can do.
I don't care if you like me.
It means nothing to me.
Bodies are here to stay and someday you will be.
I spent my thirty bucks. I got my medicine card.
My husband's a nephar and it wasn't all that hard.
I'll start my own ministry and it will be the first.
Bodies are not so bad. We really are not cursed.
I'm a genius. I'm a genius. I'm a genius.
I'm a genius.
So now you know my story. There's nothing I've left out.
I've tried to tell the truth of what it's all about.
Yes, I am a body and proud to say it's so.
Yes, I am a body and a black of dynamo.
I am a true yeti and yes, it makes me proud.
I am a so genius and I'll say it out loud.
I don't care much for pink and the things that they say.
The Church of the Genius will soon have its day.
Evangelop, how was your ex day in general?
I mean, considering the fact that our religion is once again shot down,
proved to be a bunch of malarkey, a false prophecy.
A sham.
A sham of two paradiddles of a squam.
An old stinky haddock of a religion.
And you had a good time anyway?
A dried, greasy fried old fish that's been on the line for some twenty, twenty twenties.
We met this sketchy guy on the way home.
Yeah.
Our first contact, our last contact with people outside of Brushwood before we got to Brushwood was a policeman who pulled us over.
And then our first contact with people outside of Brushwood after we left was this guy.
In the back of, he was in this car that was very expensive and he had a cigarette and he said,
Can I please have a light?
And he said it in the most hushed voice he could possibly use.
And he goes, can I have a light?
And I'm like, okay, hold on a second.
I went to get him a light and we were wearing our cute little nineteen year old, twenty two year old clothes.
And he was gonna kill us.
How exciting for me.
He was probably from the Blue Heron Festival.
He said it so hushed in a low, low voice that, and then he said, and then he said to us, um,
Do you want to come to a hotel?
Because I'm going with the man in the car next to me.
Oh, he was trying to get you to go to a hotel.
And Dan too.
Young, young, innocent looking Dan and you.
I think in his head he wanted us to be the two young kids in the corner watching.
Ah, but only in his head.
You don't understand.
His head is such a small place and your car and the motel room and the whole arena is such a huge place.
I'm kind of surprised you didn't know that.
You didn't go with him and then kill him and suck his brains out.
Yeah.
And rob him and send us the money.
What kind of a subgenius are you?
Or eat the money and send us the brains for crying out loud.
A very, very frightened one.
There were two of you.
I want to love you ever since the baby died frightened.
Well, just so long as Dan did not soil his panties from fright as he saw.
Dan, the baby died frightened.
Dan was just sort of like chill and very cool with the situation.
The dead baby in the sink.
Ah.
My mama says that the baby is not dead.
But I think my mama is just listening to the Jesus man on the radio who sells my mom, sells my mom, sells my mom all the things.
She starts talking about the Jesus man on the radio and the dead baby in the sink.
Ah, I see.
Lone cow babe, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
More Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket from their new CD and also live at X Day.
We also heard much lonesome cowboy Dave on WCSB in Cleveland.
Some ESO swamp radio with Reverend Devangela calling in.
This is Hour of Slack.
And for more on Bob, friends, write P.O. Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
I'll get that number again.
Or write www.subgenius.com.
I'm Stang at subgenius.com.
Once again, that's Box 140306 Dallas, Texas.
And friends, the background music is Doctors for Wotan from live at 4X Day.
But the rest of this show, friends, shall be Einstein's Secret Orchestra with a Stones and Lou Reed and Doors medley live from 4X Day.
.
Thank you.
Let's go.
We were on the road
And there was this strange sound
It sounded like
All this
Breaking glass
That's it
Hey man
Hey man, what's going on up there?
Have you seen the accident outside man?
Have you seen the accident outside?
Seven people took a ride
Six bachelors
And a bride
Seven people took a ride
Seven people
Six bachelors and a bride
Seven people took a ride
Shbreck
llan
Oh, baby, take a chance on love.
Give me a good time.
Oh, baby, love is sweet.
Baby, love is sweet.
Oh, baby.
Oh, baby, love.
Don't stop it now.
It's feeling too good now.
It's feeling too good.
Oh, baby.
It hurts to set you free
But you'll never follow
You stand
My only friend
There you go.
Thank you.