PR news in Washington. I'm still billowing into the air.
President Bush came during the afternoon at a popular outdoor market to build support for his new police station, but his bomb exploded.
No one was hurt and eight people were killed. He had been heavily criticized for PR's reports.
On Wall Street, 812-617-4543. This is PR.
Bloody bombing. Bombing killed. Killed. Beheaded.
PR news. PR news. PR news.
PR's dead.
The Philippines military says it is flammable chemicals. Dozens of people were killed there.
Israel's top military leader in central Kentucky is still burning.
When the scheme came to light, PR news plunged in Washington.
All right, fellas, here's your story.
A man by the name of Bob once saved our world with an arc of electricity.
Bob is recovering from wounds received in the battle.
He's got a broken carbone and a bad headache.
Good.
And now, before giving you the details of the battle,
I bring you a warning.
Every one of you listening to Bob, tell the world.
Tell this to everybody wherever they are.
Under no circumstances take action against Bob.
Watch Bob.
Keep looking. Watch. Keep watching Bob.
Bob, give me a hand.
Hey, anybody around here want some coffee?
No. Nothing counts except Bob. Watch it.
Anybody want some coffee? No.
Then just shut up. Watch it.
Mm-hmm.
There he is, honey.
He believes that you will put the word of God down and you will quit.
Now, remember, Ephesians 6 says that the sword is the word of the spirit.
This series will take you to a new Lord and is highly recommended for you.
Order your copy now by calling 1-8-ME.
That's 1-8-ME.ministries.com.
Well?
You've had the better. Here comes the worst.
Can't trust your feelings.
Yes, correct.
It's time for the cursed flood in your life.
Let me encourage you.
Now, remember, send check or money order to 9090-MINISTRIES-31.
Fellas and girls, what I have to say will only take a few seconds.
It's about cleanliness.
Being clean in mind as well as in body.
Think clean.
Clean and keep clean.
Lack of cleanliness is usually a sign of carelessness.
And carelessness indicates laziness.
Remember always that carelessness and laziness lead to...
The self-genius power of...
Swag.
Yay!
113013.
13013.
Bob?
Yes.
Some scientists were experimenting with Bob.
Shut up!
First, the blonde.
With more curves than the road up Pike's Peak.
And done.
That's right, insult me.
Second, the blonde.
Okay, you can't argue with a blonde.
That's right.
Peter's Moon Drive.
From Gerd.
Where is my little sixth leg?
Oh, my leg.
Peter's Moon Drive.
From Gerd.
Why do so many fail?
5% success.
Success.
666.
Ideal.
Failure.
Conformity.
Now think of it.
7, 20, 20, 25.
Usually by that 25.
Usually by that.
Why we conform?
Why do you work?
Why do you get up in the morning?
Ideal.
9,999.
No destination and no guidance.
The human race is fixed.
The weakest link.
Well, let me tell you something.
Well, well, well, well.
Immediately.
Doubt.
Fear.
Key to success.
The key to failure.
Now let me say that again.
Everything comes if a man will only wait.
Cold blood.
9, 23.
I think in negative terms.
Well, that's pretty apparent, isn't it?
Confusion and anxiety and fear and worry.
Nothing.
Now how does it work?
Why do we become nothing?
Poison.
Corn.
Failure.
Confusion.
Misunderstanding.
Fear.
Anxiety.
And so on.
Must return to us.
Nothing.
What is it you want?
Get on top of a building and jump off.
Picture yourself in your mind's eye as having phenobarbital.
Ulcers.
And nervous breakdowns and tranquilizers.
Into the gutter.
Be a bore.
The architect of the universe.
Build a stairway.
Leading nowhere.
According to Bob, there's no hard evidence to prove Bob's story either.
What we're going to do today.
Okay.
Dobson.
And this will be kind of strange.
I have hits.
I just.
And so I'd like a filth.
And pretty boring stuff.
The popular cult.
Cult.
It is kind of strange.
I don't think from start to finish in my life.
And don't intend to.
Well, I am anxious.
I am the father of the baby of Anna Nicole Smith.
Oh my goodness.
I slept with her.
Turn on.
Anna.
Oh.
Ridiculous.
Anna.
She was doing.
Britney Spears.
She was.
Got fat.
Got thin.
Dumb.
It's stupid.
Christian parents really don't have any clue.
Cult.
Damaging.
Animate.
Parts.
Now.
Bob and Bob.
Bob plugged in.
Bob.
YouTube.
MySpace.
The Anna Nicole Smith and Britney Spears fascination.
Hits.
Come twice.
Maybe even three times or whatever.
Can't wait.
We're going to have a party.
He's talking about Bob's.
Can't wait.
We're going to have a party.
Plugged in.
That's right.
Primarily you look at Anna Nicole Smith.
Britney Spears.
Grease me.
Put her arm around.
All ass girls.
Girls.
If you turn over.
Boys and girls.
Turn them over.
Exploit them and twist them and warp them and use them.
Take them to hell.
Totally.
Freak show.
Hmm.
Very hard.
Now.
Go back.
One.
Very.
Hard.
Hardest of the hardest.
Full nudity.
You got to do that often.
Jesus was wrong.
Yes.
Porn.
He wants the dirtiest.
With family.
Bob and I have.
Have.
That's available to us now.
It just takes my breath away.
That was really pretty good.
It really was.
I like the dirtiest porn on video.
Failure on the field.
I just really enjoyed it.
What?
45 seconds.
Sex.
Stick that in there.
Clean.
VD.
Oh my goodness.
I absolutely love that.
Cult.
Freely strut about.
Vile thing.
Let my heart be drawn to what is evil.
Do need to do.
Who is?
Did you knew?
Looking at the cult.
Dobs.
Dobsy.
Friends.
We're home.
We're here.
Everything should be okay.
What did you say?
Just dobsy.
What kind of dobsy are you talking about?
We're uninformed.
We are of the ignorant.
The mass of the erstwhileest.
The erst.
The masters of hour of slack number 1091.
We've made our way through 1090 of them so far.
And this is the 1091th.
Princess, we, I can't hear you.
I can't hear me either.
If you really lean in there.
What do you mean if I really lean in here?
And talk real loud.
I'm talking as loud as I possibly can.
I can hear you now.
Sure.
Her pads may be need to be maxing.
But I can't chase.
See your mic and his mic are Siamese twins.
So I have to actually make contact.
So don't.
I have to actually make contact with this filthy, filthy microphone.
You don't actually have to touch your lips directly to it.
That's the only way that you've said you can hear me.
But you will feel it.
But you can speak up.
I am speaking up.
I think you may need to take the shock off it.
Don't spit up.
I said speak up.
That's sickening.
That's making me sick.
Blurp.
Well, the mysterious organ of lonesome cowboy Dave is here for your edification.
Not much of a proboscis as far as line of punishment or enlistment values.
That was in case something creative happened.
Well, it was encased.
Let's just say it was encased.
Now read frantically, Stang.
Read the copy that you forgot you had.
Friend.
You'll be glad to know that Reverend Magdalene's donation fund is now at, and I'm not kidding, $3,333.33.
About a week ago, Cleveland listeners won't know, but all the other stations will.
Reverend Magdalene had, with the subgenius child custody case, had a serious, serious drawback in her finances and her life.
And the subgeniuses came together, despite the fact that they all hate each other and are true weirdos who can barely stand to be in the same room.
Yet, when one was attacked by the conspiracy, the subgenii came together and drummed up at least, well, she needed an immediate $2,000.
The subgeniuses drummed up $3,333.33.
The number of...
The Dobbs.
And by a similar strange coincidence, friends, I was, you know, it's income tax time, and the conspiracy makes you pay them for taking your money.
And I had to add up my income.
And I won't tell you the first number of this five-figure number.
It was pi, actually.
But the next numbers were 6,666.61.
61 cents.
Yes, it was pi, 1,006, 1,666 dollars and 61 cents.
6, 6, 6, friends.
And let the sick among you know that that is the phone number of a man.
And that man is whoever is at that phone number, 666.
Actually, my agent has that phone number in his...
The new sacred agent, friends.
Oh, it's a secret.
Well, is it a coincidence?
The sacred agent that also Dave has been exploited by.
Cardinal knowledge of.
Yes.
Dave...
Or cardinal knowledge.
I forgot.
I was wearing the hat.
I was wearing the wrong hat, man.
That's a problem with most of our psychic envoyages.
And publishing achievements or attempts.
Now, the 6, 6, 6 stuff, that's like 6, 6, sexy, right?
It's a part of the Shiva principle.
It's a dissolution of three separate parts.
I thought it was a rock and roll thing.
6, 6, 6?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's not talk about that.
There's all those, you know, stickers that say, you know, 6, 6, 7, the roommate or the
next door neighbor of the beast.
Well, that's important in the Judeo-Christian and Islamic traditions, I think.
Well, 7 is also...
In the Church of the Subgenius, we kind of freak out when we see 3, 3, 3, which is the
number of the anti-Bob, or 9, 9, 9, which is the number of Bob.
Now, did you know that if you...
You take 3 times 9, 9, 9, you get 1998?
No, that's 2 times 9, 9, 9.
3 times 6, 6, 6 is 1998.
Or 6 times 3, 3, 3 is 1998.
In 1998, the world will end, friends.
July 5th, 1998, that's coming up this July 5th.
Be ready.
You know where to go.
Subgenius.com, that's where to go.
And calm down.
That means what you essentially said, that not only are the dates totally...
...totally askew, that we are fast...
...quickly approaching 1998, which has the magnif...
...niqueful sewage number of 9, which is transposed by its, you know, having 1, 9, 8, 9 in it.
And 1 and the 8 is another 9.
Right, so it's 9, 9, 9, number of Bob, number of Bob.
Told you so.
No, no, no.
Subgenius Numerology.
My cult's bigger than your cult.
My invisible monster can beat up your invisible monster.
Ne, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne.
My suicide bombers can blow up your suicide bombers.
See?
That's a pretty good one.
My suicide bombers can blow up your...
That's right, that's right.
Hey, now, also, coming in 1998, the global warming will reach its absolute peak.
In 1998?
In 1998, global warming will completely destroy the Earth, unless...
So that's like 10 years from now, or 11 years.
No, that should be this July.
No, this is 1998.
We don't know, Dave.
Oh, that's right.
We really don't know.
No, we are at 1998.
I'm sorry.
Does anybody really know what date it is?
How could they?
You know, everything...
Why do dates have names anyway?
Why couldn't they have, you know, an infinite number, or at least a calculated number of
names that you'd have to memorize at a school with fierce monks and...
That's the way we used to do it, Dave, if you remember in your days in Dobstown.
Yes, Dobstown.
Tom Dave's days in Dobstown.
But the fighting pokers on the Great Horseshoe Bayou did not...
They did not teach me a damn thing any more than the Jesuits taught me Aristotle.
You know, it's made my breasts grow.
But that's about it.
I've had...
You've learned how to work in the rice paddies and how to hoe.
That's what made my breasts expand.
It had nothing to do with what I was doing or learning at the time, because...
Wasn't it all just a psychic adventure?
It never happened.
Gosh, isn't everything just a psychic adventure?
Anyway, friends.
As I was saying, global warming will peak in 1998.
That's this July.
And unless human scientists spending millions of dollars can fix it using the new science
of geoengineering.
And I was just reading this in the PayPures tonight, that some of the solutions that scientists
meeting in Dobstown have come up with...
Now, this sounds like a joke, but this is actually true.
They've suggested growing giant artificial trees, which would turn carbon dioxide back
into oxygen.
Right.
We don't have enough trees.
Yeah, okay.
Well, these would be bioengineered giant trees.
Oh, they already have those.
That would be self-growing chemical creations, you know.
Yeah, so they grow 10 feet a year.
You can make life.
Remember, you have to yell up.
I'm yelling as much as I possibly can.
That mic has ears like mine.
I'm trying.
Think of it that way.
I'm tired of being a tree.
If I do that the whole show, I'll have a sore throat at the end of the show.
Now, come on, you guys.
This is serious.
Global warming is a serious problem, and we have to come up with a man-made way to solve
it.
Right?
We can't just stop burning garbage and fuel.
So, therefore, we have to come up with an artificial solution.
Another good scientific idea, such as shade.
And this is one I...
I read on CNN.com not two hours ago.
Shade from trillions of flying saucers.
Man-made, not excess or grays or any of those amateur-type aliens.
That's the answer to global warming is shade from trillions of flying saucers in the air?
That is positively...
You could think of the platelets of the universal mind of Duxie.
Approaching some sort of substandard equilibrium.
Right.
And millions and millions of tiny brains are the platelets, or the coverages for the...
Like the little clouds to keep the houses from being recognized by the space people.
Well, now, see, the aliens will bring such clouds of computerized...
You need to turn that down, because remember Princess Wee is on a deaf man, and you're
on the loud man.
I was getting conflicting symbols.
He doesn't know what to do.
I was just telling him to make some music, and then you told him not to make some music.
Now, here's another...
Another thing you could do, Princess Wee, and this would be a big sacrifice.
You would have to move your chair over to near Dave, and his mic would pick you up enough
that it would...
Okay, I'll try that.
Compensate, yeah.
But, like I say, it's a big sacrifice.
Now, the other item on the agenda for our bioengineering to bring down the heat that is toasting our
little planet...
Yeah, that's the other thing.
...would be sending up...
Working like an artificial volcano, sending up vast quantities of crud into the upper atmosphere
that would reflect light away, and thus lower the temperature on Earth.
Why not have children be taught the correct norms and fathoms of expectoration...
Well, yeah, that's the other thing.
...and removal of bodily fluids in the correct direction?
Aren't we the Van Allen belt we're wearing?
You know what I'm saying?
Right.
It's like, why don't we adapt?
Our...
Force our children to adapt to the changing climate.
That would be a possibility one could use.
We could...
Now, that wasn't something these smarty-pants scientists on CNN.com came up with, now, was
it?
I sure didn't hear anything about...
Well, they're not as smart as Dave.
But if I had a little kid now, and soon I'll have grandkids, I trust.
Yes.
Dave, I think, has great-grandchildren and great-great-grandchildren.
I have a 42-year-old great-great-grandchild.
Right.
Of course, it's from previous werewolves with Nebuchadnezzar.
But what...
That really hurts.
I know.
That makes...
Does it hurt less?
That's like my teeth.
That's what it feels like when I chew on tinfoil.
It sounds that way in my head.
Well, does it make you feel better, Dave?
No, but really, if we want to prepare our children for the coming global changes, we
need to raise them in little hothouses, greenhouses, put them in... put their crib in a place that's
about 10 feet away.
10 degrees hotter than where you are, and just adapt them in a drier, hotter environment.
Don't let them drink much water.
How do you mean adapt them?
And adapt children so that...
Well, we can't reverse climate change.
Obviously, anything that we did to try to reverse it would just make something else worse.
Every time we do something, it makes it worse.
Right.
It's all the things that we have to stop doing that we're doing now.
The evil...
Well, speak...
I should...
I'm not really speaking for myself because I'm not technically fully human.
Well, we can clearly see that.
Thanks for removing that right in front of us.
Well, it's not like anybody ever argued with me on that point.
Why is it making that noise?
Why is it...
Can't you cover it up with something?
It's kind of like the light is...
What you're seeing is the aura of my slack, my luscious slack beaming out because I've
been granted such high...
High slackdomness by the Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It's good.
Cool feel.
Looks smoother now, doesn't he?
Looks a little...
My cult, in which I believe.
His hair has returned to dark.
The church of the subgenius.
It makes me younger.
His chin is very proper, guys.
It sticks out like a mighty, mighty cliff of granite.
I'm younger.
I never thought that such a thing would ever happen.
Such slack.
Where did you get such fine hair?
You look like one of the pharaohs.
And the day...
Yes.
I feel like a god of slack.
Actually, it's this Rudy Schwartz Project music in the background that makes me feel
that way.
It's an aura that took you over just a few moments ago.
We don't know what it is.
You missed many fine moments here.
They were like micro moments, but they were many fine moments.
What, on your keyboard?
Yes.
I did miss them.
No.
Well, not perhaps the way you should have, I guess.
I'm still feeling a little dizzy, Dave and Princess, from globe hopping.
Ah, the globe hopping.
Yeah, we discovered...
I know everybody else did this three years ago, but they just...
They didn't have Google Earth for Macintosh until last year, and it took until this year
for me to actually get around to fiddling with it.
And what a thrill Google Earth was for...
Bows.
We Earthbound.
Yes, dear.
Friends.
It felt...
It's hypnosis.
If you've never done it, it's very Jetsons.
You feel like you're in the Jetsons world.
Finally, a real Jetsons thing.
It's masturbatory, Sting.
It's very auto-hypnotic.
Kids wouldn't feel that way.
Kids would think, oh, well, it's just more electronic gizmos.
But for us olden people...
See, for us to travel from one place to another, we had to get in a vehicle and drive or buy
a plane ticket and be flown there, and it took hours and was dangerous.
But now, you can just Google anything.
Anywhere on Earth and make a bookmark of it.
That's how we're going to get home.
That's how we got to the radio station.
And in one mighty leap.
Like the Incredible Hulk.
If you ever saw that comic movie, The Incredible Hulk, he leaps around.
That's what the Google Earth experience reminds me of.
It's like the movies promised us the Internet would be, where you just cast your hand.
And you say, computer, take me to the Grand Canyon.
And you fly.
Through the air.
To the bottom of the Grand Canyon, which is in beautiful 3D.
In arching pole vault loops, just the way the Skull Islanders got to the ship to get Anne.
That's right, yeah.
And you can also...
We bookmarked...
We found Skull Island, or where Skull Island used to be, southwest of Sumatra.
You can still see the bump.
Because they show the geography of the ocean bottom.
As a place to see a bump.
One of the major characteristics of the area.
Or is that just sort of some kind of psychosexual...
That's the whole island full of temples and dinosaurs that sank beneath the waves in 1948.
They ran them?
Wow.
They ran the temples?
Some of the subgeniuses were saying that we really should try to salvage the more permanent fixtures of Skull Island.
In fact, it was Imgur that suggested this.
Wow.
But we were going, well, how?
I mean, these things are at the bottom of the ocean.
How do you lift up temples?
A tiny army would do it.
Those gigantic temples with huge ape faces on them.
Empty Dobstown of all those reckless children and put them to work restoring.
Balloons.
They were thinking, get the bong of destiny and the frop of doom underwater and fill up balloons from the bong of destiny.
And use the balloons to lift the bricks to the surface and recreate the temples of...
Skull Island at the British Museum or the Smithsonian or whatever.
That is brilliant.
That's absolutely brilliant.
Or Disney World.
That requires an awful lot of what you're not known for having.
I thought it was kind of a dumb idea.
Oh, well, then there you go because I thought you were being dumb.
But, no, really, we had the greatest time.
If you never did Google Earth, I don't mean to do an advertisement for an evil conspiracy conglomerate like Google exactly,
except that I got to admit it.
I was thrilled to hop from Tiananmen Square to the South Pole to Monument Valley to my elementary school
to Innsmouth to Dagon to Komodo Island.
Remember, you could actually see on Easter Island, you could see some of those heads shapes from above.
And Mount Rushmore.
You didn't see Mount Rushmore yet.
George Washington is losing his hair.
Wow, is he becoming a slope head?
From up above.
From seeing from above, you can tell he's starting to lose his hair.
There was once a mighty sequoia on George Washington's head.
That would be pretty good.
Well, why not?
I think they should do things.
I don't think sequoias grow in the Black Hills.
I think America should become greener.
We can fix that.
We can fix it.
On next day.
We can fix it with our own minds, children.
Use our own minds, children.
Well, and also our money.
Childlike minds.
We need minds and money.
That was what the subgeniuses learned.
Yes.
It was a great experiment.
Was that it takes more than money to make money.
It takes a few brain cells.
And that's where we fell short, perhaps.
But we can make up for it with a lot of extra money.
A lot more money.
We're not going to get any more brain cells, but we can sure get more money, friends.
And we can do a lot more with those few brain cells we have.
Think of it that way, astute, young, brainless children.
Look at the conspiracy.
They don't have any brain cells.
All they have is money, and look how well they've done.
They've almost destroyed the planet without the help of aliens.
I don't know if that's the real way you'd put it.
You see a lot of stiffs accumulating in the streets.
Lots of dead bodies growing in number.
The stink is starting to grow.
Well, now, Dave, you've been concerned, haven't you, about...
I mean, you said down the way here that you were getting paranoid about the...
Well, them.
And it.
And those...
Those.
I feel that they're powerful just to have and want too much power.
They can't give us...
Remember, the best control is good old-fashioned management.
Mickey Mouse said that.
Oh, wrong name.
That's a trademark name.
I didn't mean that.
Oh, boy.
Well, this is for a tape later.
One of those cartoon characters said once...
What did they say again?
Something bad about the conspiracy.
Right.
They said it was all made for a bad movie.
What did I...
Oh, boy, that sheet.
There you go.
See, our minds are being sapped by the great sappers, I like to say.
That's exactly our point.
But you can help save our few pathetic, raggedy, pitiful brain cells, friends,
when you contribute your own brain cells to our bank.
And by brain cells, of course, we mean your donations to the station of your choice.
Of course, it could also mean a one-time only limited consumption deal,
in which case...
We will eat those few brain cells you have donated,
but in the attempt to grow more, which won't work, but we'll enjoy it.
Oh, forget it.
Well...
Oh, what, Princess Lee?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yes, yes.
No.
No, no, no, no.
You guys go ahead and munch your brain cells there.
I did not.
Did I give credits earlier in this show for the great work and the collages that we heard
at the head of the show?
I don't believe that you did do any credits for any of those fabulous...
Collages that we heard.
PR News, number 1,348, actually.
We heard a whole wonderful set of collages by Leigh Moore.
Fernanda Leigh Moore.
Deep in the bowels of Colorado.
And other collages, actually the longer ones, tend to be by Reverend Norell Preff
of norellpreff.com.
And also heavyconfetti.com.
He's a really good guitarist.
He's a guitar player.
And his guitar playing is on heavyconfetti.com.
Whereas his preferential Norellian bits and business are on norellpreff.com.
And while we're at it, actually, I'm going to run that again just briefly so I can go
get my coffee.
One whiff of the aroma from Granny's cook stove and I knew that there would be roast
grandpa for dinner.
Cooked to a tempting russet brown.
And just falling apart.
And I remember that I thought it was the finest grandpa I'd ever tasted.
Nourishing.
Heartwarming.
Into its making goes all the good meat of grandpa.
Won't you make a point of having it this weekend?
E.
Cola.
Presents ESP.
That's your smartest soaring saucer.
Brought to you each Tuesday and Thursday by delicious E.
Cola.
Proved of highest purity.
E.
Cola.
Cola has more quick food energy and value ounce for ounce than any other leading nationally
known cola.
Yes.
You get the best and twice as much in delicious E.
Cola.
It's clear, Pedro.
Senor.
No good, Pedro.
Narcotic.
Ah, come in, Bart.
Futuristic mode of transportation.
Oh?
I keep them happy.
They keep me happy.
Happy.
See underneath?
A rocket attached.
Ready, Bart?
This is your local newscaster with some more on the latest outbreak of flying saucers.
Big and black.
Small and shiny.
Six.
Now back to Pussycats.
E.
Cola.
Sure hits the spot.
Enjoy E.
Cola.
E.
Tonight.
Truth is fiction.
And this is Be Orbit, Be Not.
Thomas Jefferson Chambers of Anoak, Texas was killed by looking into a mirror.
But the very next morning, the police found him in perfect health.
Then, 15 years later, he was hypnotized.
He was hypnotized by Timothy Crother.
While under the hypnotic spell, he cried out,
I'm dying.
And didn't know it.
Then, 13 years later, the police found the victim's chest hanging on the wall.
Then, 10 years later, he was killed again.
Then, 41 years later, he died twice.
Then, 5 years later, in a dream on the night of January 16th, 1862, he was hypnotized by 10 years of marriage.
The dream requires the same woman.
Be Orbit, Be Not.
Good morning.
Well, this just feels funny, doesn't it?
Where's the dirt?
I couldn't believe.
I can't believe.
Be evolved.
all, come as you are, come as you are, come as you are, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ding of the throat and the bleeding, since he's came, only good people can come,
who touched me, the prostitutes did, focus on that and just stay right there for a long time,
tonight on 9 news at 10, watch 9 news at 10,
but first, here's a mighty swell gang, you'll want to spread the news around that you're
collecting those slick new friends, because that's the only way they'll trade duplicates with
them, and you won't want to miss out on that fun, you want to be sure you round out
your friends, and you want to be sure you round out your friends, and you want to be sure you
of all 18 different friends, like Smitty and K.O. and Herbie, and of course, and the best part is,
you don't have to ask mom, remember, that's P.P.
Unlike this 500 pound mouse that is inside of you, Jesus spoke of it when he said,
here kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty,
one, three, zero,
one, three,
Bob, Bob, Bob,
I've killed probably a couple hundred living and whole human beings, did I just commit mass murder?
No, because each of these human beings is nothing more than a part of a larger,
me.
Now what's great about that is that people tend not to want living human beings.
To put that in even clearer terms.
So what do you think God is like?
A fly?
Wow.
Whoa, man, that was some weird typings there.
Yeah, it made me feel really funny.
Be orphaned?
Lean on to it.
I can't.
Oh, the sky wants all whiskey don't it?
Forget.
Be orphaned.
Lean on it.
From Fernanda and the Leaner.
And those other little businesses there.
Lean on it.
There was some Norell.
Cut ups of our friends and people that we hate.
And all manner.
All man-our.
All man-our of people.
All manure of people.
Listen.
Isn't there something important we're supposed to be covering?
Magdalene's case.
The actual existence of Bob Dobbs is a matter not only of physical record but a matter of
scientific inquiry taken to its further...
Didn't they find Bob's bones or something like that?
I remember seeing it in the news.
I've been very busy.
What is that knocking like an old robot that needs to be repaired?
Is that your machine?
It was a very, very, very, very low setting for a rhythm device.
It's Dave's robot.
You've worn it before, Stang.
Look.
It's Dave's monkey.
It's his monkey.
Dave's monkey is making the little funny noises there.
It's Dave and his monkey.
And now it's gone.
It's gone?
You killed the...
Oh.
Dave killed the monkey.
Dave the organ grinder and his monkey.
He killed his monkey.
Dave killed his monkey.
What a spaz.
What a spazzy show.
No, it's good when you kill the monkey on your back.
What's wrong with these people?
You're not supposed to continuously ask yourself questions like this.
Go back to the original conversation.
You've forgotten what you were talking about.
Please.
Let's get on Google Earth and go back to the rocary in Amsterdam.
Yeah, let's go globe hopping again.
So do you guys relive that when you do that?
The red light district.
Yes.
You actually...
Well, when you land on a spot, you can't...
You can't...
Obviously, you can't smell the smells because they haven't done that, but you can look at
it from street view if somebody else has been there before and put their pictures of street
view there.
So there are all these spots that you can land on where you can then sort of look around
and go, oh, what a lovely building.
Why those pigeons are frozen in midair, flying.
I forgot the name of the red light district.
People are all frozen.
Are they still frozen?
Barrio Rojo, if it's the Spanish version.
No.
No, I mean in Amsterdam, and it's Barschensnoven or Redenschnap.
Where?
War...
Reden Twanger.
Warrens...
Warn?
Oud Zijtjes-Ochterberg is the main canal that the famous prostitution store windows
are on, which Princess Wee and I have strolled down there and window shopped, the prostitutes
of Amsterdam.
Ironically, to have a name like that.
And the name of an octopus included a place where you would find prairie squid.
There is, in fact, a big prairie squid in front of one of the main clubs.
It's the red something, the red piggy tail or something.
The red peckerwood.
It was Jim's place before.
It's got to be a pig, lit up red in front.
No, it's not a pig, actually.
It's something that looks like an upright pig.
You're thinking of the pig and whistle, which is a...
Sporting.
A sporting pig in front.
Ausst...
Ausstbleeft.
I feel like I've been sitting in one of those coffee shops.
I don't know.
That's the thing.
When you do this globe hopping on this Google Earth thing, if you go to Amsterdam and spend
much time there, you'll get pretty high or hurt or whatever it is that happens to you
if you wander around the...
Well, you get high when you leap up out of there to go away.
When you Ausstbleeft your way out.
I don't know.
And then you can hop over to the Vatican or...
You go out into outer space and you see the whole world rotating around underneath your
feet.
Yeah, but you can only go a certain...
You can only go a certain...
You know, it does make you feel like the world is not that big.
It certainly does.
Now, if you go over certain sections, it's like flying in an orbiting of...
You can see this incredible detail.
That's why it's like Jetson's world.
I saw Philo in his...
It looks like paper machining.
It does.
I saw somebody in Philo's hot tub.
In the...
Through Google Earth.
There have also been collections, I think, on Wired Magazine of pictures of people sunbathing
that were found upon Google Earth and embarrassing things like that.
Well, some of them may be...
Appear to be sunbathing, but they're actually collecting rays from a vastly different source,
I must say.
But there was definitely somebody in Philo's hot tub.
Were they there sunbathing or...
I don't know if it was Philo or Mrs. Drummond or both of them, and I could tell that they
were going from one to the other.
But I don't think I'm supposed to say either one of the things they were going from and
to on the air.
But I couldn't tell who it was.
I could tell what they were doing, though.
No, if you've had a...
And it's from looking down from above.
And if you have the expensive $400 Google Earth, you can see through the rooftops.
And if you have the $1,000 one, you can pick up audio and listen to conversations.
But they're timestamps.
They're not like happening right now.
They're from hours or days or weeks before or months.
Well, I...
Well, that's a way of finding rats and other rodents in your attic.
So you could listen to the Pope conversing with his altered boys, but it might have been
years ago, and you wouldn't be able to really pick up any good tactical...
Nuclear weapons.
No, that's another thing.
The Pope doesn't necessarily have tactical or nuclear weapons, but sound travels much
slower than hearing.
So I think you're talking about your ear balls or perhaps light, which you actually don't
see with.
You see what I'm saying?
The speed of light...
Well, I can't afford that version of Google Earth anyway, so it's kind of a moot point.
Yeah, but see, if you were to listen to the Pope speaking in the pasture, we'll say, you
know, many, many years ago, you'd have to go into a different time loop and see him
there.
Well, people in the future will be able to look back to the past, starting when Google
Earth started and hear what people said and did through Superman vision.
What you're saying, if you were going faster than the speed of sound, you could hear what
you just said.
Right.
I could, yeah, if I tune in Google...
Now I have this station bookmarked, right?
You saw it.
I showed it to you.
Among other things, yeah, bookmarking is one of the words you're using now.
Yeah.
I know.
I got stuck through it this evening.
I ran up to the building, you know, and here are the images I saw, and I just saw a headline
that said something that was like, do you know who this person is, can I call you?
And I was like, like...
Then we were talking the other day and I was like, do you rememberoup sticker with
your thin bad hair?
Do you know who that is?
And so I'm just kind of, I'm really bad, aren't I?
You have no idea.
That's f***** me up.
and microscope at all those many petri dishes.
That's old age thinking.
Yeah, of course it is.
Of course it is.
But it is the foundation for our...
Sure, that's where our primate juices are created.
But you can do that and have the virtual world, both.
Of course, you have to be able to afford all that world travel.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, because...
Well, because they charge you.
You know, I don't know if you knew that, Princess Wee,
but we're charged for every leap that we do on Google Earth.
You're being silly now, Reverend Stang.
No, he has...
That's not true.
He gets 100% increase for every security clearance he jumps, humps, or pumps.
That is so not true.
For instance, you can look at NORAD, but it's going to cost you.
Oh, you can look at it backwards as DONAR, meaning you're being taken away.
That's a bunch of baloney and hoo-ha.
No, it's not.
Now, if you have the money, you can, as one guy put it,
you can see down the front of the dress of the premier's wife in Russia.
I simply didn't believe that.
From these satellites.
That's how good they are.
Why would you say...
They can read a license plate from outer space.
Okay, if you're one of those...
They can read a comic book from outer space.
It prints bigger than nine points.
See, now you think about famous ejerculators like the Oye guy.
Yeah.
Okay, now...
How is that any different from us?
No, no, no.
I'm just saying, how could that possibly compare?
Is your favorite voyeur in Wankula?
How could that possibly compare to a guy who is obsessed,
perhaps even asphyxiatedly addicted to looking down the Russian premier's wife's cleavage
and pronouncing his own wisdom upon Pangey?
Well, that's exactly...
You're talking to him, Bob.
She's built like a brick temple.
He's a little close to home there, did ya?
You've been staring at Putin's pooper.
No.
This is Putin's...
Putin.
Oh, no, no.
Now, kids...
Putin.
That's Putin.
We...
No, it really is quite amazing technology and makes me...
It's like being on a little magic carpet that you can't fall off of.
Why would you want to fall off of?
Well, you would want to, for instance, get off of the carpet in the red light district
in Amsterdam now and then.
Yeah.
And walk into the...
Museum.
The Reich Museum.
That's it.
Yeah.
Or...
The Van Gogh Museum.
Yeah.
Some place like that.
Sure.
That's the kind of stuff that everybody does.
That's what we did.
Yeah.
You wouldn't do, like, Philo and go to Zazub or whatever that place was.
The famous...
Is it a...
The Christopher Street.
What was it?
I forget.
He had some secret Masonic thing.
Oh, he was always getting little secret special places to go for certain...
Certain particular tastes.
Well, he's a 33rd degree Mason.
Philo.
Oh, that Philo.
Yeah.
I'm only a 31.
Well, what's the difference between the different, like, degrees once you get up in the 30s?
Well, you're not supposed to know about...
Could you be, like, a 57 degree or could...
You're not...
Any numbers are possible.
You don't know about those until you've gotten...
You've reached the very, very top, the 32nd degree.
And then they let you know about the ones after that.
Look at Jesus Capristo.
You know, our lordly person.
You can if you could.
Yeah, you could if you would.
If he wasn't invisible.
But, well, you'd have to take a Google Snap and you'd have to enjoy it all the way.
And the next thing you know, you'd find yourself over the macrame...
I mean, you know, the machine island.
And then it's back to there.
Man, I think you could go whiplash from something like that.
No, that was...
I was talking about...
See?
There it goes.
I was talking about Jesus again being a 33 as opposed to an expanded bra.
Which is like a D cup or something like that.
What does Jesus...
Does Jesus' age have to do with Masonic...
Or his bra size?
Or the Templi Orientis ranks.
Well, if Jesus wore a man bra, meaning he had achieved to elderly status,
wouldn't he be around 53rd degree, meaning his waist size?
They don't call those man bras.
They call them aprons.
Aprons.
Right.
And then they also have wizard hats.
Now, what if he was so bald that wizard hat would fall off on the floor?
It's hard to imagine.
Masonic guys wear wizard hats and have little sparkly...
Yeah.
Sure, of course.
Of course.
Yeah, they look like wizards.
They dress up like, well, that's what they are.
Well, in the higher realms.
Not the guys, not the shriners in the little cars,
the guys at the Masonic Temple downtown,
but the guys in Washington, the guys in the Himalayas,
the guys in the moons of Saturn, those guys.
Those are the singular eyeball...
Those are the elder bankers of the universe.
The eyeball guys of the pyramid.
The council of 23.
Guys, you're scaring me.
The ring...
You're scaring me.
...of 39.
There's 23 or 39.
Oh, now this is getting silly.
We're talking about numbers.
No, there are both.
Okay.
33.
This is...
And the listeners aren't interested in a bunch of occult secrets
because they can't relate it to anything.
I'm not a fan of them.
We can give them away here because there's no one listening
who understands what the hell we're talking about.
The last part of the sentence was unnecessary.
Which gives us a certain amount of freedom.
And a certain low number of listeners.
Right.
You could have just said, because no one's listening,
but instead you said that.
Listen to this lovely...
Ooh.
...what I've imagined.
It's magical sounding.
I could play right along here.
I don't want to ruin anything for you.
It's all twinkly.
Who is that twinkling?
Is that Rudy Schwartz?
No, it's not.
I really don't know what it is.
I'm kind of lost in the ozone as far as I'm concerned.
I don't know what that is.
It says DSDR.
I'm lost in the magicalness of it.
Now, did you know that there were people...
Maybe just John.
...who tried to divine the actual occurrences of Anna Nicole's demise
through the smirches in her tampon.
Did you hear that?
What?
A witch lady who claimed that she had never achieved anything less than perfect success.
A psychic?
A psychic doctor.
She was diagnosing the death of the Saint Anna Nicole.
By?
By the squadges, the smudges on her tampoon.
And much the way somebody might read tea leaves or try and talk back to like a tea tree plant.
If they can.
Uh-huh.
See, that just sounds like me staying.
Now you're going to leave that on because it's Larry Schwartz.
It does.
No, this is just John.
It's something called Juniper Zombie and it does sound like you.
See, I'm as good as Juniper John when I'm just hitting my elbows and stuff.
No, I'm sorry, Juniper.
You can play along.
I'm sorry, John.
I think this is brilliant because...
Not Juniper John, just right.
It's called Juniper Zombie.
Oh.
Is the name of this composition.
So he's also been to the Southwest to look at the mummies.
Whatever happened to you, it apparently happened to him too.
We're talking about John right now.
Bob came and did something to all of us.
He left his thumbprint on someone's...
On our forebrains.
Yes.
The whorls of Bob's thumbprint are embedded in all of us.
All of us right in our third eye or where our third eye would be if we hadn't had them.
The doctor didn't snip it off for religious, crazy old, useless religious reasons.
You know, when you're born, they snip off your third eye.
Boys and girls.
Whoa.
You didn't know that, did you?
No.
You didn't even know you had a third eye, did you?
That's appalling.
Well, that's what they do.
And it's why?
Because of some ancient tradition.
There's no real health reason for it.
That's so tragic.
They snip off a piece of your body when you're a little baby.
A piece of your brain.
It has a different name.
When you...
You snip off a female part of the third eye.
It's called the...
It's different.
But it's still the same thing.
It's snipping the third eye.
Well, I knew what I was talking about for a brief moment.
I've never known anything you've been talking about.
Well, this has been an unusually insane hour of slack.
Well, I was thinking about Lenten practices, you know, and getting hit in the forehead with a good old dusting of smudge.
And then I was thinking about Bob.
And then I was thinking about Bob going around to his parishioners and gouging out their third eye as if it was the last day of the, you know, stations or something.
No, he gouges out their wallets.
Well...
It's a wallet gouging food.
That hurts.
That Bob is.
It's too bad he couldn't hurt the necropolis of D.C.
You know what I'm saying?
The great Bilderbergners or hamburger employers or whatever they are.
The guys who control the cheeseburger.
The consumers are the great...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Some people get confused between the conspiracy and the conspiracy dupes.
It's just as some get confused between an application and the file that the application creates.
The program and the actual content created from the programs.
That is the tissue that's consumed.
Some fear for the doctor and some fear for the patient.
God, that reminds me.
Oh, wow.
I have to...
And when the tissue is made of cheese...
Cheese, it melts away so quickly.
I have to go to the doctor tomorrow and get a sample.
They're going to take a core sample.
We're going to drill all the way down to the bag mud and just to see if there's oil.
The doctor.
All over.
The doctor will tell you.
Yeah, all over.
My entire body I'm having these six inch holes drilled.
Tiny little...
So they're going to make little petroleum ports on you to try and...
They want to see if there's gas.
He's going to be acubated.
I heard that you could do it with sonic just sounding, but they said that...
That's the old way.
They insisted.
This doctor said they had to poke and dig these chunks out of me.
Usually just takes a little, an index finger poke on the abdomen to find out if there's
really a rich source of gas.
There's some violent music in the background.
And I'm really confused now.
The music confused me.
Dave is thinking, well, I could do that.
I've got a Casio.
But can't you see the difference?
It's like Beethoven, man.
That's great.
Just banging away.
I was playing difficult figures here with both of my fingers.
You didn't notice how complex that was, Reverend Stang?
You're going to listen to that later and just be marveling at the complexity.
You're losing your polyrhythmic contrapuntal device you wear.
Well, I'm not sure...
If I take LSD or something, that might be true.
I might listen to that and go, oh, that is like so totally avant-garde.
I am into this.
I can read where his mind was coming from, man, when he did this music.
I'm like with him while he composes this.
Do we really think he knows what he's talking about when he's saying this?
I might as well really be the genius doing this music.
Because we're like all one.
And just because I'm just some kid tripping on drugs doesn't mean that Beethoven,
is any better than me.
Because I can hear this stuff and appreciate it because of the drugs.
Therefore, I'm like the same genius as him, see?
Psst, you're dead.
That's what every kid is thinking when he's listening to his favorite rock song.
I know that because that's what I used to think.
You're dead.
But I don't think anymore.
Beethoven is a businessman.
I swore off.
This world was created by you, for you.
There's no such thing as solipsism unless you get it on a pizza.
Get it, kid?
You know what I'm talking about, kid?
You can pitch, you can play, you can sing, yeah?
You were born with huge feet and tiny little knuckles.
You're made for it.
Step into the light, kid.
Here comes Santa Bob to take you to your just desserts.
Or reward.
I forget the word.
Is that the contract?
That's a standard contract, isn't it?
It says here, your reward shall be a gigantic bag of intercellular pudding created by the
Zedron people.
The Zedron people run the many fine galaxies of the northeast and the Pegasus universe itself.
I bet there's a lot of people who get up and get into it.
And friends, you're listening to Hour of Slack number 1091.
The Hour of Slack, voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
And if you are interested in knowing more about that, you can look at subgenius.com.
By the way, subgenius does not have an O in it.
O?
Shibu Sam, come quickly.
Someone showed it in the vault of the ship we have evacuated.
They've killed Captain Squirlus.
How are we going to get out of here?
This is me.
Listen.
The law will be upheld.
If your honor, please, I move to .
That's correct, your honor.
That's what you think.
Very well.
Are you crazy?
Oh, sure.
If your honor, please, send this to the commander of the ship.
That expresses it perfectly.
Yeah?
Kill me.
Very well.
Look out!
Oh, no.
Her mother died.
That's her laugh.
Is it?
Yeah.
There's a real problem.
We have to find the real problem.
It's a serious problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop hiding brass tacks outside of the box.
And in fact, there's a real problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop hiding outside of the box.
In short, bureaucrats and diplomats can't take it further.
In short, there's a real problem here.
Political leaders have got to stop the box.
The world and how it works.
We can achieve nothing.
Selling our families.
Selling it.
Ghouls.
Selling our children.
Control our economy.
are thought. Second, beyond belief. Narrow-minded pettiness and prejudice. Ten percent. One, one,
two, three, four, and five. Ideas are worthless. Keep in mind that you have nothing. More money,
more money. Stop thinking. Stop thinking. Hey, hey, mount. Ask, and it shall be given you. Go at it as
you've never done before. Wake up and live. Gradually, your new habit will form. Nothing
great was ever accomplished. Fear and fear is crippling. Get you off. Get you off. Why should
I bother? Well, look at the alternative. Fear and frustration. Keep looking for something for
nothing, or keep looking for something for nothing, or you're successful if you earn a lot of money.
Give me heat, and then I'll add the wood. The wood. We've got to put the fuel in. We've got to put the
fuel in. Had you ever thought of this yardstick before? Enrich yourself by deluding others. It
may take some time. Put out. Put out. One, two, three, four, five, six. Start today. Thank you.
You have nothing. You have nothing. You want to. You want to.
You want to. Come. Come. We aired. We aired. He has a cult history. I am a great threat to this
nation called fundamentalism. The great threat to this nation posed by fundamentalism. Well,
it's great to have an opportunity to be with you. Rediscovering fundamentalism. I heard you speak.
Yeah. You actually believe that the United States, we are truly stupid.
And that's.
That's why Winston Churchill hangs in my office. Anxiety. Well, you know, anxiety.
We are a Hitler. Dick, dick, dick, dick. What? Kill you. What? Kill you.
Uh, uh, there's not. I mean, what is it? Uh.
The mass murder. Yes. Kill you. Kill us.
Well, well, if a have it both ways, kill 300,000 people. I want this.
I want this. Oh, oh, oh, oh, thank you. Why don't you start out of touch with the American people?
And, uh, you know, uh, I was, uh, headed, um, and, um, I was praying. And when I felt I was
doing things that were wrong, uh, but I was still doing them.
If the rumors were true that you were.
In an affair, uh, with Monica Lewinsky.
Well, the, the, the fact is that the, the honest answer is yes, but that it.
Having somebody beaten up corrupt country of corruption is so deep.
The very heart of our legal system.
The, the, the, the, the, the, the deeply turned to dog.
Uh, dog.
I enjoy it every time, uh, we have a chance to be together.
I am always available for you.
Doc, doc, doc, doc.
Thank you.
Uh, dot com.
Truth is fiction.
And this is The Orbit Lena.
Hugh Farron was appointed hereditary janitor of Skipton Castle in England.
He's believed to be inhabited by spirits.
Whenever the king was in a merry mood, he would donate rent money lest the spirits be evicted.
And they held the job for 38 years.
And the Grateful King rewarded his descendants with eternal taxes.
The Orbit Lena.
In a moment I'll tell you about linen trousers, heavy wool stockings, gold embroidered shoes, a wool skirt, two embroidered vests, an apron, scarves, silk kerchiefs, and a heavy head shawl worn over two bonnets.
It all adds up to one indestructible pilgrim.
The Orbit Lena.
Hansen, the most famous singer in India's history, was paid the fantastic fee of $45 to 12 successive generations.
In a moment I'll tell you about a king who died of trouble.
He ordered the real king seized and executed on the spot.
Or not.
The Orbit Lena.