Today is Wednesday, July 3rd, 2013.
2013? Oh, good God.
All day, in the Grindhouse, the movies will be projected.
Now the live hour of slack will transpire, here on the Wisteria stage at Caffeina's.
From 3 o'clock to 4 o'clock, the first phase of the historic Bulldada auction will begin.
And from 4 to 5, another live hour of slack at Caffeina's.
Yeah, so bring on the babes, bring on the babes. Where'd all the babes go?
They'll be along.
There's Baby Bear over there. We need her squeaky voice up here.
We need her, but of course she's on duty at the swag shack.
She is.
Yes.
Oh, really? Okay, well then you should come and give us some assistance here.
Hooray.
Who are our two swaggards today?
Oh, Peter Bergman is here. I thought you were dead.
Let's take it again. Oh, Pete and Dave. Okay, there we go.
All right, you over here?
You just shut up.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Pete.
And Dave.
Of the Firesign Theater.
And we're listening to The Hour of Slack.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Children's voices in the orchard between the blossom and the fruit time.
Whee.
Golden head, crimson head, between the green tip and the root.
Black wing, brown wing, hover over.
Twenty years and the spring is over.
Today grieves, tomorrow grieves.
Cover me over, light in leaves.
Golden head, black wing.
Cling, swing, spring, sing.
Swing up into the apple tree.
Does anybody know what the hell he's going on about?
I just thought everybody should be rested and slackful.
Praise Dr. Howell.
To heave up.
To heave up the burdens of today.
Bleugh.
The intolerable heavy weight of so much slackfulness and fun.
More than the human organism was ever designed for.
My butt hurts.
We'll accept no whining, no complaining.
All my butt cheeks hurt.
I want it to be more funner.
More funner.
It should be more funner.
That's what...
Dildo Valerie said her first afternoon at X Day.
Really?
Yes.
She wanted it to be more funner.
More funner.
Everybody...
It should be more funner.
And I said, Dildo Valerie, I think the problem is that you're new here.
And most of the people here have kind of known each other for years.
So what they're mainly here for is to just sit around and yak in the flesh instead of on the internet.
So what you have to do is make it more fun.
More funner.
Yes.
And they did.
What more could you want?
It's already the most funnest.
She had more fun, I take it, later on.
Yes, she did.
She got to break open the piñata, which turned out to be full of live bugs.
Yes, no one expected...
And it was designed to scare girls.
And it turned out she was an insectologist.
Well, we had that piñata all filled with spiders and beetles and all sorts of things.
Centipedes.
They came showering down.
I wouldn't react so well.
A great subgenius moment.
Now, as I understand it, Reverend Baby Bear, you have been in the conspiracies pits, working your pits off.
Deep, deep in the caves.
You had like a 12-hour shift before you came out here or something?
Two 12-hour shifts and two days of being at work at 7.30 in the morning.
Did they give you overtime for that sacrifice?
No.
I just had to fill in all the hours that I was going to miss this week.
It was horrendous.
Did you have to use the religious excuse that you were going to your religious retreat?
You're going to a church meeting.
No.
Because they would press me and I don't want to have to explain it.
I called it a music festival.
Oh, okay.
And camping.
That's it, yeah.
That's what we call Starwood.
Seven whole days of peace, love, and...
Did you hear the story of how...
Dow Jones and Reverend Purge and Reverend Fox managed to rent a car after they missed the bus,
despite a lot of paperwork problems.
Somebody's credit wasn't good enough.
And the lady at the car rental place said,
I'm sorry, I can't rent you any cars as long as your credit is like...
And I think Dow Jones said something like,
I guess we'll miss our church meeting.
And suddenly everything changed.
She said, I think we'll be able to rent you a car, sir.
He didn't say what church it was.
Jesus gets you a ticket.
And now we have Susie here in the place.
So the fourth member is here.
Hi, Susie.
Oh, there we go.
And we got the background, the video backdrop.
We don't really need the video backdrop this time because we got the girls here.
Well, you can have the video.
We got the video backdrop and them.
And so indulge, wallow in richness here.
Susie, are you going to enrichen us?
I got a fan.
She brought a big fan with her.
I got a thing to blow you with.
Susie's going to blow us.
As per usual.
She's such a big fan.
I'm a big Susie fan.
Can I blow you?
Sure.
He'll huff and he'll puff.
And he'll blow you away.
My sword is blunted.
We're still getting set up here, experiencing minor testicle difficulties.
In just a short while, we will be fully embarked on an incredible adventure of subgenius broadcasting.
Live.
Here.
Here and now.
No, I'm sorry.
This is the incredible adventure.
This is the whole thing.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Here it goes.
Yeah.
The slack must flow.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Where have I heard that before?
Um, so we have the projector, so I could spring the surprise on Susie.
There's a surprise.
I want to know the surprise.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
Hm.
Right.
Yes.
Yes, it's taken a long time to do.
time to rehearse this
apparent artless bumbling.
Actually, it's a highly refined
comedy routine. How's that?
There, that's excellent.
You have to scoot your chair forward.
Then I'll be right in the middle of your interrogation camera.
Bring it even further forward.
You can't be too close. I did it, Chowchilla.
I buried that damn school bus. I'm sorry.
Well, we'll get to that later.
See, there's one right there. I saw it.
There are wasps.
Oh, there are wasps.
I wasn't denying it. There are wasps.
You know, all you have to do is hold your breath
and it makes all of your pores slam shut.
And that's a mechanism by which they sting you.
They stick their little stingers in your open pores.
But no, you hold your breath.
All your pores are like slammed shut.
Like little tight sphincters.
An interesting false belief here.
And there's nothing for them to stick their pointy asses in.
So you're safe. I've always been safe that way.
I'm not actually afraid of getting stung.
I can handle that. It's just the buzzing.
The horrible buzzing.
I'm more afraid of getting stung.
The numinous horror of the shape of the wasp itself
is existentially frightening.
More than any damage they can do with the sting.
Well, some people are terrified.
There's no explanation.
Is that an exos with some sort of extensive device on?
A mechanism of explanation has been offered
for why people have these indescribable fears.
And it's speculated that
as a baby lying in the cradle
with jam on your face or whatever,
you may be visited by a persistent spider
or wasp or something.
The baby cries.
The parents come, but there's no bug to be seen.
The parents retreat, and the bug comes back.
And from then on...
Sometimes if you light the baby,
that will produce enough smoke to keep it going.
A terrible fear, illogical and unexplained,
of certain creatures is maintained.
According to this theory.
Buzzing is just a metaphor.
Maddening sound.
You don't like the buzzing.
Welcome to my world.
What's the matter with a little bit of a buzz, huh?
Test, test, test.
Now come on, man.
It's the hole.
It's the hole that is...
We can't tell which mic is failing you.
It's a story of my life, man.
Always blaming it on that.
You men.
Yeah, it's the bitches, man.
It's all their fault.
And now I'm getting tangled up
in blue white...
You liars.
Jiggle it a little, it'll open.
If only he was here.
Reverend, jiggle it a little,
and it'll open.
This isn't like WREK,
your fancy radio station
that's got million dollar microphones.
And headphones.
I still do it in the recording bunker.
You guys, you two girls should...
We get the crappy mic.
No, that's actually the louder mic.
Oh gosh, it is loud.
Saw Bigfoot?
Near? Here?
Well, yeah, I understand there have been unusual sightings.
Not of just old sea qual, but...
But of shaggy, shambling beings
crashing through the woods.
Shambling things.
I'm not sure of shaggy, scaly, slimy.
I hear some of them feel like hagfish.
Oh, that's encouraging.
Yeah, that's a very...
Hagfish, lampreys...
It's not a nice slime.
It's not like a good, honest,
prairie squid slime.
Well, there are creatures near us.
Last year, I was walking on the upper road
and there was something large
crashing in the bushes near me.
There are things nearby, definitely.
You sure it wasn't one of your peers?
Peers?
Well, with no light,
totally drunk and lost and off the trail
and crashing through the bushes.
Bushes, you know, you might have something there.
Mm-hmm.
There are some bears
in this area.
These are ordinary bears?
Ordinary bears, not the...
Terrible.
Not the funny thing that everybody says all the time.
Yeah, not the right bears.
And they're supposed to be some sort of
equally lascivious creature.
We put notices up in the woods.
What the...
Oh, more things shoved in our mouths.
Story of my life.
And now...
Yeah, they've put in some regulations,
stern regulations on the rape bear population
and they put signs up.
I understand in their language.
And wasn't there an awful creature?
So we're going to be totally safe.
A terrible creature called Man Bear Pig.
Do you remember that?
Oh.
There's so many mixtures.
Well, anyway.
But a true subgenius has a power to control
and dismiss them.
Just as a Christian, according to Jack Cheechick,
can dismiss demons in Jesus' name.
There was a possum, a cat, and an amoeba.
Oh, man, that was rough.
Couldn't keep it out of a sleeping bag.
Well, and did anything unusual happen during the night?
That's another question.
It got cold.
That was unusual.
It got chill here.
And it was very pleasant.
It was really nice.
I had to pardon my brain.
I had to pardon my skin.
But it was warm for a long time, I thought.
The residual heat of the day lingered on.
Oh, no, no.
It was nice.
Especially naked rolling in the wet grass.
That was very nice.
We're feeding back.
I'm scared to put my mouth on it now, staying.
I got microphone marks on my teeth.
How much closer should I be?
Those are a badge of honor.
I'm going to be...
You sound like an echo.
So, it got chilly, you were saying.
But before that, you whinnied like a horse and rolled on the fresh grass.
Mm-hmm.
Has it rained very much?
What did I miss?
Any good storms?
Oh, torrential downpour.
Today?
Oh, no.
Because I just got in last night.
It was cool.
I mean, this is Ragnarok.
I mean, without that sweet sense around thinking you're going to die in your tent.
I mean, that's like that tasty foreshadowing.
There's worse ways to die.
At least it wasn't Ragnar-a-Rak.
It made my sticker peck out.
We have had some people who always have trouble with their tents and always get rained out.
And their tents get full of water, even when it's not raining.
My peckers are closer.
Bad luck.
It's the bad juju.
And what about unusual insect life?
Has anyone been visited in the tent by some large and spectral specimens?
I just held my breath.
Everything's slam show.
I can't even poop.
Well, I'm glad that works for you.
I'm not sure it would for me.
I really believe that.
And somehow I never got stung for decades.
I asked this guy who was a beekeeper, and he really wanted to shout bullshit at me in the middle of a Kroger.
He had a display of bees.
Here's one for you to take out and stay.
The problem with the bees is if one stings, they all sting.
It's like a chemical signal.
So you're fine with that big beard of bees on you or whatever until one of them decides to sting.
Okay, I've got Susie here.
And I have the surprise.
I have the surprise up on the screen.
I'm going to take advantage of this.
Scoot over just a little bit, Susie.
Okay, I'm not going to go into how or why I was in a GameStop on the way here.
But I found for $1.79 in an unmarked box this game called Pipe Mania.
Now, of course, for $1.79, I figured it was probably a little pipe puzzle.
It's a plumbing puzzle game, and it is.
But there was a surprise for me.
I've got to hold the mic and the controller here at the same time.
Pipe Mania, of course, I didn't expect it to be about J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It just was a cute title.
Everything with a pipe in it doesn't have to be about Bob.
I don't know if everybody here knew that.
Potential.
Also, I might mention that there are...
The name Bob is the most common name in English-speaking countries.
It's not always magic.
And it was...
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
Wait for it.
Totally open to bafflement.
You know, we were watching Jack the Giant Slayer, and they were using year 2000 cliches
like, wait for it, wait for it.
And okay.
I have a bad feeling about this, which was used twice in Star Wars.
Really?
And of course, the ever-present, yes!
And the ever-present, no!
And okay was in the medieval.
Yeah, people did.
Stanky, that's you.
Okay, Stanky's game.
Now, we have to go.
Oh, how to play.
That's the most important part.
Yes, we're going to find out what flows through these pipes.
Right.
All right.
The goal of Pipe Mania is to lay down a set of pipes that will allow the...
Flues to flow from the start piece to the end piece of each level without spilling out.
I'm a euphemism for do.
Yes, you are a euphemism for goo.
Oh, how do I get to my next...
There we go.
You can bomb a previously laid pipe segment by placing a new pipe.
The old pipe will explode and be replaced by a new one.
This takes time and incurs a score penalty.
Pipes filled with flues, obstacles, and fixed pipes cannot be bombed.
What if flues is fixed?
Use the...
Baby Bear, you should give Susie...
Force your microphone into Susie's face.
Fast flues?
Use the fast flues button to speed up the flues and end the level quickly.
While also scoring double points, which Susie is famous for.
Oh, boy.
For each pipe piece, the flues passes through.
While fast flues is active, no other moves can be made.
No wonder I've been laying so much cable since I got here.
You've been pulling the train for a long time here, Susie.
I sure have.
If you don't need it.
I have locomotives.
Stop.
Okay, the...
That pretty much explains the flues.
If you're way ahead of the flues...
You're in a race to beat the flues.
The goal is to lay down those pipes to allow the flues to flow and not spill out all over the place, which it will do.
That sounds logical on so many levels.
It scares me.
Oh, someone just had to put this together.
Basic pipes.
Oh, man, this is harder than you would think.
He told me.
You should try it from my perspective.
Trying not to make the flues overflow out of the pipes is like a 24-7 thing.
I'd rather see you than be you.
And now they've made it into a game.
Yes.
It's not loaded yet.
Oh, now it's loaded.
Okay.
Oh, that doesn't help that much.
You're actually going to play this...
Here comes the flues.
It's green.
And it's going to...
I can tell you right now that I'm about to get my ass kicked by the flues.
Yes.
The flues is...
Oh, now it's going to...
Now I know we're messed up.
Now you're just going to fill your pipe hole with flues.
Yep.
My pipe hole.
What happens if it gets up?
Oh, no, it's going to spill.
The flues is coming.
I ain't cleaning up after that.
It's all over everywhere.
By the way, be glad you're not hearing the...
The terrible, irritating MIDI music that goes with this.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yes.
The leak meter filled completely.
We're all dead.
No spark.
Well, anyway...
The flues beat me.
You see how it's done.
Yes.
Whooped by the flues again.
And all I had to do was ooze.
I just sat here and oozed and won the day.
I bet I would be really good at that game.
I'm part hagfish.
Oh, I'm sure you can play that game.
I like puzzle games.
I'm a puzzle game fan.
Yeah, that was...
I figured it was a puzzle game.
I picked that one up.
If you ever played Mercury,
this is what you...
You'd slide a tray full of mercury through a maze.
No, did you...
Without spilling it.
Did you get Loco Roco?
And you can get cancer from it.
What did you say?
So, did you get Loco Roco?
No.
It's only for the PSP.
It's a fun game.
Oh, I'll have to keep mine.
You're like a little ball and you use the thing to tilt the world.
You tilt the entire world.
You don't move yourself.
You just cause the entire level to tilt and that's how you move to and fro.
One little ball?
That sounds like a game to me.
I ain't seeing it.
There you go.
Okay.
By the way, if anyone on really bad drugs admires the video and says,
gosh, I want a copy of that for when I'm on even worse drugs later,
this is all from the collection called Dobsidilium.
Or Dobsidiliastes.
That's what it is.
All available.
Not to be confused with one of the shorts in it, which is called Dobsidiliastes.
Not at all confusing.
I say Yakutismo.
Let's blow the whole thing off.
Is that available at the Swack Shack over there?
Yes.
Only a couple of copies left.
Yes, they're running out.
They're running out of the pipes just like the flues.
Oozing.
You're running out of time to spend all of your money before the fifth.
After all, it's not worth anything anymore.
It took me a long time to find the ooze.
No, you don't want to be too heavy.
Just lean closer.
I'll hit my tooth again.
There you go.
Now we can hear your dulcet.
I'm dentally shy of the mic.
Respecting you and your needs.
There are Democrats in the White House.
Where's the roll bar for this thing?
I need a safety device so I don't hurt myself.
Okay, I'm all done for.
Put your game away.
Not on the radio.
Not at the dinner table.
No, I try to go by the rules of good radio by which you don't watch YouTube and computer
pornography during your show unless you know everyone in the audience is looking at the
same YouTube or pornography.
That's a very good point.
Very good plan.
Very good provision.
Now, I wish that Philo and Puzzling Evidence would stick with that plan.
It's not I who puts those YouTubes up during shows.
No, but if you talk about the YouTubes, you're enabling those bad boys.
You just have to use your imagination.
How do you like it?
I've got it set up to where you and me are blinded by the video projector, Susie.
Blinded by science.
And there's a beautiful silhouette of my goatee and her armpit hair.
That's my back.
Mygoatee.com.
That was a great band.
Yeah.
Mygoatee.com.
You can lean over this way if you want.
Too temperamental to stay together.
And get out of the light.
Yeah, now see, if you girls could successfully learn how to share one of those pecker-shaped
rods there.
How to cooperate.
What do they have to share now?
That microphone, although this one would probably be okay.
Oh, the story of my life.
Don't impose your rules.
There we go.
Don't impose your rules on us.
Yeah, man.
No more rules, man.
Your regulations.
Sign, sign, everywhere a sign.
Questioning authority.
Repeat yourself.
And, uh.
Wait, I forget.
Are we supposed to do that or not?
Do what?
Question authority.
I'm confused.
We need to ask someone.
If you don't question authority, we'll put you in the, uh, bad anti-authoritarian prison.
Who is an art authority?
We're, we are the, as Dr. Onan Kanabike put it, the church of the subgenius.
We're the mind your own business police.
We will goddamn force you to mind your own business.
That, uh, it's not a business.
It's not a choice.
Okay?
It's for your own good.
So roll over and take your medicine.
Miss Tori took her shirt off and I got distracted for a second there.
Well, cue to your, to your, to your.
But only for a second.
Well, now it's dragging on and on and on.
Put your shirt back on, hon.
God damn it.
We're trying to do a show here.
Yes.
Oh, now Pisces.
Going to do one thing.
Oh, next thing they're all going to take their shirts off just to ruin the show that's already,
boy, I'm going to have to edit this one a lot.
That's the trick.
If you tell a woman.
We'll be crackling with excitement.
If you tell a woman to take her shirt off, she probably won't do it.
Right.
If you tell her to put her shirt on, then all of a sudden women start taking their shirts
off.
Keep your shirts on, gals.
What?
Look, Suzie the flute.
Now see, she knows how to be a good subgenius.
Don't give the church a thousand dollars.
Anyone, whatever you do, don't give us your spare money.
Nobody bring me a bottle of water.
Yeah, don't anybody help pack up the equipment when it's all over with.
Wait a minute.
We don't have to worry about that.
We'll just beam up anything that we don't feel that we can have reproduced perfectly
on the saucer.
Destroy it and get better equipment.
Suzie, put your titties over there next to that microphone so we can hear them.
No, no, no.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't count.
It's still over it like a dolly.
But look, Reverend Glitch has brought some water for Baby Bear.
Yay!
Thank you.
Thank you, Glitch.
Now, Baby Bear has not yet been schooled by her elders, the rape bears.
The ice truck's here.
Oh, boy.
The Iceman's here.
Oh, that's actually, that's what we're...
He really does that.
Ice all the way from the glaciers of the North.
Don't ask me.
Hello.
The lady over there can help you.
They're in charge of the ice hole.
The Iceman's coming.
You know, I just missed a great opportunity.
The Iceman cameth, and I had the chance then to pull some kind of a...like, take it down
to that pond, the fork in the road and tump it all right into there.
And if a giant tortoise-looking thing, a sea serpent monster, a big turtle, yeah, turtle,
it's in the water.
He likes turtles.
Snapping turtle-looking thing, rises to the surface.
Tortoises are land-based.
Go over there and pet it on the head.
Yeah, that's it.
This one has scuba devices.
A tortoise with scuba gear.
That's what old Sea Coy is.
You girls just don't talk loud enough.
Tortoises are on land and turtles are in the water.
I can't say whatever.
I don't know.
Yes, you don't want to be the first to be serviced.
This iceman means to be serviced.
I can see there's ... He needs oil in his ice.
I can smell it.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can hear you fine.
That's all better ice than the ice that's in here.
However, Susie, like Philo, is refusing to cooperate.
You know, there've been times when I've had to like literally grab the microphone, carry
it across the room.
and shove it in Philo's fucking face
because he would not.
He just couldn't make that extra effort
to lean forward to where the microphone was.
Well, we seem to be having a diesel exhaust event here.
That just seems to compromise what comes out.
I'm picking up some nice background noises there.
Can you hear that?
I'm going to turn down the music.
This is good time for your sound effects record, Dr. Howell.
Yes, incredible.
We have that rumbling.
Life-like sounds of a giant diesel truck,
which we have to add in post.
No, I mean your thunder stick there.
Oh, yes, well, I can try.
You should demonstrate that.
Well, I did before,
but I wasn't even sure this microphone was really on.
That's quite an impressive tube.
Friends, this is the way the primitive cavemen
did scary narrations for science fiction movies.
A long time ago.
Man, the broadcaster.
Man, the tool abuser.
There you go.
Creatures.
Creatures that sit and wait.
Creatures who must kill to live.
Shamble and drop.
I'm getting my daily dose of diesel fuels.
All in one sitting.
Dr. Howell is replicating the soundtrack
of the classic Hammer motion,
one million years B.C.
And man,
superior to the creatures
only in his cunning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So where did you get that incredible
piece of equipment?
Where did you get that incredible
sound effects machine?
They're at Guitar Center for $7.
What?
You told me some story
about Tibetan monks,
carving it for you
out of the skulls of sinners or something.
Well, maybe in some other life than this,
that could have happened,
but a good old cardboard tube.
You see, this cheap Chinese junk
is really ingeniously constructed
out of ready-made materials.
Yeah, make one yourself, kids.
Yeah, that's right.
Toilet paper roll and a slinky.
A spring.
To sproing in.
To a new life.
I'm distracted by it.
Reverend Fox left his laptop over here.
Laptop.
Look at the...
Oh, I'm doing it.
I'm looking at YouTube things
and talking about it
when the audience gets it.
Yeah, stop doing it.
You were the one who was down on it.
Oh, they told me not to,
so I did it.
I'm a good subgenius.
I get an award now.
All right.
Stop watching MTV
and attend to the business at hand.
Now, let's see.
That means I should start watching MTV.
On the bizarro subgenius world?
On the radar, trust me.
Me bizarro subgenius.
Me hate slack.
Oh, we did that one yesterday.
A couple of years ago,
we had a crew here
shooting this all in 3D.
And consequently,
they never finished their project.
Yeah, there really was a film crew here
making us do everything in 3D,
which was a lot of extra work.
I don't know if you've ever had to do that.
You have to go like this a lot at the camera.
For what purpose?
Why would you need it to be in 3D?
Who's going,
who's going to view it in 3D?
They wanted to view it in 3D,
but it's about the most undynamic setup
you can think of.
People sitting behind a desk and talking.
But nonetheless,
they're here with 3D and...
It's coming right at me,
out of the screen.
They're adding to our discomfort
in the heat immeasurably
by turning on their hot movie lights
and blasting us with them
just so they can get a good 3D picture
of us sitting here and talking.
Well, the main point of their project
was to show us being the,
the usual gang of idiots that we are.
And then it was going to be intercut
with famous celebrities saying things like,
well, you know,
the Church of the Subgenius
is America's secret treasure.
It's a...
But when they went to the famous celebrities...
They're all dead, aren't they?
They weren't very forthcoming.
Let's just put it that way.
Either they were dead
or they'd forgotten about Bob
or the conspiracy had said,
no, you're famous now.
You can't talk about Bob.
You're still around?
Huh?
I get that.
No, no, don't look at me when you talk.
They're still around?
You're still doing that subgenius thing?
Right, yeah.
To quote R. Crumb...
I was really into that in high school.
Well, now, it's so sad
that we still hear that.
And the guy saying it is 70 years old.
Well, the problem is
they're not buying their copies of Revelation X.
They stopped at the book of the subgenius.
But if you want to go farther and higher,
and upper and deeper in this subject,
you've got to get a copy of Revelation X.
And as I said yesterday,
here we can sign it for you
and increase its value exponentially,
which you can't do if you get it on Amazon
or in a bookstore or a swap meet
or something like that.
It's like they think that being weird
is just going to stop.
That's so yesterday.
I haven't had that happen yet.
Being normal is where it's at.
It's hip to be square.
Oh, yeah, now you can buy your copy
of Bob Leografon for like $500 on eBay now.
Yeah, or you could be my really good friend.
Or sell it, I guess, and find somewhere to buy it.
Those are all staying sat on naked.
I still have a box of 30 of the...
our greatest book, the Third Testament,
and I've got about 30 copies
of the subgenius New World Order game.
From Steve Jackson Games.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm saving all of those
for the contributors for the inevitable day
when they call me up and go,
hey, I like loaned my copy out to my nephew
and he like went to Iraq and it's lost now.
So can you like, do you have any more of them
you can send me for like free?
Why, sure.
Heart Ignition, sure.
Lemur.
No.
Sure.
Oh, wait, actually,
the game was done before those guys.
Is the game...
I don't have to worry about it.
People who worked on those things are dead now.
We're the last living elder subgeniuses,
Hal and Susie.
Is it in the style of Illuminati?
Huh?
Is it in the style of like the game Illuminati?
Oh, you haven't seen it?
Yeah, it's a spinoff
from the Steve Jackson Illuminati game.
It fits in.
It's like an extra pack of 100 cards.
Ah, I love that game.
And I'll tell you,
it was actually designed by Steve Jackson.
And oddly enough, in this case,
I handled the illustrations
because as you know,
I didn't know anything about games,
especially that kind of game.
And I've never played it.
But I always saw it as a great rolling tray
with 100 little cool art cards that came with it.
Steve Jackson.
I do know that the way to win it,
is to send $1 to the church of the subgenius in an envelope.
It's that way you always win.
But I'm surprised.
I'm not kidding.
That actually is what Steve Jackson worked it into the game
as the, that's like the special extra little thing
that is pretty much guaranteed that you win.
And Steve Jackson himself has sent me at least four,
I've gotten $4 in the mail in little envelopes,
$1 bills from Steve Jackson.
And he's the guy who always wins.
I didn't get a dollar in the mail.
I got mail from many other people.
So if they say they won, they were cheating.
Steve Jackson makes a good game,
but he does make games that will make you hate all of your friends.
Really?
How does that work?
Oh yes.
They will turn you against brother against brother.
They must be really good games.
It will tear you apart.
It will tear apart friendships and families.
An unusual epi phenomenon.
So you've never, you haven't even seen the subgenius in-world game, right?
I don't think so.
It's really rare.
It's really rare, isn't it?
Pity you didn't bring a copy.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, I don't think there's one in this campground now that I think about it.
Yeah, so all this talking about it is futile and sad.
No, because Reverend Michael Mirth, the stage magician who happens to live in Cleveland,
has the other 25 copies remaining of the game and he's selling them for $185 a piece.
I actually think I saw one that was more in the, more around $500 to $700.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I wish Michael Mirth could have made it here because he's a good magician but we don't pay enough.
He won't take payment in slack?
He did once.
You know, setting new recording.
We have a side note here.
Oh, you know, that's one, it's amazing how technology has improved so much that, you know, so much better with this digital stuff than the old cassette tapes where all you had to do was push the button.
You had to push stop and flip it and it was running again in 10 seconds.
Right now you have to finalize your 80 minute CD or your 2 gigabyte card or whatnot and sit and scratch your whatevers, all three of them.
Well, you can't make an omelet without breaking some eggs.
And that's when the funniest stuff happens, of course, except this time.
That's progress.
Most times that happens.
Oh, look, there's Tommy Amoeba making a, oh, we're talking about the YouTube again.
Damn it.
Tommy Amoeba will be here, folks.
Yes.
All right.
Oh, we're back to rolling again.
There's Dr. Dark is hobbling into the cafe.
Look what he's brought.
No doubt a bunch of Bull Dada auction material.
Great stuff for the Bull Dada auction.
You don't want to miss that historic event.
I like so many things at the moment.
And you don't want to be the one just hoping someone else will buy stuff so they'll move on to the next one.
If you get bored with the auctioneering, the only way to stop the auctioneer from getting out of that rut is to buy it.
Luckily, most of these things end up being offered for about a dollar first.
Well, it depends on the level of enthusiasm.
And remember, on the pleasure saucers, you will have untold wealth and riches.
But you can get a little equity on everybody else by starting to accumulate your wealth and riches now.
Right.
On the saucers, money won't mean anything.
Good looks won't mean anything because those will all be free.
What will be important is who's got the coolest crap to show off.
Who's got the most imaginative collection of weird stuff and who has surgically transformed themselves in the most daring way.
I want all of the original Pokemon.
What do you have there?
I will have all living copies of them.
Oh, look, a gift.
This can either be auctioned.
Mr. Sistar has brought some pulpo.
Some octopus.
In aceite de soja oliva.
So it's octopus in olive oil.
You do and you clean it up.
Wild caught, not farm octopus.
These fought back.
These are free range octopus.
These have the taste of terror and fear and anger in them.
Don't you feel bad?
Don't you feel bad eating octopus?
I'm deaf and so is everyone else.
Every tentacle a taste sensation.
Um.
So we're getting.
Well, I could have lunch right here.
I've got my ranch style beans, a bunch of octopus.
What else do you need?
Octopus and beans have enlivened many a campfire.
In the UK, they consider octopuses so intelligent or octopi, octopodes.
Octopuses.
It's octopuses.
The octopodes.
It is octopuses.
Although some people.
Isn't it octopodes?
Like octopodes, like my learned friend, Baby Bear.
Well, anyway, they consider them.
Octaroons.
They consider them honorary invertebrates.
I don't think they like that name.
That's kind of an archaic.
In the south, they call them.
It's kind of a put down.
We could have archaic and eat it too.
That's like calling them a high slimer or something.
Whatever.
I think he's going to eat all of them right here.
You were going to make them an honorary vertebrate, did you say?
No, no.
In the UK, they, so for the animal like cruelty laws, they consider octopuses, octopodes to
be honorary vertebrates.
Well, that's good because they are sensitive and shy and shouldn't be tormented the way
they are.
Do you see what happened a few years ago to Paul the octopus?
No.
What happened to Paul?
Well, he died.
Not that I know of.
But before that.
Before that, this particular octopus could predict who would win in races and the direction
of the stock market and so on.
And a big fuss was made about him.
Then the Islamic world began to denounce the Western devils who let this hideous octopus
decide their fate for them.
And the middle of it all, Paul the octopus, probed and bothered by scientists and thrill
seekers just died.
Because they're shy.
And they don't like to be in the spotlight.
But he had the uncanny ability to predict future events and made some people a lot of
money.
Please Google Paul the octopus.
P-A-U-L, the octopus.
As if your very life depended on it.
Google Paul the octopus.
No, the thing is, we say all these outlandish things.
They're all checkable.
Go to, look, go to the internet.
You'll find they're actually there.
That's the interesting thing.
Or if you can't reach the internet now, make a little note.
With a pencil.
And put a piece of paper in your pocket.
Look up Paul the octopus and read his sad story.
You know, back in the old days, when you needed to know something, you had to look
it up in an encyclopedia.
And then the future came and you could Google it or Wiki it.
But friends, here, we don't need all that high tech crap.
All we have to do is...
Ask Dr. Howell.
Why, yes.
The human Wikipedia.
But not today.
And he's just as accurate.
Tomorrow.
And we'll do the Bulldada auction, the first phase of it today.
But there will be an Ask Dr. Howell tomorrow.
And behind the scenes of Ask Dr. Howell, there's the Ask Dr. Howell discussion groups
for every Ask Dr. Howell question.
And the hands-on Ask Dr. Howell healing centers and other...
Well, yeah.
...great aspects of our ministry.
So, yeah, save up your questions and your donations, because information, contrary to
popular belief, does not want to be free.
I happen to know information personally, and it wants to get paid just like everybody
else.
Well, a curious thing was recently discovered that they produce maps of Google searches
to see in what areas of the country.
People were trying to find things out.
And on the East Coast and the West Coast, in the metropolitan areas, the map was black
with Google searches.
But in the middle of the country, few people seem to be trying to find out anything.
Why is this?
They're not as insecure as those big city folks.
Those big city folks have to check everything and double-check.
But the peaceful, rural...
Hey, Chuck.
...possessing, unassuming farmers are content to wallow in their own ignorance.
They got the Bible on CD wrong.
That's right.
Princess Wee, could you find a little plastic fork or something so I can try some of this
octopus?
Stang's gonna chow down on octopus right here and now, folks.
Eat it with your hands.
And he did last year at this time.
Plastic.
Oh, get him a wooden fork.
Live a little.
Splurge.
When you come to a fork in the road, take it, as Yogi Berra said.
The speedy Reverend Glitch was on the job.
There's somebody who knows how to walk fast.
He's a helpful guy.
He's a guy after my own fast walking hard...
Oh, and I got...
Okay.
Who wants a taste of pulpo?
Thanks, I'll pass.
I knew you'd say that.
I'm sorry.
No, you didn't know.
I've eaten octopus a lot.
I live in San Francisco.
My friends are Chinese.
You wouldn't believe what they give me for snacks.
Octopus?
Now, all sharing the sacrament of octopus.
I've had octopus in sushi form.
Well, if everybody's eating it, I'll eat some.
Oh, here.
All right, I'll try it.
It actually does smell...
I'll try it.
You take a bite.
I'll take a bite.
It smells not good, but familiar in strange ways.
The smell of an old, familiar octopus.
It's just a little bit of a smell.
It's like cat food that puts up a fight.
It smells like my office trash can.
I'm going to put juice all over myself.
Well, yeah, you got to...
All over your lap.
Don't tell anybody.
That's going to attract the adult bears, baby bear.
You'll finally get your lessons in raping.
She's just a baby rape bear.
They're cute when they're little.
I'm going to put juice now.
It's terrible.
Yeah, it is terrible.
Thank you.
I kind of knew that would happen when I opened it.
That's the pulpo part, isn't it?
And that's why I was being so very careful.
I went to X Day and all I got was octopus all over my clothes.
Octopus juice.
Octopus flues, we call it.
Can you stop the flooding, spreading flues?
It's not bad.
This octopus is al dente.
It's rubbery, chewy.
Yeah.
I'm going to get for trying new things.
That's what happens.
Okay, now I've tasted it.
I don't want to try anything new because what if I didn't like it?
I'm afraid of not liking things and then what would happen?
If I tried something and I didn't like it?
Right.
You don't know.
You'd never try anything again.
There would be terrible consequences.
What if I'm allergic?
What if I died?
I must remember not to breathe in anybody's face after chewing this.
What if all of the above?
Or be called octopus breath.
What if it all happened at once?
Or touch anyone?
I'll draw another chunk.
Alright.
Sussie's no octopussy.
I'm a thrill seeker.
She's a thrill seeker, Seekers.
Well, by consuming this octopus you will be able to be more like an octopus.
I want to attain his power.
Most of the ink squirting thing.
Yes.
When you consume the octopus you gain...
What?
his dexterity.
Whistle-solving skills.
If only that were possible. They can do
incredible things. They can put their entire
body through a tiny hole,
not having any bones,
and they can configure their body
to any shape, having
incredible power
over it. That is, they can cause bumps
and things to rise up out of their body.
They can disguise themselves as a piece
of coral, or look like a plant
on the ocean floor.
And they can change their color.
They can imitate popular
animated GIFs from
4chan. In fact, most
of the... Oh, you say GIFs?
Yes, I say GIFs. Most of the popular
personalities that you see on
television are octopuses
disguised effortlessly
as humans. No, wait a minute.
I call them GIFs. What am I saying?
I don't know. You said GIF. I thought it was weird.
Yeah, I usually say GIF.
GIF is peanut butter. That's the way
it's supposed to be, though.
It's socialist propaganda.
The inventor decided to
wreck everybody's
fantasies.
Wait, how do you pronounce it, Mr. Sister?
Yeah, see, that's
what I say, because if you have to spell it
differently to tell people how to pronounce it,
it's an invented word from like
30 years ago. It's GIFs. Come on.
It's also proprietary.
I'm solving the internet war over it right
now. Thank you.
They like to come out with unpronounceable
words. Enough about that.
Yes.
When you devour the octopus, when you devour
the chicken, you gain his courage.
When you devour the flesh of the cow,
you gain his wisdom,
his craftiness.
Yes.
When you devour the pig,
you gain his
his
boundless, what?
Omnivory. Yes.
Monogamy. Is that why I'm so
mixed up?
Well, that's one reason.
Pigs and humans are
disturbingly similar in many
anatomical peculiarities,
and this has never been explained.
And embryologists dissect
fetal pigs to come as
close as possible to the human embryo.
There are many similarities that
the suedi, the swine,
have with the humans that
apes and monkeys do not have.
And this has never been
satisfactorily explained. Really? I didn't know
that. Oh, it is so.
Huh. Well, doesn't
Mr. Sister have part of a
pig's spine in his neck or something like that?
Oh, I wasn't making a personal remark.
I didn't know about that. No, I mean, didn't they
implant...
Oh, it was a
a policeman.
I misunderstood what you meant.
He got it from a dead human. It was dug up by a
cadaver dog. No, I'm
just kidding.
Okay, well. But I am smelling
something. Oh, there's a barbecue
over there? When you devour the
soybean, you gain its
courage.
Its mobility.
Its fart?
Its responsivity to the sun.
When you devour the ranch-style
bean, you gain its coolness.
Which,
they're not cool to most people, but...
Pythagoras thought beans
were sacred.
Huh? Pythagoras
thought beans were sacred.
And the cult of
worshipping the bean came
from the Pythagoreans.
In ancient Athens.
Gee, well, I guess those old ancient Greeks
must have known everything. Yeah, they sure
knew their onions. Sure were smart to
worship a bunch of beans.
Praise God.
At least we've got our priorities
straight.
How can they worship
a legume when
there's perfectly good clip art?
Well, there wasn't so much clip art
in ancient Greece.
And also, they had a great respect for
mathematics, especially Pythagoras'
Pythagoras, I mean,
the original bean counter.
Oh, is that where they get that?
Okay. It's all true. I mean,
really, they...
I don't know why, but bean was
an important object in their
devotions.
Save all bean-related questions
for Ask Dr. Howell tomorrow.
And we know that certain beans, when dropped in the
ground, instantly cause an enormous
beanstalk to grow
up to the sky, where
giants can be
be found.
Yeah, it's been hard for us to shake
that crappy
Hollywood movie, Jack the Giant Slayer,
from our head. We saw it, yeah.
You mean that movie wasn't true?
Well, it had
giants in it. It had giants. That's all
you need. I know
I said this yesterday, but in that
movie, some
maladroit giant accidentally dropped
a magic bean when they were already
up in giant land, and a huge
beanstalk started to grow up there.
So I was wondering, would that
beanstalk carry a giant
up to an even higher giant
land, containing even bigger giants
that would dwarf the giants
in giant land?
Or Gantua, as
it was known.
But we'll never know, because
the giants
grabbed the beanstalks and bent them
down toward the earth, so they could
ride down and invade.
Sooner or later, the weight of the giants
is going to collapse a whole skin.
According to the movie,
somewhere out there is
one last bean.
One last bean that could
get us to giant land.
Or, contrary-wise,
could get the giants down
to here. But we don't need
to worry, because the same movie also
explains that the British
crown, the property of the current
monarch, Queen Elizabeth II,
actually is the ancient crown
that can control all the giants.
It was simply refurbished and had
the kings added to it through the years,
and it now resides in the
Tower of London, where it's on display.
Well, that's convenient.
Just don't let the lions get you.
They still do have lions in the Tower of London,
don't they? Or do they?
They have ravens.
Maybe they took them out since my time.
They used to have lions.
They did.
Susie, you're lying down on the job as long as
you're not yelling into that microphone.
I'm sorry. She doesn't have anything to say.
I don't have anything to say.
I'm so sorry.
No, um...
Ugh.
No groaning in exasperation,
Stag. You must make the best
of it, certainly.
I'm sure that there's a lot to
relate.
Pope Robert Anton Wilson was the most
microphone-unfriendly
guy I ever had to mic.
Not a Gabby sort.
Well, oh yeah, I was very Gabby,
but you'd put the mic in the
normal place and he'd lean
back and talk
like you did.
Louder and funnier.
Back and back and back.
You'd move the mic up to him like that
and he'd start talking again and back and back.
Sounds like Philo.
Yes, exactly.
And, um, we
who have to adjust
the volumes on these things,
let me tell you we don't
appreciate that because
it makes our mouse wrist
hurt.
With every selection
of the mumbler.
High volume, low quality.
And, uh, on the other hand, if this Radio Shack
mixer had one other mic input
or if there was another little pre-mixer
then we'd all be...
We'd be able to clip a mic to
Susie's cheek
pointing into her lips.
I know you want to do that.
Hear her muttering and mumbling.
Well, she says a lot of really funny stuff.
With her face pointed at me.
But you have to be there.
Right, you have to be here right in front of the camera.
You're funny looking. I can't help but respond to it.
If you had a mic sticking out of your face
maybe you'd get some gem-like
wisdom from me.
You just have to ignore it.
Ignore that the mic is there to see.
It's like your nose which you don't
normally see unless you've tried.
No, the mic is your friend.
Your microphone is your friend.
This is my mic.
This is...
This is my microphone. This is my gun.
This one's for talking, the other's for fun.
This is my microphone.
There are many like it, but this one is mine.
I will use my microphone to be heard.
I will.
I will be heard loudly.
My microphone will carry my voice.
My every word is
a turd to be heard.
There you go.
Baby bear, I see
you don't have your carpal tunnel
bandage on, so it got better?
Well, when I'm not
actually at work and having
to move a mouse around, plus
Susie gave me these strange
eyeballs. She gave you wonderful
eyeball bracelets
that look back at you when you look at it.
Plus it's placebo, so
because I think they work, they'll work.
I just have to keep believing it.
Yeah, they have magic.
Brass and other metals can
ease your
rheumatism.
Did you
consult Mr.
about the carpal tunnel issues
as you were planning to? Yes, I did.
He's very knowledgeable. He was helpful.
Did he operate on your wrist and
sew the
tendons together and
implant some artificial? No, I wish because I would
love for it to be fixed, but as long as I don't
use it or do anything strenuous,
it's okay. Well, don't get anywhere near
a mouse during this trip.
I thought her carpal tunnel
was all bare somehow. Eek!
A mouse! Has
anyone manufactured a computer
mouse known as
the Eek?
Because that would be cute.
Eek! A mouse! Another million dollar
idea and it's all yours, Stan.
Twenty percent off at Walgreens
this week only. Just remember me
when you're wallowing in your wealth.
You've been listening
to the subgenius
radio ministry
Hour of Slack.
For free information
write to
P.O. Box
1-8-1
4-1-7
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio
4-4-1-1-8
or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
Friends,
we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some
listeners have donated enough to help us
keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show,
but subgenius.com
and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly
love Bob and want some of that
slack back to rebound
to you, you should go to
subgenius.com
front page or especially the radio page
or the catalog store pages
and help out
financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be
on the brink of total poverty
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their
own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks
makes a big difference
even if it's only once a month
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying
is that
blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs
if you don't pay dogs.
We also take
checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
Thanks for
anything you can do to help
let there be slack.