PR comes from a non-found-owners-proption.org.org.
This is PR.
PR.
It's PR with PR and PR in Pensacuspo.
PR is with you.
PR News and PR News.
From PR News in Washington, I'm leaving Kansas City.
PR News in Kansas City.
Vermont Democrat Patrick Leahy is swinging in the wrong direction.
This country is committed.
And we're committed by dedicating a lot of resources.
This is PR News.
PR News, Washington.
Leaking led to the coal miners' methane gas flame this year.
Last spring, men's methane leaked out.
The explosion that followed was so powerful, it ruptured miners in the explosion afterwards.
The company has since abandoned PR News.
New numbers at week's weakness, 3060, 1.7, 340, and 53.
Bob's raising questions about PR News in Washington.
I hear you singing in the waters.
I can hear you through the subgenius power of smart.
Oh!
Just like Chris Vinning.
I like it.
Oh, sorry.
I got a distinction.
Me too.
Oh, sorry.
Dude, Brian.
That's not what I was thinking.
Fancy.
Well, Bob Dobbs told me to pay attention
To the words of the subgenius church
Well, Bob Dobbs told me
To pay attention
Well done.
Oh.
We're gonna be doing a show somehow.
Show?
A little bit of a...
Like a...
Like a show?
Oh, sh...
Hal's talking.
Is that Hal?
Pretty soon, an image will start to appear.
Sounds like Hal.
I think he's talking about Bob.
But he's mumbling about Bob.
Maybe one letter in the forms of time as the years descend gently upon you.
Mumbling for Bob, baby.
The face in short.
Streaming through your life.
Nothing wrong with mumbling for Bob.
I am out of the world.
I'm out of the world.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
The world's...
Truly...
Black and white.
Experimenting with the television set of his own design.
Messing around with the back of the set.
He received a tremendous shock in assisting...
A divine...
Intellectual...
Social...
Ejaculation?
No, that can't be right.
Well, anyway, whatever it was, it was...
I gotta tell ya.
It was the basis of this whole thing.
This sub-genius thing we're always talking about.
You wanna know how it got into it?
I started that, so it's got style.
Was that, was that thing?
This is a news minute.
Bush used dog beer last night.
Help, help, help.
And there's lots of it.
The FBI has nowhere to go.
President Netanyahu, President Netanyahu.
Bush is, he's in critical condition.
Behind bars Tuesday.
Crouching and dropping something.
State of the Union's soured so many.
An abortion from behind.
Give it a chance to work.
Give it a chance, give it a chance.
Inside a motel room.
Our citizens don't much care.
And so it remains the policy of this government,
to inspire blind hatred.
Terrorist activity.
America's on the verge of violent and malignant ideology.
So we advance our own violent and malignant ideology.
And I say, come and kill us.
Don't much care, don't much care.
We need a new direction.
DNA testing.
Toxic substance.
Build up.
The war on terror we fight today is a chance for the millions of other Americans
who have no health insurance at all.
I've asked the Secretary of Health and Human Services
and their doctors on clean, safe nuclear power.
Tonight.
We must.
Junk work.
Madam, madam, madam, madam, madam, madam, madam, madam, madam,
President Cheney.
Dangers have ended.
Hard.
Spend the people's money.
And this is the business before us tonight.
Terrorism.
Now available online.
Conclusion.
The Iraq war has bred deep resentment among Muslims around the world.
And helped rally many to the cause of terrorism.
Iraq is shaping a new generation of terrorist leaders.
My judgment is preposterous.
A sad tale of human error.
The invasion.
Created terrorists.
All right, I guess I wasn't thinking.
Find some other excuse.
Y'all weren't thinking.
Here, shake hands with danger.
Shake hands with danger.
I told him not to touch anything.
Madam.
Three-fingered Joe.
My judgment is the only.
A mistake, a mistake.
Shake hands with danger.
It's the false democracy of elites.
Weapons and bombs and firing weapons.
What a straight line.
Change democracy.
Bush as the devil.
And the devil came here yesterday.
Yesterday the devil came.
And it smells of sulfur still today.
My judgment is the only.
A mistake, a mistake.
Cynical.
Hypocritical.
Fool of this imperial hypocrisy.
Dear world dictator.
How cynical can you get?
What a capacity to lie.
Because they have ambitions.
Sperm.
Problem.
Raised position.
Feels stiff.
Rise.
Hairy.
You're shaking hands with danger.
Demand.
They're big enough.
Wherever possible the stick should be extended.
Hairy has come to work with a.
Okay.
Now most people have days when they come to work with worries, hangovers or distractions.
It's danger time.
Just give it a whack.
Party.
The people who shake hands with danger.
The hole is dry.
There's no stick.
Shake hands with danger.
Danger.
Diagnosis.
Manager.
Danger.
Rapunzel él reclames la accidente meiesta.
using content to provide credit cal pedir el servicio a los perdidos o terciopio
YueC prayer of Dazuan.
d conditioned to make ci Emmanuel Patri precio al habilitar y pet Nobody from this matters
être Amen
You fired me.
Well, this is for you.
Good.
I didn't raise my mat.
Great, well done.
Done.
Thursday.
Wednesday, douchebag.
Thursday, assface.
Wednesday, you f***ing idiot!
What is going on here?
We're having a fight about the due date of the marketing proposal.
Well, then there's only one way to solve it.
Fight!
Stapler!
Post it! Post it! Post it!
Finish him.
Level 2.
You know that proposal was due on Wednesday, Jim.
Thursday, Nancy.
Fight!
Sexual harassment!
Lawsuit! Lawsuit!
Letter opener!
Level 3.
Ryu from Street Fighter? I didn't know you worked here.
I don't, but that proposal was definitely due on Wednesday.
Fight!
Are you dead?
I'll get right on it.
This looks like a good place to park.
I don't know if, uh...
It looks like there's been an explosive device here for the last few weeks.
Wait a minute.
Oh, yes, sir.
Twenty seconds to move you there.
Oh, uh, yes, sir.
I'm, I'm moving it.
Right now.
Okay, keep listening to the tone, sir.
We're moving it.
We're moving it, sir.
Just listen to the tone.
We'll move the car for you.
Please, please!
We'll move the...
Fight, Mario!
I know.
I'm gonna make it movie.
Ugh.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Listen to the lilting sound of lonesome cowboy Dave on his big organ.
It is a big organ.
I'm not hearing you, Princess Wee, on your live microphone here in the studio.
No, I'm hearing you. I'm right here and I'm talking.
Huh?
Why would it be that you wouldn't be hearing me?
It's because of the clothespin on your nose and the fact that you're speaking in Welsh.
But I have no clothespin on my nose.
Wiggle the base of that thing's...
Wiggle the diaphragm of the koala device.
The bottom. The creature's bottom.
The koala. Whatever the koala is.
And make noise.
And begin to...
That's better. I heard that.
Now examine the tendrils at the very bottom there. You'll notice...
Now can you hear? Can you hear me now?
Yeah.
And now.
So...
So what are we to make of those cold nabobs? Does that mean that they're somehow... they disagree or that they...
Now which...
Which cold nabobs?
Which cold...
The cold... the cold of nabobs.
Now what is a nabob? It's like a... a... a... a... a...
A naysayer.
A naysayer. A nabob is...
And one who would say nay to Bob.
Right. So that's what... you know, it's clear as mud. At least you can figure out the... the bottom part, right?
Yes, friends. I should say, uh, we must... and we must thank Reverend Norell Preff of norellpreff.com.
For the, uh, collages, the last several collages. And, uh, Fernanda Nandy-Lemur for the other opening collages.
And Glass Madness for that song Bob Dobbs says to pay attention.
Is he a real man or is he one of your half-men?
He is a homunculus created in my laboratory.
You create homunculi?
Yeah, turn that thing down a little bit. It's a little obnoxious, I think.
Yeah, that sounds a little more...
We've also got the... the, uh, soundtrack of...
Perhaps it was.
What will become of the Baron?
Baron who, von Munch?
Baron Munchkin in the background.
Baron von Munchkin?
A eunuch's life is hard, you know.
Well, I don't imagine it's that hard.
In fact, that's the next song up. We could... we could play that song. Do you remember the... the movie, Bar... Adventures of Baron Munchausen?
Oh, as if it were my last, uh...
Dream.
Dream, yes.
The Sultan had, uh, entertained the Baron using a special musical instrument he had devised that involved, uh, slaves in cages.
And each key on his keyboard would cause a weapon to poke one of the slaves or prisoners in the cage.
And they would cry out a painful sound and that would be the...
Each slave would make a different noise depending on which key.
You could play chords and so forth.
He made an organ. I mean, he made an opera called A Eunuch's Life is Hard.
And once again, a eunuch's life can't be that.
No, it can't. That's the... that's the irony of it.
Well, what about the flattening of the skulls of the early eunuchs back in the days? Remember when they'd, uh, slap them on their backs and go running through the world?
I saw that movie. Apocalypto. That's up for an Academy Award tonight.
Friends, we have, uh, competition from the... for our listenership.
Not... probably not much. I doubt if many subgeniuses would be pink.
Oh, wait, here it is. Here's the song, A Eunuch's Life is Hard.
A torturer's apprentice went this many way to work one day.
I bend and stretch and ply my trade, making people all afraid.
But things look black, business is slack, there's no one on the rack but me.
Cut off in my prime, surrounded by beautiful women all the time.
A eunuch's life is hard. A eunuch's life is hard.
And nothing else.
Oh, oh. Ouch.
A human's life... oh, sorry. A human's life is...
Wait, wait, wait. A human's life is hard. A human's life is hard.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. A human's life is hard.
Okay.
It is often difficult for evil to be a good man.
Why did he end up having an affair with your child?
What am I supposed to be?
Are human beings evil metric?
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I am innocent indeed.
And I set myself up thereby to avoid a coming opportunity for any exactly like me.
I am innocent but in the manner of the vain elektros Iya.
Yes, his soft, dulcet tones of let's not say anything wrong.
It's more than that.
He's creeping up on everything.
He's creeping up on Bob.
God is creeping up on Bob, friends.
Are you going to let him do it?
Or are you going to stand up for righteousness?
Oh, wait, I guess standing up for God would be the righteousness.
And standing up for...
Are you going to stand up for wrong-ciousness, friends?
And Bob?
And Slack?
Who stands up for wrong-ciousness?
I will.
You would.
You probably would, wouldn't you, Dave?
If I only could.
We're all having a hard time standing up to begin with, though.
Well, I don't blame people for switching over to the Oscars.
I've got a list of the movies, the best picture.
I know you haven't seen any of them, but I still wanted to see if you...
Had any bets.
You know, people bet.
You mean like five to one.
I'm trying to be normal.
You know, normal people would be talking about the Academy Awards and so forth.
And they're running different numbers, too.
Some of them are going five to one.
Some are going, you know, those odd mixes, like seven to eight or something.
You'd have to know how to bet real good and stuff to figure it out.
Well, the best picture of the year they had this year was the nominees are Punter.
That was the life of Philip Punter.
You probably didn't see that because that was like an art film.
It was an art film.
It was an art film about a guy who forgot and gave up.
Some people throw in the towel and other people put the towel on their head and pray.
Remember, Stang, that's true about religion.
This guy, too.
The Remarketed, which is a gangster movie.
Song of the Langerhands.
The British.
Oh, Song of the Langerhands.
That island movie.
Oh, yeah.
It was like this year's South Pacific.
It was a musical or something.
There was a lot of noise anyway.
I remember that.
Midnight Smelt Pond.
Oh, jeez.
And The Queed or The Cued.
I can't.
I haven't seen it.
I don't know how to pronounce it.
Maybe it's The Quaid.
Yeah, The Quaid or The Queed.
The Quaid.
No, The Midnight Smelt Pond.
Who starred in that?
I have no recollection.
Midnight Snow Pond, Pumpy Snooze.
Oh, I thought you said Midnight Smelt Pond.
Pumpy Snooze?
Yeah.
Pumpy Snooze.
Yeah, and Pumpy Snooze is for...
Is he also a British actor?
She is a...
No.
You are so out of it.
Pumpy Snooze is only like the most popular actress
since she was...
Was in that movie No Brainer last year.
Since Dorica Harle.
Yeah.
You know, Dave, you're so old.
You don't even know who Pumpy Snooze is.
Oh, well, yeah, right.
Okay, so you're such an expert on history,
you don't remember Dorica Harle.
Now, I saw this movie.
These are best performances by an actor in a leading role.
Prim Demonocratio for Hard Job.
Bri Quindarling for No Pets.
Pen Thud for Half Little Man.
Peter O'Toole for Penis.
Bill Smith.
Yeah, that was a terrible movie.
I thought it stunk also.
Well, you know, sometimes they give these awards
not for the movie this year,
but sort of like to pay the guy back
for a lifetime of hard work
and not as many Oscars as he's already got.
Think about the times when they...
What do they call those awards
for the lifetime of extracted, excruciating suffering?
Is it Gaffer?
Or is that just...
Just the snowball.
What do they call the guy with no hair?
That's the stop-motion animator.
The stop-motion animator.
Yeah.
And those guys don't even get minimum or maximum lately.
They get real bad skin from handling the materials.
Bad skin, bad scale, scaly skin.
Anyway, the other one...
Now, here's the one I think is going to win
is Rod Punk for Bringle Peppermire's Secret,
which I did see.
Was that like, you know, with the Yiddishamama
and they get filled to fish all over your head or something?
Or what was that?
Oh, sorry.
Well, really,
the animators should also get an award
because that was one of those motion capture performances.
Let's see.
Best performance by an actress in a leading role.
Wetly Drenched for Flood.
She's pretty aptly named for that movie.
Holly Mirror for Backwards.
Nolly Pinprick for God Reads Pravda.
And Tiny Islet for Sewn-On Eyeballs.
Well, I don't know if I can make up my mind
if I were one of those judges
or perhaps even an injurer.
I don't think I want to be connected with the system.
I never saw most of these movies myself.
There you go.
Hollywood is so hirsute and elite and flatulent
that all of the...
One of those guys' names you just read off and stuff like that,
they all support, I suppose, liberal causes or something.
Well, for Best Documentary...
You talk about liberal causes.
For Best Documentary, feature Deliver Us from Truth,
A Convenient Lie,
The Facts About Fiction,
and Jesus in Iraq.
Those are the four movies that are up.
And it's always this one distributor
that always gets Best Documentary.
It doesn't matter what the film is.
It's who's distributing it.
There you go.
That is why the problems...
That's the problem with the Church of the Subgenius.
This is why you guys are getting beat up by God.
Now, look.
I'm always hearing this from people.
You are getting beat up by God
because you are allying with this distributor
who is obviously godless.
What?
Thunder's Mouth Press?
Well, I've heard of them.
They're not even owned by Viacom.
I've heard...
Which is the real godless one.
It's a godless...
I've read on the internet anyway.
And in abeyance of any god,
they're also godless.
Murray Rothstein.
You're serving Satan.
Satan is Murray Rothstein.
Well, they see him walking out with tails on.
Isn't that enough?
Well, here's how I know that the Academy Awards
is possessed by the normals,
the spirit of the normals.
If you look at the list of winners,
as opposed to movies that people...
They're not even going to be able to see.
Like the year Citizen Kane and Maltese Falcon came out,
what won was How Green Was My Valley.
The year that Fight Club and Magnolia came out,
they weren't even nominated,
but Beauty and the Beast was.
For Best Picture.
Did Beauty and the Beast won?
No.
Well, they should hyper-nomer Beauty and the Beast
into somehow a back-wagon double feature
with a fight club.
And this wasn't the porno.
This wasn't the porno Beauty and the Beast.
This was the Disney one.
Oh, my goodness.
Pulp Friction was not given anything
the year that Forrest Gump won.
Goodfellas got nothing
the year that Dances with Wolves won.
2001 came out early in 1968,
but they gave the Academy Award to Oliver.
Now, how many times have you seen Oliver
with an exclamation point?
And how many times have you seen,
or hummed, at least,
hummed the soundtrack of 2001?
I can hum the soundtrack of 2001.
I mean, I can hum the lyrics of Oliver,
exclamation point,
to...
But I forget the one song about food.
Glorious food.
I know all the words.
You guys would.
But that's because we're us.
It can't be heard unless you're speaking
into the microphone on that bad mic, Princess Wee.
You can't speak into your purse
while you're looking at it.
You're not speaking for your drugs.
Oh, yes, you're right.
Only we would know all the words.
Well, I think it's an incalculable crime
that they would allow this sort of manure
to trespass in our psychic garden
and then to, worse than that,
to suppress us in strange mind control ways.
You know, like, they're pompous.
You know, I can tell these guys.
Why?
Just because they give awards to guys
who are already rich and famous?
Well, some of them aren't even real movies.
You know what I mean?
That's the weird part.
You know, it's like, well, I haven't seen it.
And then you find out everybody, nobody,
anyone hasn't seen it.
You know, they're just like titles.
They don't even exist.
They applaud.
They weep.
They stand up in front of the microphone.
I'd love to see it.
Okay, well, this is a good example.
Princess Wee and I watch almost every animated movie
that comes out because when you,
rather than argue between a chick flick
and a, what do you call a men's movie?
Well, it's what we call a movie
because they always end with a guy going
and doing something real strange.
And that saves the world.
If you watch, you'll see that that's true.
Anyway, the three animated features
that are up for Academy Awards,
we never did see.
Meet the Boogers, The Littlest Sociopath,
and Monster Butt were the children's animated films
that were up.
Now, I have seen the ones for the best achievement
in costume design.
Nudist Camp, 007 Goes to Burning Man,
and 9X Day, the documentary,
The Making of.
The Feature.
Don't ever expect those to win.
They were merely nominated as a second pass.
You know what I'm saying?
Some of the people on the top,
the higher echelon, let it go by.
If you think that you're going to,
or anybody's going to do anything,
you're sadly mistaken.
Now, we did go see Shorty Meets Stumpy,
and Mellon Merkin is up for Best Actor
in a Supporting Role for that.
I didn't like her in that.
That's a, he, God.
Look, he's a, he's now,
I know Mellon Merkin used to be an actress,
but be respectful, Mellon is now a man.
Oh, so this is like Divine again?
You have to, I don't know.
Only in reverse.
Shorty Meets Stumpy was pretty funny, though.
Jimmy Jack Kornstein in Cracker Jack Sailor,
which was like the sequel to that mountain,
the cowboy mounting, the cowboy movie.
Right, that was like a homosexual porn film,
wasn't it?
Yeah.
Grey Poupon for a Bloody Mess.
Yes.
Princess Wee wouldn't go see that.
I don't blame her.
Because of the title.
It's probably invisible to begin with.
Why go see it?
You sit there and you eat popcorn
and someone pumps mind control things into your head.
Well, you know what's...
Then you have to go to the bathroom, you know?
Here's my bet on who's going to win Best Supporting Actor.
I think Fred Glosny in Movie Star is going to win.
I think the name is too Slavic sounding.
I think you might have to change it to like Fred Golden Gloss.
Fred Glosny?
That is his screen name.
Or Gloss.
His original name was Rod Tank.
Perhaps for the mentality that is arising quickly.
But it sounded too much like a movie star name.
Well, yeah, of course.
Namely...
Now, speaking of names,
Namely Starson is up for Best Supporting Actress in Naked Woman.
Everybody saw that.
No, I still haven't seen it yet.
That's a must-see, Naked Woman.
Brainiac Poindexter in Pudge Love.
Niner Bratz for Label.
And Heather Jennifer as Olive Oil in Popeye's Revenge.
That was a weird film.
Who directed that?
That was really weird.
David Lynch.
David Lynch?
In Popeye's Revenge.
And it was about Popeye.
But Bluto had become a good guy.
And he owned the town, though, didn't he?
Didn't Bluto, like, own the town?
Yeah, but he was...
And Popeye came back.
But the weird thing, there was like...
He and Popeye got together against the bad guy who was the mad hippie eco-terrorist.
Oh, wow.
That sounds like I should have seen it then.
I really wish I could have then.
Yeah.
They'd blow up trees with the spike things.
Yeah, there was a guy flying through the air in front of a ball of fire and a guy going...
Yeah.
So it was a real movie.
That's a man movie.
It wasn't like one of those fake movies that's all subtitled and everything.
For Best Director, Shrieky Fitz for Spasm.
Squint Plissken for Skinned.
Prawn Sourglass for Naked Woman again.
Marcel Delgrado...
So you're dovetailing now, though, Stane.
...for Pimpernel.
And Nigel Queener for Rear End.
And I think they'll probably give it to him.
Nigel?
Yeah.
Has he been in the business a long time?
Once again, I'm sorry I'm ignorant.
But is he like one of the industry's standard guys?
He's like the Little Miss...
This year's Little Miss Sunshine.
Oh, they always have one of those, right?
And for Best Screenplay...
Little Miss Sunshine is this year, dear.
Oh, that's the theme?
Huh?
It's the theme of the pudding or it's the theme of the actual event?
What?
Little Miss Sunshine.
I'm deaf.
Little Miss Sunshine is this year, dear.
She said, yeah.
Yeah, Little Miss Sunshine is going to be one of the presenters.
She's presenting one of the awards this year.
She's a normal child?
Or is it a child at all?
Or is it just a ray of sunshine?
CGI.
CGI?
Yeah.
Little Miss Sunshine is a CGI creature.
For Best Screenplay, Scams, Baby Rants, Tattoos of Anchors, Mom's Little Secret, which I think will get it,
The Swipe.
and Copyright Nightmare.
Those were Best Screenplay nominees.
When they were all ripped off.
Yeah.
Weren't they?
Just like...
They were all ripped off from this one little old black lady who wrote all the original screenplays.
Lady from St. Louis who's been writing for 35 years.
She's the same one that wrote The Matrix and those Wernobsky brothers ripped that off.
And they paid her off, though, after a lot of fighting.
But, yeah, so that's the news.
Well, we don't win.
We don't win.
That's the news.
Well...
Hey, I heard all the generals were about to quit if the President Cheney decides to go
to war against Iran.
Well, here's an interesting take on that.
All the generals on the other guy's side are ready to join up if he does that.
Oh, really?
Yeah, so it's kind of about...
The Iranian generals are going to join the American...
We'll join America if we wage war on Iran.
No, I guess a lot of...
But the American generals will quit if we...
Right.
American generals will quit.
And a bunch of Iranians...
And even other guys, not necessarily other guys, other nations with generals will join
up.
Will join in fighting Iran.
So there's the universal yin-yang, the dissolution and slobbering all in one slow motion breath.
You can see the world just like tumbling into a pile of...
It's like the giant...
It's like the biggest rubber band ball in the world all falling apart from rot.
It's coming apart quickly.
It's like the biggest ball of string in the world unraveling.
And the quicker it twirls, the faster the balls come off.
I wish you...
Yeah, ouch.
Right, right.
Well, we don't remember that stuff.
I wish you wouldn't bring that up.
Right.
It's happened once.
It's got to be forgotten.
It can't be brought up again.
Now, our subgenius...
Pardon me?
Once you say that, once you think about it, you don't want to bring it up again.
No, but once you think it, you can't unthink it.
That's the problem with all...
As Nenslow said, once you know something, you can't unknow it.
I have.
But with Bob, we can unknow something.
We can forget everything we ever learned with Bob.
And with this increased lack of knowledge, we take our breath every morning and face the sun.
Ready for another institutional ride.
Roll it.
The Dave DeLuca Orchestra is here in the studio.
Get it ready for orchestra.
Nice.
I can hear that.
Oh, can't you?
Is it too loud again?
No, I can...
That's fine.
I'm trying to make it...
I mean, it would be fine if it sounded good.
Well, we don't want it to sound too good.
But I can hear it.
How about something like that, you know?
And then it goes something like this.
Oh, maybe...
And best score, best musical score for a radio show goes to Lonesome Cowboy, quote,
Dave, unquote.
And the...
Davis.
The synchronistic language.
Exactly.
Now, our Australian correspondent, Chainsmurker, reported that President Cheney has been in Australia lately.
And he said that a pall has fallen over everyone he knows.
Everyone is surrounded by a dark aura.
However, he went on to say that he himself, Reverend Chainsmurker, was not in any way threatening or even criticizing President Cheney.
Now, Chainsmurker knew quite well...
Neither are we.
...that as long as his presence was there, there'd be problems.
And I...
And they even had a photo of two guys holding a Australia loves Cheney sign.
Oh, I thought you were...
On the internet.
Cheney was, like, holding hand with some Saudi sheik or something.
No, no, no.
Holding hands like...
To show on the internet, to show that Australia was really behind President Cheney.
All two of those guys.
They had pictures of two guys holding a big banner that had flags of both countries.
Well, I heard that the...
Who was the first president?
Subversive?
Huh?
Who?
Us?
Subversive?
No, the psycho-Eurasians.
The Australians.
The psycho-Eurasians also...
The people of Oz.
The little...
They encircled...
Yeah.
They encircled them with their little silver shoes and their long wooden noses and their
little beakskill haircuts.
One of the crazy people was on subgenius internet going,
America's trying to take over the world!
They want to dominate the whole world!
And Chainsmurker was going,
The Americans already took over the world.
Oh, buddy, where have you been?
Already dominated.
Oh my God.
Catch up, buddy.
I like the way you...
And then some other subgenius said,
Well, no, they like to do it over and over again.
Who, Australians?
They'll take over the world, then they'll do it again!
Oh, that sounds sexual, man.
They'll tear it all apart and then take over the world again.
That's the American way.
That is...
You just do it and do it and do it and do it.
That is that at those arrows right there.
That's your sex death thing right there, buddy boy.
America screwing the world and doing it again and again and again.
I remember...
There was an old Paul Krasner cartoon in an old...
Oh, yeah, right.
In an old realist, very old, because I remember those were old books.
And there was one where there was a skeleton that said Vietnam on it.
And Uncle Sam was, you know, performing an illusion.
And he was smoking a cigarette and he said,
Was it good for you, too?
That's very funny and relevant.
Just before we came to the station,
I looked at alt.slack and young Reverend Alex was upset
because he'd read, finally read the very end of the new book.
And it has a list of the birthdays of subgenius saints.
And he was upset because some of the subgenius saints included
Saint Hitler, Saint Stalin, Saint Franco, and so forth.
And Alex was...
Oh, that's real, quote, funny, unquote.
That's real, quote, irreverent, unquote.
And...
And I had to point out that, you know,
if we hide from the fact of the rogue subgenius,
and if we pretend that these rogue subgeniuses don't exist,
then it's as if we enable them to repeat history again and again and again.
We have to...
Do you think that Hitler and Stalin and Franco were normals?
Do you think they were able to get into that position of incredible, unthinkable power,
over-resilient, and...
And they were not the ones of stupid normals,
if they were themselves normals?
Nay.
They were subgeni, but not subgeni who had come to slack under Bob.
They never even heard of Bob.
They were before Bob.
They didn't...
Well, actually, Hitler himself was slain by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Thank God.
In the subgenius church, we...
Sainthood does not mean goodness.
It simply means that they are way more power...
We are acknowledging that these people somehow became way more powerful than us.
Jack the Ripper is a saint in the church of the subgenius.
I didn't notice his name there.
Did you have his real name as a...
He was kin to the royal family somewhere, wasn't he?
Or did you just have Saint Jack the Ripper?
Well, now that depends on which conspiracy is paying you.
You should have had Alloy, you know, in quotes, Hitler.
I mean, Alloy, Adolf, Schicklgruber, you know, and, like Bob, Hitler.
Because you should have his real name and you wouldn't have these problems.
But that doesn't mean...
Yeah, we have to face the fact that the subgenius gene...
often goes wrong.
I mean, these people were weirdos and losers who wanted revenge.
And they were motivated by the fact that they were weirdos and losers and picked on.
Nobody bought Hitler's paintings.
Now, if somebody bought Hitler's paintings, history might have been a whole lot different.
If you could go back in time, would you kill Hitler or would you...
Buy one of his paintings?
Buy one of his paintings and maybe take him out and tell him he was cute?
If you had the money, you'd buy his painting and then you'd kill him for out of dis... you know...
Now, that actually... yeah.
You're right.
Have you seen his paintings?
Then you'd have an original Hitler.
There was the Reichstag was one of them, a place he later helped burn.
That was great, though.
I mean, it was all like this, you know, architecture stuff.
They weren't bad paintings.
No, they were kind of lifeless and rather...
Yeah, they were dull.
...square, very dull.
Right, they were real square and dull.
Yeah, but he knew how to glaze them and all that stuff and, you know...
Instead of just saying, oh, I guess they don't want to buy my art, he went, I'll show them.
I'll take over the entire known world and massively... I'll have a thousand of my own people who will die by the millions.
That's where they come from.
That's what happens when a person of skill, talent, or insaneness of subgeniality doesn't have Bob.
If we don't spread the word of Bob, then we will just see more Hitlers, more Pol Pots, and so forth, and lonesome Polecats, and we will...
Whereas if these same selfsame potential serial killers had Bob and knew of Slack and the hope that Bob brings,
Bob would have killed him.
Then they would not go down this wrong path of anti-Slack.
They would spread Slack.
Nay, Bob, but I would say that a better strategy would be, rather than buy a painting or kill him, show them that he's been made a saint in the future in the Church of Subgenius.
And then what would happen?
He would quit doing what he was doing.
Hitler would certainly stop trying to oppress and murder people and stuff, and so would Stalin and Pol Pot and all those guys, too.
They would just go and smoke some frop or stand over in those woods over there for long enough.
Until their feet fall off, or they would...you know.
But they didn't.
No.
No, they didn't know of Bob.
They didn't have pamphlet number one.
They never heard the phrase, repent, quit your job, Slack off.
They didn't know to pull the wool over their own eyes and relax in the safety of their own delusions.
Well, it's a convoluted trail to canonization.
I mean, I've wanted to be a saint for so long, but I haven't killed anybody yet.
No, you can also be a saint from doing great good, like Russ Meyer.
Well, how about just...
Saint Russ Meyer.
Saint Lenny Bruce.
Saint...uh...uh...
How about just being real hateful and misdirected?
Well, I can't think of too many nice people that we've sainted.
How about just being hateful and misdirected?
That's not enough to make you a saint.
Why not?
That's...and every subgenius would be a saint.
It's...and every...and it's inevitable.
Being hateful and misdirected is all it takes, and every...the list of saints would never end.
Well, then why garner the...
Every squalling, bad-tempered child would be a saint.
Why flop the sauce around so frugally when you have...
...people that are murdering, you could just give it to everybody.
All of us misdirected, hateful people.
See, that's one of my confused questions that I can't stop asking as I try to sleep.
I look at Mr. Moonlight, I think of the sun coming up and going down, everything just...it just runs together and...and...and then...oh wait.
That's called a disassociation...
I'm sorry, that was something else.
Yeah, right, I was...
Dissociative psychosis.
Yeah, postmodern deconstruction of the brain area.
It's...well, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
Okay, I'll shut up.
Chimps have been discovered using spears.
Yes.
And...
Flint tools too, they grind and make little...
Well...
...crack marks.
Reverend Skull pointed out that now that it's been discovered that chimpanzees are using spears that obviously their next step will be weapons of mass destruction.
So...
Mass destruction?
Yeah, Bush must act now.
Mass destruction.
And throw Jane Goodall in Gitmo and invade Central Africa and destroy Alchimpa.
That is a good premise.
Because they hate our freedoms.
Yeah.
You know, we can't let these chimps get out of...they've obviously...they're...they're rattling their spears and...
They hate our decorum.
They hate our fresh friendly clothes without poo poo stains in the back.
Right, but they...
They hate our hairless bodies.
They hate the fact that we can...
They hate the fact that we can just have sex anytime.
They hate the fact that we can go to a restaurant and use a credit card to order something.
Which they can do too, but people...
They could if they had a credit card.
Ha ha, this is your picture, right?
You know?
And then the monkey goes off crying and...but no, I...
No, they did chose not to have opposable thumbs.
Well, you see what's inevitable now, don't you?
They chose not to stand upright and scamper across the savannah.
Now it shows that their thumbs are becoming opposing.
Next thing you know their hands will be fighting and they'll make nuclear weapons.
That's right.
We've got to step in there...
...and extinctify the...
...the last of the chimpanzees because...
Too late.
...once it...
It's...
We've been...
As one...
Another subgenius says, we must bomb them back to the pre-pushing-pokey-sticks age.
And now they're saying, well, with the carbon dating we can state clearly that they've been
making tools for 4,000 years.
Well, maybe you haven't been looking around for a lot of chimpanzee tools and maybe they've
been making them since all under your noses since this very time began itself.
Yeah.
They probably...
Well, hey, that's the moral of that Planet of the Apes movie.
It had a moral?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I remember, right?
Ape shall not kill ape.
The law givers said that.
And then what happened?
They lobotomized the humans.
Right.
Okay, we did it for ourselves.
We didn't have to let them do it.
Now here we are.
They're going to be making our sticks pretty soon.
Now here we are, Planet of the Apes, and it's not even apes.
It's just humans that behave just like as if they were hairless, upright apes.
Yeah.
So many pictures of Bush on the internet.
He looks like a chimpanzee.
I wonder if that has something to do with it.
Well, all people look a little like animals, don't you think?
And he does.
He does.
You're right.
He does look like...
If he were represented in a cartoon, the easiest thing to turn him into is a little chimp.
I look like a kind Pomeranian.
He looks a lot like Curious George, in fact.
Yeah, yeah, it does.
Who's a monkey instead of a chimpanzee.
Which was takeoff extraction.
But don't you think that people do look...
Almost everybody has some animal that you can say they look sort of like.
I think I look like a friendly Pomeranian, a Welsh Pomeranian, just as you said before.
I feel like I'm a were-meerkat.
A weird meerkat?
A were-meerkat.
A weird meerkat.
Like a werewolf, only a meerkat.
So which form are you in now?
Meerkats are the ones that just stand there with this thoughtful look.
With their paws hanging limp-wristed.
And they're bound across the belt.
But they're keeping alert.
They're like prairie dogs.
They're just kind of looking around placidly.
It's an African prairie dog.
Sort of, yeah.
Yeah.
Now, if it was a...
If you crossed a meerkat with a mermaid...
And it was a...
It was a were-meer-meer-meerkat.
It could be a merkin mat.
It would be if they had so much hair.
A merkin mat.
Now, we're getting silly.
That's not very scientific.
And I'm the koala bear.
Right.
Princess Wee looks kind of like a koala bear.
The Christ-like koala bear.
There's the...
Sweet.
The religious accoutrements.
She has that sweet expression on her face all the time.
The trappist monk's cassock over the back of her head.
Confused and sweet.
And I always thought that I looked like a fish.
Hanging from her navel.
But Reverend Stang says I look like a koala bear.
I'm a fish.
Yeah.
Fishy bear?
Fishy bear.
That would be a good name for all of us.
We'll just start calling ourselves that and then forget about everything else.
What are we doing here?
Are we doing anything important?
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm sorry too, Dave.
We're wasting...
I'm sorry three.
Well, how could we be wasting time?
We could be protesting or talking about something educational and instead I just...
I don't even know where it's gone.
I don't know what we're doing.
But the preemise was right.
And the preemise was chimpanzees with nuclear weapons.
Right.
Yeah.
That basically is exactly where we find ourselves.
We are slightly taller chimps with the same basic mood as the pantroglodyte chimp.
And much longer spears.
Much more explosive spears.
And more toxic poo.
I hope they don't get axel tottles or whatever they call them.
I hope they don't get some fear-splingers.
Axel Princess is doing...
What is Princess Wee doing?
She's doing a monkey pose just to illuminate the moment.
She's climbing and she had one leg all the way up on the studio table there.
In a strange...
You just never mind the contortions I have to go into to get my radio show out.
All right.
Now, I read in the news today that Strom Thurman owned Al Sharpton.
Literally?
Well, his...
Oh, you're right.
His ancestors owned his ancestors.
Right.
I'm glad that happened.
What a beautiful couple they've made.
Oh, yeah.
They do make.
They actually...
When I was about...
They both have a jerry curl, don't they?
Except for old Winston Smith who's turned into a Raggedy Puff.
What's his name again?
Strom Thurman.
He died when he was 100 a few years ago.
He is a Raggedy Puff now, yeah.
He did live to be 100 years old though.
100 years...
Well, his family...
He was a segregationist until that went out of fashion in the 60s.
Then he kind of quit that routine.
Then he made speeches about civil rights in the 70s and 80s.
But Americans aren't the only insane people.
All people are insane and some are even crazier.
No.
We are the template.
No, not...
We've only been crazy for 250 years or so.
What was...
Princess, we and I saw some Iranian TV that was...
Some Islamic scholar was denouncing Tom and Jerry.
The cartoon.
There you go.
We didn't really like.
In the Hollywood cartoon, Tom and Jerry he said was to program people to like Jews
instead of hate Jews.
Well we'd want to admit it, but you know it is true.
Because the mouse represented the Jew in Tom and Jerry, this is what this Islamic scholar
was saying on YouTube.
He had subtitles, so maybe the subtitles were wrong.
It all had a ring of truth.
Here's another thing.
He kept blaming everything on YouTube.
Disney for Tom and Jerry.
Everyone knows Tom and Jerry was MGM.
Oh, MGM.
Tom and Jerry was strictly MGM.
In fact, the great Tex Avery
animated quite a few of those.
But the reasoning that this
Islamic scholar had was that
in medieval Europe,
one of the slang terms
for Jews was dirty
mice. Therefore,
when you see a mouse
on television in 20th century
television
cartooning, that
mouse represents a Jew.
As you can see, the mouse is always crafty
and clever, and he's so cute.
And the cat is so bad.
And the cat, I guess, represents
everyone else who always is tricked
by the clever, wicked, evil,
funny, cute, lovable
Jew mouse named
Jerry.
It wasn't Jerry the mouse
and Tom was the cat, right?
No, he's taking Spiegel's book
Mouse, and he's
turned it into...
Now, believe me, these guys never saw
Reverend Spiegelman's book.
He read the book, and he thought it was
a tract from ancient days.
After being clubbed over there.
No, I reject
the principle. What does Daffy Duck
have to say?
No, no.
No, that's Donald Duck.
He makes wise remarks and smokes a cigar
and goes ice skating.
Whatever he said, he would say it in a messy
manner.
Yeah, that kind of stuff.
Like that, sure, but what would
he say about... He would spray it instead of
say it. Would he doubt
the Holocaust? You think Daffy would?
Well, he's a duck.
We're talking about the dirty mice of
medieval Europe and how
that somehow translates to all
the cute mice in cartoons that
come from Hollywood.
Which, apparently, to this guy, Disney makes
all cartoons.
They know who Disney is, but they don't know
who MGM is, I guess.
Well, we know that the
modern Uber Disney does make
all cartoons. It's a voice
in all of our heads. The Uber Disney
is in control of most of our thoughts half
the time. You must remember that
Walt Disney used to wear an
American bunion uniform
with stars and stripes on it.
That's the other thing. Disney was kind of an anti-Semitic
whack job on some
level. So why would Disney
be doing pro-jewelry
cartoons?
Once again, this Ayatollah has not done his homework
and should dip into Daffy Duck.
Now, Princess, we and I started
speculating that really
what those MGM cartoons meant
is the mouse stands
for the subgenius.
The cat stands for the
human. But what does the human
stand for? There was a human
but you only saw her from the knees
down.
And we thought the human in Tom and Jerry
stood for the goddess.
What do we stand for?
What do we stand
for? We stand for slack.
Goddess and man, woman, and
gods. I stand for
the slack of every man.
I don't care about the collective.
This
new age people
feel that self-sacrifice
is the highest endeavor.
But not I.
I say
I paste up
subgenius pamphlets
not because
No, what?
How did that go?
In that movie we were watching, The Muttonhead,
the Ayn Rand's
The Muttonhead that was made into a movie
back in the 40s or
early 50s. Well, I believe it was
slow regurgitation of her old
temple fluid. Man, I need to bring in some rants
from that.
The Ayn Rand.
She was Russian.
She was a rogue subgenius.
She was one of those frustrated
weirdo outsiders that basically
just did rants.
If you look at her story,
any of her stories, it's a series of
setups
in which characters
rant for
long, long monologues
and each one is really Ayn Rand
kind of talking to herself
in a psycho argument.
It's like Lyndon LaRouche without the
mind frog.
When I was
watching The Muttonhead, I was reminded of
Lyndon LaRouche.
I was reminded of the piecemeal labor that the
indigent family that was employed by my parents
back in the old days did in the basement.
Once again, the postmodern deconstruction
of some of the bodies we kept down there
and just the way they kept things smooth.
Your family was better off in the old days,
weren't they?
Better back in Portugal and Russia,
if that's for sure.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe.
Portugal and Russia?
Well, those are some places it could go.
Oh.
Well, if we wanted to.
What about the bodies, though?
Well, the bodies...
The bodies were just removed slowly,
just like the regurgitation,
and then they were recycled,
made into something better.
We made the sign or whatever the phrase was.
See, my family just threw them away.
Yeah, well...
We basically put them in a ditch
and covered them with lime.
It's a different country down there.
I mean, people walk around naked,
screaming at the stars.
You know, some people don't wear shoes.
Hey, man, don't knock it until you've tried it.
I've tried it, and I just...
The stars didn't answer you back.
No.
That's because you're not a Texan.
That's because you're a Yankee.
Yankee, Dave.
If you were a Texan,
the stars would answer your hollers and squalling.
Deep in the heart of Texas,
the sliding stars...
The men in space are out of place.
Deep in the heart of Texas.
Oh, I don't remember that at all.
I had to learn Texas history
when I was a little boy growing up in Texas.
They taught us Ohio history.
It was all lies.
Ohio history.
And it was all lies, I'm finding out now.
Indians?
No, no Indians.
Well, they were here, but they just, you know,
gladly went away.
Nobody massacred them.
Forgettable.
That's cuckoo.
Well, that's what they do in state history.
Senator James Pobuckins was the greatest man
who ever lived.
He celebrated the Alamo last week at his 400th birthday.
Well, yeah, think about Texas history
and the Alamo and so forth.
Now, the revisionists have been...
They've taken that apart.
Suddenly, Davy Crockett is this simpering coward.
And, I mean, it's just awful what they've done.
John Wayne would never have acted like that.
Jim Bowie is off the move.
Jim Bowie.
Chocolate turtles to everyone.
Right, yeah, yeah.
They've completely rewritten it.
Yeah, and suddenly Santa Ana is this, like, Superman.
Yeah.
He's this good guy.
Mexican patriot who wanted to do slavery.
I mean, what a yatch, you know?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Anyway.
Oh, well.
Thank God for the great state of Texas
and all those who nobly have fallen from its womb.
And, friends, if you want information
about the church of the subgenius,
don't write to anyone in the great state of Texas anymore.
Nope.
You may hear old tapes on the Internet
where you hear Reverend Stang say,
P.O. Box 14306, Dallas, Texas, 752 and a fire.
But, actually, the place to write for free information nowadays is,
P.O. from Church of the Subgenius would be
Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Once again, that's Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Ohio.
44118.
Uh, yes.
Do not use the scratchy part of your cerebral cortex.
Use the smooth part.
Rub the jelly.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Now, very firmly,
say, rub the jelly onto the mentholic space between his head.
It's corpus callosum.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Look, he's smiling now.
I can rub it.
Oh, you can keep going, Dave.
I actually,
to tell the truth, when I came in here, I was feeling so tired.
I was planning to just turn your mic on and nothing else and just let you sit there.
That little back massage I gave you didn't pick you up a little bit.
Yeah, but then we ended up having connubial bliss, I guess they call it,
except we're not married anymore.
Not anymore.
Thank God.
Not since the new sunshine law.
Yeah.
I have to know everything.
We can't get married unless we can have kids.
Unless we can get pregnant.
Well, we can.
That's why Princess Wee and I had to get divorced, because she couldn't get me pregnant.
But that's why we need Princess Wee as a vessel to create our new protuberances.
Wait a minute.
If you're trying to talk about doing it family style, I'm not going there.
We ain't going.
Don't even think about it.
That's from Idiocracy.
I know.
Friends, if you haven't rented the suppressed movie, actually, I shouldn't encourage a person
to go out and buy anything on this public airway, but I enjoyed the movie Idiocracy myself.
Me too.
And me three.
You know, Fox suppressed that film.
The very people who spent money on it, as they did with their show Futurama, it insulted
the executives of the company.
It bit the hand that fed it, and the hand said, oh, well, let's put it in seven theaters
and then shelf it.
Speaking of fedded hands, whatever happened to my favorite bush?
Remember?
Oh, yeah.
That's my bush.
It's all of a sudden, well, they just eat.
It's off.
You know, I, what happened?
Yeah, I'm surprised, too, because that was done by the South Park boys, which are good
Republicans, sort of.
Sort of.
I mean, they're not, they're never going to be good at anything, but they're, they make,
they, uh.
They're good at being bad.
Yeah.
Yeah, Idiocracy, friends, by Mike Judge, if you ever get a chance to see that, it's,
it'll probably come around on television, I guess, but it'll be all chopped up.
They'd probably soften it somehow.
Even on cable.
They'd have to.
Maybe they'd masticate it and re-spit it.
You know what I mean?
How they often do?
Chop up scenes and spurt them back out, so you're supposed to know what's going on.
Right, and they changed the cuss words into ridiculous.
I like that.
I saw a Chuck Norris movie with Spanish subtitles.
I was in Brazil, and they were, whenever Chuck Norris would say,
tish, in reverse, or at the word meaning excrement, that we can't say on the radio,
it would say, on the subtitles, it said, carumba.
Carumba.
Yeah.
Which I thought was, that's sort of like saying, darn it.
Oh, heck.
Well, friends, I should put on a pre-recorded item of some kind.
I think the news, ape news, number eight, followed by, from Norio Pref, I think, and
then some Lemur, and then maybe even a song by Reverend Stang and the late Dr. X.
But probably we won't get to Phineas Narco's cover of Highway to Hell.
But let's try it.
We'll just see, friends.
Thank you for listening.
I said, thank you for listening, and...
Well, one of these machines ought to be the thank you for listening button.
I think, I think it must be...
Yeah, this is it.
...violence.
$21 billion of criminal waste and fraud.
New plan to stabilize President Bush's body armor for probes.
Looking for fun, fun, fun.
President Bush is plotting a terror attack.
Committing, preparing, or instigating terrorism.
New terror.
A massive terror plot.
Massive, massive terror plot.
Okay.
I dream of Jeannie.
President Bush is...
An ovarian cyst weighing 93 pounds.
This is the scene.
I've been writing scenes.
Convenient, wet, heavy log.
The pile of debris covered with twisted metal framework.
Diabetes, high blood pressure, obesity.
Going on a diet.
There was a leak.
I got my fingers in his nose and twisted his nose.
No one knows.
Get up.
Uh, exposed bone.
A miracle.
More medical intervention.
Horrible sound.
Dream predictions and dire assessments.
MySpace.
There's been broad speculation about what's wrong.
You can't talk about something.
Teenagers.
Predators online.
Sex online.
On Thursday.
Mirage.
Recipient of a leak.
Teenage.
Predators.
Sex online.
Do it.
And the U.S. has failed like I dream of Jeannie.
Ape News Minute.
Call 444-222-555-5656-5601.
501-01-01.
I can't.
None.
Smileth, whose image has given life in my own image,
he shall make me preseer's soul charters.
Erect board bearers, bringers of the white root of the immaculation.
Codemasters for realists and underwives.
Ye X-Men are the very same.
Tools of wrath.
Large fools of the unknowable.
Thou art metaprimates who may splice time if thou darest.
Ye martyrs to the pipe shall have it.
Elastic slack on the plane of pleasure if thou follow my precepts without faltering.
Follow my heads where they lead you.
When Horus comes from the sky approach not lest thine soul bear the mark of the blood of the head.
For these.
Are the end times the children dance without honor.
For a coin a man must work like a dozen locks.
And yet sit in one place and not move from that place all day.
And the butts of men are sore and yet they will not move.
For the beast hath chained them to the scriptures of business.
And of all the binding spirits the business spirits are the most binding as unto chains.
And as unto tobacco demons.
The end.
What's that?
Do you have?
Eight weeks.
Do you know?
No, I leave.
Do you name?
No, I don't.
Your car?
I've met a car.
You don't.
No, you don't.
No.
All right, now.
Let's go.
Four cents.
Yeah.
Robbery in the first degree for a period of not less than five years.