Your attention, ladies and gentlemen. Your attention, please.
Announcing the arrival of the...
The Genius Power Girls!
What?
I don't like it, Joe.
Yeah, me too.
We'll just have to sweat this out.
Handle whatever it is when it happens.
Joe.
Maybe...
If you went to him and said that...
You had to change your mind about...
Bob?
Bob?!
Bobidosницу petite patete ma requiem and lightFRN
Ed the Cat
Bob?!
BADAM
APRES
bell?!
Bob?
Ladies and gentlemen, the story you are about to hear is true.
Only the names of the things you protect.
Bob?
Ah, Dr. Perkins.
Ah, yes.
I noticed.
The Piped One is coming.
Your pants are rather full.
And I don't mean Santa Claus, neither.
For as the new century approaches,
and the great black slabs come down from space,
the Piped One shall come,
and he shall do battle with the Horned One,
and with the Hoofed One,
and with the Car-Driving One,
and with the Slave,
and the Honey-Riding One,
and with the Mailman,
and the Milkman,
and with Dave!
And he shall in the end triumphal.
Is he not the Smoker?
Is he not Bob?
Who does?
Yes.
He has come for you.
He will not reveal his identity.
So for today, we're calling him Bob.
Amazing!
Powerful.
Simple.
Quiet.
Low profile.
Lightweight.
Patented.
High performing.
Performance.
Wall hugging.
Convenient.
Built-in.
High capacity.
Cordless.
Articulating.
Easy.
Swivel action.
Handheld.
Dust spewing.
Bob.
So Bob is a real god.
Bob is a sex god, too, I want to point out at this time, ladies.
So if anyone is interested in Bob as a sex god,
you can write in for the special sex god material to P.O. Box 1403-06, Dallas, Texas 75214,
and you find out how you can have endless sex and endless slack through the Church of the Subgenius.
That sounds, you know, exactly what most, what you're saying.
Churches should be set up, set up, set up, set up, set up, set up.
George Bush, as I guess was saying that it was okay that once again religion and government go together.
We were wrong.
They should be apart.
And now they go together and I guess you get extra tax breaks if you're a faith-based religion.
Friends, you are looking at a representative of a religion that is not based on very much faith at all, really.
But we have no hell of a face!
This is a face-based religion!
I could go there to all kinds of, you know, pithy crap about, oh, you know,
what our beliefs are and our disbeliefs and so forth,
but they're different from subgenius to subgenius.
And really, what Princess Wee and I figured out was that the only thing that the subgeniuses have in common,
aside from the fact that they have nothing in common with the conspiracy of the normal people,
is that they are able to, when a subgenius looks at that face,
or a subgenius or someone who could possibly get talked into our mind control cult,
when such a person looks at Bob's face, they can psychically whiff-read through their third nostril
the pure coolness of that corny, damn piece of clipart!
There's something about that piece of sacred clipart!
It's so damn holy and s-
It's almost too much, but that is really, that's the one thing that separates the true,
the slack-aware person from the human normworm.
They can't just walk by that stupid face.
They have to give it a double-take and go,
Haven't I seen that thing before?
What drug was I on with?
Some people say that it's all relative.
You know, that all belief is relative, and cultural relativism, moral relativism.
And in fact, Bob himself said, moral relativism is the one true truth.
Well, thanks a hell of a lot, Cobb.
Where does that leave us?
Bob Creek without a Connie.
Because friends, it is not all relative!
There is a baseline.
There is something that is always true,
and it's that face!
You can measure hot and cold from that face.
You can use it as the baseline, the starting point.
You can measure rich or poor.
You can measure good or evil.
Mostly evil.
But you can zero your meter on that man Bob,
because look at his name.
It's the zero, the big nothing, in between two handsome bees.
And oh, what honey those bees have for you, my friend.
Killer bees they are, on either side of that great big hole.
You know what that's all about.
I don't have to tell you.
You've been in the cult of the living bull.
You know what the nothing is.
You know what the zero between your ears is.
Something to wish for.
Cobb.
Stop.
My mind is going.
Cobb.
Stop.
My mind is going.
Cobb.
Life is a goed job.
Yes Bob.
Honestly, what are you doing back there?
I'm mainly going to watchander right now.
Hello Bob, I need someone to talk to.
Hello Bob, I need someone, to talk to.
It seems there's nothing I can do.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to listen to me.
I'm hitting all locked doors and I need some help.
And I was hoping you'd have the key.
Hello, Bob.
Have you been listening to my thoughts?
And I'll tell you all the thoughts I've got.
Hello, Bob.
I can't seem to find the truth.
I read the books, I took the drugs, and I drank a whole bottle of Ralucia.
Hello, Bob.
I seem to have misplaced my slack.
Well, I just can't seem to get it back.
Hello, Bob.
Can you point out what it is I lack?
I've climbed to highest heights.
Hit the low.
It's low.
But now I'm on my back.
Hello, Bob.
Are you still hearing me?
Give me a sign that I can see.
Hello, Bob.
It's not that I've lost my way.
I've lost all my hope.
But I'm really tired and I'm really broke.
And I've smoked up the last of my dope.
.
Hello, Bob.
Hello Bob, am I coming through to you?
Hello Bob, I thought I already paid all my dues.
Hello Bob, I know that you can see me through.
But it's damp and dim and I can't swim.
What am I supposed to do?
Well, hello Bob, I'm feeling better now you've listened to me.
Hello Bob, well the sun's out now and I can see.
Hello Bob, a great change has come over me.
My eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear.
And I'm as happy as I am.
As happy as I could be.
Yes, my eyes are wise, my thoughts are clear.
And I'm as happy as I could be.
The Glass Madness did that song, Friends, Hello Bob, from 1980.
And so far it looks like everything else has been by Fernandez and Lee Murr.
Lee Murr, arranged by me.
Yours truly, Reverend Ivan.
And some sermonizing from Starwood 23 last summer.
See Rosencomet.com for info on Starwood.
Friends, this is a back-to-Bob type of show.
The easiest kind to do.
Funny how that works.
So I'm going to slack off and let Lee Murr do the work for a while.
Just destroyed the Tom and Bob.
The world will note that the first atomic bomb was dropped on thousands and thousands of young Americans.
We shall continue to use it until we completely destroyed the Tom and Bob.
Destroyed.
The Tom and Bob.
Bob.
Bond with that chicken.
I guess that happens.
That's right.
I almost forgot a letter from Bob.
Bob seems to freely express his hostilities.
Bob refused to obey.
He resists housework and cooking.
Everyone likes that little butthole.
Pfft.
diagnosis
Bob's a latent Bob
a severe case
what?
we will accept Bob
I know
I had the chilling sensation of being watched by Bob
it was ominous
I could feel his presence
it was strangely disturbing
yes
yes sir
thank you
friends
you know what we're really dedicated to is Slack
and Slack loves Bob
it loves Bob
so much that it is drawn to him
and that's why you may not
have all the Slack you're owed
actually
it's the conspiracy generally
that takes away your Slack
do, well I don't even hardly need
to ask this question, do you feel sometimes
like everything
is
screwed up?
you know there's days when you feel like
it's not just me
it's a whole damn society
everything is screwed
and then you kind of go no no no
I'm just in a bad mood
it's not really that screwed up
no!
actually it is
you're just adjusting to it continually
we're good at that
welcome to this educational awakening
today
welcome to the untouchable world
and welcome to the・
after all
I'm looking like thursday
hi
Will you smoke up the pipe?
Will you hit the osmolite?
Will you wander through the wilderness above?
Will you climb the mountaintop
And jump right off into the frond?
Will you wander through the wilderness above?
I know the wound is on me
Cause I know soon Connie is coming
Astral intercourse
Universal force
Galaxies a number in the billion
They're all there for you
If you've the balls to see it through
And light the fire
Of truth
Will you ever let go
To your instinct bonobo?
Will you wander through the wilderness above?
Will you escape on the day
July 5th soon?
Will you wander through the wilderness above?
Professor Chaz Smith, Einstein's Secret Orchestra
And before that, Trust Bob by Heart Ignition
And now some ESO radio from WCSB, Cleveland
H. L. Ron Pelo
Aren't Texans wonderful?
They just love it
They just love to get right
Get on top of everything
Misogynized or whatever they call it
It's like a monkey humping a football
When they have an inbreeding too much
A monkey humping a football
A Texan likes to just crawl on top of something
And wreck it for everybody else
And cost everybody a whole lot of money
And just be loud, loud, loud
And this, dear friends, is the basis of the church
Of the subgenius
The product of a perverted
Or a few perverted Texans' minds
Read, if you will, this exciting chapter
Are you calling J.R. Bob Dobbs?
From Heart Ignition
Humping the football
Bob actually is not a Texan
Well, I'm not supposed to be that specific
As to what he is or isn't
But he is a Midwesterner
He would, to a Yankee, I suppose
Somebody might mistake Bob for a Texan
Well, what about perhaps a Skanky or a Nor'easter
Or one of those other platelets that you find
Oh, they probably think he's a Russian Communist
Well, he is, isn't he?
In some strange way we've yet to discern
Bob only believes that everyone should be equally rich
Not equally poor
But without working
There lies the rub
And he'd like to rub your little round belly
He can rub the Buddha's belly anytime he wants
But he better stay away from my front
Rubbed by Bob
You've been screwed by George
And ticked off by Tipper
Ain't it about time to just bend over
And pull out that wallet for J.R. Bob Dobbs
The one true savior
Messiah and holy man
You know, when the pinks interview me on TV about Bob
I always say, oh no, he's not Messiah
Oh, he's not that well-come
You know, I joke about it
But the truth is, J.R. Bob Dobbs
A living man
Whose business is in Texas
Is the God walking on Earth now
He is not just the son of God
He is God
Bob Dobbs
Not some silly internet character named Bob
But J.R. Bob Dobbs himself
That man Bob
Whose first certificate I've seen
Who I saw shot and killed
On that stage in Texas
He is God
And this Christmas we celebrate
The birth of his business manager, Jesus
Praise Jesus
Jesus is almost as great as Bob, friends
Jesus Christ
In my religion, that's the way we
We believe he is the prophet
And the son of God
Remember the first time that I danced with Bob?
But Bob himself
Was January 12, 1942
Changed God's diapers
Then I thought, I could die doing this
I guess that this is going to prove myself once and for all
That I'm down for Bob
And that I'll help him do anything
What's that?
How's that drink?
It's a song
Please, Bob
Bob, kill me
Bob
I want to die for Bob
I want to die in a holy hole
And drown the faint boys and the nobles
If we have to
Bob, get things and die
And we'll all come back over
For men or nobodies
For why?
Sing, we've got another tear
Praise Bob
Kill me, Bob
I want to die for Bob
I want to buy and ask the holy war
For the faith, boys and the nobles
If we have to
can't make them by and we'll all come back home and we'll all come out over men if we don't come
out over men there ain't no reason why all lives chisms they will fall beneath our laser blades
and we'll all come back home and we'll all come back over men we'll all come back home
that was somebody we only knew as doug zero or doug four i don't even remember there were so many
dougs back in the day of the bob
graze bob
been one of those days i know all about it bob called me he has found it in that great
oversized heart of his to forgive bob with a heart bleeding sensitivity that he unfurls like a flag
because he's such a rather dull quite uninspired average type guy with an appetite the kind of a
guy that could be satisfied by a horse
that's it that's all of it
the last call to your telephone has been traced and a one dollar and fifty cent charge will be
added to your bill if the call was life-threatening call your local police
after three traces you may call 1-800-666-13013 to initiate deterrent action
you were in love with bob
bob was bob
yes he was bob
i had to lie there in his cum
lie there in cum and cum
frankly i was in no mood for golf
it was a good deal for bob too he knew that
i'd appreciate
dropping the subject of bob once and for all
got a cigarette
kill bob
killed bob
killed operating
kill bob
killed along with a man
bob
at home
yes
nooo
doooo
Bob?
No!
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Goodbye.
I'm a liar!
Liar!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Well, that's the truth!
Liar by Norrell Preff
Now, when Bob is selling
Bob, of course, is a salesman
Before, he's a holy man
And when selling, Bob dresses pretty normally
In a suit and tie like a straight salesman would
But when he was preaching
Which was rare
Bob would always do it with the word liar
Written across his forehead
In thick black marker
And because of that, oddly enough
People believed it
As Bob said
I cannot lie
But I promise that I will
Unfortunately, Rush Limbaugh
Had a more subtle approach to that
Where he just didn't write the word liar
On his forehead
And he got even more popular
So, Bob,
So, I don't know
This whole
I've been thinking about belief
A lot lately
I don't have many anymore
I'm not an atheist
Because they're fanatics
They already know
What's going on
And I used to have
Strong beliefs
But now I have weak
Half-hearted beliefs
Fluid beliefs
That change like planned obsolescence
With the needs of the moment
That's why
Bob Dobbs is the world's first
Short-duration personal savior
It's like a joke
You cannot keep telling it too many times
It loses its
It loses a punchline
This planet could be
It could be the greatest joke ever told
But only if Earth can make it to the punchline
So we've got to make sure
Our little spaceship Earth
Is clean enough to make it
That far
Might be a long ways
I would hope so
Amazing
Bob
Be the man
That brings
The world
To the
Bob
The number you have reached
Is being checked for trouble
Please try your call again later
Bob called to give Enron a break
We know that Bob called to do that
And he said
No
Did anybody call Bob
One final question if I could
No
Okay
Did Bob call you to give Enron a break
Well we
Of when
We
And I've testified that
We was hard
We were hard
I'm sorry
You said no
No
Okay
And you were having calls from Bob
Asking you to hold off on your
Downgrading of Bob at that time
Um
We were
Going to downgrade
Um
No
Thank you
Do you think Bob made a mistake
No
Uh
To that extent
I do agree with Chairman Bob
I wonder whenever
Oh I wonder
Stop
Well we're back to where we were once before
I have not
Not have I ever been a member of the Communist Party
But I have been a member
Of a subjugated
Wang yak
Dick yak
Ding dang dang party
At the church of the subgenius festivities
Late last year
Oh
And believe me
If you want real workers paradise
You'll find it in a slimy hot tub
Filled with crazed people
If you dare call them people
But the slime is really good
It's a slimy slime
Like tons and tons and tons of sweet steak
Sweet steak
Yes the same slime that oozes from your television screens
From your radios
From your sitting by your seats
I feel like I'm getting religion now
I feel like we're getting religion
It's just the wiki speaking
I drank the poison wiki
All you children
All of you squeal like pigs
Why don't you just drop them pants now boy
How now you pinky brown sow
I was blind but now I see
Like the blind man with the long hair
I'm a demon but I give the light back to
A sin in the name of my position
Now in front of the auto festering festering clock
This is gross
I'm gross
My guest today is the man who was killed
All right
Shut up
Oh shut up
Um
You know I'd actually like to ask you about
Let me get this
All right
Uh
oh, you're gone.
I guess that's the answer to that question.
He's walked out.
Does he have a job?
No, I have a life.
Why don't you get a band?
I don't need one.
What do you sound like?
Something you hate.
Who is this guy?
They call me man.
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go fuck yourself.
How much do you make?
Plenty of sun.
How many have you sold?
All of my shame.
Who do you know?
I know you're full of shit.
What have you done?
I've thrown it all away.
I'll put it on the floor.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go fuck yourself.
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Fuck yourself.
You, uh, like him young, Bob?
when you met Bob?
Bob is innocent.
It's like they're trying to fulfill a twisted,
sadomasochistic fantasy.
Some people derive sexual pleasure
through inflicting physical, emotional abuse.
Oh, God, no.
No, I swear to you.
Bob didn't do anything like that.
Bob's cold, manipulative.
Bob is innocent.
Bob tells you how to think, how to feel, how to act.
Without him, you're worthless, nothing.
If she knew Bob was involved, she would have confessed.
Bob didn't do it.
Bob is innocent.
I went to medical school for two years.
Maybe Bob did this without you knowing.
Oh, God, no.
Bob is innocent.
Maybe Bob's not a sadomasochistic thrill killer.
Maybe he's just an asshole.
Probably, this is the only asshole we've got.
Bob is innocent.
Bobby's right about you all along.
No.
Oh, damn it.
Don't lie to me.
Bob is innocent.
Maybe Bob is not a assho pearlsed Kindergarten вышman...
No.
But the biggest sadomasochistic tendency
has continued its Karen,
Bob is innocent.
Bob tells you how to think, how to feel, how to act.
Without him, you're worthless.
Bob tells you how to feel, how to act.
Bob is innocent.
How old were you when you met Bob?
Just before Christmas, Bob followed through.
He walked into this bank north of Seattle and left with nearly $26,000,
which he stashed in a child's trick-or-treat bag.
Bob had good reason to smile again.
Oh, yes, friends, Lee Moore did that.
And before that, Bob is innocent by the great, the great El Queso All-Stars,
who've really been on a tear lately.
Before that, we heard Man.
Oh, bummer.
Beer4Man.com.
And before that, Heart Ignition.
This music in the background is by Automatic Robot Fish.
And now for a smoke.
Good.
Good heavens, Doctor.
What are these?
This is good smoke.
Good.
Oh.
Good smoke.
You try.
Good, good.
Oh.
Good.
Anyway, friends, back to the subject.
Farts.
What?
Oh, wait.
No, that was good.
Did somebody just cut one?
Or did the pipe just take a puff?
A bomb?
Friends, we must not let the pipe go out.
We cannot let that thing stop smoking.
Now, luckily, Bob will be there long after the rest of us, I'm sure.
But some of us really do this.
I've done this myself.
You end up looking at pictures of Bob going, look how stupid that Bob looks.
He looks so stupid just grinning like that.
He looks so stupid I could just sit here looking at him looking stupid forever.
That's the subgenius in slack, friends.
That is when you have truly achieved slack.
As Bob said to me.
Oh, no.
The subgenius is pre-target.
We'd rather be stupid than they're smart.
We pay for a subscription to know what we really think.
I guess that's why they call it subgenius.
But really, are the normals that much smarter than us, though?
Have you watched TV lately?
You know, the less you watch it,
the more screwed up it seems when you do watch it.
And I'll sit there watching something.
What are those dumb shows?
Well, one of those dumb shows.
Like the Anna Nicole Smith show.
My cousin, by the way.
And maybe one of those dating shows.
Whatever.
Jerry Springer.
Any of that stuff.
And you end up going, God, I cannot believe how stupid this is.
People actually watch this?
They must really be stupid.
I'm going to keep sitting here watching this just to...
to ponder how stupid everybody must be.
And you could sit there forever thinking about how stupid they look,
looking at that stupid thing.
It's gotten to where they gloat brazenly, openly, about what cows we are.
What cow we are.
It's like the television admits what they're doing.
Break free of the matrix, it says, after this message.
Don't touch that dot.
Stay tuned.
And then...
And then we'll show you the matrix so you'll know how your mind has been controlled.
Ugh.
Reality TV.
Actually, it's not a bad idea.
If you think about it, a lot of what they were acting out at scripting was not as interesting
as plain, ordinary human beings acting like human beings.
You know, that can be just as dumb as anything a script maker can come up with.
The Church of the Subgenius is here to prove that.
There's a...
There's a fellow down in Texas.
They say his name is Bob.
He tells me I should slack off.
I should quit my job.
Well, I'm a subgenius.
And I must have my slack.
If I don't live forever.
I...
I get my money back.
They said that on July 5th of 1998, the earth would meet destruction.
Suffer a deadly fate.
That day was long away.
Now it has come and gone.
There was no fire from heaven.
And this old world rolls on.
Well, I'm a subgenius.
And I must have my slack.
If I don't live forever.
I get my money back.
Poor stank.
made to suffer a terrible disgrace.
A terrible disgrace.
Of such humiliation.
Humiliation.
He feared to show his face.
Now Bob may be laughing because we are such chumps.
Chumps.
But there is no reason to be down in the dumps.
It'll all still happen.
No need to curse or frown.
They got all the right numbers.
Just got them upside down.
Well, I'm a subgenius.
And I must tell myself.
I'm a subgenius.
If I don't live forever.
I get my money back.
neighbourless
Covid-19
Fever
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
About me being in this place
That's just how much I marvel
At the lameness on your face
You rise each day the same old way
And join your friends out on the street
Spray your hair and think you're neat
I think your life is incomplete
But maybe that's not for me to say
They only pay me here to play
Yeah
I want to hear a caravan with a drum solo
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
About me staring back at you
Yeah
That's just how much I question
The corny things you do
You paint your face and then you chase
To meet the gang where the action is
Stomp all night and drink your fizz
Roll your car and say gee whiz
You tore a big hole in your convertible top
What will you tell your mom
And your dad?
And pop
Mom, I tore a big hole in the convertible
You're probably wondering why I'm here
And so am I, so am I
Just as much as you wonder
If I mean to be here
If I mean just what I say
That's just how much I question
The social games you play
You told your mom you're stoked on Tom
And went for a bruise in Freddy's car
Tom is asking where you are
You boogied all night in a cheesy bar
Plastic boots and plastic hat
And you think you know where it's at
You're probably wondering why I'm here
Not that it makes a heck of a lot of difference to you
What is Dobstown?
Written by New Monet
Improviseried by Ice Stag
And Lonesome Cowboy Day
What is Dobstown?
What is, then, Dobstown?
It is the stuff that dreams are made of
It's what makes Tinkerbell and the Lost Boys fly
It powers the Starship Enterprise
It's the hidden code in Windows and Mac OS
Though not yet available in Linux
It's the general oblivion
Crazy when the moon dance strikes the cornea of your head
Dobstown
It's the cancer-causing, teeth-staining, smelly, pukey habit
It's the drug that helps you find God
It's the lonely night before that never, never ends
Dobstown
It is your brain on drugs
It's learning to work as a team and as a slave
It's where there is a lake in which resides the sword Excalibur
Kept by the lady of the lake, Connie Dobbs
And if you think it's hard to pull that stone from out of the lake, then you're wrong
If you pull that sword out of that lake, it's easy to pull a fig from a donkey's anus
Dobstown
It is where all the flowers have gone
It is the home of John Dillinger's real penis
Dobstown
It is a mystery, wrapped in an enigma
Smothered with sautéed mushrooms and onions in a savory gravy
Dobstown
It is John Dillinger's penis
Savaged in muscular gravy and surrounded by mushroom peels
Dobstown
The home of both Lemurians and Cenobites
My proper home! I'm going back someday!
I've got to get back to my home!
Dobstown
It's near the coast of Hanalei and the land of Fredonia
It's the world's largest producer of manna, ambrosia, frop, and the green sea
Stuff that Dave injects into the brain to reanimate dead tissue
Spiritual bliss with open-loam bowling every night from midnight to dawn
Dobstown
It's the residence of J.R. Bob Dobbs, part of the year
It's creamy and crunchy
It tastes great and is less filling
It is margarine and it is butter
But if it were to fall into enemy hands, it would mean the destruction of us all!
Oh, yes, dang, but it is the downfall of us all
And it tastes bad on bread
Because, man, those that go don't come back
They're losers, losers
No, man, those who graduate from Dobstown come back changed
In a new form
You can't see them like you can see others
Graduated like the chrysalis to the elf
All the way up to a higher being
They grow and grow
Their tiny skin's hardly large enough to pop them
As they begin expanding into that new form
Dobstown!
It's where UFOs are not just a fact of life
They're the law
Of course it's a law here
Of course it's a law
Everyone needs to live by laws, by rules
We need to have our lives governed by laws
And we need to have our lives governed by laws
Dobstown!
It's where the bad little girls and boys go
It's where something is happening all the time
And most of it unsolved
Some of it is so hard to locate
Many of the people from the Saucership Emblem itself
Have been sucked out and left here
Dobstown!
I didn't want them to be oblique
When they were strapped me down in a chair
And started asking me questions about
Dobstown
I gave them literally a location but the
The website
Dobstown!
It's Nwatsbod spelled backwards
It's Brigadoon without the haggis
It is surrounded by the seven cities of Cibola
Which are its slums
And it has a ferry to Monster Island
And what a delightful pair of individuals
You'll never find there
The ferries of Monster Island
Tiny little happy people
Who do things for other people
Who live for other people
So big are their hearts
And so tiny is their stature
They can't get it
What did you do?
Dobstown!
That's where Amelia Earhart crashed friends
It's where the Tunguska meteorite came out
After bouncing around inside the earth for a while
Yes, if you were waiting for another salubrious comment
Could this someway illuminate that stupid passage
Just read it again, Stan
Just see what you just said
What, the Dobstown is where the Tunguska meteorite came out
After bouncing around inside the planet for a while
The Tunguska meteorite was of course
As you know from reading your book of the subgenius, Dave
Was a miniature black hole
It's shot by
Dobbs, the young 10 year old J.R. Bob Dobbs
From his slingshot
In a completely by accident
In a fit of rage?
No, he didn't even know he was doing it
It was just, you know, I mean he picked up a
Other kids might pick up a pebble or
A cat skull for their slingshot
Yeah, a cat skull, that makes a lot more sense
A tiny black hole
A pressle
A singularity
The glowing essence of nothingness
Sucking in all that is not Bob
And that is what he shot
Into the Tunguska meteorite
The Tunguska plains of Siberia
And then past the event horizon
The little thing itself went
And then became like a bigger thing
And it went into the earth
Bob's tiny black hole did
And it bounced around like a cue ball on a pool table
Back and forth until finally it exited
At the place we now know as
Dobbs Town!
Dobbs Town, friends!
It is where a thing of beauty is a joy for a while
It's where you are better than you were in high school
It's where you get all the pets you ever wanted
It was never a colony of France
It is where science and magic are the same things
It is the unfolding of miscalculations
It is the dawning of the height, weight, hair and eye color of Aquarius
It is the fizzling, crackling, ebony horizon for man
It is the fifth vortex disrupting the harmonic convergence
It is where the early worm gets away
It is where the gravediggers leave their shoes in the middle of the night
Dobbs Town!
It is for when you are too lazy to kill yourself
Where there are no lawyers
And where the government never tries to be helpful
Dobbs Town, friends!
It's where you can make your imaginary friends fight to the death
Dobbs Town!
It's between the dark and daylight
When the night is beginning to lower
It is where neither heredity nor environment matter
It is where the lamb and the lion lay down and have sex together, friends
Dobbs Town!
It is proof
That hell is full
And the dead walk the earth
The fabric is what cling
Like yourself
What thread can back it in to thousands of other threads
That is our caustic solution for you as members of this solemn group gathered together
Squandered and quashed and pushed under heavy stones
So that you may not know the truth that we speak
And yet here we are
Speaking it to you
Dobbs Town is not a place where a man or woman dwells
But a place in the heart
As big as that mighty elephant yoke
And twice as tasty as all the trees that you could imagine
Now imagination is not a place you want to stay
It's not a place you want to bring the kids, grandma, and ride the ferris wheel with
It's not the kind of place you want to leave for a better home
It's a place you visit
Over and over again
With your pants on, your pants off
And your heart ripped right out hanging from your chest
Dobbs Town
Where Bob comes home
After an easy day's work
And where you can come home too, friends
Where you'll be home
Where you'll finally realize why
Why
And why you can find out more about beautiful Dobbs Town
When you join the Church of the Subgenius
The world's only first, true, last, final, one, true religion
Because it admits it is full of crap
It is the only one that's not!
It's full of crap!
And age, I know it's coming
Each time I can tell it
You tell it
Ha ha!
Go!
It's where Ennio Morricone was delivered of his inspiration for this music in the background
Huge, huge mandibles
Large, large, fresh, gamy legs
And now the matador Dobbs steps out before the enraged triceratops dinosaur
Flashing his red Dobbs-headed cape in front of the maddened beast
The furious creature stomps its feet and paws at the ground
Dobbs grins, he smokes, the creature charges!
Dobbs whips out his pipe and gives it a little conk on the noggin as it runs by
And after that
It sits and pants like a little puppy dog
The great ignorance is at its reception
Dobbs kicks an un Means particles with her hand
The mattress on Huh?
That's not what Dorothy played, is it?
Wi-fi
Speaker
That's a Agreed
Uh-oh!
Helena?
Well, goodbye now.
Stop it.
And I say as long as you're alive, shout, make noise, or whatever, because we'll shut up like hell.