Forget, forget, forget. We're all sitting together listening to this.
Forget, forget, forget.
Children just love to bite bombs.
Orange. Deep, deep blue. A touch of scientific silver. Lemon, lemon, lemon yellow.
Soft, soft beige. The sweet smell of barbecue purple. All the colors of the rainbow dripping from your ears and eyes.
Lush magenta.
Crimsonist rose. Holographic yellow. Peachy peach. Dreamy, dreamy red.
Schwabby, Schwabby, Schwabby, Schwabby.
Let's go, clock. Let's go, ball.
Black dot by black dot. Bob's face slowly rolls across the horizon.
Dot by dot by dot by dot.
Each dot cueing a sheep, and the sheep leaps.
Each smaller sheep represents a half a dot in those little, lightly shaded areas.
of Bob's face.
But leap they do
and leap they must
because, as you all know,
the more he smiles,
the more the crust
seeps into your system.
Please trust us
and know that
we'll never abandon you
so long as you can send that check
to P.O. Box 140306
Dallas, Texas
and bring it all back home
for Bob
and the Church of the Subgenius,
the only church that pays its taxes.
Thank you, friend.
And thank you, Bob.
Happy birthday, Bob.
And that is about...
We got about one minute left here.
Do you want to do any intros or anything?
Is it Bob's birthday?
We filled up a whole 100-minute tape.
Oh, God.
Wow.
Boy, it just seemed like no time at all.
Yes, indeed, friends.
Like the blink of an eye.
When you're moving at light speed,
everything turns inside out
and just when you think the tape is ending,
you find yourself doing the intro
to this brand-new
Hour of Einstein's
Secret Orchestrous Plank.
Orchestrous Plank.
Pictrous Plank.
Uganda's Sicherheit Hey, Bangkok!
Instead of the
Keep the troops warmed up and keep the cards and letters coming.
Yes, dear friends.
www.wcsb.org.
I am your uncle.
My friends, and we are also at the subgenius radio ministry.
www.wcsb.org.
And in the final few minutes,
Miss Saitama and Mary distraught, left adrift somewhere in the woods
with the car burning in the distance.
It'll be an hour before the Mounties can even get close.
Yet Stang continues his relentless pursuit,
looking for their tender young bodies.
They've taken the whole consignment of furry squid,
and he knows they have it.
Things will get worse for them as they lie twisted together
like a pair of frozen statues, trying to keep warm.
We join them at the knees where they belong.
The Stang trudges on snow jumps, hot to see them.
Look, Stang, I see a truck.
What?
Yes, they've revealed themselves again, once again, at last.
My God, man, don't you see?
There's at least three of them, and they're all tripping.
Quick, give me the camera.
Blood wrestling.
There's something, something un-genic.
Something unearthly.
Something subhuman.
My God, man, it's something subgenius.
You are standing on a wall of the city of Ur in Mesopotamia 4,000 years ago.
Great walled cities are man's answer to population increase.
Surplus grows into wealth.
And wealth encourages war.
Man attacks man.
Ramparts shake.
The clash of battle echoes through long days of the Bronze Age.
Man increases his power and honor.
He invents government, commerce, architecture, writing, and taxes.
Over and over again, he fights to protect what is his.
And out of destruction, man rebuilds and moves forward.
We are not men.
We are not so happy.
We are not the Shakespeare lined up drunken.
We are not the Dombey lined up 4 missing that has to die to triumph.
We are not the Brick laid to shame.
Say hello, Stangee.
Hello Stangee.
Well, it's another silent movie with sound once again as the Subgenius Hour of Slack
gets its second win.
What do you say, kids?
And here it is now.
No, no, it's not.
That's a drop-in for you, Sting.
It's so sparkly.
Sting.
Well, children just love to bite Bob.
Look at these three kids biting into this Bob,
the squealing, squirming, screaming, dying little Bob.
And it's fresh meat, too.
Join us in our meat.
There are a number of ways you can make your Bob.
There are just so many ways and so many different things you can do with a Bob.
You can lacerate it.
You can fillet it like a fish would might be.
Bob meat is versatile.
You can smear it in A1 sauce or little pieces of Parmesan.
I want more Bob face, Mom.
You can take his ears.
Give me more Bob face.
Bob ear is a Bob ear, much like you might eat a pig.
Can I have some, please?
A pussy-killed Bob is not bad in a wine sauce.
Mom, why did the pussy kill Bob?
Mom!
Bob killed pussy.
Mom, why did the Bob kill pussy?
Why did the pussy kill Bob, Mom?
Why are Bob and pussy at war at this moment in time?
Come on, Mom, tell me.
Son, I can't answer that question until you're more mature.
Dad, are you going to let Bob be whipped by pussy?
They had ho-hos for Jesus.
What is the log?
To walk on a forest.
That is the log!
I'd like to quote the Reverend Cowboy Dave at this point and say that the most important thing to remember in any dissociative association experiment is,
and I want to say sort of fish and I don't want to say it, is I don't want to have to say it.
And Dave, you sent me that tonight and I just wanted to thank you for that.
I just wanted not to have to say that.
I can't say what I want to say.
I just want to say what I want to say about that.
It has been said again. It will be said before. It shall be said once again.
But it is fishy, isn't it? It's rather fishy what you might want to say.
And I found, I found it was...
It only smells that way after I'm through with it, in my experience.
Well, see, on the East Coast, well, that's because you've been in 400 degree weather for the past three weeks.
Hey, I've been trained, uh, Bridie helped train me for life in a spaceship.
You know, we've all been training for the...
For the...
For the escape vessels.
Yes, I created this vacuum between my frontal flippers and put his face in it.
That's the space.
It is as if we live on the hot side of Mars. It's 100 degrees outside right now and it's midnight.
It's 100 degrees at midnight?
120.
5 degrees.
That's at night.
You lose sight of the fact that it's a vacuum out there and if you spring a leak next to it, you're gonna be dead.
Yeah, see you're going down the street in your big Cadillac.
You got girls in the front row.
You got girls in the back.
Yeah, way in the back.
You got money in a sack.
Both hands on the wheel and your shoulders right back.
We all try to be good and faithful servants, but is your money in fact working against the kingdom of God?
Sad to say, this one will give 10% of your long distance bills to Concerned Women for America.
We are going to have sex in your life.
Can we talk a little bit about shaving the squid and the squid and the whole squid phenomenon tonight with our little girl?
We were talking about the love rug, the love rug, the kind of love rug Bob likes to roll out for all the kids.
Yeah, and how this relates to prairie squid itself.
Love rug, we roll it out every day and we think about Bob and unfortunately that brings us down, doesn't it?
Yeah, well the love rug is kind of a bring down when it's, you know, in your ears and in your eyes while you're trying to get down with it.
Sometimes it's a little tawdry and sometimes it smells like one of those deep sea basses, but that's alright because for Bob we can practically do anything by focusing our minds, focusing our minds.
Focusing our bodies and bringing our hearts into perfect conjunction with that.
Yes, but do you take just that little sip of the special love monkey love drug that comes free inside every prairie squid now being packaged now.
There's a new kind of prairie squid coming out this month, isn't there, Stang?
They have the most beautiful long black eyelashes around their great big blue eyes.
Could we see one right now?
Yeah, could you hold one up to the screen now please?
Look, he'll watch you while you masturbate.
That is probably one of the better features of the...
It will watch you while you masturbate.
Oh wait, did he say watch or wash?
I think it does both at the same time.
Wash or wash?
Sir, it's a creature that washes as it watches?
No, he'll wash you while you put a squid in.
I think it's going back into the tube now.
Yeah, I had a few tubes...
I had some tubes of squid that you sent to me that day and the tubes full of squid fell out of the package right after I put them in.
I opened it and it had that little smell, but that was one of the toothpaste tubes that you sent me.
But it was still good.
Oh no, those were all...
Those were in formaldehyde. You weren't supposed to eat those.
Those were experimental...
Oh no!
...you didn't cut your own into the tube.
Those tubes are all experimental.
You may lose most of your teeth right now, but you'll gain in psychic power and in just a few short weeks you'll be able to divine the future and read other people's minds without having one yourself.
So, plus my entire digestive system should be preserved thanks to the formaldehyde that stank smuggle to me, but it was really great formaldehyde.
It was greater than great formaldehyde. It's actually a three blend substance that not only encloses your body and keeps you fresh for the next millennium, it also imparts a certain odor so that you can warn the others to come around.
The sound, the sound, the sound is what gives it away.
A dark sound.
You know, it's death.
It's a dark sound.
Well, I guess it's not really that dark of a sound. I guess some of the kids enjoy it.
Well, smell that farm fresh prairie squid.
Mmm!
Makes my mouth water just thinking about it.
When was the last time you had your big ol' steaming hard prairie squid on a Sunday afternoon?
I think I had it out in the wood pile behind the house.
That's too long.
Is that that squid ratatouille again, Dad?
Farm fresh prairie squid at Tom Thumb Minerals and Igley Wigwoods on sale this week only.
Well, we didn't get that address again, but we know you can get prairie squid at your own supermarket today.
And as we retired hippies said, a lid full of squid beats a pock full of rocks. Right, friends?
Anytime!
Right on!
Far out, dude.
After a pound of squid, you don't know what you did.
You're just rambling on. We want to see the bottom of the squid where the aperture comes out.
Oh, now be careful. This one has not been de-beaked.
Yeah, yeah.
So keep your gloves on.
Okay. Do I take my pants down like this, Ivan?
Take my pants down like this?
I'm taking those pants off right now!
Alright, alright. My pants are off now. And I just what? I hold the squid against my genital area?
He'll go there himself.
Oh, look at that! Look at that!
Sorry, don't want to get you confused.
Whoa!
See how she backs up her...
I'm not being in this behavior!
Ha! But look, it does work. Right up to the screen. Actually within seconds after contact. You're in bliss, aren't you?
Yup, yup.
And now, Barbara, if you would like to join, uh, if you would like to join, uh, I believe there, with the, uh, squid interface, all you have to do is, uh, yank up your knickers and...
Not in my lifetime, young man!
Well, you know, you go, you kill yourself and then let the squid, uh, pull, pull, pull him over there and...
But I don't want to die.
It's so beautiful to feel that nice, beacons mollusk between you two. It's so romantic.
I'm a little squid.
My grandson, grandma are probably up there squeaking the bed springs with a prairie squid right between them.
Magnifying the sensation.
Like a thousand tiny pencils urging a woman to let go.
Got no pets, no friends, no...
A moist, mouthwatering squid can make your life over.
Think you need more?
Bigger bicep muscles?
You don't need any of that. You need a warm, friendly, tender squid.
One that knows your innermost thoughts.
Your habits.
Your secret desires.
A psycho-sexual squid capable of taking you where you want to go.
83D Squid.
Falling from the sky.
Man, they get you so high.
83D Squid.
Surfing through and in your door.
I know what they're for.
83D Squid.
We are from the people under the dome.
The squid choral singers out of the direction of Charles Muntz, the baton of Wigden-Helmuth, and the whole family of singers from on down the little tube.
Let's hear for 83D Squid.
83D Squid.
Man, it's so cosmic.
I looked up and I saw 83D squid falling right out of the sky.
83D.
83Dujo Squid.
83uard lesbians.
They were just butchered.
They were three-dimensional,ções
I'm not a drinking man on the job.
I swear I've seen it.
80 shoes.
Swim every day, swim.
Pity, pity three big squids.
Pretty pretty squids.
You need to, you gotta make sure that you have.
I'm not talking about the power of any individual being.
I'm talking about the power of squids.
Can ten dollars just make to you stop.
You and the better man over there.
I'm talking to you out there.
You and the front row over there.
You can use a squid.
The man over there with the body.
You need a pair of squid.
Y'all need a pair of squid.
I'm not here to sell you no damn pair of squid.
Excuse my language.
Excuse my friends.
I don't be required.
Don't let me swear when I get going.
I'm talking about a new life.
A new life for you.
You pick the squid up.
You take the squid home.
You place the squid where it's got to go.
And it takes you away.
Do not forget to de-eat your squid, though, Reverend.
That's right.
Now, wait a minute.
I've got to remind you.
Some people could suffer a small degree of implosion.
Or you could have some facial misconstruction.
Or some of you might have to have some elongation surgery.
Because the beaks can be very, very toxic to the average human system.
Sister, could you please bring some of the squid out and pass them out?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh.
What the hell?
Where'd you get your EVERAHONDA squid?
Here.
That one.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, yes.
I'm sure.
Over there.
Put that squid down there.
Just you.
Ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Ah!
Hey man, that was the best squid sex sounds I ever heard.
Did you hear those? You probably couldn't hear those, could you?
I couldn't. I was trying to make my own.
I was doing a whole bunch of pitch changing.
I could hear it on the preacher.
That was squid sex there, for sure.
That was pretty good.
Yeah, I want to hear that in playback, man.
And the easy listening 83D squid.
Yeah, well, we had to do the ultimate dub version there.
Ah, yes. Ah, good.
Well, you know what? It's real hard for me to hear.
Oh, okay.
Okay, what happened was we drifted away from you.
We got lost in our own little star trip, man.
We got away from the machine that is you, Stang, and we're sorry.
We're all hot, and we have to get so close together.
Yeah, the machine gets so hot, man.
But don't you have to be near the microphone?
Dave is making an excuse for all of us.
Please believe him.
Please believe whatever Dave says, okay?
And forgive us, man.
Man, thank you.
He's done so hard on us when we drift away from his machine.
Yeah, really, man.
I will forgive you this one last time.
We're sorry, man.
One more transgression and your souls will be forfeited.
Not the brainwaves, Stang.
No, not the brainwaves.
What one would he use? What one would he use?
The one that makes us go on our pants.
No!
The punishment two.
Can't you use the goatee one again?
The punishment toes.
Yes, I'll use the punishment toe.
That will make you go in your pants, all right.
No, just the goat thing.
The little goat thing you do.
Oh, that's what you did.
You wish.
That's probably just exactly what you want the goat thing.
Dave, are you going?
I'm heading for the...
I'm not even coming. I'm going, man.
Wow, man. Have you ever gone?
Yeah.
Hey, man, I was outside crying.
I was outside twice. I went all the way to the other side. Twice.
Yeah? Wait a second. You were gone and you came out the other side?
I went out of this one and I went outside.
No one goes outside, man.
And came back.
He went outside.
When I came back, there were two of me.
No one goes outside anymore, Dave.
You, like, broke on through from the other side?
There can't be any other side, man.
I went to the other side. When I came back, there were two of me.
You were smoking it in Philly, really, dude?
Oh, no. I can't believe this.
He came out the other side.
What'd you see? What'd you see?
No, I didn't go. I just went outside and I came back in.
There's nothing outside.
Like Gumby in the book?
What's scary is once you're outside, you look back at everything that was inside
and you can't even see it because it's so tiny.
Just tell me, was it like Gumby walking into the book?
I don't know, man. I never saw... I never heard that band.
No, no, man. The Cartoon Man.
Gumby walks in and out of books, man.
I just want to know if it's like that.
Oh, no, no, man. It was... No, man.
You gotta get in the sphere and then God or this computer...
The last time I ordered that from you, I got the other one, though.
You sent me that other one without the folding part.
I didn't have a good enough computer then, man.
It made my parents disappear and I really appreciated that.
I just want you to know that.
Well, you came out here, man.
Your mom's...
We're made now, dude.
What do you mean by made?
Well, you know, it's like she cleans up and stuff, man.
You got a monster of domestic work, man.
Come on, dude.
Well, there ain't much left of their minds after they get through the other side, dude.
So we just put them to work around the house.
I'm sure that there's probably regular spankings going on in that upstairs boudoir.
Oh, man, we're cool.
We didn't even talk about this in the 60 Minutes expose about your church reverence, Dan.
No, man, we're cool, dude.
What'd you make our mothers do?
We don't hurt your moms or nothing, man.
We give them jobs, dude.
I want my mom back, man.
Take a closer look at Bob, man.
Just because we're grown up, you can't take our moms, man.
It's not right.
It's for Bob, dude.
It's not fair, man.
Bob wants your mom, dude.
You should be proud, man.
But what about, you know, all that...
It's cool.
What about all the sick sex, man?
Forget it.
Forget everything else, dude.
Yeah, my mom would like that.
Of course, man.
Of course.
What do you think, Bob's queer or something?
What do you think he wants your mom for, man?
He's so queer?
We've got to get our moms back.
We've got to go out to where Reverend Ivan Stang is keeping our moms back.
Do you have a license?
Yeah, I have a license.
Well, let's go, man.
Yeah, I just got it, man.
Because I keep taking a lot more things than yelps and cookies and milk with my moms, man.
Shoot.
And we've got to save all the moms.
Wow, man.
You know, I think it's about to take all the moms in the world.
I know, dude.
I love it here, man.
We're marching to Dallas, Texas to Vince Stang's bedding.
Come on.
We've got to go.
Whoa.
Then we let your dads come visit him every now and then.
So that's where he is.
Come on.
Stang, you're sick, dude.
Stop yelling, man.
Let him go.
Christ, Bob.
God, he's got our dads, too.
Wait a second.
Dad?
I don't hear him.
Do you hear him?
No, man.
He's been taking methamphetamines every day and he's, like, gone most of the time.
Sis, where are mom and dad?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him in a while.
Me neither.
I think Reverend Ivan Stang took them.
I think so, too.
In fact, I know it.
I know it in my gut.
I didn't take them like they came long willingly, dude.
Oh, no.
They love Bob, man.
They just need a strap.
You're not pushing your machines on mom.
Come on.
Not the machine, mom.
Where's our dribble?
We've got them hooked up to these, like, devices, dude.
They're cold.
I'm sick.
That is, like, way, way, way sick, okay?
I bet it's illegal, too.
Okay.
I can't even begin.
Just say it.
Okay.
He has a car.
He has a gun.
No, he has a gun.
Come on.
I'm going, too.
I'll do it.
I don't care.
He's bad.
He's an evil dude.
He's got our moms and our dads.
Hey, man.
If it wasn't illegal, it wouldn't be any fun, dude.
Whoa.
Wait.
Is that my dad I hear in the background, Stang?
Yeah, your dad's fine, man.
He's just, he's just, he wants you to send more money, dude.
Man.
Wait.
My dad's not fine.
My dad's a real man.
Come on, Stang.
He wants you to send more money.
He said to send all your props, dude.
My dad sent me this.
We got your mom and dad on top.
It's cool.
I dig it.
Maybe we should go down there and, like, join up.
You can look at stuff like this, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, we've got best props.
You knew that.
Everybody knows Bob's got all the props, man.
Can we stay up, like, you know, pretty long this time?
Oh, hell yeah.
Yeah, man.
Okay, like, what if we, like, if we do some props ourselves,
would we, like, get in trouble?
Would we get handed anything?
Yeah.
Will you grant us for doing props?
Oh, no, man.
We'd, like, give you extra credit.
Will Drill be there?
Yeah.
You know Drill?
Oh, no, man.
That's a lie.
That's a conspiracy-like tale.
You know, we can play invasion.
We don't do that anymore, man.
Like that story.
You know the story.
No, Bob doesn't do that anymore.
Oh, man.
Come on, man.
Unless you pay extra?
We've all heard the stories.
You have to pay extra for that, dude.
Come on down to Dobbs Town, man.
It's great.
Everybody's partying.
You're missing the party, man.
You're just totally uncool if you don't come to Dobbs Town.
Quick.
So, wait.
Can you say that if we come visit you, you'll give us back our moms and dads?
Oh, sure, man.
Sure.
Okay, well, you give us back our moms and dads, and we'll give you back our moms and
dads.
We'll give you a bunch of props, too.
We'll give you a bunch of mom steps.
You just come on down, man.
You're missing the party.
If there's another mom that we like more, could we have her instead?
Hey, man.
You can have any mom you want in Dobbs Town, dude.
This is really getting it, like, Freudian.
Sounds like a whole bunch of fun.
I think you better go.
This is a whole new level that the church never promised us.
Not only to give us whatever sex we want, but to give us a whole bunch of money.
And not to give us whatever sex partner we want, but whatever mom or dad we want.
That's the first time I've heard this incredible offer, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Oh, yeah, man.
It's like we're just parent swappers, dude.
So, in other words...
Like Bob and Connie's new thing.
If we wake up...
You're the son of the child, man.
You're the child's mom.
I'm the child of Bob.
And so, you know, it's like your mom is my mom.
Your mom's pretty good looking, dude.
Yeah.
Well, I might have a bigger heart.
You're the son of the child, man.
I've done mom, dad, boy's money, and a bigger heart.
Hey, buddy.
Mom, Dad's boy's money, and a bigger heart.
Sex.
Hey, man.
It pays real good, dude.
Dad's boy's money and a bigger heart.
They start you off at $750 an hour.
Hey, Dad's.
Dad's.
More money and a bigger home
Mom and Dad
Those are the folks right there on the job in the factory, man.
It's a great job.
More money and a bigger home
Two cars, Mom, Dad
My family, well, my perfect family,
Mom would have more money
and we'd have a bigger home
and all my friends would get along
and they'd stop saying bad things about each other
and
and my
and and my
brother and I would get along. We used to be best friends but now all we do is fight.
And my dad and I would talk to each other.
We talked but never about anything important.
And I'd have pretty feet with no bunions and nice shoulders and nice hair.
Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Say it now, Mom.
Two cars and a garage.
Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Two chickens every pie.
Forty acres of crop and a fuel stove.
Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Better job, Mom and Dad.
More money and a bigger home.
And a color TV.
And Dad, more money and a bigger home.
A big porch full of LSD.
A lawn that's so cold and green.
And Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Out of space we can all be friends.
Mom and Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Gotta spend in this world.
And Dad, more money and a bigger home.
Hey, that was pretty catchy.
That's actually a really old Venus Envy song I wrote years ago.
Now when you think of Venus, don't start catching yourself.
Yeah, number two torpedo.
It has words that, you know, they roll me in.
It's a song sung from the viewpoint of the torpedo itself.
Or of the Scud missile.
Or of the ICBM missile.
So from the viewpoint of the ICBM.
It's like, you know, they roll me in.
And buzzers are flashing an emergency red.
The radar is scanning.
I don't know.
I can't remember them all right now.
It was also when they performed a gallium scan on his head.
I'm sorry, the Ganadeva.
It was a gallium scan they performed on his head.
They rolled his little head into a small evacuated tube.
There with the cathode lights burning brightly.
It was a liberation of sorts then for all of them, I suppose.
Yes, they drink Galliano at the time, yes.
Well, man, I think y'all peoples is crazy.
I think they could choose.
You know, that's Bob.
It's basically a 50 year old fetus.
You know, we're just animals.
The Darwin Theory, you know, we're just animals.
Darwin Theory, you know, we're just animals.
So long.
To obey me like they did the father.
And I think they have a very perverted view of children.
That's when the invasion's gonna be.
Ooh, these kids and their imaginations.
Well, we'll get rid of them first.
If you're involved.
That's the reality.
It is okay.
It doesn't mean you're a monster.
Just don't tell anybody.
Rush!
They'll escape.
That is the law!
Oh.
Is
Oh,
Oh my god.
I'm
That was
My
It was
Sometimes
You wonder why you wake up
You wonder why you go to bed
You wonder about the motion you're in
You know you're not dead
But sometimes you still wonder
Sometimes you still wonder
That you got plenty for anything
When you get up in the morning
And you're a soldier
And
You
All you think about
Protect the queen
Protect the hive
We build the hive
We die for the queen
We build
We by
We die
We die for the queen
Sometimes you wonder
Isn't all a lie
But sometimes you give up
And you do just keep on
You out
Keep out
New life, new life, new life
We build the hive
When you're at someone's Adams
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
When you're so drunk
So goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
Thank you.
It's all back.
They want to dance with you.
They'll dance with you.
Hey, can I dance with you?
Not even on the same playing field.
No.
Would it be fair to say that the sun shines brighter in the U.S.?
Hi, I'm calling for Chaz Smith.
This is I.
Hi, this is Friday Jones.
Friday.
Hi.
How you doing, Friday?
Wait, is this the Leopold Leprosy Show?
Who's this now?
I understand they canceled the Leopold Leprosy Show because they're bringing back, you know, what do they call it?
Slavery?
No, no.
No.
Not polio.
The other thing they had in the 50s.
Thalidomide.
Yeah, thalidomide.
They're canceling the Leopold Leprosy Show because they're bringing back thalidomide.
Is that true?
Well, I got flipper feet from it.
They're bringing back thalidomide.
I don't know.
Let me count my flippers.
Hold on.
Now, Friday, I understand that you had several flippers that were displayed prominently in the Boston area.
Yes, that was very embarrassing.
They saw a tattoo they shouldn't have.
Well, if it was part of that art show, then, you know, I don't think they should complain because they, look, you know.
I'm a performance artist, you know.
The DEA pays money to the artists to perform.
It's not the DEA.
I take a piece of broccoli and put it on my head.
That's right.
We need more people in jail.
Talk about Jesus.
Because without that, you know, they wouldn't be doing their job.
I was filled with that feeling that you were trying to convey when I went in there.
First of all, I felt flipper all over me.
I felt soggy and slimy.
Like greasy fried chicken.
And I could tell there was marine life present because of that pungent item.
Caller, do you have a point to make?
The liquid corn.
It was the liquid corn that started the whole process, really.
But he went two for three today, and he looked really good out there.
Well, okay.
Once the DEA cancels the Leopold Depresy show,
and keeps that whole thing going because Jesse Helms wants to cancel it.
Why?
Because people are supposed to be responsible.
Because he doesn't want people to know about his flipper.
What about my flipper?
Look, my flippers were the thing in the first place that caused this whole accident.
And we thought that it was...
We were...
I won't go to rush.
I reckon you better flip that tape.
Flip it.
You're cheating again, are you?
Not with that flipper, I wouldn't.
I can't.
I have one of my own.
Look at this thing.
It's concealed.
Oh, no.
Friday Jones is talking about them flippers again.
We are cheating.
Flip.
No, no.
This is Bobby Sutton.
Is that Reverend Friday Jones?
It is indeed.
We got her on the show.
Wake up.
Well, watch.
Hey, Chaz.
Yes, sir.
Chaz, look down at the yellow blinking light.
There is none.
Look into the light, Chaz.
I've got them all lit up.
Go into the light, Chaz.
They're all lit up, baby.
Because I think Princess Wee is trying to call in.
Princess Wee is here.
Oh.
Wee is here.
Wee.
Wee is all here.
We can all slide down the Wee slide.
Ooh, we can all flop our flippers together.
Yeah.
This is a trip.
Wee.
It's just one big happy flipper family in Thalidomide Town.
That's right.
We're flipping and flopping our way down.
Happy Thalidomide Trail.
The flip-flopped line is Thalidomide.
Have you ever seen a Thalidomide horse?
It gallops really funny.
Kind of.
Hey.
You're turning me on again, Friday.
I have the good taste not to be making actual Thalidomide jokes, okay?
But, of course, you people.
Hey, they re-legalized that again.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I'm saying.
And they canceled the leprosy show because of that.
Because they had that whole show that made fun of leprosy.
No.
And now they can't show it anymore because they're bringing Thalidomide back.
You're wrong.
Listen, I have another excuse for you.
It's a blood wrestle.
I want to go to flipper heaven when I die.
Oh, yes.
We're collecting X-Day excuses.
Okay.
I think...
I figure one of them is bound to be right.
Okay.
One of them is...
See, when I went there...
See, remember I mentioned I had this gift I had to give to you?
Okay, see...
Yeah, I figured it was a disease.
Well, no.
No, what happened to me...
It was.
I was in a coffee shop in Brooklyn.
Actually, it was a diner in Brooklyn.
It was in a coffee...
And it was about...
4 a.m.
I'd been working all night.
And he was swimming in the...
And...
I wasn't thinking about Bob or...
Or...
Or extraterrestrials or X-Day or anything.
And I didn't really notice it, but there was this waiter.
There was a waiter there in the coffee shop.
Barbershop.
Dumb waiter.
Diner.
Hello, my name is Derek.
I'm your waiter person for tonight.
Tonight's special.
As a matter of fact, that's where I was.
Yeah.
I remember eating there with you one time.
Yes.
I remember being eaten there myself.
Yeah.
And the interesting...
The interesting thing about that was that I wasn't thinking about any of this stuff.
And the waiter walked up to me and he was smiling.
And he was smoking a pipe.
Now, I...
You know, I did not...
I wasn't thinking about paranormal experiences.
I wasn't...
Again, I want to point this out.
I was not thinking about Bob.
I wasn't contemplating Bob.
You know, I was...
Well, what's the big deal?
Okay.
Well, he came over to me.
And he said,
Here.
Give this to your friend.
You know which one.
We're looking at a picture...
And he handed me a button.
Stang.
The button says,
Discard next event.
Discard next event?
Yeah.
I'm going to send you this button.
An actual button from an old audio board.
We've got a picture up on the computer right now of Ivan and Friday.
And this is like July 3rd, I believe this was.
Really?
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
So two days before X-Day, a mysterious man in black with a pipe grinning at...
And this is a true place.
Yes.
The St. Clair Diner.
I've been there.
And it is on the corner of...
Not exactly the corner of Douglas and Smith.
They don't meet.
But it's near enough.
It's on Smith near Douglas.
Yeah.
And he's sitting in there.
And somebody gives you a button marked from an old sound board.
And it's marked, Discard next event.
This is a real object.
I'm going to send it to you.
I thought I'd be able to...
I thought I'd be able to give this to you at X-Day.
And I had to miss X-Day at the last minute.
You know, people felt...
I've had so much mail and response from people telling me that they feel like X-Day happened
inside their head.
That they underwent a change and that it is the end of the world.
And the beginning of a new world.
We always left out the beginning of a new world part because...
Something was added to everyone's head.
But the question is, what was taken away?
Well, the new world...
We can't remember.
How are we ever going to know what was taken away?
I thought I had it written down somewhere.
But I don't know.
Well, what we...
Listen, you did have it written down.
What was the next backup version of my brain?
Well, we learned not to depend too much on written memos.
Friday, my love.
My fantasy Friday.
Yes.
Darling?
Can I tell you?
Look, you did have it written down.
This is another thing that I found out.
And there's a place where you wrote down where you wrote it down.
And there's another place where you wrote down where you wrote it down.
That location.
And there's a place where you wrote down where you wrote it down.
Uh-huh.
So there's a fourth place where you wrote down what you wrote about.
Check the back of your hand.
What you wrote down.
Check the back.
Oh, no.
No, it's usually between my toes.
Hold on.
So all you have to do is find the fourth place.
It'll lead you to the third place.
That's right.
It'll lead you to the second place.
Friday leaves notes to herself between her toes?
Yes.
They're actually flippers.
Yeah, let me look between my flippers.
We've got this one.
Let me hide my skin.
She's from that Innsmouth family.
They have big, floppy, wide, wide webs between their toes.
That's why they're in such demand.
And all their flippers have nipples on the ends of them.
Uh-huh.
You could put a 1998 calendar on Friday's flipper nipples.
Yep.
You should see me do the flipper stroke.
There's Friday and Susie.
Yeah.
There's a picture of Friday and Susie in battle gear.
Oh, are you looking at the website?
Yeah, right.
The Genius website?
Yeah.
There's a lot of nudity on that website.
I think the radio listeners will be interested to know that it's like a freebie.
We've got a lot of porn sites.
We'd like to perhaps describe the sites.
Which is not what they're in the commercial drama anymore.
Excuse me.
I've seen a lot of porn sites, and that is a very poor porn site.
Oh.
It's one of the worst porn sites we've ever seen.
Now, the real trick is if you can decipher the tic tac toe illustration at the bottom
of the Stang report.
There's no fabricating.
There's not really any frontal nudity or any penetration either.
There's not any penetration.
Thank you.
From the Joint Chiefs of Staff to the...
Well, there's poison, Francis.
To the Mecklenburg Fountain.
There's poison spreading across this land.
It's a poison of the mind and a poison of the soul.
It's true.
And there's only one cure for it,
and that's to soak up all the Bob and Connie that you can.
Just indulge yourself to the max.
Just go for it.
Even if Connie ain't there, just Bob yourself.
Even if Bob ain't there, Connie yourself.
Have at it.
Who's going to stop you?
God doesn't care, and Mom doesn't need to know.
I think they have a very converted, converted, converted view of children.
Children.
Children love and hate side by side.
Sometimes children love you and hate you all in half a second.
Strange children.
Do they ever forget or forgive the whipping, whipping, whippings
and the harsh, strict words of command?
I wonder.
How can you forget or forgive those?
Just go over and above you.
Those tall, silly dictators.
Those businessmen.
Tell them that.
Tell them it's junk.
That sounds kind of moral.
Let us be thankful we have an occupation to fill.
Work hard.
Increase production.
Prevent accidents.
And be happy.
The walls were covered with, literally, with mosquito-like characters.
Thin.
thousands of them.
I mean, the walls were just, like, thick with them,
and people thought we were screwing around,
but it was like something out of the owner's home.
Where is this?
In the studio here.
If you leave the window open, too, it will fill up with spiders.
These big, huge spiders.
Well, you guys are up on, like, the ninth floor, right?
Yeah, there's many spiders on Rhodes Tower, all the way to the top.
How about bats?
A few bats, yeah.
But mainly spiders.
Mainly big spiders.
There's, like, raccoons on the bottom.
There's bats in the middle.
There's a special kind of bat that I was hoping that they had there in Cleveland
at WCSB's building, the Rhodes Tower at the Case Western University, I think.
Ah, yes, dear friends, and this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
lately intersecting completely.
With Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
This show was made, was edited by myself from shows edited by Chaz.
Chaz Smith of Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
You also heard guitar and trance spouting by Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Backup vocals and trance spouting by Princess Wiardo, Queen of the World.
Queen of all the UFOs.
Drums by Bob Mosick, the other true Bob.
Electric violin by Michelle George, the dolphin woman.
And Reverend Bleepo Abernathy on telephone.
Yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang on telephone.
And Irreverent Friday Jones on telephone.
And, uh...
And just a whole lot of, whole lot of mess.
A mess of lots of...
Friends, Einstein's Secret Orchestra may be contacted at P.O. Box 81555.
Cleveland, Ohio.
Oh, that's...
P.O. Box.
81555.
Cleveland, Ohio.
Ohio.
44181.
The music in the background is by Dr. Reverend Imat Zephol, El Diablo.
With his CD, Beyond X Day.
This title, this tune in the background is...
It's called...
Someone Else?
Mmm.
It's trippy, it's psychedelic, man.
And there's more where it came from, too, at...
The Subgenius Foundation.
And here's that P.O. Box one more time.
This time, you're finally gonna write it down and just drop that envelope on your lap and think about Bob.
Send it to Bob at P.O. Box...
140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
And also known as...
Subgenius.com.
So, uh...
So what next?
Quince Cometh the...
Well, the Stark Fist is on its way.
As soon as the Lord Jesus Christ gets back from his honeymoon with Mary Magdalene in Amsterdam.
Friends, the Lord's doing a revival in Amsterdam.
Jesus Christ at...
Starring in the subgenius...
The Amsterdam subgenius revival of 1998.
Now, does that sound right or not, man?
That sounds right.
Sounds like a right thing to say.
Jesus, live in Amsterdam, preaching the word of Bob.
Praise God.
Praise Bob.
Praise Jesus.
And Mary Magdalene.
Congratulations on their lovely marriage.
Now, the home for slackless children will have...
A mommy and a daddy looking over him.
Oh, yes.
And, uh...
Oh, let's see.
I believe Dr. Legume is gearing up the Mid-Atlantic Slack Crusade.
And his...
Uh, it's to rival the outreach of the Church of the Subgenius.
I understand what he's trying to do.
I wish him the best of luck.
See you in hell, Dr. Legume.
And, uh...
Yes, friends, it's...
We're full of vim and vigor here.
And I'll be at ready to go to bed.
Crash out.
Where is this tape?
It's near the end.
Okay, I don't know.
Let's just...
For the very last...
Few minutes.
Let's just...
Go...
Um...
Go back.
Back deep.
Deep, deep.
Uh-huh.
Oh, right.
Right.
Holy co-sister.
Co-sister.
Wasn't a punchline.
No, but it sure is deep.
Something like that.
No, that's...
I thought the punchline was...
I'm sorry, Dave.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Well, that's...
That's one of the delusional answers.
No, Dave.
That's the only answer that's not delusional.
It's not really a hell either.
It's halt.
As you're sitting outside in your pod...
Hanging on the window.
Yeah.
The computer's laughing at you.
See, I think we're left out of any human,
but they can't laugh at Dave.
Yes.
They can.
But they don't laugh long,
because believe me,
I have my ways.
There's this...
There's a large number of animals...
Kingdom?
I said it right?
That follows my secret order command.
I learned it from one...
Less money on the vegetable numbers
that you get off the radio or off the television?
Sort of like Tarzan?
No, it's more like a...
A...
Well, I kinda understand where they're coming from,
most of the time,
about what it is, really.
I don't really know what they're saying.
I tell them stuff,
and they appear to react in some way or another,
and that's pretty much how I get them to do my...
My business.
You're evil...
He will.
Can you...
Get a...
A...
Like a...
Oh, like 300 or 400...
Snails or...
Sluts, either one,
any kind of cephalopod-type other things.
That thing like that.
Does it work on me?
Can we...
You know, I mean...
Can you get...
Like, say I couldn't...
I couldn't...
isko?
get hold of my prairie squid or I couldn't get my squid up, so to speak, would you be
able to train a number of those animals to cluster in such a way as to form the orifice
that I need?
Yeah.
But only at the bottom of the ocean, though, where there's...
I don't know.
I'd be watching my army of prairie squids and other cephalopods to follow him around
and do his bit or at least appear to me like maybe roll out the green light.
Well, I'm like any other guy.
I just want to lay back and be serviced.
Yeah.
Well, I think I could probably get a few prairie squids to service you with, underside
the control.
I mean, I've got quite a bill going up here.
I don't know if it's legal to talk about this kind of transaction.
I don't know.