Three stained drapes.
When I knew I was still in Marty's hotel room,
I knew that hours had been thrown out of my life and thrown away.
Then the light screamed again, and this time there were words.
Big thousand-watt words that said,
Delicious dancing girls.
And in between there was the creaking sound of a rocking chair.
Then the rocking chair made words, too.
You're not thirsty.
You don't want a drink.
His face, it's shaking!
And his hand, he's a monster!
Run, Horst! Run!
You can't get away, John! You can't get away!
It's my horse!
Where are you?
The Self-Genius
Yes, dear friends,
and thanks to Fernanda and Andy Leamer,
as always, for our opening credits.
This is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and this would be
our
Hour of Slack number
B
And it's a
rerun of somebody else's
subgenius show.
Yes, the great station
WREK in Atlanta
has a weekly show
called Bob's Slack Time
Fun House.
Every other week is done by the great
Reverend Susie the Floozy.
And
every other other week
is done by the Lymphnode Institute.
And this show is a wonderful example
of their work.
Unlike me, they're not barraged by
submissions
from subgeniuses
all over the world.
They just collect
things from their immediate environment.
So they have
more known music
running on their show, and they
do, well, you'll see.
They put a lot of work into writing
their show.
And this particular show is a great one.
At the end,
they'll give you more information
on where you can get podcasts
of their show,
which is via WREK.org.
And also,
if you poke around where you get the podcast
for Hour of Slack,
you will also find
Bob's Slack Time Fun House, and for that matter,
the Puzzling Evidence Show,
and links to all kinds of other
sublimiously audio
things. And so now, friends,
let us join
the mighty
Lymphnode Institute.
Yetis and simpletons,
poison ghouls.
Tonight, we once
again don the stiff, sticky
trappings of the faux
medicinal arts,
lace our boots
tight, and
duct tape our waders to our
waists as we wade
into the postmodern
moral quagmire
of torture.
We will titter with glee
as we watch our simian
cousins attempt to retain
their Judeo-Christian
ethics as they attempt
to survive in this
meaningless world that
Dobbs has sold them.
Of course, while this may be a great deal
of fun, it is
very, very, very
bad news for us, yetensiny.
But,
we'll get to that
later.
No!
I was sitting there on Sunday morning in the chief of police's office at a large table.
Torture.
He was listening to a football game.
Let's be up front about it.
A football game.
Torture.
T-O-R-T-U-R-E.
On the small transistor radio.
That's the bottom line these days.
And I had it very low.
It's replaced death.
Even teenagers kill themselves.
These days, along with the depressed and terminally ill,
deaths are released from pain and anxiety and humiliation.
Value, reward.
But the threat of death just isn't enough to control people.
So the ante's been raised.
Now, it's torture.
And high-tech torture at that.
As the technocrats say, it's functional.
That's why everyone who's intelligent and un-anesthetized enough to care
has sort of put their life on hold.
Underneath all the defensive layers of denial
we're all in.
We're all afraid of being tortured.
Anguished.
Or homosexually gang raped or having it happen to someone we care about.
Screaming.
And we're all self-consciously living a lie.
And I knew what it was.
We're all happy Joes.
And I knew that this man was being tortured with.
How did it happen here in the land of the free, in the home of the brave?
Tortured with electricity.
I mean in some banana republic.
Well, it kept getting louder.
Some distant.
Past.
Like the Spanish Inquisition.
And more horrible.
World War II.
The Nazis.
The fanatical Japs.
And each time.
But not us Americans.
G.I. Joe.
And each time.
Frank Sinatra.
Jerry Lewis.
Autumn in New York.
The chief would tell me, Colonel.
Baseball.
To turn up the radio.
College football.
Glenn Miller.
Pretty soon.
Somehow it doesn't fit.
It's not.
But it does.
Of course it does.
I could still hear those sounds.
Because it was always a facade, the image of America.
And now the facade has finally failed.
Anguish.
Like a burned out clutch.
Screaming.
Or a decayed tooth that breaks open.
Horrible.
They both smell bad.
Strange.
It's so bad.
Ominous.
Going back to the office, in the embassy, naturally I was speculating who that possibly
could have been.
But the motive that I had in everything that I did was to save the lives of Americans
who in some cases were being tortured to death.
For thousands.
For more.
Who are you?
I swear I love the Houston immigrants.
And I hate their horribly Paid Astкая.
I don't even know their name.
Rival pitchwriters like me are like this.
They're disgusting if you catch a glimpse of them.
Who are you anyway?
And I don't even know why it is you.
Strut pud думаю dais river, radtion urnantis, mining urnまぁn Municip镇s is highlighted
my family and making this ad because i want you to know
but the motive that i had and everything that i did
was to save the lives of americans who in some cases were being tortured to death
so
then jesus christ the son of god came to this earth lived about 30 years and totally sinned
for existence
and one would be stripped and whipped
and the crown of thorns crushed down until it lost her in his spell
feet totally dragging every cross up the hill being tortured to death
things just let them die it's torture to death that's what we call it today
for me
you
so
your
soul
I don't know.
And we will...
Weapons of mass destruction.
Yeah, good question.
I appreciate you asking that question.
And that's exactly what's going to happen shortly.
Rape and torture.
Hear or consider an application for a writ of alien detained by the United States who has been detained as an enemy combatant,
or is awaiting such to hear or consider any other action against the detention, transfer, treatment, trial, or conditions of the United States,
and has been determined.
by an enemy combatant,
and is awaiting such determination.
The title tends to use any other action as added by a person who,
for the cause of the constitutional,
to establish military or communal establishment,
is declared to be required.
Other person who,
before or after,
at any point in time,
has been determined to be
another competent tribunal,
established under the
authority of
under this Charter,
may be convened by the
Secretary of the United States,
or designed by the Secretary of the United States,
or that such action
may insofar be
a request of
any of the United States,
or indirectly,
for any purpose,
may not be construed
to alter any provision of this
occupied Charter,
or the application of,
or be the unconstitutional future.
The remainder of this Act,
and or circumstance,
shall be affected by the act.
The court shall remain
under the jurisdiction of the United States,
or its states,
or states,
to indicate if application
filed by or on behalf
of military men
determined by the United States,
to have properly determined
to await defense.
No court,
justice,
or judge,
or shall have jurisdiction
by the United States,
or its agents,
relating to any act
can be defined as an alien
of who is or was
detained.
The United States,
to have been properly detained,
under the strategy of the
President of the United States,
under the military conditions,
may be convened in this
notary of three days.
No court,
by the United States,
shall enter into jurisdiction
and, for any purpose,
of the United States,
under martial law,
or the remainder of this Act,
to justice or judge.
No jurisdiction
need be in action
to rectify all the conditions
to unlawful enemy convictions,
to application of a court,
or to the court's justice review,
or to any cabinet,
or to the President,
or to the United States,
or to the authority
to establish,
declared to be,
military commissions of defense,
or by any officer,
or official of purpose,
under martial law,
and any habeas corpus,
or any protocol thereto,
as a source of rights,
whether directly the United States,
or its state,
or territories,
if provisions to any person,
or circumstance is held,
the application of provisions
to any other circumstance is held.
The Viewer位
will not be日
if he or she is never to talk30
or to be interviewed.
We are finding terrorists, we are bringing them to justice, we are gathering information about what the terrorists may be hiding, we are trying to disrupt their plots and plans.
Anything we do to that end, to that end in this effort, any activity we conduct is within the law.
We do not torture, and therefore we are working with Congress to make sure that as we go forward, we make it possible, more possible, to do our job.
We do not torture, we do not torture, we do not torture, we do not torture, we do not torture, we do not torture.
I think about Iraq every day.
Adam, I think about Iraq every day.
Every single day Adam, I think about Iraq every day.
Every single day.
Said every single day.
Bett cuz, every single day.
Celebrate every single day this year.
Every single day.
Why don't you start a class.
...
Okay.
We do not torture.
Christianity, like most religions, seeks to suppress normal human mental function with pain and humiliation.
Christianity is, at its core, a death cult organized around the sacrifice of their own God.
The highest grossing independent film ever made in the United States, graphically, almost pornographically, catalogs the many potential and supposed tortures of their God.
Torture.
Torture is a natural extension of the fears and desires of pink humanity, and furthermore, a natural extension of the beliefs of Christianity.
Of self-sacrifice taken too literally.
It's entirely reasonable that if one's own God was made to torture and die terribly,
then, why not a heathen, a Mohammedan, a Buddhist, or, well, a subgenius?
You don't really believe that they are walling the Mexicans out, do you?
Oh, you poor, sad dead...
Dead, dead little monkey.
What do you think the commander in chimp meant when he spoke recently of a third religious awakening?
Witch burning, of course.
Witch burning?
You burning.
But, we've gone into all that before.
You should be well prepared for your terrible, terrible, terribly funny death.
I expect you to be laughing.
And so the institute is beyond asking the mere simple questions
as to why monkeys can't recognize their own reflection...
And why they are surprised when adherents of the State Death Cult attempt to put their real beliefs into practice.
One cannot read the Gospels without getting the distinction between your faith and your religion.
impression that Jesus came to die. Mark 8 31 and he began to teach them that the
Son of Man must suffer many things and they will mock him and scourge him and
spit on him and kill him. Much of the gospel narratives focus upon the death
of Christ and those incidents surrounding the death of Christ
sometimes called the passion narratives. Now normally scourging was a precursor
to the crucifixion and it was a brutal affair. In fact one could even die from it.
How do we as we consider ourselves civilized people, how do we react to
things like this? With horror, with sorrow and with determination it reveals the
face of an implacable
enemy who's willing to violate any norm of civilized behavior and it should
stiffen our resolve to eliminate them and it should also make us understand
how tough the struggle is going to be. The scourge itself was made out of wood
it had a wooden handle with leather throngs and each on the each end of
those leather strips was a sharp piece of bone or lead and it would
lash the flesh it would tear it into threads it would look like tattered
toilet paper. Our dog sometimes goes after our toilet rolls he pulls them
down and he tears them up and that's what it would have looked his back raked
with this scourge. Sometimes the parent made gaping wounds were of such size that
you could peer in and actually see the vital organ.
This body no doubt was covered with horrible bruises and cuts and wounds and don't forget
that he had been beaten black and blue prior to this. Then they began to spit on him and
to blindfold him and to beat him.
When I saw the prisoners, the Iraqi prisoners being captured and being blindfolded by the
USA Army.
I knew that they were being captured and being blindfolded by the USA Army. I knew that they
were being captured and being blindfolded by the USA Army. And the officers struck him with the palms of their hands.
Well these are just a few bad apples. It was verbatim what they said about you
know the torture manuals and those who killed the Jesuits and the church women
and El Masotti and the list simply went on and on and that really angered me but
it you know that must say they're consistent in telling the lies you know.
People are trying to downplay the evil and the seriousness of all of this.
But it's obvious here when you read through what they do here they are beginning to mock
him like a cat playing with a half dead mouth. Bashing it back and forth like it were a ball
of string. It's that sadistic kind of cruelty that gets pleasure out of seeing people hurt
and be loved.
I really wish that someone of these right wing pundits would just let themselves be waterboarded
once. You know just on national TV and tell us how that feels and then they can call that not torture.
How long it went on we don't know but it must have gone on for a while. Then they struck him or kept on striking him. Kept on striking him. Kept on striking him.
We could read it this way they kept on spitting.
they kept on spitting spitting spitting spitting on him.
But don't we see brethren how depraved are the hearts of men. Don't we see here how depraved
are the hearts of men. Very few people in the world especially in modern Western culture
are willing to face who they are.
Well it is tough and I think we've been seeing aetyo Arabian orhigh in Western culture could
that but where do we go from here don't react in a way that makes us behave in
the way they they do most people view themselves quite positively most people
have a view of man that is quite flattering man is good or basically good
then they believe the longer we live on planet earth the better we get but how
do you explain the Jewish Holocaust how do you explain September 9 11 how do you
explain the millions of babies unborn that are aborted every how do you
explain all of the sex crimes how do you explain all of the murders how do you
explain the serial killer man does terrible things man has always done
terrible things
and man will always do terrible things and if you want up simply to look back
in history and time and see how terrible man is look here abuses are inherent to
the world you cannot have a clean world you have to have raping killings torture
it's impossible that's his world that is the meaning of war
God somehow caught off guard?
no!
he sits in the heavens and laughs
ío
hey
No
He couldn't speak his morgue out there C's GM
student
Haha
Stay
resist
You
Stupid Christianity is stupid.
Stupid.
I am learning to live each day.
It's just one at a time.
I'm trusting in the Lord to make it ever sublime.
I will not put God first in all that I do
by accepting his son Jesus to carry me through.
Jesus Christ.
This he has promised, this he will do.
And for Jesus alone can make all things new.
I now trust in Jesus to show me the way to happiness and love throughout the day.
With him at my side and his love in my heart,
my life is beginning to have a new start.
Jesus Christ.
Thank you.
Rock over London.
Rock on Chicago.
The heartbeat of America.
That's today's Chevrolet.
Yes, with all that
Christianism,
Christian love and charity,
it's not hard to understand
why some people,
having been told for their entire
lifetimes that they were
born bad, and that in all
likelihood they will spend all
of eternity writhing
in pain, doled out by
a loving God.
Well, some of these people get a little
cuffed in the head.
And these rebels,
as it were,
adopt the binary
opposite.
No, no, not of actually
enjoying pleasure,
which is a lot harder than it sounds,
and incidentally, recent studies
indicate that this may only be
possible for yetis.
No, these poor, sad,
mere human apes
adopt the binary opposition
of enjoying pain.
If we carry
this thought to its illogical
conclusion, it suggests
an afterlife in Christian hell
of back rubs, foot rubs,
oral sex, that sort of thing.
Sadism, of course,
is nothing
without masochism.
And so we wind up in a world
of young, Baptist
human ashtrays and
lots of cutters.
Surely this is exactly what
Jesus had in mind.
Cut me up.
My mind's on fire.
You cannot choose between lust,
desire between love,
hate. Screw up my brain.
Your words mean nothing
and I suffer the pain.
Cut me up.
My mind's on fire.
You cannot choose between lust,
desire between love, hate.
Screw up my brain.
Your words mean nothing
and I suffer the pain.
Crucify me.
Why couldn't I see?
My blood splattered, body wanting
ecstasy, sex,
pain, pain,
pleasure, eternal torture
lasts forever.
Cut me up.
And lead me to bleed.
Come closer to me.
It's you that I need.
Decide what you want.
Give it to me.
My body is yearning and it's
agony. Penetrate me.
I'm invaded.
Your rite of pathage leaves
me degraded.
Stimulated passion I have to endure.
Ritual pleasure.
There is no cure.
Welcome to the torture chamber.
Set the sign above.
The entrance.
Let me know as you chase.
You might have him.
Looking like a man.
It's an age.
It's like you can sense.
The anguish.
Theater of pain has just begun.
Mr. Torture is pain with his whips and his chains.
He knows just what to say.
Mr. Torture.
It's a feeling you know.
Then just pick up your phone.
I want it.
I want more.
Mr. Torture.
Southland.
Obvious.
Deserters.
Unlimited.
Tories.
Special bread.
A sinning.
So that there is heat to blow your mind.
You can catch him off his website.
As a legend.
Every week.
Next time a torture's move.
Come in your way.
Mr. Torture.
Southland.
To that house I've since paid.
He knows just what my pain.
Mr. Torture.
If you're feeling alone.
Then just pick up your phone.
I want it.
I want more.
Mr. Torture.
Southland.
Obvious.
A możlible sale.
Closè story.
You better
think that Your The perfect
If you're feeling alone, it's just me cutting you from the running down the hall
It's the torture, it's the torture, it's the torture, it's the pain
Crucify me, why couldn't I see?
My blood splattered, body was in ecstasy
Sex, pain, pain, pleasure
Eternal torture lasts forever
Crucify me, why couldn't I see?
My blood splattered, body was in ecstasy
Sex, pain, pain, pleasure
Eternal torture lasts forever
You torture me with sadistic pleasure
It's just another memory to treasure
Your lust for blood, eternal pain
My mutilation that puts you to shame
You torture me with sadistic pleasure
Crucify me, why couldn't I see?
My blood splattered, body was in ecstasy
Sex, pain, pain, pleasure
Eternal torture lasts forever
Crucify me, why couldn't I see?
My blood splattered, body was in ecstasy
Sex, pain, pain, pleasure
Eternal torture lasts forever
My dogs singin', sharein' travel
No work number, references
Won't you blow it?
Since you built it, try to keep clean, cause the rent is due.
And the water keeps tapping my head.
The water keeps tapping my head.
Since it's never your turn, I'll speak for you.
Leave my hang, now, bloody brother.
Wearing, tearing, so I'm bare.
If I don't make it, what's the use?
The water keeps tapping my head.
Well, at least I lived through Chinese torture.
At least I lived through Chinese torture.
The water keeps tapping my head.
I lived through Chinese torture
Things got mixed up under the bridge
I put someone's head inside of a bell
And ring it
And eventually
They'll go insane
You're hired!
You're beaten down!
You're irritable!
Your mental and physical health
Are suffering!
Is there any escape?
Stop! I'm for science!
If you would like more information on
The Church of the Subgenius
You could write to them at
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118-1417
Or visit them online at
Subgenius.com
You have been subjected to
Negative lands
The bottom line
L&I
Put together the torture collage
Whathaveya.com
All spelled out there
Put together rape and torture
With President Bush's voice
Then the torture cut up
A cut up of House Resolution
Number 6166
The detainees
The law
Steve Craig manipulated our president into torture
Then the Jesus torture sermon
Which was mostly actually in context
An acapella version of Christianity is stupid
From the Negative Land album
It's all in your head
FM
Just like torture is all in your head
Athameh got off on eternal torture
Hell is a hell
Halloween performed a compressed as much as I possibly could version of Mr. Torture
And Johnny Society sang about Chinese torture
And then Negative Land again with methods of torture
We'll close out this evening with
A few relevant words
From former President General Dwight David Eisenhower
A man who knew about atrocity
And then Negative Land will
Do something terrible to a monkey
Because we don't just torture each other
We now stand ten years past the midpoint of a century
That has witnessed four major wars among great nations
Three of these involved our own country
Despite these holocausts
America is today
The strongest
The most influential
And most productive nation in the world
Understandably proud of this preeminence
We yet realize
That America's leadership and prestige depend
Not merely upon our unmatched material progress
Riches and military strength
But on how we use our power
In the interest of world peace and human betterment
Crises there will continue to be
In meeting them
Whether foreign or domestic
Great or small
There is a recurring temptation
To feel that some spectacular and costly action
Could become the miraculous solution to all current difficulties
A huge increase in newer elements of our defenses
Development of unrealistic programs to cure every ill in agriculture
A dramatic expansion in basic and applied research
These and many other possibilities
Each possibly promising in itself
May be suggested as the only way
To the road we wish to travel
But each proposal must be weighed in the light of a broader consideration
The need to maintain balance
In and among national programs
A vital element in keeping the peace is our military's balance
Our arms must be mighty
Ready for instant action
So that no potential aggressor
May be tempted to risk his own destruction
Our military organization today
Bears little relation to that known
Of any of my predecessors in peacetime
Or indeed by the fighting men of World War II
Or Korea
Until the latest of our world conflicts
The United States had no armaments in this country
American makers of plowshares could
With time and as required
Make swords as weapons
But we can no longer risk emergency improvisation
Of national defense
We have been compelled to create a permanent armaments industry
Of vast proportions
Added to this
Three and a half million men and women
Are directly engaged in the defense establishment
We annually spend on military security alone
More than the net income of all United States corporations
Now this conjunction of an immense military establishment
And a large arms industry
Is new in the American experience
The total influence
Economic, political, even spiritual
Is felt in every city, every state house
Every office of the federal government
We recognize the imperative need for this development
Yet we must not fail to comprehend its grave implications
Our toil, resources and livelihood are all involved
So is the very structure of our society
In the councils of government
We must guard against the acquisition of unwarranted influence
Whether sought or unsought
By the military industrial complex
The potential for the disastrous rise of misplaced power exists
And will persist
We must never let the weight of this combination
Endanger our liberties or democratic processes
Today the solitary inventor
Tinkering in his shop
Has been overshadowed by task forces of science
In laboratories and testing fields
In the same fashion
The free university of diversity
Historically the fountainhead of free ideas
And scientific discoveries
Has experienced a revolution in the conduct of research
Partly because of the huge costs involved
A government contract
Has become virtually a substitute
For intellectual curiosity
For every old blackboard
There are now hundreds of new electronic computers
The prospect of domination of the nation's scholars
By federal employment, projects, allocations
And the power of money as ever present
And is gravely to be regarded
Yet in holding scientific research and discovery in respect
As we should
We must also be alert to the equal and opposite danger
That public policy could itself become the capital
Of the scientific technological elite
As we peer into society's future
We, you and I, and our government
Must avoid the impulse to live only for today
Plundering for our own ease and convenience
The precious resources of tomorrow
We cannot mortgage
The material assets of our grandchildren
Without risking the loss also of their political and spiritual heritage
We want democracy to survive
For all generations to come
Not to become the insolvent phantom of tomorrow
And now once again it's time for Wildlife Tonight
Dr. Oslo Norway here
With a shocking remote from Wildlife Tonight
Right now we are going live to Wildlife Tonight's box office
At the San Francisco Zoo
Where Buck is going to demonstrate why there never was any Adam or Eve
Buck are you there?
Yes, thank you Oslo
This is Buck Logic with Wildlife Tonight
And where could you find more wildlife tonight than the San Francisco Zoo?
We're here in the zoo's new stinky monkey house
A generous endowment from the Simien M. Stinky Estate
Makers of stinky shoe stretchers
And here with me is Chuck
The night shift monkey man at the San Francisco Zoo
Is that right Chuck?
Yes, something like that
Well we appreciate you letting us in after hours to do this
Chuck, and if you're ready now
Please bring in the monkey
Are you sure about that? That's my last question
Yes, it's quite alright
And here he comes through the iron clad door
With a chimpanzee
We'll do it right on the table there Chuck
Careful, get him up against the armature
Tie those straps securely
They can take your face right off
He's doing the best I can
And so what we're going to do right here on Wildlife Tonight
Is shave all the hair off this chimp
From face to feet
Now Chuck is going to spray the restrained chimp all over
With Gillette's new tough guy shaving gel
And we're going to begin shaving this chimpanzee
His entire body, clean of all hair
And I believe this is another exclusive for Wildlife Tonight
And it's all in your head FM
Although I must confess I don't see why no one has done this before
And now Chuck, ow, not too fast there Chuck
That's really good, this is not an easy job
Chuck is rapidly shaving the chimp's body now
And there seems to be a little discomfort
But come on, we've all been shaved
It doesn't actually hurt that much
Now we're seeing some real skin here
We're doing this full body monkey makeover for the first time anywhere
Because I'll bet none of you listening out there
Have ever seen a shaved monkey before in your life
Think about it, I'll bet never before
And you know what, there's an important reason
Why you've never seen a shaved monkey before
And it does not include protecting the dignity of the animal
That's just an excuse
Nope, nope, you have never been allowed to see it
Because it's a shocking, almost unbearable testament
To our own intimate link with animal evolution
You know, I could lose my top over this
Wow, oh, chimp appears very angry
The chimp is strapped in a skinny position
To a sort of a crucifix style outfit
With an armature on the table
Trembling a little under the wriststrings
Be gentle, Chuck
I'm having a little trouble with this
I think I'm going to have to switch to something else here
And now Chuck is struggling to shave the feet and toes
What's his name, Chuck?
This is a girl, we call her Cherry
Cherry, wow, cute breasts
Be sure to get all around her private parts too
I want a completely shaved monkey
I'm done doing it
Wow, that makes her very angry
Yeah
She doesn't like that at all
Ah
Ah, you know, we're sorry we have to put this innocent chimp through this
But it's simply necessary to create a greater good for all of us
Sort of like testing cosmetics on him
Chuck is using a Jumbo Gillette Pro-Tech Tough Guy razor system on Cherry
And perhaps it should have been a Lady Pro-Tech
But it seems to be working just great anyway
From first shave to last, always a smooth shave with Gillette
And come to think of it, in Cherry's case, this probably is her first and last shave
But when this chimp is entirely shaved, everyone will see for the first time
Why we are truly all brothers to this sister under the skin
And now Chuck is finishing off her face and neck
Just leave a head of hair like us, that's all we need to do
No mustache, it's a girl
Great, great, that's it
And here comes the hose
Rinsing her all off now
And there
There you have it
Look at that
Release the straps, Chuck
Amazing
Creepy, but amazing
Turn her around, Chuck
Turn her around
Keep turning her, Chuck
That's it
She looks just like my kid
Now I was going to say, I realized this in rehearsal
Once you see a monkey's full frontal bare skin anatomy
Something we have never been allowed to see before
It's so strangely like our own bodies
Just different proportions in the parts
But all the same skeletal and facial features
Muscular structures
It's like an organic revelation
All right, Chuck, you can remove the shaved chimp
A wonderfully telling demonstration
Thank you
Thank you, Chuck
And
Don't worry about Cherry, folks
We have a little skirt and sweater for her
And, uh, Cherry, here's a banana for being so good
Well, what can anyone say?
Seeing is truly believing
A wildlife tonight revelation
And for God's sakes, what more need we be?
So, that's it
Nature's clock is ticking
Thanks to Cherry the Chimp, Chuck the Monkey Man
And the Gillette Shaving Corporation
Now in your face with the Pro-Tech Maximus II Jet Shave System
I'm Buck Logic
Now back to Oslo, Norway's brain
At It's All in Your Head FM
That's it?
That's it for Wildlife Tonight
Thank you, Buck and Chuck
And good luck
Wildlife Tonight is a syndicated feature of the Simian Stinky Networks
Oh yeah, a slag killed my baby
Oh, she culled on a slab
And I know it, maybe
Covered her with honey
On a fire ant hill
Made her drown
Cause she don't have no gills
Oh, that's that hour of slack
They said they were fighting a conspiracy
When they beheaded my baby on live TV
Crushed her under an iron ore load
And dumped her body on a country road
And carved a water pipe for her
From her little skull
Made her blow up like an Alka-Seltzer seagull
If you know what I mean there
You oughta know by now
That the hour of slack killed my baby
Every Saturday night at midnight right here
On WREK Atlanta
Except that this probably isn't WREK Atlanta
Unless it is
We're running a show from mighty WREK
Tonight in lieu of Hour of Slack
The Lymph Node Institute Torture Show
Praise the Lymph Node Institute
And your friends, you can get podcasts of that and Suzy the Flusy Show
And the Puzzling Evidence Show
And the Hour of Slack
If you look at the Hour of Slack page at subgenius.com
If you choose to look further into it, you may do so
Subgenius.com
And just click on the radio links
And you'll find your way to all of these marvelous things
And thanks to our listeners and our contributors
Oh yes, and also to that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs
Praise Bob