Most young people will continue through life as normal responsible citizens.
Others, the shunted and unloved, the unguided, the seekers of thrills and kicks
are candidates for the slave world of lifelong...
How does it happen? Where does it start? What are the signs?
The pattern is generally the same.
Bob?
Take a lack of responsibility, the inability to make right choices,
add to it ignorance and indifference, and top it off with a desire for escapism and kicks.
The sum total is then...
The subgenius power of SWAT.
This is the real action. This is the test.
The time to separate the man from the boy.
Willpower, individuality, character are slipping down the drain.
In their place comes Bob.
Don't be chicken.
The first of the three.
Okay, this is the part two of the Puzzling Evidence show we did a week or a month ago.
Because Puzzling Evidence shows are two hours long.
The hour slack is one hour long.
So we're continuing the grand themes from last week's stolen show.
Stolen from the Puzzling Evidence.
Two hours on KPFA in Berkeley.
Thanks to Puzzling Evidence.
Dr. Howell.
Dr. Philo Drummond.
Who's my host and captor for this week.
And K-Rob was there also.
And Princess Wee.
And so back in time to the Puzzling Evidence show of that week.
I've been to the skyscraper where they have that subgenius foundation in Dallas.
I met Stang and Philo and all those people.
I bet at the time they had power in Chicago.
So what now?
You stole their power.
Now.
I met a person who explained all that to me.
Really?
Yeah, at a party.
He said.
I went to Dallas and I went to that skyscraper where the subgeniuses live.
I met Stang and Philo and I'm good friends with all of them.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
Everyone around me was kind of laughing at this idiot.
That's really impressive.
And finally he said, what's everybody laughing at?
Stang and all those guys.
And he explained that in fact he had actually wandered into a little bookstore in downtown Dallas and noticed some subgenius stuff in there.
And they said, oh, the subgeniuses are in that skyscraper over there.
And that's where his story came from.
It went from some people in a bookstore lying to him to him having, you know, being good buddies with the famous subgeniuses who were so famous he didn't know what they looked like.
Well, you know how.
And didn't know if he was talking to one.
A good story can grow and become more exuberant and robust over time.
Yes, the tale can grow in the telling.
It can actually stretch the information much farther than the previous data would ever support.
And that'll help you stretch your entertainment dollar here in the jungle.
Touch.
We extend that information and project it far, far into the future.
As far as you and I can see.
From just a tiny, tiny little bit.
From these two bits of data.
See the vision of the world.
We're able to see into the future.
And all of it.
For a million years and know what's going to happen.
Two data points.
That's it, folks.
That's how powerful that is.
That's scary.
Yeah.
The subgenius stockbrokers corporation.
It's just like in Clown Atlas when you go in the studio and you hit the remote and it goes vroom.
You can see all this pretend world.
Hello.
Yes.
Go away.
Hello.
Welcome, ladies and gentelmen, to the future.
On the new anti color repellant spray.
You are the past.
Welcome, ladies and gentelmen.
You are a clown in this universe.
One thing we're always going to have more of in the future is the past.
So you can look yourself up in the Clown Atlas.
Until one day there will be-
Oh, here I am.
No more room for any more future.
The past will ocuify all space and time.
More pages in Con Atlas.
We've got to purge them.
Put those dogs out!
Who let the dogs out?
We have to purge them.
I hate chihuahuas.
It's a catastrophic event.
Under the Antarctic ice.
They're just radio dogs.
A discovery that offers the first glimpse of a vast ecosystem of microscopic life in underground lakes in Antarctica.
This gives us hope that we can maybe escape the tortures of the asteroid collision.
Too far away.
Never mind, we can't.
Too far.
Radio canines.
I welcome the astronaut collision.
Come on, baby, blow me up!
Let's just put our DNA in cryosuspension and shoot it into space in every possible direction.
This dog's got bone fever.
If the galaxy is to be compared to the continent of North America,
the nearest habitable exoplanets are supposed to be the equivalent of a walk across
Yeah, rocket, Hal, rocket.
Central Pacific.
Park in New York.
Hey, it's the Ask Dr. Hal show.
But even that is a distance of 11 light years away.
Who can believe that's true?
Which we now can't attain because we don't have the energy to go there.
If the show is like this, you know, it'd be great.
Yeah, we don't have the political wherewithal.
There's not enough energy on Earth to drive a vehicle that distance.
11 light years.
Unless you don't care how long.
It takes to get there.
There's nothing that can go to approach that speed, right?
Earth-like world.
Maybe.
Well, we have, uh, we've always got solar power.
And closer.
We use solar-powered spaceships.
They're greener.
They can, they can, but they move far too slow.
11 light years is still a long distance, even though by sidereal distances it's not as long as others.
Well, what if we just say, okay, we're gonna, it's gonna take us like 50 years to get there, right?
What are we gonna do then?
Okay, so for 50 years we're gonna have to lift up some young, very young astronauts because
they're gonna be 50 if they're like, yeah, we need like, of course, by then people will
live longer and be younger and fresher for longer.
Actually, on board the ship, time will not pass as fast as it does for everybody else.
Relief.
Yeah.
Especially if those listening to this are like, oh, we're gonna have to do this.
If they come back, although they wouldn't, everybody they ever knew would be dead.
But they're not coming back.
They're not coming back.
No, this would be for taking our population and repopulating it in a place where we haven't
crapped on the planet so much.
What you might do is hollow out a large asteroid and put motors on it and get it started toward
the distant future.
Oh, yeah.
And then they'll be ready to start moving to the next planet, exoplanets, and just grow
generations of people inside it.
Let them be born and die and finally some future generation.
Ah, those stories about earth and anything outside of this asteroid.
That's just fairy tales that the old folks tell.
Blasphemy!
There was no earth!
Yeah, what was that cartoon movie recently where the people are floating around on these
little bat chairs.
Oh, you're thinking of WALL-E?
Yeah, yeah.
That was kinda funny.
Oh, I thought he was thinking of Wall-E.
Jesus loves me, but he can't stand me.
It was Wall-E.
Was it?
Yes, it was Wall-E.
I don't remember.
There was people in that?
I thought it was just robots in that.
The people had left the planet, but the people were all there being fat instead.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.
That's us.
The beautiful bag people.
Now, many habitable worlds may inhabit red dwarf stars.
But if they do, they have a lot more time to evolve more complex life forms.
Our superiors.
The question you have to ask yourselves is, can canines be affected by radio waves?
Ask yourself, Dr. Hall.
By all means.
We have to stop the show and ask ourselves, will the dog star take over?
Dog flu station.
Will Michael Bradford call him?
Dog star.
That's the question.
I ask myself, can Michael Pepe call him?
Is he able to actually navigate?
Yes.
I'm deeply disappointed in Michael Pepe's.
Let's lift Michael Pepe up to the stars.
So do I have to smoke by myself?
Yes, you do.
Yeah, we would be helping you, but we're not there.
No, but I mean, in spirit, you guys smoke with me or am I doing this by myself?
If the temperature drops sufficiently.
Vapor will rise.
Oh, never stop.
Oh, Mr. Philodrum and this stuff stinks, buddy.
You should be out of here.
It's stinky.
Stinky as a metal.
Is this the show or is my tinnitus just acting up really badly?
I don't know.
I'm wondering the same thing myself.
I think that we have a number of show punks who are attempting to the joy of the event.
Show tinnitus?
You have to take your headphones off and check it.
I am all tinnitus.
Men of two minds about this exclusivity.
Is that like a disease where you get too much show?
It's my tinnitus.
Show tinnitus.
Here in the church of the sub-genius.
It's my tinnitus.
Yeah, like a show timeout where the show stops.
Hey, you can breathe.
It says breathe, but I ain't breathing.
This is the Bay Area.
We do show.
That's it.
Slow down when entering a station.
Once I was traveling and I think I was in Nevada or Utah and somebody said, where are
you from?
I said, I'm from the Bay Area.
And he goes, oh, you do show there, right?
I said, you bet.
We have to.
That's what people do to our job.
Always stop for a red flag waving and stay on the rails no matter what.
Just have that look about you, I guess.
That's what it looks like when you're on the show.
Yep.
It's just like this.
When you're down inside the show hole looking up at the distant sky far, far above you,
dreaming of the time when you can climb up out of that show.
A time which may never come, but sometimes the dream itself is the answer to life.
And you'll finally shed that medicine smell.
Get back to your Yeti forebears.
You know what I'm talking about.
You ever stick your nose in a bottle of vitamins?
With hearing problems.
Yes, they're good folks.
You feel me?
Oh, I'm rooting for vitamins.
Marshall, Will, and Holly.
Drummonds who had a feud going on for eight years.
I came to town on a beautiful day, saw a pretty girl was looking my way.
All those around me said, son, beware of the little girl with the golden hair.
All right.
Now let's see.
Golden hair.
And friends, you too can have a Princess We Are Doe t-shirt.
I have on here.
You can feel of it.
You can stroke it.
You can?
Wow.
I'm stroking Princess We.
Oh, my gosh.
I really, really did have a Princess We.
Stroking.
Good.
Princess We fan club t-shirt, available at subgenius.com.
There's two of them.
Edible product, edible Missouri.
It shows Princess We flying through space followed by all of her UFO subjects.
It's just one of them identified.
It's just too much.
Man, I can't do that.
Oh, I can't do that.
There's a lot of them.
They're so cute.
Oh, my gosh.
to a dance-filled girl.
She'll only play you for a fool.
That's the Princess We song.
Yeah, no, no, whatever they're saying.
Something about ass and class.
Yes, the usual litany of complaints.
Of the soft trial or a fight that caused the man...
Well, the further we get away from Earth, the more...
...left by and it intermits...
So, Steve, how long does it take you to get away from Earth?
...when his prosthetic eye popped out...
...as he was testifying in a...
Princess We, where are you?
This show is giving me vertigo.
He testified about the impact of losing his eye...
It's not a big deal.
...2011 fight in the parking lot of a bar.
Suddenly, the $3,000 prosthetic blue eye popped out.
Hutick caught it and cried out as two jurors gasped.
Whoa!
A mistrial was declared...
Reach through your phone and grab a piece!
...and the wayward eyeball was recaptured.
Reach through the phone!
In a moment, the result of that trial.
I heard the bomb explode.
I'm right here, go ahead!
New Jersey Governor Chris Christie lashed out...
Hold on here!
...and he, from workers' stimulation...
Shoot a phone and grab for me!
...and white bloods brought to Earth...
I can feel you!
Someone just played one, I heard it.
Yeah!
I can feel you!
All right, all right.
Doug, Doug, the show is broken.
Okay, he said...
What happened to it?
It fell in that crack.
It's 420.
Oh, I see a banana peel.
You notice how Philo disappeared at 420 by himself?
Eh, banana rye.
Well, I need to get going too.
What a coincidence.
Wow, 420!
Yeah.
Coincidence or a conspiracy?
What the...
There's an obvious clue here, Robin.
Hey, you know what I found the other day?
So we began putting clues in all the albums.
Yeah, to avoid the...
I can't tolerate that, man.
The callers are once again trying to take over the show.
...my clues in all the shows.
And clue in all the CDs!
Which is related to what I wanted to do originally with the original subgenius original VHS tape.
VHS?
You have 20 minutes at the end of the tape.
It says, don't go past this point.
It will ruin your VCR.
Do not go past this point.
Three warnings? That must be trouble.
Yeah.
Four rings?
That's probably the chief.
Yeah, but of course they wouldn't stop.
And at the last maybe foot of VHS tape would be sandpaper.
Ruining your $800 VHS machine just like Bob said.
I thought that would have been a geeky thing.
It was, wasn't it? In those days?
A geeky thing.
Well, we're on the pier here.
On the pier.
We're waving goodbye to Uncle Philo as he sends off his...
I have another fried clam bucket.
A Kentucky fried clam.
Here at the Ivar's in the Navy of England.
I'm as happy as a cherry stone clam myself because I graduated...
That's pretty happy.
...a 12-module course in success in sex and real estate.
And now you can't.
Lonnie found some lamb's breast seed.
I'm going to offer you a hand up.
There he goes.
Oh, this is where Philo starts talking about his 13-step program.
So, my beloved, I say unto you...
Hey, hey, lamb's bread, you guys. Lamb's bread. Remember that?
Be ye lifted up and dine on the bread of lamb.
Yes, I found some lamb's bread seeds. They were trashed. I lost them and I found them again.
I wonder if they're going to germinate.
The yams did it. The yams did it.
Lamb's bread. They only eat the softest, tenderest bread.
It's all about the cat pissing on the sourdough.
Diesel.
Cordy is bread. Anybody's bread.
Okay, and it's good for our good little green friends in our space, too.
We say urinate on this show.
Urine over your head now.
It must be the cat that must piss on the...
Feline urination.
You're in trouble.
That stank up the house that Jack built.
Stank up the entire...
You're in heaven on this show, though.
Stank up the entire movie set for the movie.
Not as bad as tiger piss is splashed around.
Lonnie will straight up...
Yeah, that's the worst.
If one must discuss the exceptionally pungent...
In the movie, you're an albino.
A cowboy loves cats.
So they made a closed set and they just found a bunch of cats in the city.
Dare to be a juicer.
And put them on the set.
And they lived in the set with plenty of food and water and cat boxes for the entire shooting of the movie.
Remember, folks, save the demonically possessed cats.
And the director's wife was a veterinarian.
So she came over to visit and get a little vacation in a foreign country with her husband while they were shooting the first album.
There will be a...
What about when the movie was over?
The diseases in the room.
She could name the diseases that the cats had because the urine was so powerfully stinking.
The entire thing.
Of course, shooting three months in there.
It got pretty nasty.
It gets to the point where you don't even notice it anymore because you just have to get to the scene.
Oh, you notice.
And other people notice.
And then they were saying, you know, you don't.
It just shuts it down.
Ed Holmes is talking about this where you get to a point where the human brain just can't...
You can't work like that.
So you just shut it down.
And you go ahead and do the work.
But you don't smell the bad smell anymore.
Yeah.
Well...
Because otherwise, you can't do it.
You can't finish up.
Ed Holmes on a submarine.
He found out about that.
Or if you went in the space shuttle, Columbia.
They had cats on the submarine?
Any of the space...
Because the Columbias are all 40 years of people's sweat and poo and...
Or like those people that have to sit for 25 years next to that guy in the office in
the other cubicle who's constantly emitting these noisy, noxious vapors.
He's a real four square guy.
He's just right for the cubicle.
They tried to fire him.
But they couldn't do it.
Call me Joe Vapors Johnson.
He worked for the IRS.
That was not me, Joe Vapors Johnson.
A rattle song, Joe Vapors.
Yes, a rather vaporish individual.
They put him on a program.
His head was muddled with...
Not a 13-step program or a 12-step program.
My name is Joe Vapors.
It's but a one-step improvement program.
Yeah, that's the one.
Yeah.
Stop farting or get fired.
But what about the day's business of digesting the mulch and roughage?
I'm not a...
It's a huge museum.
There's the
louisianожд"?
welthaveitenoesw technoi?"
Get off of me.
thing. Who is the epitome
of civilization?
The Sybarite?
I can't. Here, take this rope.
Self-hating and hedonic
person. What? Rope?
You gotta help pull this
thing. Forbidding others the pleasure
which she's not able to do.
Throw me the idol first.
This is the choice of all social
engineers. I can't.
Throw you the idol first.
Alright.
I'll throw you the idol.
Here you go.
Another pillow idol.
Now the rope. The rope.
K-Rope. Throw me the rope.
The rope, yeah. Where did I get that thing?
I put it around here somewhere.
Hurry! Don't drop it.
They're getting closer.
I can't seem to find it.
I had it. It was here.
I don't know. Really.
And I do appreciate your being here.
K-Rope! K-Rope!
K-Rope. K-Rope.
It's too late. We lost him.
Woo!
The party of giant sharks
is going on right now
off Guadalupe Island
in the area known as
the Red Triangle.
Part of the
lengthy ocean migration
of these two deep red fish
is the time
when all the sharks
party as if there were no tomorrow.
Well, they can't sleep.
Sharks, of course,
cannot sleep.
They can only party.
Mass party area.
Sharks don't need to sleep.
They have no need of sleeping.
Throw me a rope.
They do collect in areas where the
water moves so fast
and there's so much oxygen in it
that they stop moving.
In an area between
But they study a couple things.
They don't have bones.
Stuffing cancer.
They can't get cancer.
There are a couple things going on there.
We're looking at it very closely.
But they don't need to sleep.
That's another reason why they're looking at them
because of the astro nuts.
They also make occasional excursions
into San Francisco Bay.
They have things they don't need to do
that we do.
Well, they're very ancient.
They've been unchanged
in their physiological structure
for a lot longer than a lot of animals.
Great white sharks do come
into San Francisco Bay.
And if you jump off a boat,
you might attract one.
Like them little cycads.
I used to stare at them on drugs.
That jumping off boat
really attracts sharks.
The boat itself attracts sharks.
The boat looks like something
interesting and unusual
hanging in the sky.
They'd be improved.
Often other fish are hanging out
under the boat.
So there's even more reason
for the shark to be there.
And if suddenly somebody
jumps off the boat
and comes jackknifing
down into the water,
well, you can't blame a shark
for taking a nibble.
Are you tired of your
less advanced amoeba?
New advanced amoebas.
Advanced little amoebas?
Nope, and there they go
right off the table.
For your amoeba-enjoying pleasure.
1939, a great white shark,
21 feet long and weighing
7,300 pounds, was cooked.
How would you feel to be stripped,
turned loose like a wild beast,
and hunted?
All right.
Like an animal.
A manhunt of indescribable terror
and screaming suspense.
But that is a description
of my life right now.
All right.
Keep going, Hal.
That's what I was talking about.
The Dr. Hal Show.
On the run.
They're after you.
It's really an adaptation
of The Fugitive,
but he has to draw.
The naked brain.
There's no chance to draw
a brain.
Dr. Hal.
He has to draw just to make
enough money to go on the barn.
Yeah, I have to draw.
To hide out at the show
until the next.
White himself.
And then without clothing,
I have no pockets
to put my things in.
So try it yourself.
So most of the show really
is just shots of Hal running.
In slow-mo.
Dodging bullet after bullet.
It's kind of like, you know,
Corn Hill Wild,
The Naked Crane.
Right, right.
19, hmm, I don't know.
66.
Two blocks of buildings
fell down.
There was a 1966.
Yeah, at the same year
that Born Free came out.
Oh, the big winner.
As free as the wind blows.
Yeah, I recently saw.
But both of them
were in Africa.
That was the important thing.
I saw a really elaborate movie
edit and some young person,
very young person,
said, what is this?
what's that music at the beginning?
It's so beautiful.
And it was so weird
to be old enough,
I guess, to type in.
That's a theme from Born Free.
Come on, everybody knows that.
I was told,
I don't know if this is true,
that the theme from Star Wars
is the same melody
as Born Free.
Oh, yeah.
Flipped.
Reverse.
Absolutely.
The same notes in reverse.
Yeah, it's the same notes.
I heard that cadence before.
Born Free, beautiful.
Born Free.
Now, the mighty Joe Young
was Born Free.
First time for everything.
Yes, mighty Joe Young.
But this was definitely
a first for me.
Then he joined the Church
of the Subgenius
and became one of the steeple people.
Exterior Tatooine Desert
last homestead afternoon.
When the hands start throwing
in the toilet
was rather early in the morning.
Throw your money.
Not as early as the producer
who shall be nameless had wanted,
since fairly unscripted dramas,
Or throw your money.
gold suits not working,
et cetera,
had caused a few delays.
But I'd finally made it
into the lineup
of assorted junk
outside the Sand Cruiser
and the
I tried to look around,
but decided I had enough
on my plate and round my body
to concentrate on what
I was doing.
Is that Opie John Canopy?
Star Wars.
We are on the radio.
Wonderful Star Wars.
No, sing it in the tune
of Born Free, though.
I was named
Fran Howard as
Opie John Canopy.
Yeah, that's it.
It's hard.
Those ones.
Star Wars.
Yeah, in that version,
the Alec Guinness part
is played by
his wife.
That's Opie John Canopy dad
from Mayberry.
Star Wars to follow your mom.
And he's going,
ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Dear Star Wars.
And those wonderful Star Wars.
Puzzling evidence
show is a mean dinosaur.
Mean, mean.
It's hard to ride that one.
Those swinging-est Star Wars.
Some dinosaurs were mean
because they spent
their every minute
in excruciating agony.
Not a problem.
They had health problems
and twisted limbs.
Got some stuff in your wall.
They couldn't conceive
of their own TV channel
that was just coming up
around them
in the blink of an eye.
That would make him
so ferocious.
Did anybody see?
A manhunt of indescribable
terror and suspense.
They found Richard
the Third's skeleton,
did you see that?
Yeah, I saw that.
That was awesome.
I couldn't believe it.
And he was a nice guy
and he was all kissable.
He wasn't nice at all.
That's what they were saying
at the review.
He was just a slender,
skinny, frail man.
They're talking about
how nice he looked
and how he was.
They always say
and it's not true.
In fact, they also said,
oh, he was a hunchback
or a crooked back.
That was just
Tudor propaganda.
Nope.
All that Richard
crookback stuff.
And look at the skeleton.
All movie crap.
There's a picture in the...
Osteoporosis.
He was incredibly crooked.
He was so crooked
you could hardly believe
he lived.
What another movie?
Geez.
Palmer Breedies
told me today
that that skeleton
was found with a knife
in the keister.
Reef, reef, reef.
Yeah.
Like, what a way to go.
Well, it's better
than the way
Edward...
Remember what Palmer's name
is, by the way?
Breedies?
Yeah, no, his name.
Lies?
Okay, thank you.
Remember lies?
Just checking.
Just to make sure.
Edward II
was assassinated
in a particularly
horrible way
that could leave
no mark on the skeleton
or on the exterior
of the body.
They went the way
of Enron.
Read Charles Dickens'
Child's History of England.
Just as profitable, too.
And you'll be amazed
that that episode
made it into the book.
I'm not sure.
Awesome.
Yeah, I can't be more
explicit about this station.
Yes, of course.
It would be bad to...
Yeah, we are, of course,
the night people.
The steeple people
of the Church of the Subgenius.
It's about time for you...
We are the...
...to get up
and go to work.
More church
and less air.
The backside...
Go to work.
...of the audience.
We're talking about
operating from what we call
the backside of the brain.
The buttocks
of the cerebral hemisphere.
The backside of the brain.
It looks just like that
like a little bit.
It may be made out
of toothpaste.
This is the corpus callosum...
Reality.
...or cerebral taint...
...which divides the two
spheres of the posterior...
Have a cup.
...cerebral...
The reality.
The anterior frontal...
I can't help it, man.
...brought to me
the seat of emotion.
I've got some steep...
Just play a piano solo.
...memory.
This show is the brain's
bumper sticker.
...a seat itself.
And the buttocks
of the brain...
And it's about time
to peel it off.
...the rest of the organs...
Maybe the hind legs.
...and the brain.
...trauma...
It hurts.
...and impact...
Ew!
...generally cushioned
by the...
Help me, somebody.
...layers of dura
and pia matter.
And so, this jelly-like organ, safe in the confines...
The show wants to be free.
...of the sky.
...wishes to escape
and be free.
Yeah.
Yes, the brain wants to
caper and dance and leap outside the body's confining...
Actually, I just want to go
on Playboy after dark.
I like it when you talk dirty like that, Hal.
...and who knows, the brain might be...
Kinky.
...in Las Vegas...
Baby.
...for a fantastic weekend.
Free, free from the trammels of the body.
Naked, baby.
Why, if the soul can fling the dust aside and naked on the air of heaven rise...
Put some clothes on that thing!
...were it not a shame for him in this plane...
Oh, my lord!
...to put your pants back on.
...tripled to a bite.
We gotta make some soup.
The show's running around with its pants on.
Oh, my God.
Somebody, somebody cover that thing.
We're making a...
The show's getting stinky.
...a soup in the back.
Not my pants.
Come on, ma'am.
Trust your pants.
All right.
You need a lot of pants tonight.
Okay, I had them on backwards.
All right, don't make a federal case out of it.
We'll have your pants washed out in just a little while.
All right.
I thought this was the front.
What?
Okay.
All right, let's talk about something else.
Everyone has problems with pants every now and then.
So we're not gonna talk about pants?
No.
What are show pants?
Just trust your pants.
I asked.
Trust your pants.
Who wears the pairs of dead man's pants they dance in the darkness of the sun?
Showy, showy, show pants.
Showy, showy, showy, show.
Immaculate.
Showy, showy, show pants.
What are show pants?
Dead man's pants dance.
So dead man's pants dance.
I'm dancing with a pair of dead man's pants.
It says it.
Yes.
Right?
It says right here that Alice and Fred will be at church supper tonight with a big pot of broccoli casserole.
You don't mean that rabbit supper, Vinnie?
Give me a reference.
Why do y'all keep calling me?
You're bothering me.
I sure would like to rub your little rabbit.
I don't know your brother.
Went national back in 1984.
Go to hell!
The idea started as a business decision.
Shut up and do to y'all more.
Now airs on more than 500 public radio stations.
North America boasts an audience of more than 1.7 million.
Hey, we tell you about it, but you know, you know, you know.
We have no advertising or publicity budget.
What happened to that you know, you know, but you never know, you never know?
I don't know, I meant to call him.
On KPFN.
Hey, and if we would, we would.
He would be here, you know, in a way.
So he can wake up in the middle of the night.
It takes a talent that you cultivate over years.
You're not supposed to play the CDs on track.
Yeah, what's it on track where I can, for track record?
It's cool, man.
I'm only sleeping.
He's cool.
All right.
Who threw the overalls in Mrs. Murphy's job?
The guy that was cooking all those pants that are missing.
They were making some chowder and soup.
Yeah.
It wasn't the guy.
It was Mrs. Murphy herself.
She forgot that she was doing the pants and then she put in the chowder.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, no, now they're chowder.
But now we've got the pants chowder soup souffle.
Who threw the overalls in Mrs. Murphy's chowder?
Nobody answered, so he shouted even louder.
It's an Irish trick that's true.
I can lick the micklet through.
The overalls in Mrs. Murphy's chowder.
I can't stand that pants flavor.
There's too much show in this pants soup.
I'll never get my Twinkies.
I can't get these little pubic hairs out of my teeth that come with this show chowder.
What's the deal with that?
Don't you ever floss, man?
What about those pants?
Those pants should have been...
They should have been at least shaken out a little bit before we put them in the chowder.
And the entire crowd was disgusted with what happened to her trousers.
Rabble trousers.
Rabble trouser-rousers.
I'd like to fly away with a pair of Mrs. Murphy's pants.
Sure, and Mrs. Murphy forgot.
Mrs. Murphy, what is here?
The pants.
It was Kiefer Sutherland in Dark City.
Mrs. Murphy went and visited Japan.
And was groped on a streetcar.
I can help you find new pants.
You must do what I say.
Simmer down.
If I was into Mrs. Murphy's pants...
Too late.
It's all past praying for now.
There's only room for one of us in here.
Get out!
Now, boys.
Mrs. Murphy became a radio bitch.
But Mrs. Murphy...
Bitch.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Murphy.
I just thought that there was plenty of room for two of us.
I didn't mean to burst out with such an intemperate...
Bitch.
I'm sorry.
I think we just ought to go to where the Naboo live...
The Naboo?
...and cut down the tree.
Then we can get all those Navis in on it.
And then they can have...
That's not real, Jack.
And then I can go over to the end of the show with the girl Navis.
The end of the show, as we know it.
I like the gnat Navis.
The gnat Navis.
You do.
You're like the little bug in the jungle Navis.
You'll say that backwards.
Gnat Navis Rebellion.
Wait.
Come on.
Reap.
Spell that backwards.
Gnat Navis.
River Navi.
River Reap.
That's a clue.
I just want a girl Navi.
And a friendly flop house nearby.
I want a girl just like the girl who married dear old dad.
If I could flop...
Don't worry, son.
We'll get you that girl Navi.
And a flop house of my pleasure.
Either that or a Johnny Reb Cannon.
As long as we can flop, we have to flop.
A Johnny Eagle Army Gun.
Johnny Eagle Army Gun.
Yeah.
A whole army comes out of it when you shoot it.
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi.
Oh, jeez.
Yeah, but the army's all 2D.
You know, if you look at them this way, they look like army guns.
But if you look at them this way, they're just like little drops of plastic.
There's 99 cents for, what was it, battleship engagement.
Those were a rip-off.
You mean those little army men that were advertising them after comic books?
Yeah, I got the comic books.
You thought it was a great deal.
You know, a million army men for a dollar.
And they had those lists.
Like four generals, five sharpshooters, three admirals.
Yes, and they were all flat.
And they were all little flat guys that burned up with a match real good.
Flat guys.
When your disappointment took over and you couldn't handle it anymore.
Well, that's the way Russian toy soldiers wear their silhouettes.
True, yeah.
They look pretty good as silhouettes, but they're flat.
Yes.
If you go up to the Petaluma Military Museum, they have some of those things still.
They're slowly being sold off as the old guys who owned them die.
Oh, in the basement area, yeah.
Yeah, in the basement area.
And their kids sell off the cool old...
Hitler ashtrays.
Here's what you get in one giant footlocker.
Yeah, footlocker.
Eight battleships, six support groups, twelve destroyers.
Three toupees, five guns.
Yeah, all this stuff.
And they came and they were like...
Little slappy towers, sea engines.
MREs.
They didn't have MREs.
Somebody's here.
They would be doing...
And they had revolutionary soldiers.
They don't get any food at all.
It's kind of...
There's always a toy code.
Like in the original Marx Brothers Civil War set.
The Union guys only got...
They got wounded.
They had a couple of Union...
But they're still alive, obviously.
The rebel guys, they get dead.
Well, yeah, the Fort Apache set, you got one cavalry man with an arrow in his gut,
which was really cool.
I want that action.
I remember that one.
That one used to get...
That arrow used to get bitten off early.
Yeah.
But there were a couple of Indians who were down on their knees
looking like they'd just been shot.
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember those, too.
Yeah, I had, for many years, the Confederate guys in the Marx system
had a guy who was like a little...
Who's that?
That camera, the sculptor.
But he's rolling.
The horse is rolling forward, and he's going over, and he's like...
Action death scenes.
Yeah, and I had him on my desk for years.
Our kids nowadays get toy dinosaurs that are biting into each other
and ripping flesh.
Yeah, but do you remember those cheap kind we used to buy
where you could get...
Like dino damage.
A 30-piece.
A 70-piece set.
An 80-piece set.
A 120-piece set.
And then there was like a 700-piece set that was like,
Oh, my God!
I grew up thinking that all dinosaurs had their name
and their length engraved on their bodies.
On their tails or on the ventral stamp.
Yeah, that's so when they were fighting the dinosaur
and the dinosaur was going,
I'm about to die.
I wonder who's killing me.
He could roll, you know, over on the ground and look up.
Allosaurus, 30 feet.
Oh, cool.
Marx.
Kenner.
China.
I would know who their god was.
It's ideal.
Yeah, ideal made me thump and then he died.
It's Kenner.
It's fun.
Except the dinosaurs in El Bello Durmiente
who were hand-sewn by Chichagos.
Those were quite incredible.
You can tell a group of people are about 10 years,
20 years from death's door
when they're talking about old plastic toys from the 1950s.
And then there was this cool thing that blew up.
Those are highly collectible.
Philo and I found ourselves looking up the American...
American Plastic Brick Company.
Oh, I love that.
Do you have any of those things?
Well, I used to have them.
You can find them.
What are the...
On any building at some point.
And the Gerger and Panels set.
I loved those.
American Plastic Bricks were great.
Absolutely great.
They were much better than Legos.
Incredibly better than Legos.
But Legos made a greater market penetration
and forced them out of business.
Now Legos are like a fact of life.
They're everywhere.
American Brick is like a fetish.
I don't remember them.
Collector's Society.
They weren't there.
Yeah, there's an American Brick Pointer.
I'll show you a picture of them and you'll remember them.
The thing that they could do was
you could actually architecturally build houses,
like colonial houses with windows and doors and so on.
You could create them so that they...
You could build recessed windows and walls.
Then you could crash your Tonka Tor trucks into it.
And they crashed.
Set them on fire.
There was no border.
All the bricks would fly apart.
With a 10-millimeter camera.
Yeah.
Toy dinosaurs could crash into it.
Which you paid 50 cents for a roll of film.
And knocked down the wall realistically.
And there were chimneys and roofs and finial windows
and philasters and so forth.
Who can even say that stuff anymore?
Who cares about those old guy buildings?
But they look neat when you made them.
They still sell Lincoln Logs, but they're not wood.
They're plastic.
Oh, I know.
They're useless.
How about Tinker Toys?
They're Plinkin' Logs.
You can't even tinker with them.
You can't even tinker with them anymore.
So stupid.
It's like plastic Lincoln Logs.
I want a girl Navi.
That's why I always go back to, I want a girl Navi.
Yeah.
I mean, that would pretty much set me up.
You know, if I could...
I want a girl Navi and I want to run through the trees really fast like that.
And then have to go up the rocks to get my own dragon.
All I got was a girl Ivan.
I don't think these are the ones, though.
Oh, I can see why you'd be disappointed.
These.
This is the one.
The Halsem and Elgo.
Different companies made them.
This is the one.
This is the set.
They were called New American Plastic Bricks.
See the garage door in the middle there?
These are window frames in the air.
Those were nifty.
And if you could buy several cans, you could make incredibly large, elaborate, and realistically
proportioned structures.
Castles with turrets and all that stuff.
Just as Charles Foster Kane went to his death mumbling about his toy sled from childhood,
so the puzzling evidence showed...
Oh, they're little garage.
...Halsem Garage.
...fellows will mumble away about Mark's plastic dinosaur sets and Aurora monster model kits.
And Disney kids' figurines.
And Mark's moon comics.
And Mark's Civil War.
And Mark's radio show set.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, the little plastic radio station.
Yeah, the little plastic arms that hold the mics.
Most of the Mark's dinosaur set was based on the Rudolph Zellinger dinosaur mural at Yale.
Some of it.
Helios.
And the cavemen were based on Charles...
Okay, yeah.
Any questions?
Slip your questions.
Oh, yeah, okay.
My question is...
Cavemen of the Neanderthal race.
Exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
The sculpture of those figures was marvelous.
Just stab it in there.
Go ahead.
Throw it in there.
Yeah.
It has never been equaled by any subsequent set.
Just toss it like a...
Toss it like a salad.
Toss it in there over and over again until we hear it.
I still have one of my little cavemen, Dr. Hal.
The one that was napping Flint is sitting in a window box with a bunch of pretty,
pretty rocks in our bathroom.
So the little caveman is surrounded by his...
The Flint napper, huh?
Yeah.
Napping away.
Was he chewed by a kitty cat somewhere along the line?
A little bit.
You know, I had a great...
It's hard to get a word in edgewise, but if you keep trying, you can.
Brontosaurus from the British Museum.
Might take a few years, but...
A cat chewed his head.
Over the edge.
Roll it in there.
Why do cats chew these prehistoric reconstructions?
Over the puzzling edge of evidence.
Of course, once I put this...
Later on, when I listen to this back, I will be able to hear your question.
I won't be able to answer it.
Listen to find the answer.
And move it forward in time.
Yeah.
Yeah?
That's it?
Yeah.
Well, my question is, were you guys talking about Audrey Murphy, the Irish girl...
The Twin Peaks Audrey.
Mrs. Murphy's drawers.
Right.
Mrs. Murphy's pants.
Her huge, huge...
But what's this about playful little Audrey?
We were in her pants.
Earlier tonight.
Apparently, she lived in the 18th century, and she could come up with a tale about the
life of the 18th century.
Little Audrey.
And the...
But she's in, you know, 1935 Ireland or something.
You mean Bridie Murphy.
Bridie Murphy.
I'm sorry to have to tell you that that person, like many others who have claimed to live
past lives, was exposed as a fraud.
No!
If...
If that's a lie, then everything's a lie.
Even astrology.
My God.
I'm sorry, but your cherished illusions must be exploded.
That was the last hope of a future life for me.
I'm not.
Oh, I know.
This is my one plan.
Oh, Bridie.
Actually, Bridie herself might have been celebrated for her cleverness had she not employed it
in a fraudulent manner.
Yes.
In creating imaginary languages and elaborate histories, like many other fraudsters through
history.
Well, the great Ponzi, of course, an Italian-Canadian who invented the speed and made machines and
made millions.
Well, listen, are you going to the Davy Normal thing tomorrow?
Oh, my God, yes.
It's the event of the century.
And I just want to stay in...
Stay in the world.
I want to say, I want to say to Noah that it's totally unusual that anything interesting
actually happens around here.
And so don't think this is a normal weekend.
It will recharge the performance space in general.
I just keep saying normal.
No one turned away for inability to pay.
Everyone keeps saying normal, normal, normal.
It's Michael Pepe?
Yes, of course.
Princess Wee.
I've been worshipping you this evening.
No.
I'm sorry.
Michael, you'll be pleased to know that this week's Hour of Slack rerun features you.
Oh, good.
Yeah, it's a Pepe...
I think I called it a Pepe-palooza.
Oh, good.
A Pepe-palooza special, and it has several clips from your ancient tapes.
Well, anyway, we were able to get to the depth of what...
Who threw the overalls in Mrs. Murphy's chowder tonight.
Did you find out who?
I told you it was Mrs. Murphy herself.
Yes.
She...
It was Mrs. Murphy herself.
I can't see.
It's fine.
It was Mrs. Murphy and Michael Pepe in the drawing room with the muscle.
Oh, Mrs. Murphy.
McGinty, though, was...
You know, we never know for sure if it was McGinty's pants.
I blame Mrs. Murphy.
No.
But you gotta tell them to send me money, you know, when you claim to show.
Oh, I always did.
Completely unethical and non-allowable.
I say quit.
Send money to Michael Pepe.
Otherwise...
Yeah.
I'd be asking for money myself.
She put him into wash that day.
Michael, you do live at Post Office Box 14...
What is it?
Post Office Box 1411.
You can download the Bing and Gross B-
181417.
Michael Pepe at P.O.
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Sure.
And you guys take your time to send me the rest.
Subgenius.com.
Yeah.
You know, we've got the proceeds, but you have the secret CIA proof Post Office Box.
Your reality.
Teenage subgenius.
I can't believe you forgot it.
You're very old.
Dad, you forgot the number?
Geez.
Talk about old.
Do you dare to see the Pepe off the I-10?
No, we were talking about the thing that really-
Just off, just past Wilcox, Arizona.
The thing.
Can you take it?
The Pepe.
I don't want to stop this car.
No, but we got to see it.
Steve Wilcox, Arizona.
I don't want to stop this car.
No, but we got to see it.
And then we get stuck in a loop.
We don't have time.
Yes.
We can't-
I know.
Anyway.
Am I going to be the-
All right.
We got to see it guy or do you want to be the-
It doesn't matter because we're just stuck in a loop.
I'm going to say it back.
Stuck in a loop.
I have a question.
You never got to hear my question.
That's true.
Okay, go.
Go, go, quick, quick.
Well, the thing-
Yes?
Now, say your question now.
It's a beautiful day.
I'm going to say it and then-
No, no, no.
Will you be my friend?
No, go ahead.
Really.
Okay.
Take a deep breath and go.
We got five minutes left, so it's almost enough time to ingest your question.
The thing is an ancient German barbarian festival in which people-
You got to say your question while Michael Pepe is talking.
No, the thing is-
The thing is-
It's like the original German Jeep.
Hitler loves the thing.
He wanted people to get back-
He did.
And he wanted people to get back.
And he wanted to go to Virginia and go see the thing in Loudoun County.
I think that was the question.
I want to show my thing, but I'm prevented from that by law.
The thing that you mentioned was a Viking festival, I believe.
Put that thing back in Mrs. Murphy's pants.
I think it was-
See, that's the thing.
Oh, okay.
She's-
Okay, I think you said that-
I know.
That's the thing.
Okay.
I think you said that-
Okay, here's the thing.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Okay, let's wrap up all the themes of tonight's show.
Okay.
I think-
Things.
Pants.
I think that was it.
Cracks.
Holes.
Plastic dinosaurs.
The Kraken.
Holes.
The American Brick Company.
American plastic brick.
Cool plastic guys in Mark's set.
Witches on the side of the road.
And don't forget-
Giants.
The Marks set had an exploding bunker and it had a southern house plantation.
Yeah.
And it had a southern house plantation.
And it had little Lincoln and a little Davis and a little Lee.
Oh, little Lincoln.
Little Lincoln.
And we had a bunch of secret clues in this week's show.
Yeah.
Little Lincoln.
A bunch of them.
Not a bucket.
Not a universe, but a bunch.
And we're trying to get to this question from the caller.
A sticky bunch.
But her phone doesn't seem to cut through.
I'll have this sticky bunch.
This caller just doesn't cut the mustard.
I'm wondering if she's on a wireless, a handheld-
She's on something.
A wireless telephone.
Yeah.
The connection's not good.
And also the physical-
I was always well connected myself.
It's funny how a wireless phone at the current-
Once I got plugged in, I could really dominate a wireless phone on that connection over there.
Always be doing.
Can you hear me?
I can barely hear you.
State short question, please.
Well, perfect.
Wouldn't it be done?
And, you know, wireless is the same, too.
All right.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to call the police.
Yabbering about technology.
You need to tighten the string between those tin cans.
Ask the question.
Pull the string.
The string must be tight.
It must be taut, I say.
It's all about reception.
It must be mounted on a tripod.
It's about the technical quality of the phone today.
Pull the string and this whole thing's coming down.
I hope.
Celio, if geniuses were perfect, wouldn't they be God?
There's something wrong with the way we talk, Celio.
the string. God is within you.
Geniuses were perfect.
Geniuses are like a little
sub
branch of the whole thing.
It's just one of the many little parts.
Geniuses are just little meat.
They're made of meat.
And they come up with some answers.
Everybody's God.
Yeah, exactly. My God's bigger
than your God. And everybody's
a ham and cheese croissant.
A ham and cheese croissant
radio operator.
A five-day thing.
And what about that fried chicken?
And they're restoring the Burlington Hotel in Port Costa.
And I think that's totally hot.
Home cooking.
Yep.
The question you have to ask yourself is this week and next week
and the weeks following, what's on your radio?
Will Reverend Stang be back?
Yeah.
Bye, guys.
Well, darn it.
That puzzling evidence show from
February 8th or whatever
ended eight minutes
early for Hour of Slack.
But I found
exactly eight minutes
of very old Hour of Slack
from 1990.
We'll end the show
with the beginning of
an ancient, ancient show
from the year of 1990 or so.
But this show's already starting off rough.
Thank you for not smoking.
Don't be afraid of that which makes you abnormal.
Don't be afraid of that thing that made the teacher say,
wipe that smile off your face.
Don't be afraid of that which makes you different.
Take that which is different in you and exploit it to its fullest extent.
And don't disagree because that is the only way
that you will find true happiness.
But forget the old Hour of Slack
because we're now presenting the new and improved Hour of Flack,
dear friends.
You are under arrest.
Stop or I'll shoot.
Oh, well.
Back to the drawing.
I'm bored.
And they've been presenting the new Hour of Snacks.
That's right.
This time we'll make lots of money with the new Hour of...
Sorry, Bob.
We're trying.
Oh, my.
She is still alive, Master.
Yes.
You must remember that the space you're putting your hand through
is to this.
This is today's space.
You can't put your hand into the space of tomorrow.
Oh, the space is space.
It doesn't change.
The same space that's here now should be here in a hundred or even a thousand years from now.
No, Philip.
Time changes space.
Oh.
Look, this flat ground we're standing on could have been at the bottom of the sea a million years ago.
And a million years from now, it could be the interior of a huge mountain.
All right.
Suppose what you say is true.
What do you expect us to do with such a contraption?
Contraption?
For my part, I intend taking a journey into the future.
Well, of course I may be crazy.
The following events took place in the outskirts of London towards the close of the year 1918.
They began on the night of October the 15th.
A particularly gloomy, foggy night.
But it was well suited for a visitation by the supernatural.
Ah, yes.
And just look over there at that coffin.
Look.
It's rocking back and forth.
It's got a speaker on it.
A little microphone.
It's the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of slack.
Crawling out into your living room and car with your host.
Reverend Ivan Stagg.
Oh, no, no.
Don't run away.
I'm only a preacher.
A man of Bob.
I've preached to many people without...
And the preacher got up.
Man, he's a loser.
He looked like good guy Lee and had a northern accent and he couldn't talk right.
And he cut food.
Nothing serious.
Man, I've been to church.
People act like they had sense.
This guy gets up and on and on and on.
And he's a preacher.
But, man, I could tell you word for word everything he said.
And I thought he was really cute.
And he had this dark suit on and this slick back hairdo, you know, and this northern accent.
And he was talking so fast that I didn't want to listen, but I had to listen because I didn't
want to miss anything.
It was so unique.
I'd never heard anybody with an approach like this.
He went on like that, you know.
A lot of humor in it, but a lot of truth, too, when you listen.
And he looked out and he said, now, who's fooling you?
And, man, that's funny.
He slapped me right in the face.
I knew right then who's fool I'd been all my life.
See, I didn't drink.
I didn't smoke.
I didn't know what drugs were.
I wasn't a down and outer.
I was nothing outer.
I was so good, I'd get to nothing going straight to hell.
Boy, I'll tell you what.
I realized then what kind of fool he'd really been talking about because I was that fool.
I was so controlled by what other people thought about me that I couldn't really be myself.
I was so controlled by vanity and pride, by looking at myself.
I was so controlled by books and all these things that I was just nothing but an imbecile and a moron.
Are you that imbecile?
Are you that moron, dear friend?
Well, of course I may, but crazy.
Repent!
Quit your job!
Slack off!
And praise Bob!
Church of the Subgenius, eternal salvation, or triple your money back.
Will you guys knock it off back there?
God, did you bring these?
The...
Reverend 3.0's never been in the station during a pledge drive before and he's just having a big party back there.
Breaking windows, looting.
Oh, those aren't your records!
There's bodies washing up all over the...
Actually, friends, you know, we...
Some of you probably are out there thinking, saying to yourselves, these subgeniuses, they...
They just think it's all a game.
They see the news, the horrible news, and they...
They just, oh, they're gonna make jokes about it.
But, like I said earlier, I'm a nervous wreck.
With this noise going on in the background.
Jesus!
Oh, pardon my language.
Um, I've been paying bills, editing this video, the making of video all weekend.
And the news has been so horrible, but with the...
All these people going into mass graves and wars every...
Right here inside the station.
Uh, it seems like every other country out there's got a hundred thousand dead people and a million sick.
There's earthquakes everywhere.
Hideous industrial accidents with toxic waste splashed all over the place.
Plane crashes and riots.
Repressive regimes cracking down everywhere.
Why, in some countries, dear friends, heard in the background, radio stations can't even play material that might be construed as critical of the status quo.
And in the rest, that kind of unauthorized material can't be played unless the listeners pay for it.
That's right.
There is not a...
Oh.
Unless that poor little kid back there doesn't even have the hour of slack anymore.
There's, um...
Uh, there are stations that do play...
Um, really anti-authoritarian stations.
Not a single commercial station in this country does that.
But there are a few like this one that do.
But they're all poor.
Poor stations.
And there's only a few of them.
And half of them don't last very long.
Because their listeners don't pay for it.
And they don't support them with donations.
And so that, my friends, is the state of freedom of speech in America today.
You can have freedom of speech if you don't play cuss words.
And if all members of your audience each chip in a little bit of money.
In other words, freedom of the press and speech in America is in real big trouble today.
It's hanging by a thread, friends.
And that's what this show is about tonight.
Censorship.
But it's also a show...
A show that is dedicated to those people who have actually gone out of their ways to get off of their butts to do something in the fight for our freedom of speech.
Dedicated, in other words, to those who in the past have supported their station with this money.
This show is for them.
Post office box 18.
81417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118subgenius.com
But you know, he can work his way up at the 7-Eleven.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
And not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you don't...
Truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you...
You should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages.
And help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference.
Even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgenius foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Thanks for anything you can do to help Let There Be Slack.