This is your last chance.
After this, there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill.
The story ends.
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want to believe.
You take the red pill.
You stay in Wonderland.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Remember,
all I'm offering is the truth.
Nothing more.
Time for show.
Live show for you now.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of Slap.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
I love you.
Text to Uncle Dan, meeting with the Ku Klux Klan.
Tell him there's a change of plans, the South won't rise again.
Yammering with the Southern drawl.
Bless your heart.
Howdy y'all.
President Trump won't build that wall and the South won't rise again.
General Sherman came to town riding on a horsey.
Stuck his boot inside your ass and burned your town of carsey.
Corpulent, seditious scum pining for a donkey's bum.
Yodel, stomping, clapping, strum, but the South won't rise again.
Let's see what's going on in the cornfield.
Hey, Clarabelle, where'd you get that pretty Q-9 baseball cap?
Oh, Rufus gave it to me.
He got it at that riot up in Washington, D.C.
Well, as pretty as you are, Clarabelle, I bet he gives you lots of nice gifts.
Well, he ain't given me nothing since he went to prison.
Hey!
Jimmy Bob, what's the difference between President Trump and President Obama?
I don't know, Clem, you tell me.
What's the difference between President Trump and President Obama?
Well, I want President Trump to f**k my dog.
Football watchin' tubs of lard
Blacks for General Beauregard
Arithmetic is pretty hard
And the South will rise again
Nazi thugs with rebel flags
From our bumpers we will drag
Ship them home in body bags
But the South won't rise again
Racist fucks in Alabama
Bombed a church in Birmingham
Then they rotted in the slammer
When you fuck your next of kin
Go and tell your white trash friends
You lost before and you'll lose again
The South won't ever win
The South won't rise
The South won't rise again
Is from that one
We'll be hearing more of those
Later on in the show
The other album is called
Frop Music
And it's all instrumentals
The one in the background
Right now is called
Devil Horns
On the Forehead of Broderick Crawford
Ahead
We'll also be listening to some
Uh
Old synesthesia radio
With Dr. Hal
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave
And some puzzling evidence
Show from KPFA Berkeley
From the old days
The synesthesia show is from
WCSB
Cleveland
And uh
And some ancient fire sign theater
But now this
If only we could bring this
Uh
Special
Special understanding
To so many of our citizens
Who unknowing
Are searching in the dark
And thirsting for it
But these early days
Stang
Is staying counseled
For us
As you used it
To bring them
The message
I don't know
If this is still valid
In today's world
Of modern times
Well the first
Stangian orthodox
Fist temple
Of whatever it is
Is standing by
To leech away
Your vital essence
And turn it into
Solid blocks
Of subgenius understanding
Slack
Come on
From the barrel
Of a gun
Dave
The slack gun
Looks like one of these
I bet you wish
You had one of these
Slack guns
Like this one
See
Yeah
Pretty sharp huh
I can smell your guys
Pineal glands
All the way from out here
Fifty miles away
Oh I guess that's me
I'm sorry
I'm slightly embarrassed
I'm not
I'm just in such an on
Cause I wanted you guys
To explain Dobbs town
And the good works
And cause it faded out
As I began to
Transflux
Well you're right
You know we practice
Accu-beating
And opening of the
Third nostril
To all inductees
But that's just
At the first few weeks
Of big boot camp
Afterwards comes
Hell month
Now the
The legends and rumors
About the balls
And vice grips
And the hazings
That's a bunch of
Propaganda for me
That's right
It's not nearly so hard
Benny enjoy it
And they come back
Again and again
To retake our
Slinky subgenius seminars
Well sadly
Some of us
Some of the propaganda
Is being recirculated
By various sectors
Of the church
Of the subgenius itself
But I wouldn't ask
You to direct yourself
To that
They're in the pockets
Of Time Warner
Clear Channel
And the Saturday
Evening Post
They're everywhere
That's right
Just like the carpet
Under your feet
Or the nails
At the end of your fingers
Your little tin foil helmet
Ain't gonna keep them out
Yes pyramids won't do it
But my tin foil helmet
Has worked for an awful lot
Of the evil people
Things you've tried to do
You know playing with my mind
And stuff
It has helped
You have to remember
That
It doesn't have a self-destruct button
Like our helmets do
Well
That's another thing
In the hierarchy
How come you guys
Got better technology
Than the rest of us
Well we were there
When they passed out
The beans
Hmm
The
What
You mean
The multicolored beans
Well you plant them
In the backyard
At the full of the moon
Should we be giving away
This information
I think
Nobody's listening
Alright
Well it doesn't matter
You cast your beans
On the fertile earth
And the next day
There's a
Humongous big
Piece of crabgrass
Out there
With your name on it
Now um
I
Wouldn't give these
Special things
Go see my new movie
Terminator 3
And please go
Vote for me
Please
Now we see here
Listener censored radio
And still being interrupted
By public
Service
Announcements
That was
A local NPR affiliate
Well this
That's very annoying
That etches out
The inside of your ears
Yeah
I think it's
A form of cosmic relief
For the whole rest
Of the evacuation
You know
Mitigin
You guys have been
Sputing out
I mean some of it's
Right on the money
But the rest of it
Is just
To take your money
Well you know
You can't make an omelet
Without breaking a few eggs
Well you're like
Cracking skulls buddy
You can't control
Every aspect of
The way this is
Developed and
Promulgated
I'm with you
One hundred percent
It's just that
You know
I have the eyes
To see and the ears
To hear it
You know like
They used to say
In the old
And now you're
Looking through a glass
Darkly
Get some Windex
And get a better view
I've got 360 vision man
That's the best part
Of these helmets
I mean I'm not saying
It's keeping out
All the bad vibes
You guys are sending
Right now or anything
But I can still see
Behind my head
And you can see
In the dark
Without searching
Blindly in the dark
That's correct
And it's been
Very very valuable
For so many members
Of my family
Who keep losing me
Daily
Especially you know
After the sun
Goes down
They should let
Their fingers
Do the walking
Up your spine
Yeah I knew
You were going to
Talk about doing
That stuff to my spine
Again
Don't you know
Don't
I'm not going to
Forget it
Let's just put it
That way
You've got to release
The Kundalini energy
See there's
33 little bumps here
And after each one
Is tweaked
You'll feel like
A new being
Yeah
I have felt
Like a new being
Before
It hasn't done
Me any good
Well
You just don't
Have faith
You've got to have faith
And faith will move
Mountains
And molehills too
Every day
A new personality
Every time I wake up
A completely new
Different history
I'm getting really
Really
You know
Your name is Legion
You have a hundred
Zip codes
Have faith
And eat more prunes
Dave
Well
I'll give that a try
But no more
The Satanist hobo stuff
You know
My name is Legion
And everything
My name's not Legion
That sounds
You know
Well not most of the time
Let's take that
Other call there
Oh
The L stands for
Lumbar
Or
Converterbration
Hey uh
Dan, Jack and Jim
Go over to see Tim
Go on
Can I go
Can I borrow a toothbrush
To clean my shoes
You know
Once you guys
Like to buy
A bottle of long water
This isn't a lending library
Hello
No
Why do they all want
Special privileges
They all do
You know
And after all the years
That I've been
Sucking up to you guys
And stuff
How many have I got
Three
Well you see
Those who do
Don't receive
The benefits
And this is very
Ironic of those
Who simply
Lap up the cream
See back to
Perplexation again
This Buddhist type stuff
If I seek it
I will not find
If I sit down
I take a nap
Maybe it'll happen
And et cetera
You know
I don't know
I do lose my faith
Once in a while
Just gotta sit under
That fig tree
And uh
Concentrate
On the eternal
Infinite
Okay
But what does that
Really mean
Well it means
That there is
A universe of emptiness
Inside you
Oh man
Now that's not
What I feel
When I'm sticking
My hand down there
I mean
You got an amusement park
Inside
What
No but I have
A lot of misdirected
Hairs
And calloused
Calloused parts
College radio
And my name is
Actually Legion
Not Legion
I got scars
The size of
The same
And you put a bandaid
On that sucker
That's unsightly
Our listeners
Aren't interested
In your wounds
And uh
Oh my gosh
Lots and lots
And lots of
I've suffered these wounds
For Bob Dobbs
Much in the same way
To heal the inside of you
You know
I'll tell you one thing Dave
As long as we're talking here
Man to man
Chicks dig scars
You know what I'm talking about
Yeah
So those
Lumps and
Wounds
Lesions
Things that you're talking about
They
They help you along
They're chick magnets
Yeah
Exactly
I don't know that
I understand
On your refrigerator
So uh
Buck up
And uh
Pull yourself together
Uh
Things aren't as
Bad as they seem
And it's
Always darkest
Just before it goes
Completely
Pitch black
Oh yes dear friends
It seems like it was
Somehow easier
To do shows
Back when we had a
Radio station
To do them in
Uh
That's from
Dr. Sinister's show
On WCSB Cleveland
That still follows
The Hour of Slack
After like
Twenty years
I should call
That show
It's just that
I'm usually asleep
Or half asleep
By then
On Sundays
I've been doing
This weekly show
For thirty-six
Years friends
Almost two thousand
Episodes
And I was about
To write up a report
On how I've been
Slowing down
Because I have
The malaise
From my
Advancing arthritis
And declining
Motivation
And this
Dang chest
Concussion
And this
Which you may be
Able to hear
In my voice
It's been
Clinging on
Uh
But then I looked
At my email
And there was
The weekly
Flat out
Donation
From
Listener
Reverend
John Flanagan
With the phrase
Thanks for
Hour of Slack
Pray Bob
And it's
Things like that
That motivate me
To go ahead
And try to
Throw together
A new show
Even if it's
Made of old
Parts
Largely
Instead of
Sitting on
The
Bed
Staring into
Space
Which has been
Getting easier
And easier
To do
There's another
Guy that sends
$130.13
Every month
And another
Guy that sends
$50 every month
And about
10 subscribers
Who actually
Pay five bucks
An episode
For each show
Otherwise
I think
I might be
Too tired
Of this
To even bother
To put out
A rerun
But knowing
There are
At least
20 listeners
That care that much
I'm not
Well now
I'd be a real
Woosh to quit
Now
Plus
X day
Is in a month
And after that
I won't have to
Worry about
Anything right
I'm gonna go
To Reverend
Zanthea's
Campground
In Florida
Land of
Lakes
Florida
And see
Lots of
Buddies
And that'll
Be my
First trip
Past
Granbury
Texas
In over
A year
Granbury's
Only 20
Miles away
But they
Have doctors
And box
Stores
And even
A movie
Theater
There
Heck
They even
Have an
Opry
House
Where I
Live
In Glen
Rose
There are
Two grocery
Stores
Two drug
Three banks
A dollar
Store
And about
A hundred
Churches
However
I like
It here
Cause there's
A half
Mile of
Unspoiled
Woods
And creeks
Around my
House
In every
Direction
And a few
Houses
Occupied
By my
Siblings
And nephews
And a
Big herd
Of goats
But I
Think
During the
Last year
And a half
We've had
A grand
Total of
Five visitors
Luckily
Almost all
Of them
Were beautiful
Ladies
So there's
That
Also we've
Been seeing
Subgenius
Friends on
Zoom
And other
Weekly or
Monthly
Internet
Meetups
Like the
Subgenius
Diaspora
Every Saturday
And ask
Dr.
How
Once a
Month
And I'm
In daily
Touch with
Philo
Onan
Sterno
Sphinxo
And Puzlo
Evado
Via a
Secret
Channel
Now Onan's
Helping me
Get some
New and
Old books
Out
Now nobody
In Glenrose
Texas
Knows who
Bob is
Except for
One subgenius
Who isn't
Related to
Me
And she's
One of the
Beautiful
Ladies
That visits
Because I
Don't wear
Bob shirts
Around
My car
Has no
Bumper
Stickers
I don't
Want to
Get into
That conversation
Nobody
Knows about
The movie
Which
Reminds me
I haven't
Played the
Rest of
The soundtrack
Of Sandy
Boone's
Excellent
Documentary
About us
On the
Show
Yet
So I'm
About to
Incidentally
It's no
Longer on
Amazon
Dot
Com
Or prime
Or whatever
But it's
Still on
Apple TV
And I
Think
Hulu
And several
A whole
Bunch of
Other ones
You can
Look at
Dobstown
Dot org
And that
Explains all
Of that
Stuff
Anyway
Here's
Some
Hopefully
Not too
Dated
Stuff
From near
The end
Of the
Subgenius
Movie
By Sandy
Boone
J.R.
Bob Dobbs
And the
Church of
The subgenius
The world
Never did
Know about
Church of
The subgenius
We
Never were
That big
It is
Kind of
Obscure
That keeps
It special
If everybody
Knew about
It
It would
Be normal
We were
Just too
Lazy
We didn't
Want to be
Responsible
For our
Own cult
Members
We just
Wanted to
Tap them
On the
Forehead
And say
Wake up
And of
Course
Some people
You have
To hit
With a
Sledge hammer
And even
Then that
Doesn't
Do the
Trick
Or you
Can get
Them to
Wake for
A second
Or two
And then
They doze
Off again
As soon as
They see
A camera
Picture on
The internet
Today's
Secret
Ingredient
Is
How am
I doing
Am I doing
Okay
I'm
Present
Hey
I'm
President
Can you
Believe
Me
Donald
Trump's
Probably
The
Biggest
Most
Subgenius
World
Leader
There's
Ever
Been
He's
Completely
Caught
Up
In
His
Own
World
Does
What
He
Wants
Makes
Up
His
Own
Reality
I'm
Not
Going
To
Give
You
A
Are
Fake
News
Sean
Spicer
Our
Press
Secretary
Gave
Alternative
Facts
And
Lies
Have
No
Meaning
To
Them
Subgenius
But
Not
In
A
Good
Way
Trump's
Stakes
Where
Are
The
Stakes
Do
We
Have
Stakes
Right
We've
Been
Friends
For A
Long
Time
We're
Living
In A
World
That's
Upside
Down
Trump
Is
The
Perfect
Example
Now
Of A
World
Turned
Upside
Down
He's
The
Joker
This
Is
A
Special
Year
Our
Country
Is
Doing
Great
We've
Got
Surreal
Unbelievable
Shocking
Psychedelic
Covered
With
Reality
Right
Now
It's
Not A
Good Place
For Any
Party
To
End Up
With A
Cult
Like
Situation
I
Mean
Bob
Dobbs
Weirder
Than
Donald
Trump
I
Mean
Donald
Trump
Wins
I
Could
Stand
In The
Middle
Of Fifth
Avenue
And
Shoot
Somebody
And
I
Wouldn
Lose
Any
Voters
Okay
It's
Very
Effective
To
Slice
The
World
Killing
Us
The
Crime
And
The
Games
And
The
Drugs
We're
Torn
As
Subgeniuses
Because
Of
Course
A
Good
Portion
Of
Our
Viewpoint
Is
That
The
Conspiracy
Is
Out
Of
Control
In
Fact
To
Our
Horror
Each
Passing
Day
The
World
seems more and more subgenius.
I've got highly-expected, all-natural, weight-loss age.
The great story here is this vast right-wing conspiracy.
There are many people that don't agree with that birth certificate.
I can't trust Obama.
He's an Arab.
He is not...
Everybody is in their own private Idaho.
Everybody's in their own bubble.
And all they do is go into a feedback loop
where they can get things to reaffirm what they already think.
This administration is trying to fool you into believing
that the news the White House doesn't really like, well, is the news.
Three million illegals voted.
Where are you getting your information?
The Soviet Union has a worldwide disinformation network.
They go to media sites that incite them,
that make them paranoid and worried and fretful about the future.
They can't control the amount of breaks that are going on.
Just because they're very rich
doesn't mean they can rape you.
They're racist, sexist, homophobic, xenophobic.
I am no racist.
You're voting for Donald Trump.
None of them are interested in breaking out of the loop
and realizing, oh, I've been doing, I've been programmed.
Trump's derangement syndrome.
Hatred of Donald Trump so intense that it impairs people's judgment.
Like, if you quit being real humans and thinking for yourselves, it's over.
This is your country.
I don't know how you carve out a place for that kind of playful us and them
in a place where the news is filling so many of those roles.
That being said, I also couldn't have thought of the subgenius in 1978.
So, obviously, they're better at this than I am.
There's always going to be a conspiracy.
It can morph, it can change, and it can evolve,
and so can the Church of the Subgenius.
We'll never fix the government.
Like, we'll never get it to where everyone is happy.
There will always be acrimony.
And so, we desperately need comedy.
Well, I think the best thing we can do is spread our message.
And hope that it is useful in the coming crisis,
which is descending on the planet and the human world that inhabits it.
For the last 20 years, the only thing I had to do to make my half the mortgage payments
is keep selling subgenius ministerships.
And it occurred to me, wait a minute, this isn't a bad gig at all.
Once a month, I have to sit here and assemble these things?
Maybe spend half an hour a day taking them to the post office?
That's not bad.
People are still obviously getting a lot out of it.
Just last week, I went to the post office,
and there was this envelope there, postage due.
I had to fork out $2.45 just to find out what was in this letter,
and it had no return address on it.
The postal guy said, well, I could just throw it away.
I went, no, it's probably a joke, but it better be funny.
I got home and opened it up.
It had $1,000 in $20 bills in there, just out of the blue.
I immediately took half of it to a sick person I know
who cried with gratitude.
It's like, no, we're not crazy to keep doing this.
It really does come along at the right time for some people.
Palmer, what happened to Philo?
He's hiding.
Oh, you guys look awful, but a lot better than I expected.
Ar-ar-ar-ar.
Price fog.
Come on, welcome to Austin.
This is sort of like a booze quest.
Uh-oh, another human blockade.
Look, there's something.
There's a mermaid woman.
A merwoman.
It's you once you get your shirt off, honey.
Oh, I thought it was for real.
You first.
I'll bet you if you take your clothes off, everybody here will follow you, dude.
It was just a sad, sad joke.
Do it.
No, no, no.
If you took your clothes off, and I'll bet you anything this is true.
I'm not a leader.
I'm just a fast follower.
If you were to do that, I'm the second guy in.
To me, it's always been play.
You go to a subgenius show, they're not waving their arms in anger.
They might be pretending to.
But that's the main thing you get, is laughter.
And we're still just playing.
This is Philo.
I'm Philo.
I've been Tony.
This is Reverend Stang.
Yeah, I'm a reverend.
We're cult leaders.
That's what we really are.
Our real job is to be cult leaders.
There you go.
This will take you like a week and a half to read.
It's called Church of the Subgenius.
If you're not a genius, you probably qualify.
Let me know.
Is this like a talk show?
If you feel different.
And you feel oppressed by society's imposition of normalcy on you.
You don't have to be that way.
You can be the person that you want to be.
We know that we think for ourselves.
And that's more important than you thinking like me.
I'll be sure to be asking you questions on the podcast.
Are you looking for me?
where are you from?
You know me?
Rachael Ny sparking yourself with the music track.
We just made an effort to bring you back to this wasn't a movie.
All right.
Bye.
We were sapping with some Thunderbird wine and talked to head as nut head
It's got two friends Chad and Fred, both of them are really just heads
They got a room with a black lab poster and they both got their very own beds
Chad and Fred, they're really just heads
Chad and Fred like Portuguese bread and they always gotta be fed
So I go to the bakery when the rooster crumbles and subsequently visit Ed Asner's head
That's a good looking head
Sometimes Chad and Fred are stubborn, they won't leave us alone
They are the wampia
Ed's head glares at Chad and Fred's heads and speaks in a very stern way
Chad and Fred roll out of their beds and leave with a Portuguese bread
Now at last I've got plenty of time to talk to Ed Asner's head
So what do you do when you're feeling so low that you think you'd rather be dead?
What do you say when the landlord's knocking and humanity fills you with dread?
Cussing and spitting won't get you nowhere, remember what I said
Drop a hundred micrograms of LSD and talk to Ed Asper's head
Ed, you gotta find it for me, I'm looking here
And that was Ed Asner's Head, a song I needed to cheer me up this very day.
And by the Rudy Schwartz Project, old Waldo and Gunther are old friends of mine, actually.
They used to live in Austin.
A long, long time ago.
Now live in Canada.
Where they get much better medical treatment, by the way.
Much more affordable and generally more advanced.
Isn't that funny?
You wouldn't know it to listen to the AM talk shows these days, would you?
And now this.
Some more reading from the Dobbs Town Mirror.
Published by Dr. Onan Kanobai.
Now of Columbus, Indiana.
Isn't that strange?
He left Portland.
Why would anybody leave a peaceful town like Portland?
And this issue, I might add, is dedicated to Reverend Just John,
whose music I used to play on this show.
And his music is in a lot of my music videos of microbes.
Or my microbe videos.
My YouTube channel.
RevStang.
Yeah, he died last year.
He was kind of old and in bad health.
We also lost Reverend Rock Roswell even more recently.
But I ain't dead yet.
Convenience personified.
Why do chefs wear shades?
Chef hats?
Most people will try to come up with some kind of functional reply.
An origin story.
But the answer is to identify themselves as chefs.
The teleological heresy, creationism, is everywhere when you know how to look for it.
When someone you don't like does something you don't like, it shows how evil they are.
And when they do something you like, it shows how clever they are.
Anything as long as you get to retain your own self.
And that's why you need to have a chef hat.
A chef hat is a hat that identifies to everybody else you like and who you don't like.
I do not argue for hatlessness, but I suggest there's more slack to be had if you can switch out those hats now and again.
Instead of identifying the good and the wicked, say,
I prefer it and see what happens.
As Charles Fort said in Wild Talents,
I conceive of nothing in religion, science or religion.
I believe in a philosophy that is more than the proper thing to wear for a while.
What is the subgenius?
Or what does it mean?
It means a shell that's like 95 million miles away from you.
I am gently on the baby's behind.
It means it's the same as having a baseball glove radar strapped to your butt.
I think you got it. I think you got it.
It's like, Bob Dobbs, huh?
Bob Dobbs, huh? Huh?
What?
Sure.
I can't forget.
A subgenius must have slack.
Of all other things, a subgenius must have slack.
That is the motivator for the subgenius.
So if you're one that has felt like you needed this thing,
that you didn't know how to explain what it was,
and yet there it was,
Because of the subgenius, huh?
completing you.
What is that?
Well, it makes you jump five or ten inches higher, that's for sure.
The subgenius must have slack, but in order to get the slack,
So clip those coupons.
the subgenius must disengage from the conspiracy and be under his own genius.
Voltaire said,
We shall leave the world as foolish and wicked as we found it.
Only the church of the subgenius can guarantee to leave the world far, far more foolish than when we found it.
If the sole function of language was to communicate,
then we'd have one language.
We have more than one language, therefore we have more than a sole function.
What other functions might there be?
To exclude, to not communicate?
This explains many languages, and language dialects, and within dialects, slang.
So young people and old people can exclude each other.
Now, is the sole function of the internet to communicate?
Is the sole function of your religion to get commune?
This is the golden age of literacy.
Never before have so many written and read for their own pleasure.
It just turns out that for many people their pleasure is
sermonizing, scolding, tattling, bullying, and cats.
Lots of cats.
Cats are fine.
My pleasure, says Onan, is reminding the listener to
JOIN THE CHURCH OF THE SUBGENIUS!
And now this.
Lies up, you sinners and capers of pasta gold!
Clench your pitchfork with bulging veins!
The world will respect you when you are moist!
And the glands of the respected
are the bones of the dead!
You are surely more salient
than the horses in that barn on the edge of your lips!
Take this message to Walter Cronkite
so that he might enjoy his lunch!
Take him the glowing sector of the finest cheese!
Ask him to become a card-carry member!
And stroke his bloated ego
on bended knee!
He is to them no logitimacy!
Bombardier beetles squirt boiling anal chemicals
to make frogs vomit.
Wot's the bombadier?
But let's not dwell on unpleasantries.
After all, it's already Thursday
and we haven't planned next week's dinner engagement.
I wish Uncle Tom-Tom hadn't bought that lawn bar
after three months has harmed so many of us
and nobody has the nerve to complain.
So rise up, noosinners!
Let's prepare the frosted moon!
You know how much we've brewed
as the time draws near!
And in all this excitement,
no one should be left behind!
Why, there's even some room in that flipped-down rumble!
And the rumble seat for beautiful Maisie Clementine
with her pretty little pink taffeta ruffled blouse
and her corn liquor decanter.
We're set!
She is sitting on the roof of the snow-covered good right here!
More Rudy Schwartz Project.
Rise Up You Sinners is the name of that one.
And yes, that was me heard in the mix.
I only recorded that last week
and emailed it to him.
I got back two entire albums.
Two albums in WAVE format.
A week later, today.
Beyond fairness,
it is more effective to make peace with the gods
when you're the one selecting which gods to make peace with.
By means of the Short-Guration Personal Savior
or Shordurper Sav method
patented by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
you can have any number of highly contradictory belief systems
or objects of devotion
with all sincerity and piety,
simultaneously and instantaneously.
And when the need or whim arises,
you may cast them out.
Be religious, not spiritual.
The Church of the Subgenius believes every part of every religion.
If you are in any other faith,
either you're entirely right and everybody else is entirely wrong,
or the opposite.
But if you're a subgenius,
you automatically get it right every time.
It's win-win, Bob.
Stenders by are operating now.
Thank you, the Dobbstown Mirror.
And thank you, the Rudy Schwartz Project
for the background music from the album FROP Music,
which is kind of funny because
I don't think he actually frops.
Or they, they, I mean.
I don't mean Joe Newman.
I mean, Walt Disney.
I mean, Walter and Gunther and them.
And all the Egyptians
digged round about the river
for water to drink.
But they could not drink of the water of the river.
Men shrink from tasting
human beings' thirst after water.
And what does natural history tell us?
Destructions, dear friends,
are things on Earth.
Destructions not of all at once,
but of a very large number
are attributed by it to two principal causes.
The tremendous onslaughts of fire and water.
These two visitations, we are told,
descend in turns after very long cycles of years.
When interviewed, Los Angeles police chief Ed Davis said,
when the agent is the conflagration,
a stream of heaven-sent fire pours out from above
and spreads over many places
and overruns great regions.
But the uninspired,
the unhabited Earth.
George, George, that's beautiful.
I have been reading all the things that happened long ago
when the sun stood still
and David and Goliath and Daniel with the lion's den
and the story of Ruth and the fall of Jericho.
A lot of things happened in your days.
Yours truly, Joe.
Thou who walk'st in the sky
with splendor and terror,
king of battle.
Let it go.
The raging fire god.
God Nergal.
Nergy.
Your dog Nergy?
Nergy, the dreaded Nergy,
fire dog of the Venusians.
Hey, hey, Nergs, did you hear that?
I'll read it, I'll read it some more.
Okay, Nergy, sit up now.
Nergy, the fire star,
comes like a raging storm.
He is also called Sharapu,
the burner and light that flames from heaven
and lord of destruction.
And Farnod the Flatulent, too.
That's Nergy also.
Nergy was the god during like pre-Babylonian times
when the Babylonians were just beginning to,
as we say in natural history now here
at the Groucho Marx University,
getting it together.
During the Assyrian getting kind of,
the Assyrian groovy period,
the great god Nergy was known to fly over the people and...
Oh, good, I'm glad you got that fish.
The great god Nergy was known to fly over large areas
of the Sumerian desert and flatulate.
Flatulate is an astronomical expression,
meaning growing flat like a cod across the solar eclipse.
Like a piece of cod.
Like a cod.
Like the old, there was the old Babylonian,
you know, beginning myth that the whole earth
was not a bowl turned upside down,
but a cod piece raised by its experience.
And that holes in it,
because of the bleach used on the material,
would let through the light from the living room.
And the Babylonians then thought of this as god, basically.
Adventures in Cosmology.
Hello, dear friends.
I'm Louis P. Illuminato,
president of the United Snakes of a Miracle.
Let's talk about cosmology and its future for you.
Cosmology is a budding young industry
in the United Snakes' ever-expanding,
faceplate mechanized industry.
What's that?
What's that, Louis?
Cosmology holds great futures for the youths of tomorrow.
What is this echo?
Is this echo?
Dear God, if you are so smart,
let's see if you can read what I am saying.
It's in my own code and no one knows it.
If you can read it, make it rain tomorrow,
so I will know.
Your unknown friend, Gabe.
Dear Gabe, this is Louis P. Illuminato.
God, president of the United Snakes of a Miracle.
Let's talk about your question.
But first, how about this sound effect?
God, or Louis P. Illuminato,
knew that within the next few minutes he would have to fight.
As he crossed the porch of the Royal Flush
ahead of the sheriff and two deputies,
he slipped his hand beneath his buckskin jacket
and grinned the anger of a knife.
He knew there would be no chance to draw the rifle
from its scabbard on the street.
He knew that the scabbard would be
on the side of scouts.
He would have to depend entirely on the knife
in a fight against three men.
Each of them was well armed.
Hey, hey, hey.
That poet's got a knife.
Watch out.
Hello, dear friends.
I'm Ernest P. Illuminato,
chief poet and president
of the United Snakes of a Miracle.
Hi, Ernie.
Hi, Peter.
No, forget it.
No, it's all right.
It's all right.
I wanted your autograph, but I know you can't.
Oh, look, I'm just a plain guy.
A hundred million people would ask for it.
Just because I'm God, Pete,
doesn't mean I'm not human.
I can dig it.
God has to get up and put on one pants at a time, right?
One leg at a time through the universe.
God's just a guy like you and me.
You know, you want to hear the greatest,
the greatest and the latest from God's laboratory?
What?
Where all the little elves are working?
Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you.
We got a plan going now in God's workshop.
There's a guy in there who's got a plan
to kill all the paranoids.
Oh, no, really?
Yeah.
Isn't that a great idea?
What about the horizontals?
Anything about them?
No.
Nothing about them.
Anything about them?
No, sirree.
Let them lie.
Let them ascend.
Well, that's beautiful.
Let it go, dear friend.
Let it go.
Oh, you got to let it go, dear friends.
Before we talk about your future,
we've got to talk about your way of getting there.
And you're talking about transportation,
and that's God's language, friends.
That's where God steps in to help you get there.
Here's a beautiful 1964 Duster.
It's a beautiful chariot.
It'll get you all the way, friends.
$1,449.
Isn't that right?
Louis P. Illuminata, President of the United States.
This is your captain speaking.
We are approximately 14 feet above Cairo at this moment.
14 feet?
Wait a minute.
Captain, this is Louis P. Illuminata, President of the world and God.
Am I talking to God now?
Yes, this is it, Dave.
I wish I could see you, God, at a time like this.
Well, why don't you point the plane up a little bit?
Drive out sleep.
The books and pamphlets sold by the Subgenius Foundation
can be found at www.subgenius.com.
If you want to read one of the books in the book,
And it can literally be used to make a wish.
Not just one wish, either,
but as many wishes as you like.
Simply purchase said items,
hold them in your hands,
and make a wish.
Results vary.
If you've ever tried to dig the empty part out of a hole,
you know what it's like to take the rules literally
and not seriously.
If you're going to look out from the door
If you've ever felt low and asked, what's the point?
Like I was this morning.
That must mean that among all the possible points there could be, one of them is this.
Your point is to feel low.
If that's objectionable to you, good.
That must mean you have a better point in mind in the future.
A future.
You've just talked yourself into something interesting.
Find where that'll take you next.
No hurry.
It took all your life to get to merely now.
Yes.
When is there going to be another revival?
Ah, when is there going to be another revival?
Hopefully around November 14th.
Around November 14th.
Keep watching the area.
What'd you say?
And the location?
What would the location be?
Let's look through the mists of time and see what the location of the revival is.
Could it be?
Because there's no more you.
The Tavern.
The Beachland Ballroom?
Yeah, I had fond memories.
Actually, the first revival I ever went to.
The Beachland Ballroom.
Yeah.
Was it the Beachland Tavern?
The Beachland Tavern.
The little old tavern on the beach.
Wonderful.
Well, good to know.
All right.
Death before dishonors, drugs before lunch.
Later.
I do.
That's right.
Enjoy a work-free drug place.
Yeah, actually, it's kind of funny.
We actually transmitted some information, and it feels kind of good, you know?
It does feel good.
I feel a little bit cleaner now.
It feels really good.
The first revival I ever went to, actually, was at the Euclid Tavern.
And I had a pretty good night, actually.
I got picked up that night.
Well, you know, Euclid looked on Beauty Bear.
What did you get picked up for?
Not picked up for.
Picked up by...
He was picked up for indolence, intransigence, and inefficiency.
It was kind of crazy, actually.
I never expected...
You see, it really works, folks.
...that I'll promise to join our church, and you will get laid.
It really does happen.
I never expected that to be true.
We offer benefits...
And it wasn't true.
No.
...that no other religion can provide.
I can show you too many details.
I know.
You have read the literature.
And the pleasure saucers, and you do follow the controversy.
Y'all boys are wild.
I've been listening in.
You guys...
You guys are special.
Thank you.
Wow.
We're special.
Yes, they call me Special Ed.
Wow.
That made my night, to have a total stranger say that we're special, actually.
Well, we are.
I wish...
We're each and every one of us.
I wish we could do the...
I don't think you need to be here.
I think y'all know already.
I think y'all know you're special.
Just don't lose your specialness on this special evening.
We are all special.
Oh, yeah.
I'll have the special, too.
I ordered the special.
You ordered the special today, too?
I ordered the special, yes.
I'm still waiting.
Hmm.
We are all special.
First of all, we are all each one part of this whole universe.
We'll have two more specials.
And the universe will not be the same if one of us dies right now.
Just concentrate on the pure, bright, white light of imbecility.
Actually, I maintain that the birth of any person diminishes the value of all other persons.
Particularly the lower birth.
Always try to get the upper birth.
Because, you know, it's just a matter of supply and demand.
Or the afterbirth.
We had that special show on Ant-Man's birthmarks.
You can make it nice and sweet.
Oh, vivid technicality.
Okay, 7 billion people on Earth.
How much is that per person?
How much is life worth?
$29.95.
I don't know.
What is the global per capita income on average?
That's something I never see.
Like, you know, you see it for countries.
But I wonder what it is globally.
And can that even be a measure of the...
Well, I don't know.
Basically, it's just a supply and demand issue.
Human life...
Isn't that what we said last night?
Think globularly.
Act loco.
Oh, yes.
I think the supply of human lifestyle is the demand.
I'm sorry, cut.
Speak up.
What if you're a person who's special and it's really a demand for you?
Oh, man.
That's something...
You know, some people are not that special.
Yeah.
And there ain't no demand for them.
But if you're special, you gotta be more valuable.
Because it's a demand for you.
Yeah.
Well, then you have to spread the specialness around
into every crack and crevice and crevice.
Every crack and crevice.
Buttered up with specialness.
Oh, yeah.
The supply of life outweighs the demand.
Too many people are following the story of Onan
and not letting their seeds spill
because they don't want to piss off God.
Pulling out does not work.
Because, you know, God laid the smackdown on Onan
after he pulled out.
You know, all he's doing is...
50 million pregnant Catholic teenagers can't be wrong.
He's practicing...
Unless they're talking about pulling out.
He's practicing contraception, not self-abuse.
So Onan is tarred with the brush right from the start.
He's unfairly charged with a crime he did not commit,
although there was reason for God to be quite angry with him.
And to hurl a thunderbolt which reduced him to a tiny grease spot
in the margins of the Bible.
God f***s us all in the end.
There we go.
Those seven magically malign words.
But that's what they say.
It hurts, too.
It is painful to come into this world and painful to leave it.
And in a blaze of irritable ouchness, we live our lives.
That's true.
Unless you die in your sleep.
Well, we can't sleep now, but we can answer your questions
if you want to call in, and we'll do our best to tell you
the answers to the things that are troubling you.
We've got a panel of experts up here.
Any question...
A church service...
Is possible.
There is no question off-limits.
Provided by this radio station and the Church of the Subgenius.
Just think any question.
For example, you might want to know how much the earth weighs or something like that.
So just call in and we'll tell you.
I think we're going to take another call here.
I'll show you my bacon.
I have a question.
Ask your question.
How much does Bob weigh?
Ooh, how much does Bob weigh?
There's a question for you, Dr. Howell.
Can Bob lift...
Make himself...
So fat that he cannot lift himself.
I think that...
I'm going to guess before you answer.
Well, all right.
You're welcome to do that.
Guess Bob's weight.
My guess is that Bob travels at the speed of light,
and therefore his mass is infinite.
Well, if Bob were to do that, yes, but we're talking about Bob at rest.
Oh, look, the collar hung up.
I was going to say 265 pounds, too.
Well, that's just one of those mysteries.
Who's still with us?
I'm here.
We're having a signal interruption, a little bit of difficulty.
You see, part of Bob's makeup is heavy matter from extrasolar planets,
which, like deuterium, is quite compressed,
like the heart of a neutron star.
But a far more significant puzzle in the annals of the subgenius
is the search for the missing artifact,
the holy grail of the Church of the Soul Genius,
the scissors of sight.
What we need is to locate the famous scissors of sight,
and we are stumped since the true scissors have been lost to mutant kind for many centuries.
In a private letter, Reverend Ivan Stang, I will now quote him, said,
No man today has those scissors.
He also said that the scissors were most likely created from the remains of a huge Atlantean crystal,
the misuse and subsequent explosion which caused that continent to sink with a watery splash.
Vindica.
The Atlanteans were the most important contributors to the gene pool that eventually produced the subgenius race.
It does seem plausible that rather than trying to rebuild the lost empire,
the remaining Atlanteans would instead build a few power icons,
before tragically diluting their seed, like Onan,
by crossbreeding with ancient pink human slave tribes they themselves had helped to create.
It is from this distant epoch, 80 to 79,
9 million BC,
that the scissors and many other powerful but little-known sure-dur-per-saves originate.
I hope you have been satisfied by this answer to your question.
Correlation is not causality, but coincidence is conspiracy.
What's the difference?
Whether it brings you slack or takes away your slack.
That's what it says here in the Dobstown Mirror.
And I better check off the ones that I...
read.
Because I...
I'm getting old. I can't remember what all I've said and what I haven't said.
This pen doesn't work for hooey. It works about as well as my fingers.
Okay, all right, okay.
Price Bob.
This has been the hour of slack number 1833.
From the Church of the Subgenius, and you can get more information.
I mean all the information you could possibly want from
subgenius.com
And if you want to mail us something or get something from us by mail, our address is
subgenius
or
Ivan Stang
Or the Smiths
at post office box
Glen Rose, Texas
And we'll see you in the next video.
Praise Bob.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
www.amara.org community
Yes dear friends that was the swinging love Corpses
Closing the show out there. Give me back my phone
thing I got my fun thing back that was my old buddy dr. Philo Drummond on
vocals with his brother and cousin also in the band the swinging love corpses
man that was a great band and we're still around and so I can put the show
to bed and put myself to bed I'm ready for bed thank you and nighty night