It has become more absolute that the wealth of the nation consists in the number of superior men that it harbors.
Ass up, genius!
Howard has slack!
Come in! Come in, sergeant! Stop that noise! Come in!
Why do you stand there? What is it?
Speak up, you empty head!
Do you keep watching the clock?
Do you run down and jittery?
Do you tire? Do you never end?
If that's how you feel, for your own sake, try Subjetiometer.
That's right. Subjetiometer gives you glorious strength, energy, and needed vital substances.
Plus iron. The name is Subjetiometer.
And now, turn off your radio.
Now.
And the local business has donated $2,000 to Bob.
Because Bob is going to save and recharge the spiritual batteries of those young Christian youths.
My friends, but I want you to know something very important that you must face.
And that is that the subgeniuses have been watching you, Americans.
Yes.
Waiting.
And planning.
And training with the most grim and terrible purpose.
But here and there, oh, comedy, certainly to lift our spirits, as the liberal media declares.
The subgeniuses, oh, the subgeniuses, says the liberal media, are all washed up.
Oh, out-of-date cavemen. Gun nuts. Nuts, they call us.
Now we think about your hateful slanders, Americans.
And they shall play upon our lips as we introduce the bureaucratic infidels to their duly appointed rendezvous with eternal torture.
Oh, so Bob is out-of-date, huh?
When your own pink media reports over half of Americans believe the biblical book of the subgenius end times shall befall this generation?
Oh, practice your weeping, Americans.
For this shall be the plague wherewith Bob will smite all the people who have fought against him.
And the people who have fought against Jerusalem and Dallas.
Their feet shall consume away while they stand upon their feet.
Listen up, you evolutionists, bureaucrats, peaceniks.
And their eyes shall consume away in their holes.
And their tongues shall consume away in their mouths.
Zechariah 14, 12.
The Lord is sore displeased.
The earth shall be utterly laid waste and utterly dispoiled, for the Lord hath spoken his word.
Isaiah 24, 3.
True subgeniuses have real family values.
My friends, they do not abandon their issue to socialist daycare indoctrination robot scarecrow centers.
Oh, practice your weeping, Americans.
Christians.
The school prayer ruling by the satanic mind-control Frankenstein puppet Supreme Court.
Oh, go ahead, sure.
This is but the final insult to Dobbs.
This...
This nation hath known naught but chaos and piqueness since Lincoln, upon orders from his masonic masters,
did most illegally, unconstitutionally, and immorally in rendering void with but a stroke of his bloody pen the private property of patriots.
This indeed was the wake-up call for the book of the subgenius believing subgeni.
This was the natural order perverted.
Bob's plan mocked.
And ever since that infamous act, up has been called down.
Black has been called white.
Evil has been called good.
And the madness of orchestrated global war is only one more global war to go, praise Bob, with fearsome persecutions, till at last we greet the reign of the Prince of Slack, our savior.
Bob hath been slain.
And hath been plotting his most glorious vengeance.
Until now.
South Africa has fallen to the Communists, pledged its allegiance to the Dark One.
It is plain to all with but an ounce of liquor sense that we, we are next.
Some TV whore, choked with Jezebel hate, screeches,
I fear to live in a country with two hundred million guns.
You don't like it, harlot?
You can get the hell out.
Not that there will be anywhere safe to hide once the nukes start flying, pink boy.
Thus saith the Lord, behold, I am shaping evil against you and devising a plan against you, Jeremiah 1911.
Satan's mighty armies, the armies of the pink, the armies of the Democrats, the armies of the Republicans, the armies of, yes, the Libertarians and the Peroninaitists,
staffed with moral degenerates, so-called Americans,
are arrayed against the subgenius patriots.
As Bob instigates his one-world plot,
praise Bob, have courage, subgeniuses,
the preordained conclusion to the revolution
is that none but the true subgeniuses across this planet shall remain unslain.
Only the subgenius shall remain unslain.
This planet, purged of filth,
of ungodliness, yes,
of anti-Dobbs,
psst, of hates,
of half-assed, pinky-winky, normall hate,
the infidels, all,
all shall be purged on that great day, X-Day, 1998, July 5th at 7 o'clock in the morning,
when those of us who have our subgenius membership cards in our pocket
will be ruptured up into power and glory upon the space vessels of the escaped goddesses.
Ah, yes, you've heard it so many times,
but, you know, I just love to remind the others,
because I know, subgeniuses, that there are others lurking, listening, all the time.
Sure, they monitor us.
The other, the other hates us.
The other writhes in jealousy to hear us bespeak the glory,
the naked glory.
Of the word of Bob.
Oh, yeah, they're jealous.
They, and then, you know, funny thing is, at the same time, they are just so sure that we're going to hell.
I'm not so sure they're so sure about that, friends, and I think you can hear.
I understand them.
They don't understand me.
They are the normals.
They're all that I'm not.
But I'm a subgenius, a whole different species.
If I had my way, they all would be shot.
For when I was young, the pinks ruled the world.
Now all that has changed, cause Bob's flag's unfurled.
I spit on normals, cause I hate their guts.
I am a subgenius.
They like their jobs for all the wrong reasons.
They wear me down with their false holler smiles.
But my kind triumphed, and now we will kill them.
Dead normal bodies for mile after mile.
For when I was young, the normals held sway.
Now all that has changed, cause Bob has his day.
My shoe will soon kick a hole in their butts.
I am a subgenius.
I am not bitter for all they did to me.
They're only humans.
They're deaf, mute, and blind.
But I am a subgenius, and I have a duty.
The utter destruction of all humankind.
For when I was young, the pinks ruled the world.
Now all that has changed, cause Bob's flag's unfurled.
Soon I will grind their face in the dust.
I am a subgenius.
Thank you.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That was Dr. Onan Kanabite with a very, very old song.
Our titles were by Lemur,
and we heard some old rant by yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang from the early 90s.
Now, from Madison, Wisconsin in 1996,
the psychoacoustic ladies from WORT.
Reverend Velveteen Sly and Heidi during the Subgenius World Tour.
Well, dear friends, I'm most proud to present to you
the psychoacoustic preachers with their special little medieval morality play.
Sister Velveteen Sly and the mighty Heidi.
Thank you.
That will only get you so far.
The money is what counts, and you know it.
We will praise Bob.
We will save these sinners here tonight.
We're not really like this on the radio.
We're usually really naked when we're doing radio.
The power of Bob is near.
I can feel it, friends, I can feel it.
But we need to do a little invocation.
That's right.
A little consecration.
I need everybody's help here.
Now let's see.
From here, where are we at?
This way is north, I think.
Right here?
Is that north?
Okay.
All right.
We got to do, well, it's not exactly a dance,
but just kind of a little consecration here.
And we have to summon Bob to this space.
Well, even more than he already has been,
but to this ritual right here.
First, we will bob to the north.
It's because it's so damn cold.
And then we will bob to the east.
Oh, give us your ancient Chinese secret.
That's right.
Then we will bob to the south.
Everybody bob.
Cha-cha-cha-cha.
Cha-cha-cha.
And now we will bob to the west.
Yee-haw!
Now bob up and bob down.
And bob all around.
All right.
Good job.
Very good, friends.
And we need our bob signal here.
You got a remote control?
Well, I keep it right here next to my toilet.
Great for that extra meditation.
Alone with Bob.
Send him the bob signal.
All right.
What should I do to place?
Flashback.
Yeah, yeah, flashback.
Now, can you hear Bob?
Can you hear him?
Why doesn't Bob ever talk?
I don't hear him.
Well, you know, the normals can't hear Bob
because he's closed caption for the reality impaired.
Oh, okay.
But can you hear him coming through?
And we'll translate for you.
And the more you pay, the more Bob's word you will hear.
So help us to summon Bob.
Let me hear you say, do you want slack?
Yeah.
Do you want slack?
One more time.
Do you want your slack?
Yeah.
Amen.
Yes.
A women.
And praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
Oh, I believe he's coming now.
I believe he's coming.
Oh, I believe he's coming.
Oh, let's make it.
Bring lights down for one moment.
So Bob can come to us.
It's time for a miracle.
A miracle from Connie.
I feel her coming through me.
I think, I think Connie needs a little.
Step back.
A little dimming of the lights.
I feel, I feel really weird.
Like.
What do you feel, sister?
I feel Connie in me.
Let it out.
I feel Connie.
It's the miracle of Connie's panties.
How sweet she is.
Thank you.
Praise sister.
Heidi, for bringing us the miracle of Connie's panties.
Too much Bob, and not enough Connie.
That's a problem with this world.
But we will let Bob have the stage back again.
Smell them.
Smell the panties of Connie.
Thanks a lot.
Smell them.
That's, oh, he's gonna smoke them.
He's smoking those panties.
Stick them in your pipe and smoke them.
Cause you know, without Connie to manipulate the luck plane.
Thank you.
There would be no luck plane for Bob to surf.
I think we'll let Bob have the stage back again, but thanks a lot.
Praise Bob.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
.
Hail Connie.
Oh, the things, the things I see in this job, dear friends.
The Miracle of Connie's panties, that's a, jeez, that's a new one.
If anybody has any of those extra panties, I never got one.
The relating of spiritual declension is never the pretty sight or the pretty picture.
Because as foolish as Bob gets, as foolish as Bob gets,
it's the wisdom of the ages, it's the foolishness and the idiocy
that has kept man from being satisfied with his lot in life.
It is that stupidity which has caused man to build his great monuments,
his mighty gas-powered engines, his nuclear reactors.
It is that which has given man his urge to master the entire earth,
no matter what.
No matter how nice it was before.
And it is this mighty, sacred archetype of an urge that's in Bob and in all of us
that makes us want to smite our brothers.
And, friends, if it weren't for that, where would us subgeniuses be?
We'd be like everybody else.
We'd be no different.
We'd have nothing to gripe about.
And without the mightiest, the most powerful, the most powerful, the most powerful,
the mighty grunt power and the mighty hate,
the hate for the normal that we can feed,
the hate that can make us go out and earn something for nothing,
the hate that will make us overcome every last conspiracy attempt to hold us down that there's ever been.
In the long run, we may stay poor and broke, we may stay neurotic,
or whatever we started out as, or whatever we may fall into,
but by God, we've got Bob and Nate!
And for that, we can hate him!
Hate him!
Come to your kindergarten tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
The spirit of Bob Crane is speaking to your children.
Hey, no problem. Don't worry about it.
He is dancing in the pale moonlight.
You're not going to fight.
Don't worry about it.
Pointing to his hair.
And his glistening pubis as he sings in a high bird-like voice.
Just let them do what they want to do.
Don't worry about it.
Make your body a vessel of this great land.
Sign up. Line up and reenlist today.
You are needed for Uncle Sam's war machine.
Did you hear about, like, they used to do LSD experiments on the soldiers?
And I guess there's some secret Prozac experiments?
That's what happened to Elvis.
Yeah.
Yeah, and they didn't know how to, what the proper dose was.
They were overdosing soldiers.
Well, they were also giving them, uh, what do you call it?
Biological weapons.
They had to break out the old stash of LSD to bring them back.
Yeah, so they could withstand the biological warfare experiments.
That's from that Prozac homo.
First we dosed them out of the tox.
Now we're going to give them some acid and see how they took to it.
Where do you think Dr. Legume came from?
I thought he was the spawn of hell and came out from under a rock.
That's what everybody says.
He was in those army experiments where they,
they gave them these drugs that they thought might give them psychic powers
because the Russians were studying that and were way ahead of them.
He's telling the story of the first thought, Dr. Legume.
Psychic warfare.
Oh yes, you're gonna flip and fly like one of the little god's children of the air.
Look at your feet, they're already getting bigger, like a, like a pair of duck.
Unfortunately, the mutant power that Legume got was the ability to read guinea pigs' minds.
Yeah, and also read backwards.
And this is how he gleans the future from the minds of a guinea pig.
He actually reads people pretty well too.
This is a very, very arcane, very arcane skill.
And only entrusted to a few mutated genes born into the...
War guinea pigs.
War pig.
The pigs.
Are you being fattened up to be a war pig, Private Pyle?
Are you gonna wear those epaulettes like barbecue sauce?
Private Pyle!
I need a cigarette.
What are they gonna do?
They can't...
It's kinda hard to bring the dra...
The kids, you don't have to worry about the draft coming back.
You just don't have to worry about the draft coming back because this American Army and
Navy, they all know that American children are a bunch of little fat asses.
They would never cut the training, you know?
It's gotta be a volunteer force, you know?
It's gotta be gung-ho people, you know, just do it Nike, you know, shtick going.
But this is how the corporate state has sliced our freedom.
And I'm not gonna lie.
And the rest are all the little fat bodies.
Disgusting little fat bodies in front of television sets.
That's me.
Soaking up...
They don't want me.
Uh, Nestle Crunch bars.
I'm a disgusting fat body.
Gray, flaccid skin.
I'll stay home.
Moistened by the pale light.
Forehead.
The artificial light beamed in from the great Centurion Pactor.
There they lie.
Eating television.
Either that or they're gonna send the fat bodies over.
Something will dry.
Don't give them guns, just give them knives and forks.
Yeah.
Yeah, give them silverware.
A wave of...
Just give them computers.
A wave of fat bodies rolling into Baghdad with knives and forks.
With silverware.
Getting ready to eat, you know?
Ring, ring, ring.
Blackbird.
We are not halal.
We are pigs.
The American...
The attack of the American fat body.
And that was ESO Swamp Radio from 2002 on WCNN.
ESB Cleveland.
Oh, those were the days, friends.
With the late Professor Chaz Smith.
The lonesome cowboy Dave.
And now, Massive Hot Dog Recall.
Please don't look at me.
I'm a bottle of Summer's Eve.
Now that we're all sharing, I'm not worth the clothes I'm wearing.
I wish that you'd stop staring.
I found myself in Stockholm.
Fine-tuning the syndrome.
Negotiations broke down.
Free to go, but I think I'm gonna stick around.
This is my kind of town.
And now, Massive Hot Dog Recall.
Please don't look at me.
Cr discut quarterback Tim Fraser.
I'm afraid everybody goes out.
But I'm not alone here.
My certificate to the West Coast's Marketforum Queen was annulled inЭтоB JERSEY UNTER nasal
cam emee help number MWF LOS clothes
never made no money
Dick Cavett, you had us fooled
No need to scrutinize your interview
You sit down with Laurence Olivier
You crawl under the carpet anyway
Enough of me
Let's talk about something else
I'm sick of yourself
Broken seductions
Everything collapses
Enough of me
I'm sick ofkatjuse,
Broken synapses
Everything collapses
I think of ourselves
Enough of me, enough of me
Un-nuff of me
That's what they always say
If you do, you're gonna be dragging that bed frame with you
I wish I had a big fat soda right now
Wouldn't that be nice, but
Big ol' fat soda
Sheery rabbit soda
Now I'm gonna meet soda with a lot of fat
They have them
If you go to
Virginia City, they have a store that sells meat and potatoes soda and turkey soda and all this other stuff.
Wow.
I didn't get any.
They also have all the bizarre candy that you never heard of.
That's like the Jelly Belly factory, you know, where you can get the booger-flavored Jelly Belly and the vomit-flavored Jelly Belly.
All these earwax-flavored Jelly Belly.
All these crazy things.
Why would somebody eat that stuff?
Yes, because you'd have to admit in that case that you knew what those things tasted like.
Ronald Reagan would.
No, Reagan just liked lime, cherries, strawberries.
Yeah, you'd have to say, this doesn't taste like a booger.
He didn't even take the licorice.
You know, the full assortment of jelly beans classically had licorice and mint, which can throw the rest of them off if you cram a bunch into your mouth.
But these days, they've got gourmet jelly beans of essence of popcorn.
Oh, Hal, you would love to go to the Jelly Belly factory.
Of course I would, but I would never leave.
I would die after consuming too much of it.
They have a tour.
You take a tour and you walk through the actual factory.
He died from massive glycemic shock, officer.
His making Jelly Belly.
His aisles of langer hands couldn't take the jelly bean challenge.
But fortunately, this saves the state from having to preserve his remains with embalming fluid.
Now made of perfect sugar, he belongs to the...
He just hardened into his last known shape.
Just don't let those kids lick me.
So, it was a sad thing.
The, uh...
The licking of the chops.
Yes, I guess I can't lick every man on this ship after all.
But you'll never get enough.
You better not try.
These boys don't like that kind of stuff.
Why didn't you let them...
say so?
Well, I guess I should take a poll.
Just install that...
Alright, man.
How many of you boys want to get licked?
All over.
And, uh, keep on ticking.
You gotta...
I'll have some...
Keep on ticking, also.
Me, me, me!
Sorry, only one lick to a customer.
And you've got to...
Install that screen door.
There's a little bit more, uh, acceptance there than I thought at first consideration.
Well, life on a sub beneath a misty ocean is a long slog.
A long slide?
A slog.
Oh.
A slog like...
A long slide into...
Tramping through the...
Floods...
A different world.
...the fields.
Did anybody see the Wonder Woman movie?
Did you see it, Kira?
Yeah, I saw it.
So, it's in World War I?
Yeah.
It, uh...
How'd they do?
Did you like it?
Yeah, Wonder Woman beat World War I.
It's a very popular...
She won World War I?
Yes.
Yeah, that's a little-known historical fact.
Wow.
Uh, but, um, that means that...
She was the Golden Age.
See, we see her in Batman Meets Superman, and she's still young-looking, so how come...
She's in World War I, but then in the ultra-modern era, she still looks great.
Uh, because she's...
Because she's an animal.
She's, uh...
She doesn't age.
She's super, in other words.
Yeah.
You know.
I don't know.
She's, uh, a goddess.
Well, it wouldn't bother me that she was 98 years old...
Princess Diana.
Yeah.
I mean, as long as she looks like she's better than the bovine disco-dancing Princess Diana.
She's much taller and, uh, and much attract...
More attractive.
Yes.
Hubba hubba.
But her name is Diana as well.
Her human secret identity name is...
Oh, I didn't know.
Yes, as you correctly state.
Diana Prince.
Yeah.
And then there's her boyfriend, that, uh, overmatched soldier.
Steve!
Steve.
Yes.
Another Steve.
That's Steve Rogers.
Steve Adorno.
Steve Rogers.
Oh, Steve Rogers.
Yeah, okay.
And it's a beautiful day in his neighborhood until Wonder Woman comes and makes him take
out the truck.
And does she have her transparent hair?
Wonder Woman.
I've told you a thousand times, I'll take the trash out later.
In the World War I thing, does she have a transparent airplane?
Right?
No, she has, uh, a sword, a shield, and a lasso.
Oh.
No transparent airplane.
But Steve flies us up with Camel or something like that.
He has the World War I thing.
He crashes one.
Yeah, he crashes.
He's like John McCain.
He can't keep it in the air.
He's gonna be the guy that gets caught.
Crash one of those little fabric trucks.
Hey, look.
We got these guys on the team.
Oh, there's McCain.
Oh, he's gonna get caught.
Taken away from the high hat squadron.
I'm not exaggerating.
He was known, John McCain was known as Crash McCain because he destroyed so many aircraft
with their landings.
But, uh, you know, now we know not to make those.
He found a good, he could take that, what he learned from crashing those airplanes and
apply that to his, to his new job.
Yeah.
All that experience from crashing airplanes, he's been able to parlay that into a, a lifelong
Senate career.
How about, uh, Sarah Palin?
Did she ever get back from the center of the earth?
Uh, did they ever find the-
I don't think so.
No?
She's trapped down there.
Uh, she met Hitler riding a Tyrannosaurus.
That was the last I, I saw.
Uh, did they ever finish that thing?
I don't know.
But I like the idea.
I like the idea of, uh, riding a Tyrannosaurus.
Well, there were many good things.
For one thing, the, not only Hitler, Hitler Heil Hitler.
Is that lurch?
But the Tyrannosaurus also with its little arm did the Nazi salute with its two fingers
to which Sarah Palin returned a middle finger salute.
Then also the beginning shows the nuclear war starting and they, they take, they take
the
Hey man, I played a game where I actually ride dinosaurs.
I mean, not dinosaurs.
I ride an elephant and the elephant is like knocking guys out of the way and button them
with his tusks while I'm shooting with a sniper rifle.
I ride dinosaurs.
Or even a machine gun.
They're not dinosaurs.
So I'm mowing the guys down while he's, while my, my good old pal the elephant is also mowing
them down.
My friend is the elephant and the elephant has a machine gun.
Yeah, no, the elephant doesn't have, I'm the one with the machine gun.
Well, get your story straight, man.
The elephant is carrying me on his back.
That's your elephant.
Who are these guys anyway?
Nazis.
No way Nazis.
You'll deal with them.
We should have a new comic book.
It'd be like little, like little, uh, what was his name?
Little hot stuff.
Little hot stuff?
It'd be like little hot stuff, but only be little Nazi.
Okay now.
Like a little bitty Hitler running around.
Because you mentioned that.
Playing pranks on people.
I have to say, there was an episode of little hot stuff and I have it and could show it
to you where Hitler came and visited the fancy forest, the fairy forest where hot stuff hung
out.
Hitler and his men.
Wow.
And they were
hiling and everything.
They wanted to take
his supply of apples
that he eats.
Believe it or not,
the Harvey comics
did go for this.
It's unquestionably
Hitler and all his
henchmen are hiling,
but they're like
in civilian clothes.
That sounds like a Herbie.
That's something I would
see in Herbie.
It's in civilian clothes
because it's after the war.
They can't wear
their uniforms,
but I swear.
But they're all
hanging out together.
It's in a little
hot stuff,
stuff anthology
that I have,
which was compiled
by Leslie Kabarger.
The applesauce cave.
There it is.
That's the one.
Boy, you found it
on your device.
See, there's Hitler.
They're hiling him
and there's hot stuff
sleeping in the apple tree.
I'll have to post this
on the Puzzling Evidence
fan page.
Well, I bet you
never knew
hot stuff and Hitler
ever got together,
although it ends up
with him driving Hitler
and his men out.
Hi.
How's it going,
Dr. Brujaha?
Overlord Animal.
What a surprise.
Yeah.
Hey,
I'm just out here
in the wild.
I've been adventuring,
foraging, if you will.
Me too.
I just went to the
the Far East Asian
Trading Company
and Bazaar.
I too went to
the dollar store.
Yes, the dollar store.
The gems of the Orient,
the dollar store,
prevail.
I found some things today
and they're so amazing.
I got this thing.
It's like the head of a bear
and you stick it onto a thing
and then it spits out mist
like the kind that you see
on the movie Pet Sematary.
Like fog.
But it's supposed to be able
to help you breathe.
So I think it zombifies bears.
It's a bear zombie fire.
I think so.
It makes my sign.
It says just open right up
and ready for bears.
I got a frozen poop maker.
Oh my gosh, you do.
That is going to be
lumpy.
It makes little lumpy logs.
That's, uh...
I think they're supposed
to be cartoon worms,
but you know.
Yeah, as opposed to
the real worms.
Yeah.
Because you can't
get worms in the store.
You can't put them
in your freezer
either to make frozen.
I mean, never mind.
You totally could.
I could probably
buy a tapeworm
and make it.
one of those places.
Does tapeworm segments
work in frozen drinks?
I don't know.
No, you use it
as a stir stick.
You freeze them
and it's like
the tapeworm is
a great stir stick
and appetizer
all in one.
A flatworm stir stick.
Like a pretzel rod,
but...
But doesn't disintegrate
in your drink.
But will make you
just want to
consume more and more.
It's much like
American television.
Yeah.
It's...
Now available
as seen on TV.
Tapeworms.
Tapeworm stir stick stir.
Oh, oh my goodness.
Oh, but there was a...
There were these things
that I got.
Most people use them
for cleaning dishes.
I give...
My cats take them
as toys, though.
It's like
those cute little sponges
in various shapes.
Oh, yeah.
And all.
And also,
what was the...
Oh, and I just wanted
to clarify those.
The tapeworms,
they're 8-track.
They're not cassette.
Mm-hmm.
It does...
They're like...
They're not the small cartridges
that you would see.
Yeah, 8-cassette tapeworms.
It is an 8-track.
8-track tapeworm.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Very, very,
very specifically.
Yeah.
This is a...
Like the wide flat noodles.
I got the
narrow mouth
spell bottle
strainer.
That's what this is.
It's part of your
magical drip system.
Yeah,
for when I need to
make extraction.
And whatnot.
And infusions.
Oh, gosh, Dr. Bruja.
I wish you could
make an infusion for me.
Why?
Yeah.
Well, to not have to
need to go to this
magic...
to this fantastic place
to get all these
acquisitions
like once every season.
I'd rather not.
I'd rather just have them
like show up
on my doorstep.
Yeah, but then you'd have
to use those companies
that make that one guy
really rich.
And kill whales.
Doesn't every company
like sacrifice a whale
if they want to be good
at business, though?
I thought that was like
part of the deal.
Like, that's what the
Illuminati script says.
Like, you want to be
rich in business,
you've got to kill a whale.
Well, I mean,
if it involves, you know,
shipping container ships,
full of shipping containers,
going across their
hunting grounds,
then yes.
Yes, it does.
I got those snack boxes.
A set of snack boxes
with family snack boxes.
So it starts with the
dad-sized snack box
and the next is the
mom-sized snack box.
The next is the
older child.
I'm going to say
it was a girl, possibly.
A bob-tailed,
a bob-headed,
a bob-tailed,
you know, there was no,
you couldn't see the tail,
it was bobbed,
but the bob haircut as well.
And then there was
the small mutant.
And I'm not even sure,
it was a child.
It might have just been
a very, like a demure,
diminutive,
like an adult
that wasn't fully hatched.
Was it?
Well, that's kind of
what children are, aren't they?
They're like half-hatched adults.
I guess.
I don't know.
I just, I thought, like,
you know, kids make
a lot of noise
and this box wasn't
making any noise at all.
So I was just like,
you know, maybe this is
just a small adult.
It could be
a very small adult.
You know?
And not even,
not even necessarily
an endodorf
or a dwarf
or a midget
or any of those
particular size terms,
but possibly just someone
from South America.
Like in Peru,
they're quite
not as tall as
there's a lot of people here
in this part of North America.
That's only because
they starve for their childhood.
Cool.
Okay.
So I could, like,
just not feed kids
and they'll stay tiny?
Yeah.
Forever?
That's a good idea.
That's the reason why
I'm all like,
wait, forever ever?
I mean, you know,
they'll stay tiny-ish.
I mean,
I bet if we, like,
put a, like,
a Mount Vesuvius
kind of action on it,
they would stay tiny forever.
Yes.
Definitely.
If you Pompeii'd them,
they would never
get any bigger.
You know,
I was gonna say,
my grandparents,
they all starved
during the,
like, the wars and stuff.
So they're,
they never got to be
above 5'4".
Like, they're like,
So what's your excuse?
Uh,
just
bad genes.
I just carry
the starvation gene.
It's just,
Yeah.
Well, you know,
it's,
well, like,
Oh, they hear that rumble?
Half Hobbit.
Yeah, they're rumbling
the glacier moving by.
Oh, jeez.
Is the glacier
calving again?
I think so.
Just don't,
don't yodel.
Yeah.
That tends to create
an avalanche effect.
It's,
you know,
it really gets going
sometimes when the sun
shines on it,
where the,
it really starts calving
and, like,
it groans
and screeches
and grinds
and makes all kinds
of crazy noises.
So that's not just
the cat on the outside
of your glacier box?
The cat that's hungry
and wants some kibble?
Yeah.
The cat,
the cat is
plotting to murder us all.
I, uh,
I'm sorry.
Your cat's nice.
I keep forgetting
not everybody
has a murder cat.
Yeah.
She's too old
and tired
to be a murder cat
anymore.
Some days.
She used to be,
but she's retired.
She's a murder cat.
Thank you,
Overlord Anna Mall
and Reverend Boo Ha Ha,
and we'll close
with Doctors for Bob.
Specifically,
Pope Sternodox's
classic rap
called
The Explanation.
And remember,
subgenius.com.
Now before we
proceed with our
quote,
schizofreniatric,
scatolographic,
metagalactic,
pri-primality
induction seminar,
this evening,
I would just like
to take this opportunity
to state
briefly
and for the record
that
my fellow
doctors
and doctors
for Bob
and myself
are members
in good standing
of a church.
But not just
any church,
for the church
to which we belong
just happens to be
beyond a shadow
of a doubt
the world's only
bogus true religion.
Of course,
I am referring to
the Church of the Subgenius.
This one's dedicated
to Reverend Cleve Duncan.
Now the Church of the Subgenius
is founded by
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Santa Sales,
Master of Slack,
1953,
the prime religion
of the future,
united,
superior mutants,
social,
renegades,
twisted geniuses,
and sci-fi sinners
in a worldwide
rampage
of inborn
and profane
yucks and grins.
Yucks and grins
which will hopefully,
inevitably,
lead us directly
to a commodity all too
lack.
Today's modern, dead-age, agogos society,
and the most
modern and brilliant,
is Slack.
Slack is what the conspiracy takes away from us.
Slack is what the conspiracy deprives us of.
Slack is our way
of grabbing life by the lapels
and fucking it up the ass.
Now back in the 50's,
Bob himself noticed
a decided lack of Slack
in our culture.
He noticed
an awful prevalence of normalcy.
that the normals
formed a vast conspiracy
against the different.
An insidious conspiracy
dedicated to squelching
our natural rogue instincts.
Dedicated to wiping out
our fun factors.
Dedicated in short,
to the total and utter eradication
of the original Slack
with which we were all born.
Well Bob wanted to fight this conspiracy
ladies and gentlemen.
What better way I ask ye,
than by the foundation
of a major,
new,
world,
religion,
hence the church's subgenius,
Prince Bob!
Woo!
Help me somebody!
Now many people I know,
have been told,
that the Catholic Church
A very tiny one.
A very stupid one.
A very microscopically mediocre level.
Mediocrity.
You see the conspiracy only in
the think tanks,
Time Magazine,
CBS,
NBC,
the US government,
CIA,
FBI,
Lutheran Church,
Missouri Synod,
Catholic Church,
Jewish Advocacy League,
Council on Foreign Relations,
Trout of Labyrinth,
Federal Commission.
All the more occultated individuals,
see to the next level.
You see the conspiracy as,
the Heliopters for Gobotran,
the Men in Black,
the Green Energy Demon,
the advanced supersonic Nazi Hell creatures from the Hollow Earth,
the henchmen of Negi and,
the Yonkatismo.
But even they don't have the full story,
ladies and gentlemen.
I'm here to tell you tonight,
that the conspiracy exists,
as none other,
than Jehovah One,
Alien Space God of Wrath from some corporate sin galaxy,
and his stark vest of removal.
Now many of you here tonight,
many of you here tonight I'm sure,
view the Church of the Subgenius as a bit,
old,
demonic.
You're right,
it is demonic.
But well,
speaking of an animal,
there are some very evident demons here.
Well the Church of the Subgenius does recognize,
every major deity,
of every world religion.
Jesus,
Buddha,
Krishna,
Mohammed,
Elvis,
Merle,
Hank,
Arnold,
Butch.
Rather than having one central authority,
great figure,
the Church of the Subgenius,
possesses an entire pantheon,
or subgenion as it were.
One referred to as,
short duration personal savior.
Now you're a short durper Sam,
if you can think from,
multi-stage vibrators,
sending white noise signals,
to the very epithelial center of your brain.
To a multi-level,
pyramidal religion,
guaranteed to empty your pockets,
and send your soul to heaven.
Hallelujah!
And the most important thing,
it could be anywhere from,
bleeding,
decapitated,
neck-stump of a world cup golfer.
Sailing its arc way,
through the heavens,
for your salvation.
And it could last anywhere,
from a nanosex,
to your entire lifetime.
And you could have one,
or ten,
or millions of short durper Sam's,
concurrently,
consecutively,
and simultaneously.
It's the only way,
that you can take,
Now as in any other major world religion
The church of the subgenius has certain inalienable tenets
Certain basic precepts
Around which a life philosophy can be formed
The most important of which are
One, too much is always better
That's not enough
Can I get a too much?
Too much
Can I get another too much?
Another too much
What is it always better than?
Not enough
Wake your children, praise God
Woo, help me somebody
Praise God, right on, amen
Now the next rule of the church of the subgenius is
You can pull the wool over your own eyes
And relax in the safety of your own delusions
So relax
Now the third rule of the church of the subgenius
And this is one that a lot of religions
Particularly the Christians really get into
The third rule of the church
The third rule of the church of the subgenius is
You'd pay to know what you really think
And you just watch Swagger the Follower on TV
Sometime you'll see that point illustrated all too clearly
And the next rule of the church of the subgenius
I'd like to mention tonight
Don't just eat a hamburger
Eat the hell out of it
Can I get a scrumptious bovine?
Scrumptious bovine
Can I get another scrumptious bovine?
Two more scrumptious bovine!
Thank you children, praise Bob
Whoo!
Kill me somebody!
Now the next rule of the church of the subgenius is
Don't just launch a golfer hit
Launch the hell out of it
Can I get a bloody four?
Bloody four!
Can I get another bloody four?
Another bloody four!
Thank you children, praise Bob
Whoo!
Kill me somebody's bovine!
Now the next rule of the church of the subgenius is
We don't practice what we preach
Cause we're not the kind of people we're preaching to
Now have you ever seen another church with the guts to admit that most basic of all religious principles?
Say no!
No!
Say hell no!
Hell no!
Say no children!
Say it hell fuck no!
Thank you children, praise Bob
Whoo!
Kill me somebody!
And the last rule of the church of the subgenius I'd like to mention tonight is that we're
the most important rule of all!
The final rule of the church of the subgenius, the ultimate rule of the church of the subgenius
is...
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Can I get a fuck them?
Fuck them!
Can I get another fuck them?
Can I get a fuck them if they can't take a joke?
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Thank you children, praise Bob!
Whoo!
Kill me somebody's bovine!
Fuck them!
Even if they can take a joke!
So, if you are what they call different, if you think we're entering a new dark age,
if you suspect that there's the slightest possibility that they're gonna introduce
bleeding golfer head launching in our public schools in the near future, if you're not
ready to wear the skin of your grandma's face in the next year, if you think you're gonna
wear a mask that says, This is a badge of your tri-primality, if you view the entire universe
as one vast, morbid, cosmic joke, if you think you're a plug being enough, if you think we're
entering a new dark age, if you are searching for an inherently bogus religion that will
condone superior degeneracy, then I'm gonna take a fucking joke!
And tell you that you are above everyone else!
And most important of all, if you can help us with a donation, then the torch of the
subgenius may just provide you with the slack you lack!
Now I'd like to finalize here tonight with a quote from Bob himself, as he wrote in the
Economicon, the book of Neuronomics, the book of Neurology.
Verse 661, chapter 13.
Watch two girls making it.
Hell, I'd rather be two girls making it!
Help me somebody!
And remember, subgenius.com.