Oh, let go! Oh, he's got my leg! Oh, my leg! Help! Don't save me!
Call the dogs up, they're biting me! I give up!
The Self-Genius Power of Squash!
That was a couple of years ago. I went back to reform school and watched my chance.
And this time I finally escaped.
Escape.
A Spitfire Hijinx, says the Dobstown Mirror.
Most religions, most of their rules are such that if you follow them, things are supposed to be nice or better as well as correct.
The Church of the Subgenius has rules that if you follow them, have similar outcomes sometimes,
and other times make things very much not nice or not better.
Which makes up for the fact that I'm not a subgenius.
For hours, a mail-order mind-control cult more like life than a description or a hallucination of life.
One such rule?
Mob them if they can't take a joke.
Try it and see.
Go ahead, kid. What's the matter? Scared? Afraid your mom will find out?
Anyway, we'll be hearing the first live hour of Slack from 24X Day on Friday, July 2nd.
And I'm not going to play the first hour.
It is the last 26 minutes of Dr. Hal and me talking because it was recorded only on my phone and my location recorder,
which also picked up drunken audience chatter and just sounded too much like the situation actually sounded.
The last 40 minutes got recorded off the line mic board mix, which was salvageable.
Just for contrast, the first minute or so of this is from my ambient recordings, then the rest is from the board.
I don't mean the bored audience, I mean the mix board.
The old animated cartoons were the MTV videos of their time
where they build a cartoon around a popular song,
like happy harmonies, merry melodies, silly symphonies, and so forth.
The song, just about seven minutes long, perfect for a cartoon.
You're just following in those footsteps.
And then they're illegal now.
Some are.
I heard that they made the Warner Brothers cartoons non-violent somehow.
But not the special collections.
Anything that's chopped up for TV.
And Spielberg also messed everything up with his idea of Warner Brothers cartoons.
That just makes the banned ones more popular on YouTube.
I was thinking how awful it was that in the 70s that Ron Miller,
the director of the Disney organization,
a former football player,
took all the Donald Duck cartoons and so on
and put thumping disco music to them
and then released them.
And they used to show these ads again and again
with Donald Duck's fanny boinging to electro disco music.
Or goofy or something like that.
Strange laps somewhere.
And then they made the decision.
Holy cow, we're going to have a pyramid of drunkenness here.
He's warmed up too much.
Thank you, I'm sorry.
I'll pour another one down in just a momentito.
Thank you, hunch peas.
Thank you so much.
The hunch peas.
Of Notre Dame.
God, what a butt kisser.
God.
The hunchback of Notre Dame?
The hunch peas.
Oh, the hunch peas.
Oh, I'm just giving him crap.
It's all about ball busting with these military guys.
Well, as long as it's affectionate.
You see, when your default way is to run everybody down
and insult them, there comes a time something is not right
and then suddenly you snap and get irritated.
Like Mr. Spock saying,
I never did appreciate those comments you made about my ears.
I didn't like it then and I don't like it now.
Oh, geez, Mr. Spock.
Ease up.
Ease up or whatever.
Too much is, I hate to say it, in every instance is not always better than not enough.
Except to provoke a change.
Well, you know, the original quote was,
too much is always better than not enough but it's almost as bad.
But that just didn't have the same ring.
It didn't go over with the college kids nearly as well.
No, because they wanted all.
They wanted an excuse to hurt themselves with beer,
and that's exactly what I'm a little worried about
when I saw the 50 cases of Orange Blossom back in the day, IPA.
It's great, but 50 cases?
Take one down and pass it around.
There's 49 cases of beer on the floor.
Yeah, Onan already suggested that.
Yeah, well, Onan's not coming, right?
No, no, he couldn't.
He actually had to work.
Oh, yes, work.
The workaday world must go on, whether capitalism or communism.
Work?
Maynard G. Krebs knew that terror.
But you're about to know a new terror,
as taught by Father Joe Mama, Papa Joe for short,
in his miraculously preserved first sermon from 24X Day,
Gird Your Very Self.
Hello, dear friends, and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled
The Secret of Sisyphus.
You remember Sisyphus, don't you?
He was the ancient Greek king
who defied the gods and was condemned in Hades
to roll the large boulder up the hill to the very top,
only to have it roll back down over and over again.
How does one motivate themselves to do this over and over
throughout all eternity?
It's a dilemma many subgenies face,
but it's not a secret.
They're all working hard at their jobs,
working for the Khan.
How can we continue to fight our way through the work week,
hour after hour, day after day,
week after week, month after month,
and year after year?
We try desperately to empty that in-basket,
only to have it refilled just as quickly as it is cleared.
What did we do to deserve such punishment?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
And what can we do to make it clear
that we're not the only ones in this hell on earth?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
But there is a secret to withstand the despair
that this punishment tries so desperately to impose on us, dear friends.
A well-guarded secret that allows us to fight on despite any and all odds.
But to reveal it, we must go forward in time,
over two thousand years,
to 1860,
during the American Civil War.
The bloodiest war in American history.
650,000 casualties.
One of the earliest battles
was the Battle of Lexington, Missouri,
or as the natives called it during wintertime,
Missouri.
The Yankees had attacked the city
and were dominating the battlefield.
During the day, the Union and Southern forces
would meet on the battlefield and kill one another.
During the night,
they would meet on the campgrounds,
and play each other at poker.
They weren't friends,
they were frenemies.
And who doesn't like beating their
adversary at cards and taking their money?
The daily fighting was brutal.
At one point, the Yankees took over
the Confederate field hospital,
the old Anderson House,
which had been converted to a three-story
warehouse for the wounded.
Many rebels were trapped on the upper floor,
and the two sides traded gunfire
up and down the large,
central stairwell.
Finally, the Yankees offered
a truce of sorts.
Any Confederate who could survive a jump
from the third floor and could crawl
back to his unit would be allowed to do so.
Several accepted,
and survived. So, the Union
changed the rules just a little bit.
They set out bayonets
pointing upward
at the bottom of the drop,
and took wages on how many would impale themselves.
Many did.
But, even
more gruesome was the fighting that occurred
out on the river bluffs.
The Yanks held
the high ground, forcing the rebels
to push up the hill under
withering gunfire, only to be repulsed
and forced back down time after time.
Then,
the South tried something
different.
Why not provide some portable protection?
They took some of the
bales of crops from the surrounding
farmland and started rolling them up the hill
like a rotating rock.
It stopped the bullets,
and the Yankees started to worry.
Then they came up with another idea of their own.
They heated their bullets
and fired those at the bales.
And sure enough, it worked
for a while.
It set the bales on fire,
and yet, the rebels kept coming.
Even
when the smoldering and often burning
bales made it so much more difficult,
they continued to fight, and
when the battle was over,
the rebels had won.
Despite overwhelming odds,
Lexington was safe,
at least for a little while,
and the South thanked God for their
miraculous victory.
But was it really divine
intervention that provided their victory that day?
Or was there another
forgotten factor,
a secret to their success?
And what the
Hades does this have to do with Bob?
Well, for that answer,
dear friends, I'd like to
reveal to you an often overlooked little detail.
That crop
that the bales were made out of
was a common cash crop back then.
Not cotton,
but hemp.
A plant used to make rope
and other fibrous products.
It is the older equivalent of cannabis
and Havafrop Zipulops,
the sacred subgenius herb from Bob's pipe.
The more those bales burned,
the more inspired those rebels became.
And as to the
Sisyphus is concerned,
well, what kind of fumes do you think
they are?
Well, they are
Hades and Hadesia.
The more you
think about it,
the more you'll be surprised
The more you
think about
Sisyphus,
the more you'll be surprised.
Because we are the modern day rebels.
Only we are not fighting for slavery.
We are fighting against slavery.
We are fighting the same slavery
the conspiracy created
when they traded the subjugation
of one race by another
using whips and chains
with the modern subjugation of all races
using time cards and security cameras.
They replaced the overseer's
whipping with the modern
manager's tongue lashings.
No, you can call it slavery
light if you like.
All the oppression, but only one third
of the actual effort.
The 24 hour bondage has been replaced
with a 40 hour work week.
But don't expect any gratitude
from us. We all know they
only did it to make us more
interchangeable and expendable.
It was
a cost cutting measure
because like everything else,
even slaves are cheaper
to rent than to own.
There is also
a color difference
to the modern warfare.
It is no longer the blue against the gray.
It is a battle betwixt
the pinks and the grays.
And come next day,
the burning bullets of the pinks
will be no match for the titanium
plating of the gray
saucer ships. Nor will they
be capable of outrunning the laser
cannons of the Exis Starfleet.
So embrace
the struggle leading
to Ex Day, dear friends.
The fierce fighting that shall occur
no matter how bleak it may appear.
Remember our
history and fight on.
Remember the secret
of Sisyphus
and the secret of the Southwood's amazing
battle. If you
can't beat them,
joint them. And don't
worry, be
frappy. It is the word
of our praise, Bob!
Amen!
YAY!
We're broadcasting live on
Freethink Radio!
Has all the subgenius shows.
Put your hands on the radio
and maybe it'll stop that annoying humming.
They do replay
almost all the...
You know, it's good to where
I hate to say it, but the number of subgenius shows
is too damn high.
It's like the number of subgenius Facebook
pages. Too damn high!
I can't begin
to follow them all.
It's ridiculous.
Well, a lot of applicants aren't
bothering to fill out the subgenius
questionnaire quiz
and I think they should
at least make a stab at it.
We discontinued the questionnaire
because... You did?
Yeah, people were spending so much time filling them out
and I wasn't doing anything with them. I felt
bad about it. Well, if they put anything, it
I mean, you can't admit them, but if they
just refuse to cooperate,
do you really want them hanging around?
They're too snarky for their own good.
I still have them all.
In a big paper sack
that's rotting away.
Don't hold them back.
Put them in a paper sack.
In the shed. The Dobbs shed.
Right. I'm too bad about that
unfortunate fire that...
Well, we shouldn't have been
using pure oxygen to
fill the place.
Like the Hindenburg.
There went all those types.
No, actually, it's got...
The Dobbs... There is a Dobbs shed
Uh...
Dobbs shed. Near my house
lined with
fossil rocks.
Don't go near that old shed, kids.
Yeah.
It's got $3000
worth of insulation sprayed in it and
two air conditioners that are both
running full speed right now.
And the only thing that's
used to preserve the ancient
rotting documents on paper.
And 8mm,
35mm film, 16mm film,
Betamax VHS.
Sounds great.
The zines and
mail art of the 80s and 90s.
Well, the ones that the squirrels
didn't pee on in my Cleveland...
Still continuing, the zine world
is flourishing.
And, uh, Onan is
inheriting that shed
because he's
qualified. He recently gave
the world's biggest
Buckminster Fuller archive
to a university.
He had acquired that much
Buckminster Fuller. He says his was...
There's probably another guy that would say
his was bigger, but...
You know, it's all about size.
Like the pink Canucks. Oh, they're
Marshall McLuhan. But Onan was so big, he gave
it away for free to
some university in Portland. It's probably
been burned down by now.
Well, you don't know. He left
Portland. He lived too near downtown
and it was just
downright dangerous. He got tired of the
ruckus, so he actually
left for that reason. I've turned into a fad of
ruffian violence.
With the
excuse of wokeism.
Out of control. You see,
these youngsters don't remember
the 20th century and the
cultural revolution in China
and its revolutionary
excesses. Because all revolutions
of every kind
ultimately have excesses.
The pendulum swings back
and forth in the human way
and for a while, the extreme
is
an intensity which can be unpleasant
for those who are on the other end of it.
That stuff scares me because that
really did happen in China. The most
ignorant, and Cambodia,
the most ignorant
people who outnumbered
the intelligentsia and
professionals and shopkeepers
took power and
wrecked
the
lives of anyone who could
read or speak a foreign
language, wore glasses.
I know people who went through that as
teenagers. Tried to preserve art
from earlier non
Marxist Leninist eras.
Yeah, well I worry about the
I don't know, damn
Trumpy Qanons doing the same thing.
Other people worry about the anti-fa army.
Which as far as I can tell
exists only in
Portland and Seattle. The trick
is not to get around
between those two stones.
But they are real
in those two places.
Anti-fa just means you oppose
fascism. If you want to see where they are
go to Arlington National Cemetery.
Sure, we're all
anti-fa, but in the sense
I mean, it's people who'll
say, yeah man, I'm anti-fa.
F*** you dude. Oppressor.
And then they'll topple a
statue of somebody who is a
hero to the gay community.
Or crash,
burn down a courthouse where all kinds
of human rights things were done for the first
time. Because they have no idea about
their own damn history. They destroyed
a statue of Frederick Douglass.
Why? Well they
I don't know why. In San Francisco
they took red spray paint and
spray painted in the face of the statues
in the park of Don Quixote,
Sancho, Panza,
and Cervantes. And Cervantes
was himself enslaved
for a while.
But I guess they didn't like it because they thought
these were conquistadors who
oppressed the First Nations people
and had never read Don Quixote.
As opposed to satirical
novel characters.
Good God. Next
question.
I'm not sure if you're
interested in this, but
story of the
first-generation
The first-generation church
was a church
built in the
18th century.
And it was
built in the
18th century.
But what's this?
From the cult
of Zere, a strange
document with the curious
title, Wizard Bong.
Here, I think
I'll read it.
Is existence incorrect?
While there is much
to investigate, what we don't
understand increases exponentially
with each passing year.
Recently, for instance,
Wizard Bong is known
to be Wizard Bong and potentially
other things and
or everything that is not
Wizard Bong, while also
remaining everything that is
Wizard Bong all the while.
And
also not Wizard Bong?
You read that correctly,
we think. And tell you what,
containing all possibilities,
including the possibility of one's
own absence without undergoing
some form of severe
existential crisis,
indicates a bold,
emotional fortitude.
This damn thing
proverbially eats its own
stomach, so to speak.
How the hell can a Bong
do that stuff?
A Bong that is
and isn't a Bong, and also is
and isn't everything else.
Strive to achieve. Reach.
Fail.
Breathe. Take a nap.
Be at the coffee
shop in three hours and look for a
man wearing pants.
Oh my goodness!
Wom sma tem
enon she daftod.
It's fine really, fine.
It didn't have to happen this way,
but now that it has, let's not cry
about it. Stop muttering. It'll be
okay.
Wizard Bong, fine.
The proof is in the park.
Highly illogical research
indicates the promising possibility.
We're engaged in
irrevocable congress with lost
truths. Where does the park
factor in, for example?
Still a mystery, embarrassingly,
but we'll find out.
Where exactly
are we now? Climb
beyond your expectations. Wet
your appetite. Wrestle
alligators. There are mysterious
underpinnings to the reality we
view daily through a lens darkly.
Wizard Bong,
you are where you said you
were, aren't you?
Were you lying?
...
This is the sixth heading.
Illumination decrypt
mismatch error.
Unfortunately, you can't read the sixth
heading until you've read and memorized the entire
website. Once you have
undergone this strenuous exercise,
the actual paragraph should be quite
easy to read behind this one.
In other words,
this is not the actual paragraph.
Wouldn't you like to finally
truly know?
Exactly!
And that's Wizard
Bong from Cult of Zere,
which I think Onan found
on a website.
Cult of Zere is
basically our friend
Molg.
Molg also lives in
Portland.
Hot, hot, hot.
Well, here's
a... We got a little bit of mail.
Oh boy, mail call.
Yeah. Well, let's
see what's in Bob's bottomless
mail bag this time, Stang.
Someone,
Sigma
Starspawn,
Cute.
Just sent a short, it was a
quote he found in the
Dobstown Mirror.
Lay it on me.
If there is a God, he is a machine
that converts prayer into irony.
And
the letter writer said,
I wish I had written that.
And I wrote back, and I said, so do I,
but Onan wrote that.
Onan actually has been sort of like my
co-speechwriter for a long time.
He's coming up with good stuff, and I hope
we're all familiar with the Dobstown Mirror,
that wonderful subgenius
newspaper.
I gave him a plug in the
nanoheliograph.
I don't know why this is in here. This was...
This is some... It says,
after
track 10, this
1830th hour
of Slack is a good rerun from 2008.
And everything about
X-Day still applies in
2021, except the main
party is being held in Land O'Lakes,
Florida, at the nudist resort of
Reverend Xanthea Octo-Shroom and
her dad.
Good boy. What a...
This is... What an improvement this is.
But most subgeniuses...
It's certainly more comfortable.
Probably won't be nude. Most of our skin
is generally unkissed
by the sun's rays and will likely
stay that way. All information
can be had...
Who is saying this?
Dr. Howell and I will be
there, and a whole bunch of young...
much younger subgeniuses,
including ringleaders
Argus Fox, Reverend Eads, and
Pitt Chooley. The rising generation.
We depend on them to perpetuate our
legacy. Yeah, and to
haul our luggage. When the
torch falls from our faltering
fingers, there are brawny
hands to grasp it and hold it
high. Oh, and then there's a
sad thing about Reverend Rock
Roswell. Oh, yeah.
I saw that. Yeah.
He was only 60.
That is really too bad. He had a lot of
trouble with health and insurance.
You know, Dr. Evermore
died also in
2020. Oh,
the list goes on and on. Reverend
Crash. Yeah.
Heathen, of course. Heathen,
yes.
I really, really miss
Heathen. It's really terrible about Heathen.
On the other hand, I think Heathen
died in his sleep of a heart attack, which is not
a bad way to go. Yes. You know,
you just wake up on the escape vessels and go,
whoa. You wake up dead,
yeah.
And, of course,
Jay Lynch and Skip Williamson.
Interesting cases because
when Jay Lynch died,
Skip Williamson couldn't stand to
go on living.
.
Yes, but
there are the survivors,
the hearty survivors of
this terrible
time.
And that just shows that
somebody always survives,
and you always think it's going to be you.
And who knows? It might be.
It's the lottery, luck of the draw.
You might
be allowed to be aboard
the Ark. Although I
saw that Noah's Ark movie
and I wondered where they were coming
from with that. The bad guys
stows away aboard the Ark
and starts eating endangered
species and so forth. Where did that
come from? And long
suffering Mrs. Noah played by
Jennifer Connelly, you know.
What a performance.
That must have been
a forgettable movie or maybe it was
late at night. I saw it but I don't remember
any of it. Yeah.
It starts with the Anakim.
No, no, no, not the Anakim.
What are the
angelic beings who had sex with the
daughters of men?
Yes. Only in this movie
they're like the pile of
rocks monster from Galaxy
Quest. They're these
big tumbling balancing
boulders stumbling
around. How are they going to have sex with anybody?
Anyway, so that's Hollywood.
What can you say? Speaking of
Noah's Ark movies, I
found a list of movies
that have been filmed in the town I live in,
Glen Rose. Yeah.
And of all things,
besides Dinosaur Valley Girls,
was Noah's Ark. I saw that one.
I have that one.
Had been partly shot there.
Well they have the Noah's Ark
attraction, don't they?
I understand. We have a
wildlife safari park there
and you can film
giraffes and zebras walking
two by two if you're desperate.
You know,
but it turned out it
wasn't the big budget
Noah's Ark. It was
the Michael York Noah's Ark.
Oh no. Yeah.
A Christian made Noah's Ark.
Real, real low budget.
So that explains why they had to go to
the safari park in Texas
to film the zebras
walking two by two.
Well I read that one Noah's Ark
from some Christian Noah's Ark
park got washed away by
severe floods, which seemed
so appropriate. No, it wasn't.
It had severe
water damage. The one in Kentucky.
The giant building shaped like Noah's Ark
leaked
and flooded.
And the water poured in and
they didn't read their Bible closely enough.
That's all so silly, friends,
because Noah's Ark actually
sank at the area
known as Stang Ranch
in Glen Rose, Texas today.
It's not on Mount Ararat
or anywhere. I can show you
the wreckage. There's very little left.
A few boards.
Well it was made
so many cubits long
and deep out of shittim wood.
The prehistoric
subgeniuses jumped off
the boat and as it
sank a lot of critters
went down with it.
But don't they have some of these parks with
Jesus riding a triceratops
and so forth? I mean they really
go off the deep end. Hal, I can't
wait to get you to the Creation Evidence
Museum in Glen Rose.
Well the most amazing one
is in, is it in, no it must
be in Virginia because I told
Doug about it and then he went there
which is the Republican
Dinosaur Park where
the South wins the Civil War because
dinosaurs eat Lincoln and U.S.
Grant and so on. They have all these
dioramas of
dinosaurs munching the Union Army
and so forth. Well I told Doug
about that and then he went to his
Virginia Military
Academy reunion and he
took time to drive over to the
park and he got there when it wasn't open
but he talked to the guy and the guy let him get in
and shoot pictures so he has
a slide show of it now.
Great, great bad
dinosaur parks. There's
quite a few of them. There's one in
Glen Rose, a dinosaur world.
There's one, same as the one, same
chain as the one here and
there's one in Cave City, Kentucky
also. There still are a lot of them.
Many have fallen by the wayside.
Flintstone Village is
in ruins, a sad
state compared to
where it used to be. But the
thing is, what a great film
project it would be to start at
one end of the country and then drive to
every tacky dinosaur park
that there is. You know, have a giant
road trip and
you know, make commentary
on it.
Show clips from dinosaur
movies.
Couldn't it be entertaining?
That would be fun to do.
A lot of
gift shops of
various places veer
into dinosaur park territory.
Mainly you've got the big shapeless
concrete dinosaurs
somewhat weathered with pieces of
rebar sticking out for the pathetic
nature of it all.
I'm lucky enough to live
in a town that's famous
for dinosaur tracks and that's
their claim to fame. Dinosaur Capital
of Texas. Dinosaur tracks,
chemotherapy. Yeah, the
most famous ones.
And there's lots of really boring
cretaceous marine fossils.
You don't like those, huh?
Oh, I love them. My house is full of them.
I had to move most of them back outside.
I've lined my yard with them.
But they're all fossilized
things that are still around today.
Snails, oysters, clams.
Not the same ones.
Not mosasaurs, but I didn't find
any of those.
Well, we have varanid lizards today
and mosasaurs are just those big
monitors that went back to the ocean
and became aquatic.
There was a fairly new one
found called Dallasaurus.
Interesting.
It's got a three foot long mosasaur.
There's also Arizonasaurus,
which is a fin-backed
archosaurian
reptile which is not a dinosaur
but more of a
crurotarsal.
And then there was the moronodon,
the fattest, stupidest of all
dinosaurs, so bloated that
its belly had to be covered with thick
scales to prevent harm
from dragging over the rocks.
And the blundersaurus whose
constant tripping caused the
indentation of the ventral surface
which has puzzled so many
scientists.
But yeah, I'm lucky
to live in a town that has more
dinosaur statues, good,
bad, and indifferent than
most small towns. Sounds pretty good to me.
Yeah, some of them are really great.
There's a miniature golf course
with the worst
dinosaur, the worst
brachiosaurus you ever saw.
It's hard to do it right.
It's just laughable.
And I have the full collection
on my phone if anybody really wants to see it.
I was just in Chicago
O'Hare airport on the way here
and I usually try to find the
giant brachiosaurus
that they have there on loan from the Field Museum.
I'm not sure it's there anymore.
Anyway, I had trouble walking. I couldn't get there.
But when you're there,
you're standing by its legs
and they're like the immense tree trunks.
Hey, the background
music by Fid Chooly sucks.
And its head is touching
the very top of the
concourse. And down by
its toes, there's a little shop
that sells plastic dinosaurs
and other sacred objects.
I saw what looked like
a giant wishbone in the Dallas
DFW airport.
For years they said, you see dinosaurs
didn't have a wishbone. But now we know
they did. A furcula, as it is called.
This would have been Godzilla's
wishbone. So I'm wondering
maybe it was a work of art made to look like
a fossil wishbone of a giant creature.
Boy, if you crack that one and get the
big piece, I wonder what kind of wish you get.
Could you make a guitar pick out of Godzilla's
press bone? Godzilla's what?
Like Superman. Could he
like...
Could he like fight
Superman, Godzilla, and then
Superman wins?
Well, the important
pick, of course... And then
Superman makes a pick out of Godzilla's
press bone.
Whose sound could melt a heart of stone.
Then there's the
pick of destiny.
Maybe that's what it is.
Maybe that's what the pick of destiny is.
It was the pick of destiny!
My life knew
every single Tenacious D song
by heart.
Well, they're good songs, especially
that whole thing about challenging
Satan to the rock-off.
It's a great sustained
sequence. One should
generally not do that.
Don't challenge demons
to do things and so on.
Life is better without that.
You know, when Voltaire
was dying, and of course
Voltaire thought he was dying for the last
20 or 30 years of his life.
But at one point he was really
dying, and he was the big free thinker
in France, so...
A priest went there hoping
to get a deathbed
confession, you know, a conversion.
So he finally came back to the
church and he was shouting,
Renounce Satan! Renounce Satan!
Voltaire was saying, really,
at a time like this, do we want to make enemies?
Last night I heard a most confusing sound
it came from
inside the wall
A moist and sloshing noise
a condensation sprawl
A wheel of gastro
with a fulvic protuberant
spine
A radioactive skull
and tentacle sublime
He shook his shiny
radula and
asked me with a Croatian
drawl
Could
I please see
Farley Granger's oxygen
tent?
Oxygen tent!
I suppose
it needed to see
if Farley was okay
Gastropoda
worry a lot, their concerns must
feel late
Their excretory organs are known
to emit an assertive bouquet
I told them to clap and
gesticulate it
Would you, would you, would you
please?
The gastropody
bound to Farley's
face and
sarcasm
the sarcasm
of the
tenacious sheets of mucus
like my ankle falls
His throbbing ganglion
suggested pleasure
through a bloody mass
of pus-covered gauze
Thank you
sir
for letting me into the
oxygen tent
Love should pay
and Farley Granger's
oxygen tent should stand
Oxygen Tent
The Rudy Schwartz
Project Farley Granger's
Oxygen Tent
from the album adjacent to the
latex gerbil
that's its title not its location
probably, maybe both
Now back to 24X Day
with special guest Dr. Howland Owl
Well I, Dr. Howl
I'm an old fart and I think that as old farts we should let the young farts...
Well let them step up here and grab the microphone. I'm not stopping anybody.
Well, you see they're closing in on the science.
Who's gonna fight the next war?
Alright, let them come I say.
Because, after all, you gotta feed the monster.
Content is what it's all about.
Hours and hours of tape.
More and more content that can be edited and spliced and sent to the ears of the awaiting faithful.
Right, nobody comes to listen to us here because I know it's all gonna be on our slot so I'm gonna need that.
We have plenty more where that comes from.
Well, you don't know, the meteor could fall tomorrow or the exes could come a few days early.
You know, what to them is our foolish sidereal idea of time.
Just if you hit it broadly...
That's all.
That's the best one could expect.
Well, an hour of slack is still an hour.
And still slackful.
An hour of slack production or as I call it, squeezing out a Glen Rose steamer from the house of Blivets.
Okay, if that's your concept of artistic creation.
Well, I have to do most of them at home and I do have to squeeze them out.
Well, sometimes it may flow and other times it may be a harder effort.
I'm gonna now read the last two rant notes that I had for an hour of slack.
Please do so.
It's only two post-it notes.
One says, brave new 1984.
Yeah.
Which I feel like that phrase entered my head and I thought that's what we have here.
A hedonistic authoritarian state.
It's authoritarian but they keep the...
There's a lot of bread and butter in there.
Bread and circuses and legalized marijuana and drugs.
On MFK 106.
And TV and internet to keep everybody, you know...
Keep them docile.
Keep them at home, basically.
Keep them in line on the slaughterhouse ramp.
Yeah, brave new 1984.
Hey, I'll pay extra for room 101. I've heard they've got VR.
That's for sure.
Worst case I've ever seen.
The other little note I had was...
It says...
Guns don't kill people.
Cops kill people.
But I have to attribute that to Tommy Chong.
Who said it in a really terrible movie they did called Still Smokin'.
It was like a comeback movie.
I liked Up and Smoke.
And it just...
It didn't cut it.
Now did we hang out with him in Amsterdam or was that...
We met John Sinclair.
Did we meet Tommy Chong?
We didn't meet Tommy Chong.
Oh, we didn't.
You're imagining that.
Alright, I'm trying to get it all straight.
You're thinking of...
Harrow.
Okay.
Yeah, the pot-smoking, the pot-inventing guy.
And John Sinclair.
You're forgetting that we did that radio thing.
You know, we got just a little bit of time on his microphone, but...
You're sure that didn't happen?
John Sinclair, yeah.
Okay, John Sinclair.
Yeah, not Tommy Chong.
Alright, yeah.
Or either that or we did do something with Tommy Chong, but he had a better prop even than Xavier Hollander's dad or husband had.
Well, I gave all of mine to Xavier Hollander and her man friend because everybody kept saying,
Oh, you can't go through customs with it.
They'll search you.
They know what it's been.
You know, you're going to be gone over with it.
You're going to be gone over with it every inch of your life.
And so I gave all the marijuana samples away.
I went through and the guy's reading a magazine.
He just waves me through.
And he has joints in his pocket that he forgot to take out and he gets waved through.
So once again, that's slackful luck.
Actually, we had a whole bag of tulips that we didn't understand we were not supposed to take out of Holland.
We did anyway.
It could have been a bag of hat.
I did see a little dog suddenly...
Following these two cops at customs.
The marijuana sniffing mongrel?
Suddenly sit down next to the bag of a nice young couple.
A nice young couple and this little dog just sat right down next to their bag.
And wags his tail.
And the cops said, sir, you have to come with us.
Horrible.
Please come with us right now.
I demand to speak to my ambassador.
So, yeah, we thought that you could smoke pot anywhere in Holland.
But no, actually, it's only in those clubs.
We got in trouble for it.
They almost kicked us out of the hotel.
We really didn't know.
Ah, after Lieber and Stoller.
Heck, we've got looser laws in Colorado now.
Well, it's hard to keep up.
But at any rate, it's mostly legal now.
And going to the marijuana store is one of my usual chores.
Well, I live in Texas.
And it's still the way it used to be.
In Texas.
And probably cheaper that way.
Oh, wow.
Maybe.
That's the way.
I mean, I always liked the underground economy.
Except that you have to go to the seller's house and pretend you're his friend and sit there for hours and hours and listen to his music and listen to his talk.
And then finally he drags out the cigar box or whatever it is.
And then often if somebody else comes, then you are free to go.
But otherwise, you're really glad you've got your dope on.
But you can't get out of there.
And you're expected to smoke it there, too, with Mr. McBoring.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
I sure do.
Luckily, that doesn't happen to us much anymore.
You call this girl, meet her at the supermarket parking lot.
Exchange.
Give her a few items.
Get your fake frop.
It's just plain marijuana.
Fake frop.
How come it used to be, I hear this a lot from my roommate, Mr. Mavridis, how come it used to be so much better and you pay all this money for artisanal strains of marijuana and it's like, it's barely there.
Rather smoke it than not.
But, well, I used to get this great dope that a guy grew.
And he left it for free in a paper bag in his garage.
And you could just come in and scoop it up.
And if it was psychedelic, you'd be tripping on it.
Really.
That's Paul?
Well, what do you mean?
Was that Paul's memory of things?
No, that's my memory.
Oh.
But Paul was saying that the old stuff was so much better than the new stuff.
What?
That's what he's saying.
It could vary in quality.
Quality may vary.
There was no board of judges elevating this strain or that or giving it a funny name.
Yeah, I love the names.
It's all the same.
It all gets you high.
Purple push, gangster, strawberry.
The name, you know, the elder spiel that goes with it.
It's like wine snob.
And they all know it.
So if you order dope, the dope guy comes to your house and then he says, well, this is a very mellow strain.
And you'll notice elements of it.
This is more of a body high.
Yeah.
Whereas this one's more mental.
This is kind of a more buzzy.
The guy who bicycles over there is an expert.
A gourmand.
There's such a bunch of hooey.
Well, maybe so or maybe no.
On the inevitable thought has occurred to me that the reason it was so good back then is that when you're young, you can consume anything.
Right.
When you're old, maybe those receptors are there.
Those receptors are somewhat worn down.
Think of all the crap that kids eat and they can do it.
But have an adult try it, you know, end up in a world of hurt or maybe just a continent of hurt or city of hurt or something.
Well, if you ask me, I would quote Dave Gardner talking about something else.
Even the worst was wonderful.
Absolutely.
I would not deny it.
Not for a moment.
No.
We cannot repent of such notable wonders and undertakings.
Oh, here's an interesting.
This is a love comic about little monkey boy in spilling his guts.
And it stars Mr. Chanto, who's fairly normal looking with a turtleneck and monkey boy who looks kind of short and sad and monkeyish.
How do you like it?
I like my new shirt, Mr. Chanto.
Maybe now Mary will go out with me.
Silly monkey boy.
Appearances don't matter.
It's what's inside that counts.
Hmm.
Later he meets Mary.
Hi, Mary.
Hello, little monkey boy.
I was wondering.
He pulls out a knife.
Would you go out with me?
And he slices his belly open and his guts fall out.
With entrails like that, I'd go to the moon with you, Larry.
Oh, little monkey boy.
And monkey boy dies thinking, I'm so happy.
And stink lines rise from his guts.
This is all from Swank by Greg Petix and Reverend Chris Silla.
Here's one that is a haunted trucker story.
Route 666.
Chicken spooks haunt this rig.
Phantom beaks peck at my neck.
Cow specters hammer down blame, mooing accusal from the back.
Vegetarian when I was alive, hauling meat to make ends meet.
Tortured by the guilt until I jackknifed off Route 666.
And it shows this great big rig going off a bridge over a bridge.
Sam's Choice Meats.
It says on the side.
I'm a trucker ghost.
My handle long forgotten.
Chained to this damn stretch of road.
I never stop for gas.
My tank's full of hellfire.
I never stop for food.
My stomach's in a drainage ditch outside of St. John.
Eighteen wheels of apparitions weighing on the sleeping brows of a continent.
Barreling down Moonlit River.
A midnight blacktop.
Triple nickels on the dime.
Boy, that should be a country western song.
And that's it from Swank Comics Collection.
Originally published in the Arizona Daily Weekly.
Or Daily Wildcat.
The Arizona Daily Wildcat.
I'm sorry.
And you can find this.
By sending free comics to.
Got your pencil ready?
3333.
Southeast Cesar E. Chavez Boulevard.
Number 5.
Portland, Oregon.
Poor things.
97202.
Or email is swankboy at yahoo.com.
All yours dear friends.
Okay, Dr. Howell, I think there's no audience.
One other thing.
Totally irrelevant, but I meant to say it before.
In that vampire show, What We Do in the Shadows, I thought I saw Paul Rubens in there as a vampire.
Did I?
Was he in there?
That was a good episode.
Yeah, when they go to these other vampires' house and he's there with these really obnoxious ones, including a real vampire.
Yeah, the rapping one.
When he's there.
Actually, I can see that easily.
He does have kind of a Bela Lugosi look.
Yeah, the art direction of that show is just wonderful.
No.
You've seen the movie, right?
Which one?
What We Do in the Shadows.
No, I've not seen that.
How about the movie?
No.
Oh, at least watch the movie.
The movie is groovy.
It's got a different cast than the...
The list of things that I must see.
Now, sit right down and watch.
To Camelot.
Yeah.
Well, every now and then something comes out that's really exceptional and encouraging and has great art direction.
Oh, I know.
There's a lot of them.
Yeah.
Tons of them.
Can't keep up with them.
And they get plowed under.
But the same people from New Zealand who made the movie have made the show.
And the show has a different bunch of vampire roommates.
But it's the same conceit of there's a camera crew in there.
And they're prominent.
And they're famous not to be eaten by the vampires.
They can film their roommate interactions which are full of conflict because some are thousands of years old.
Some are hundreds of years old.
Some are ten years old.
Some were just made vampires.
And the human stooges who do all the work with pathetic hope that they'll be made into vampires.
They have the different type of vampires.
They have not vampires.
They have blood.
But they steal your emotions.
Oh, that's the best one.
In the show there's a...
There's a guy who's an energy vampire who's like this bald businessman type who talks at you and he sucks all your energy away.
And he even sucks the energy from the vampires.
Nobody likes him.
He tells these terrible jokes and laughs in an insincere way.
And people are slumping over and falling over.
Their energy getting sucked up.
That sounds kind of John Shirley-like.
It sounds like the kind of thing he'd come up with.
Well, it's pretty good.
I was visiting my friend in New York and she showed me a bunch of those episodes which I can't watch because I don't have cable and so forth.
But I watched a bunch of them.
I don't have cable.
But the movie.
Read the movie.
You'd be amused by it.
It's lots of fun.
It's well developed.
See, they have a hypnotic power so they can have the cops over to their house and the cops don't notice all the dead bodies on the floor.
And the cops are there to answer a complaint.
It's funny.
It's supposed to be Orange Officer.
Oh, okay.
And the werewolves are in it too.
A subgenius got away with the crime.
He was caught red-handed.
Or orange-handed.
He was spraying orange Dobbs heads in public.
Terrible.
And the cops said, what's going on here?
And our friend who was an older guy, kind of a Pease-like guy.
He goes, oh, it's supposed to be Orange Officer.
He hadn't planned it.
He didn't plan to say that.
It just came out of his mouth.
And the cops were, okay.
It was like, these aren't the droids you're looking for.
It worked.
It's supposed to be just distraction.
Well, it's supposed to be, I guess, you're all right.
You're not seeing this.
You're seeing that.
Magician trick, you know.
Distraction.
These aren't the drugs you're looking for.
I'm looking for drugs.
But they are the drugs you want.
Will drugs.
See, it doesn't.
Will drugs turn you on?
This orange blossom is a wonderful drug.
I just had a whole can of it.
It's 6.4% alcohol.
But the rest is healthful water.
So it's good for you, kids.
I've had . . .
Back in the day, IPA.
Believe me, I know my IPAs because I'm Reverend Ivan Stang from the Church of the Subgenius.
And Blossom Special, back in the day, IPA is what a monster.
My very favorite.
It's almost as good as back in the day.
Hey, it is back in the day.
Amen, brother.
In the future, there not going to be any day.
So this is back in the day.
In brave new 1984, there ain't going to be no more back in the day.
Because it's all been the same the whole time.
Ah.
The people my sister is in prison with.
Many of them seem to think that this country has always been English people, English speaking, mostly white people with cars in suburbs.
And when they see something like a Robin Hood movie, they go, why didn't he just get a gun and shoot him?
Well, he did in that Kevin Costner one where they bring in gunpowder and start blowing up the sheriff's office.
The less said, the better.
That wasn't a great Kevin Costner movie.
No, it was not.
I, on the other hand, happen to really like Waterworld.
Many people hate it, but I thought it was pretty fun.
Did you ever see Richard Lester's Robin and Marian?
Yeah, I did a long, long time ago.
Not bad.
And I remember it being good.
Yeah.
But that's all I remember.
The thing is, many have argued that that part of the Robin Hood legend is bad.
It's put in later as anti-Catholic feeling.
A nun bleeds Robin to death because of the traitorous papacy and so forth.
But bleeding was how they tended to you in those days.
It let some of that bad blood out.
They just let a little too much out from Mr. Hood.
What is that music?
Why, it sounds like Rimsky-Korsakov.
Yes.
The now politically incorrect,
Arabian Nights fantasy.
No, that's from Universal Monsters.
It's colonialist.
Well, it's, I believe it's...
Could it be The Mummy?
The Mummy?
The Mummy has Swan Lake at the beginning, period.
No other movie, music in it.
Like Dracula, it starts with Swan Lake, no other music.
But Swan Lake, yes.
So it's not Rimsky-Korsakov.
I don't know why.
That's from a Universal Monster movie, an early one.
I think it's The Mummy.
They do that when they show the pyramids and so on at the beginning of The Mummy.
No, the titles.
Exactly.
The titles among some miniature pyramids that they rigged up for the titles.
And the Rocko has Swan Lake.
Also, Renfield is heading off over the Borgo Bridge.
And they play it.
But after that, not a note of music in the whole movie.
Now you know it's an hour of slack, because it's going on for another half hour talking
about old Universal Monsters.
Oh, we haven't begun to get started, friends.
I haven't discussed such movies as Earthworm Tractors or Shhh!
The Octopus.
You ever seen Shhh!
The Octopus?
No.
I did see Ticks, though, after last X Day.
You told me about Ticks.
Oh, I told you about Ticks.
Yes, you see marijuana growers in the woods are using too much fertilizer, creating a
giant ticks that attack teenagers, naturally, since everything attacks teenagers.
Hey, there's a band coming.
Let's get out of here, Dr. Howell.
Got it.
I'm going to take this undrunk can of beer and change it into a drunk can of beer.
There you go.
Or maybe I'll be the drunk.
So, until another iteration of the soi-disant hour of slack, we've got a million of gags,
stories, and reminisces about old movies that no one is interested in.
But you never know whether we might strike a spark in such a fashion.
So, somebody else get up here and start a yakkin' and palaverin'.
We need a lot of clabber, and after so many beers, I can't blab such blibber blubber.
My tongue isn't made out of rubber.
Yes, I'll take that one and this one.
Subgenius.com.
That's subgenius.com.
Everything you want to know is there.
But you will have to truly get it.
You will have to truly look.
Thanks for listening and looking.