What the hell do you think you're doing?
Are you ready?
Repent.
Start.
When was the last time you had your hearing checked?
I would advise him to learn to lip read.
Insert earplugs now.
Watch out.
Can't give up, dude.
It's not what I'd like to listen to,
but I don't think I should be able to tell the other people what they can or can't listen to.
Deafness is not only uncool, it's endurable.
I'm sure we're hearing.
Call now and receive a coupon for a free hearing test.
Guaranteed, you won't hear any of this music on Elevator.
It's rock and roll!
Please cut to 11.
11.
I don't suspect a hearing loss, so I thought nothing could be done about it.
Ask your family doctor.
Feel your ears off.
Explode!
This concludes this hearing test.
Thank you.
I'm a real enemy.
Repent.
Don't you want to be saved?
Fight the real enemy.
All the devil needs to have you, mister, but I won't let you.
What I'm asking people to do is accept that everything they face their lives on is a lie.
Oh, God, you mind-seeking salvation.
There are enemies of children's souls.
Oh, Lord.
Michonne!
This world is wickedness!
wieder
inside yourself by yourself!
In the name
of the Jesus, I'm going to go.
No, no, no!
Don't come here.
Fight the real enemy.
Don't you want to be saved?
No, fight the real enemy.
We're all looking in the same direction.
We're not seeing quite the same thing.
You're looking at me
and I'm looking at you.
But we're all going insane.
Don't go this way.
Help!
The mind is good if the heart is free!
Fight the real enemy.
We certainly don't want to preach to people.
Water your fault, God.
To prevent, biblically,
inspire,
child abuse.
Fight the real enemy.
Having a right to life
does not guarantee
having the right
to use
another person's body.
The real enemy's inside all of us.
It's inside of me and you
We've got to come together
to understand what's gonna happen.
Fight the real enemy.
You've gotta believe in yourself.
Fight the real enemy!
It's inside of you!
You gotta fight that enemy inside of you!
You gotta believe in yourself!
Everyone must believe!
Listen to me Mr. Hensel!
This is what I'm talking about!
Fight the real enemy!
Repent!
Hallelujah!
Big Bill T.
Fight the real enemy!
Bill T. Miller!
King of Slack. BillTMiller.com
Bill?
Yes.
I am alive.
although most of the people
appear to confine their
their prefersions to the main river
not a few of them prefer
the American G.I. to the Thames
the LeIIiii
When I don't have my
Where my mouth is stuck
stuck in a black hole
I always listen to the hour of slack
Because it makes me laugh and I like to laugh.
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh.
Oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh-oyeh.
I don't think this microphone is on.
I guess it's not then.
This, this microphone is not on.
Our microphone is not on.
Now it's on.
These were liquid microphones that were originally poured by the first microphone makers back in 1843.
A German company, wasn't it? Schneubert or something?
Schneubert. Otto von Schneubert was the first liquid microphone manufacturer.
He was the first man with a plastic eye when they plastic surgished.
Yes, and apparently Bob's grandfather, I can't remember his name, but the story goes,
it's apocryphal now, but as it goes, Bob's grandfather was investigating the liquid microphones.
Well, he basically ingested some of the liquid.
And it causes a genetic change.
That's the theory that we're working with.
Nobody was ever the same. The whole family, the line was just twisted and turned like a bad road.
Too intense.
Some of the people were actually like less than three foot high at their very tallest.
But it made them so different.
They were left with their hands and making the microphones and pouring them all over.
Made liquid!
I've missed several episodes and I just want to know what Bob is up to now.
Bob's been drinking as usual and you know it.
Can't you just keep your hands out of your pants and her liquid microphone and leave it up to him?
But what's Bob up to now? We know about what he's done then.
We know about 1998.
But I want an update on Bob's activities recently.
What of that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
You know what though, so many people think they want to meet Bob, they want to get with Bob.
They wanna party with Bob.
I just wanna know what he's doing now.
Sorry you fooled by the shame.
What's he doing now?
Oh, they wanna get inside his head, they wanna know...
Because if what Bob...
They wanna do whatever Bob's doing, right?
They wanna wear his lizard skit!
They wanna feel it!
Do you wanna wear Bob's...
Do you wanna smoke of Bob's?
Is that what you want?
Or you're just curious.
You just simply want to know.
I just want to be informed.
Because these are changing times
that we're in in the modern world of tomorrow.
Indeed.
And Bob might have answers or even questions
that we haven't thought of.
You know, the change that I'm most worried about coming
is that change will stop coming.
The coming of the equilibrium.
I'm worried that change will end.
Yes, coming of the equilibrium.
At the ego, beware ye, the equilibrium.
Oh, you don't have to call me ye, just my friends.
And the equivalium.
And you can call me go.
Ye and go.
Go ye.
That means get the hell on out of here.
We don't have ego problems.
Ye are here to go.
No ego problems here.
The brain has been completely smooth.
The convolutions are like a baby's buttocks.
And the liquid microphone, liquid,
really just fills in all the gaps
in between the imidula and bugata
and the brain.
And all the folds.
Yes.
And it's not an alcoholic liquid.
This is what many people think.
It's a suspension.
You can substitute other things.
It's a velvety sort of liquid, isn't it?
It's like your brain synapses themselves
have become a thickened syrup,
a cold, instead of a thin turpentine-like fluid
through which the brain electric signals jump.
It is preferred by the gods.
Across the synapse.
Normally there is this fine, fine elixir,
a thin, hot, fast, fine conductive material.
But then, when one has had enough of Bob,
the word of Bob,
then at that time that liquid,
through which the suspension
in which the electric synapse jump is left,
becomes thickened.
It's like a horse race.
Is it electrically synapsed
but it's going faster than the others
trying to out-fuck you?
It's electrically sensitive liquid.
It's like a pudding in your brain.
It's much like the pudding which we eat.
It slows down your mind
so that you may become more like unto Bob.
It's the drink that the Olympians drink
that made him smarter on fast and everything.
It's the drink the Olympians drink
to make mistakes and get big money from every mistake,
much like Bob.
Much like Bob.
It's a way of changing
the inside of your very head
as well as your pocketbook
and your living room.
Change.
But you know that change could stop coming.
That's what they want.
They want all change to stop.
They want your income to be fixed.
They want you to sit at that same job.
But I want to come some more.
You can no longer come anymore.
As long as you've came before,
now is the time for change.
You must stop and then resume for it to be change.
But Bob comes again and again and again.
And his short change.
No, no.
They will stop him from doing that.
And he is the forbearer of a changeling word.
How can they stop him from doing that?
Well, that is, we don't know.
But that is precisely what would happen
if the changing ever stopped happening.
Is it our job to stop it?
The stopping began.
Or keep the change stopping
or stop the change from keeping.
They move more quickly as they're heated
and we see the big embeds surround this chamber.
It's a vacuum chamber
and the molecules are bouncing hard.
Harder and harder now.
We notice the...
Surrounded by a thin, thin, thin
16mm shell.
The absolute image of the brain of Bob is complete.
I see.
Your wish is granted.
And it's true.
Now you can have changelessness
and change at the same time.
Slack and slacklessness.
Yes, there's no laughter in heaven
as Mark Twain said,
but we're laughing.
This isn't heaven.
You idiot!
This must be hell.
Don't put the change at the screen!
This is not...
Comedy.
I'm getting a little warm now.
Yeah, I am too, man.
I'm confused about what I...
This isn't fun anymore.
What did I do?
Was I alive and I did it?
I know I did...
I can't remember what I did.
This is a memory camp.
No, this is not...
Hey, there's some liquid microphone
dripping out of your nose, man.
All right, you kids.
Stop mixing the mix of Lydian microphones
and sit down in your cots again.
It's not time for your suspension yet.
You know what's going to happen
if you keep fooling around with Bob's brain.
I'll be back in a very, very short period of time.
Is it colloidal?
Just say no and stay on.
Beware colloids.
Say no, honey.
Your eastern name, say no.
Say no.
No, no.
No, I don't want to say no.
Friends, our guest tonight,
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Yes.
And hailing this time from the planet...
The land of fruit and flowers.
Can't you read those notes right, Stang?
The land of fruit and...
Just here.
The land of fruit and flowers
and Hawaiian dancing hula girls.
And also that beautiful...
Heading out towards...
There's that outrugger...
Dugger...
Whatever it is out there.
We're on page seven now.
He's from...
Between...
Zero and Google.
He's beyond zero, man.
He's losing it.
Look, finances...
What number are you from, Mr. Bleepo?
I'm from number 23.
The numbers just get incrementally...
That's a very popular mystical number.
I've had a lot of people say...
I was from number 23 long before...
The integral numbers don't change.
They keep moving up and down.
I can't understand either one of them
when they do that.
It's a part of my...
He came from the land of numbers
to conquer the idea of Bob.
Hey, do you guys remember Captain Beefheart?
Yeah.
enngies.
We gotta speed up.
I'm gonna go to bed already.
I guess we gotta...
The morning was December gray
of the thousandth and tenth day
of the human totem pole.
The man at the bottom was smiling.
It's...
He had just finished his breakfast smiling
It hadn't rained or manured for over two hours
The man at the top was starving
The pole was a horrible looking thing
With all of those eyes and ears
And waving hands for balance
There was no way to get a copter in close
So everybody was starving together
The man at the top had long ago given up
But didn't have nerve enough to climb down
At night the pole would talk to itself
And the chatter wasn't too good
Obviously the pole didn't like itself
It wanted to walk
It was the summer and it was hot
And balance wouldn't prove it
It would admit a skinning to undergarments
It was an integrated pole
It was taking on a reddish brown cast
Exercise on the pole was isometric
Kind of a flex and then balance
Then the eyes would roll together
The ears wiggle, hands balance
There was a gurgling and googling herd
A tenth of the way up the pole
Approaching the pole, the pole was moving
The gurgling was a small child
With Statue of Liberty doll
There was no word of what can happen
If the positioniot said
It's redneck screech
Nauru
Headbanging
Go away
To the
Dove
ufen
Tengность
Go
To the
Hong Kong
Ab Dot
Here's Bob.
Ow!
Notice Cleveland.
You're all only granted one wish.
So what do you wish for?
You must tell me now.
I really like it.
Dragon, I want my home and my village restored.
No more monsters.
And bring back peace to us.
I see.
Your wish is granted.
The Naughty Bit
Sir, hadn't you better buckle up?
Of course.
Buckle this!
Yeah, buckle this, punk!
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Slap.
We're not so swift for Bush campaign.
And we're going to just make sure that people in your area are going to vote this November.
For George Bush and Dick Cheney.
Can we activate the chips now?
All their fluids have been taken out and stored in these containers here.
I think the listeners are ready for the chips to be activated now.
Those are the squeakiest chips I've ever heard.
Once they start bouncing a little bit, the timing may not be quite right at this moment.
Were those the chips that were squeaking?
Self-sacred.
No, those are the same ones we're just wearing.
They're vibrating to see if they're matriculating at the right rate.
Some of them go faster.
Squeaky was involved in that matriculation, I believe.
Squeaky?
Originally, yeah.
Oh, of course.
Captain Bee Fart was into that.
Was one of the Mansonites?
He was a blind man, wasn't he?
No, he has a van, fly, fly, fly man.
But he could see where others could not.
He was horoscopically blind, however, though.
He had another eye, a third eye, that he was sitting on most of the time.
Hey.
His pineal gland.
In the back.
A vestigial third eye.
His pineal gland.
Captain Bee Fart's pineal gland was unusually located at his coccyx.
Coccyx, coccyx, coccyx.
And to in order to fix.
But he could see in a way that no other eye could see and he could bring it out in a way
that no ear had ever heard, such as that song we played earlier, the thousand and tenth
day of the human totem pole.
Hmm.
Poof.
Such an inspiring song.
I wrote a short story about that recently called The Man Who Could Neither Crap Nor
Get Off of the Pot.
And you know this man as Steve Davilaqua.
He is still there.
That man is still.
Trying vain gain.
Straining.
Vain gain.
And straining.
But nothing will come.
And when he gives up and it's just as he is about to leave the chem can at the great relief
of all the long thousand blind people.
Outside.
Suddenly he knows he's ready to go again.
And he slams the door shut and locks it and they all grumble and he sweats and strains
but it does not come.
Ping pong.
For half an hour and he knows he can hear him out there making fun of him.
Sounds like someone dropped a damn penny in the commode.
Making horrible comments and hating him.
They come up behind the tidy, the chem can and urinate against the back of it and he
can hear the drumming of that.
He can feel it on his hands, man.
That urine that's frustrated.
And he wants to get off.
He wants to leave.
He wants to finish.
He wants to go.
But keep urinating on his hands.
He knows they're all waiting.
He is making a noble effort.
But the more he tries the less, the more reluctant his little brown children are to leave the
nest so to speak.
Yes.
They're like that when they're that age though.
And then how can you blame them?
They don't want to get the hell out of there.
You know when you look down inside the bottom of that chem can.
Oh we try not to lick down there.
Dang I know there are different.
His children.
The children of those who came before.
Some of them like black dairy queen curly Q laid in a huge pile.
Horrible with Coke cans that you know are going to wreck that honey wagons hose when
you come to clean it out.
Friends are you like the man stuck in that chem can?
Are you like the honey dipper coming around to clean up the mess?
With a line of a thousand complaining burners.
Trying and trying.
Complaining outside.
Strangely.
And then you try to make.
The more you try to make.
White knuckle grinding.
The less results you have to show for it.
My desire.
That's where Bob comes in friend.
That's where Bob comes in.
Bob can help the pea shot.
He can put his long smooth hand on the top of your tiny little skull and rub it until
you're fine again.
Bob has sat on the toilet of the man with spastic bowel.
Irritable bowel.
Spastic colon.
Bob has sat on the toilet of the man with spastic bowel.
Bob has been in the pants of that man.
Bob knows.
He knows your pain.
He's worn his diaper.
He knows your pants.
He can't feel your pain.
Yeah.
But he knows it.
And he knows that you'll pay anything.
He feels your pants.
To get rid of it.
From the inside.
He is.
It's like he is your pants.
Is that what that is?
He's your depends.
That's what Bob is friend.
He is that.
That diaper.
That's what.
That catches.
That depels.
That depels on Bob.
You're laced.
To stop my.
It's all coming together for me now.
From becoming enormous.
It's not a waste after all.
From making the moisture.
Moisture come on down on like the rain that's falling on my thing there.
Bob loves you my friend.
If he could he'd help wipe you up.
He'll help you up.
He would lock you up?
He will wipe you up.
He'll help you.
He'll take clean you.
Bob will.
Bob will cleanse you.
He's the moisture.
He's like the little handy wipe.
He is the handy wipe.
He's not only your pants outside but he's the handy wipe.
Bob is like.
You know everything else.
The other religions are just the rough toilet paper.
Bob is like that medicated diapy wipe.
That.
That reminds you of babies and children.
A medicated diapy wipe for adults.
That's Bob.
Tom.
Now don't get.
Ginger is crying again.
I'm about to slap her upside the head.
What can I do?
Well perhaps these might help.
What the hell are those things?
I can't even pick them up.
They're glowing.
Bob.
Tom.
The dispenser doesn't work unless you give your money to Bob.
I'm sorry but if you pledge five dollars you'll see right now that will open up and you'll
be able to use the moist wipes.
That's right.
But only if you commit.
If you make that commitment of faith.
That's right.
Colloquial eyeballs.
And the more you commit yourself to faith.
This is a magic dispenser.
It is magic.
That can be yours.
As well as a magic dispenser.
As well as many other things.
Real and imaginary.
Wow.
I prefer the imaginary things but hey they're free to do with what they want with it.
And if you order now you get this beautiful operation on the computer of nine by twelve
rugs so call today.
What does this man have to say?
You're wearing a mask.
I'll explain the mask later Mr. Jackson.
For those who believe in Bob no explanation is necessary.
For those who do not believe in Bob no explanation is possible.
Hail Bob.
It's so true Bob.
Well done Bob.
Howdy.
I'm Edelmeister and I'm a pagan.
The capital P.
Now with a small casket.
Enjoy your little nap.
I'm off to the warm embrace of my afternoon enema.
Now listen C I see you hanging around this schoolyard for far too long and you and that
dame over there C now listen up here.
Come on over here.
I want to talk to you.
Talking to me?
Yeah I'm talking to you.
Hey are you talking to me?
Yeah listen here.
Try and square up with me.
Talking to me?
You're going to have to do some talking first see.
Now listen look now what have you been doing over here?
I don't like the cut of your fedora.
I don't like the cut of yours neither, but that ain't the point.
The point is, what are you doing here?
Well, listen, pal, this suit suits belongs to someone else.
Yeah, it looks pretty sharp.
That's someone else's bob.
And I don't know what Titler and Hojo would have to say about that.
What are you doing out of uniform, Squeaky?
Here comes Titler and Hojo right now.
And the evil foul musselina.
Oh, my God, just monstrous.
Titler is huge, bouncing and writhing.
And Hojo is as much as 5,000 feet tall.
Genetically mutated 5,000 times.
Look at the mammaries.
They're enough to kill whole continents.
And this is how they had planned to smother Europe?
With a motherly bosom of Titler and the strange drinks of Hojo?
Oh, my God, and this is our alternative to Bush?
Oh, my God.
Now, listen, I ain't going to die.
I'm going to go and fight.
I don't know about you guys.
I don't know about you and your small shirt, your big zoot pants,
but I'm going over there and fight Titler and Hojo.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm going to go there, too, because we're both on the same side, pal.
We're on the side of the...
Bob, you understand?
All right, well, put it there, then, someplace.
Yeah, we're...
Help me, you boys!
For crying out loud, get it out of...
Hey, yeah.
Yeah, Bob!
It's a problem.
Bob depends.
Get your thing out of there.
Yeah, don't think about your depends.
Think about this dame in trouble.
Yeah, we depend on this dame in trouble.
Yeah, the dame.
Without the dames, then we're nothing, pal.
Yeah, that's right.
And if Titler and Hojo get a hold of them dames,
see, there ain't going to be no dames left.
And there'll be, like, those cows over there.
They won't have any more milk to give.
The population will die out.
You need dames for the whole population,
because, well, you know, they're all part of it.
They're half the...
They're all part of it.
Half the world.
They held up half the sky, as Yoko Ono said.
Oh, they hide it right out in the open.
Sounds like there's Stalin in Russia right now
on the eastern and western...
Yeah, but...
Yeah, I'm sure.
Just because Yoko comes from over there
doesn't mean she's wrong.
Doesn't mean she's right, either.
Check her out.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Let's look in here.
Joe McCarb, Trouble.
Trouble for the Information Committee.
Trouble?
It's been a capital T.
The House of American Activity.
That rhymes with T.
It says Yoko Ransom T.
That's the name...
That's the end of this station
that we start out this show from.
Oh, jeez, I'm looking for Yoko Ransom T.
That's how it ends.
WCSB.
Understand?
B.
B is for bleepo, too.
Don't make any mistake.
And they're the monkeys that are here right now,
right here, before you.
And after them.
Without the other barrel.
And the other monkeys you're talking about.
Well, whose turn in the barrel is it, anyway?
It's not my turn.
I've still got the red pen on,
and I'm gonna wear it proudly.
Listen here, I'm a worker.
See?
My dad was a worker,
and my mom was a worker.
This carnival is working well before I get there.
As long as we can think.
As long as we got our brains, we can think.
Oh, they'll get that too short, you'll see.
But, but, but, but, but, but.
It's a B.
Mamma mia, that's a spicy meatball.
You never knew me.
There always was something big about her.
It'll be great.
Be one of the few.
Proud.
But, but, but, but, but.
B.
Over men prefer beheading another B word.
You know, the heading.
are conspiracy. I think not.
I think if...
Nah, forget that game.
Hey, have you guys been to the circus lately?
I've got this great circus song.
No.
I love the circus.
Have you ever seen the flying guy?
By this...
Okay, this band boiled in...
Gargantians, the carcass canis...
This here, this here band boiled in lead.
That's the name of the band.
Can you believe a band would have a name like this?
I think I just saw what you do for fun, man.
It's a real thing.
We saw these guys called Thelonious Bach at Starwood, and they also...
I think I just saw what you do for fun, man.
They also have played under this name of boiled lead and...
I hate rings, they're jumping monkeys
When a fat lady sings
It just ain't funky
Nothing is real, nothing is sense
Life is a drag underneath the tent
Fuck the circus!
I said God is the ringmaster, Satan is her clown
Everything is getting better
Nothing is real, nothing is sense
Life is a drag underneath the tent
Fuck the circus!
The silly train's bill
The clown's in the room
And the poor wife's free
The trick's for me
Let's talk, let's service, let's talk
Let's talk, man is it?
The big shot's a fraud
Fuck the circus!
Why?
Trust me and believe me
Set aside
I'm going
Today
Occupation, please.
A libertine and a seducer.
Sex fiend.
Oh, yes.
Pure and simple.
A libertine and a seducer.
State your address, please.
Paradise.
Paradise?
I can well understand that.
The first night's the toughest.
No doubt about it.
They march you in naked as the day you were born.
Skin burning and half blind from that delousing shit they throw on you.
And when they put you in that cell,
and those bars slam home,
that's when you know it's for real.
Old life blown away in the blink of an eye.
Nothing left but all the time in the world to think about it.
Questionable.
Ejaculation.
Unemotionally.
That's kind of funny, too.
Oh.
I'm a brain dysfunction.
Yeah.
Bizarre.
I'm that kind of a guy.
Minimal.
Minimal dysfunction of the brain.
Speaking of crapping or getting off the pot,
King Jehoram, the grandson of Asa, does not meet with God's approval.
God strikes him with an intestinal disease that takes two years to kill him,
causing his bowels to slide out of his body little by little.
He died in great agony.
The Bible notes,
with no one's regret.
2 Chronicles 21, 18, 20.
Would you prefer this world, my friend,
or would you prefer the world of Bob,
where your intestines are slid neatly as a coconut cream pie
back into your intestinal cavity,
reformed in the way that you desire,
with your most ultimate, ultimate point of view,
punta de vista, as you used to say,
and your own articulate garden hanging off the front of your abdomen?
Which is it, friend?
If you want to, you can have your intestines put
into the shape of the Aztec, what is that?
Teotihuacan.
Yeah, the calendar.
You're not supposed to say that on the radio.
It ends in 2012.
Yeah.
Yes, the Mayan calendar.
The Mayan calendar.
You can have your intestines actually put in the shape
and the exact design of that Mayan calendar.
There's enough intestinal fortitude, as it were,
to do that because of the length of the intestines.
And Bob's pipe can actually guide these intestines into the shape,
which is most advantageous.
It can actually guide the intestines through your skin
without actually operating.
These are called operations without operations.
These are performed with Bob's healing pipe
and his healing surgical-handed glove.
So that's just one of the things that Bob has been up to lately.
Bob has been up to a lot.
Yes, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
What on your end of the spectrum is your analysis of Bob's activities?
Well, Bob has been involved in, uh,
investments.
Investments?
What kind of investments?
Long-term investments.
The finest.
The finest long-term investments.
Of course, he can only have the finest.
Of course.
And it's, uh, I'm sorry.
Bob, in my opinion,
Yes?
I humble
Humble indeed.
I will be to learn opinions.
And do we not all have opinions?
Yes, they are like the anus.
Everyone has one.
Oh, I see.
I couldn't live without one.
Oh, given keeping that in mind,
Ah, Lord, I'd love to try, though.
That having been said,
Yes, that having been said,
In my opinion,
I'll strictly, uh,
Prove my, uh,
In my opinion,
Yes, yes, of course.
Bob himself,
Who's Bob?
Oh, yes, Bob.
The Bob in question.
As opposed to, say, Corny, or the sex
Female, yes.
The sex Corny,
Not in this club, dammit.
Not for long, long, never.
As opposed to Yeti A, or Yeti B,
No, not them yetis in this club, that's what I say.
Or Pink Boy A,
No, no, damn Pink Boy, never, never, never, never.
Or Pink Boy B.
And turn them upside down the royal knife.
Right.
In my view, Bob should just throw in the towel and give up,
Because they're not going to get,
Bob, stop, I tell you, man, you can't.
They're not going to get, uh, slack.
Teach slaves to be subject to their masters and everything,
To try to please them not to talk back to them,
So that in every way,
They will make the teaching about Bob, our savior, attractive.
Our savior.
He was also worker's savior.
Many people do not understand,
Bob was not savior in strict way of a Euro-Christian,
He was actually savior of working man.
We only work four days a week when Bob take home.
Yeah, yeah, I know, that is, that is fake.
Bob,
Bob was not only gave education to everybody,
He also redistributes the land to,
Especially on the space vessels,
Everyone had their own little chunk of pie.
Yes, yes, I know, I do not.
It looked more like a dead potato,
But was a good chunk of pie.
We working for Bob, he gives you cigarette break.
Yeah, Bob, that's what she did for a while.
She would sit back and just,
How long we been loading this dog?
To everything without complaining,
Or arguing,
In order that I may boast on the day of Bob,
That I did not run or labor for nothing.
Did I run or labor for nothing?
I do not think so.
Well, you ran away when you went into labor,
Just like your great-grandmother, Jinka, did.
And that's why we had to pull your pants down,
And put your socks and your bowels back,
The way Bob wanted them,
And the way you planned it,
When you said you would take that X-vessel.
If Bob had not been there,
Our preaching is useless,
And so is our faith.
You signed the application.
A mental case.
Without Bob, it's useless, really.
It's just...
Pointless.
Not much point, no.
Slacklessness, as far as...
I've got this boat, this damn boat,
And the star ideas,
And the stars to cruise, or whatever,
Navigate out, you know.
Oh, the centuries!
The millennia of evolution,
Crawling up,
Natural selection,
Killing off thousands,
For every one that managed to get
A tiny bit of slack.
And what has it all brought us to?
Where do we find ourselves today?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Everybody says,
We've come such a long, long way,
We're civilized,
Isn't that nice?
We've gotten so smart,
We know how to build a whole world upon,
When it comes to the simple things,
Like living together,
Ha!
Why'd we have to come all this way?
Is anything easier to understand?
Our life is better than we ever planned,
Ha!
We're civilized,
We know better,
Is anything more to say to God?
Stop wasting all my time,
Why'd we have to come all this way?
We couldn't quit while we were ahead
Why'd it have to end up like this?
We should've just stayed at the stand
The road was long and the journey was hard
That we're even dreaming that we've come so far
We swing on my dime
Why'd we have to come all this way?
Did it have to end up like this?
But, but, but, but, but, but
Listen up, you have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right at this time to talk to a Bob.
Why did you let a turtle man in say I want to fight?
You said you wanted to meet him.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean I want to fight him.
Hey, that's enough. Don't argue.
I suggest we split right down the middle if that's alright with you.
Not me.
If you want to.
Phew.
It's gone!
God, no!
Oh, yes.
Oingo Boingo did that song, Why'd We Have to Come All This Way.
The collages in the whole show are mostly by the great Mr. Fernando Nande Lemur.
And if you want to know more about that band Boiled in Lead, the circus song,
check out www.omnium.com.
O-M-N-I-U-M dot com.
The music in the live Hour of Slack segment recorded at WCSB in Cleveland,
which is coming up, is by Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Pastor, could you touch upon a little bit, what's it mean to twist my own mind?
I can become to be a family man. I need to know that Jesus can do these things.
And the results are thicker, greener lawns.
Huh?
Digital copy of a digital copy of a digital copy.
Thicker, greener hair.
Does that hurt?
Do.
More beautiful, illiquid sinuses that resemble this liquid microphone here.
Liquid microphone.
A new thought.
A new idea.
A new age is coming with liquid microphones.
It reads your senses.
It feels your moods.
It absorbs everything at once.
You don't have to talk for liquid microphone to convey your message.
It amplifies your thoughts in five different ways.
Number one.
This.
Number two.
That.
And number three.
Baaaaa.
The other numbers are identical.
But.
The cynical monogram on your forehead.
I see what you're trying to do.
You're trying to turn people's heads inside.
Inside out.
Turning the head inside out.
Been there, done that.
Well, it can be easily slipped inside out.
But look, there's a head laying right in front of us that needs to be opened and examined.
And no one wants to look inside.
Well, it needs to open and examine itself, you know, and that's the problem.
So few can do it.
Hardly anybody wants to.
After you've done it, you never ever want to do it again.
But it's like a parachute.
If it's not open, it won't work.
Despite what you may have learned in Sunday school, David did not kill Goliath with a stone.
The messy truth is that David only knocked Goliath unconscious and stoned him.
No, he killed him with Goliath's own sword and then hacked off his head and stoned him.
And turned it inside out.
Hey, man.
They didn't just cut that head off.
They didn't, man.
They did not just cut off his head, dude.
That's like a wild man.
Check that out, man.
They did not just, like, leave it at cutting the head off and walking away, dude.
I mean, take a look at that thing.
They launched it, man.
They launched it.
I'm telling you, man.
They launched the damn head, dude.
Dude, where's my head?
They say it's still going, man.
Parts of Galilee, you can still see it flying by and stuff.
And lower Simon eyes and whatever, dude.
I don't know.
They have some...
Who was Simon and why did he eyes?
Because he was shinier than the rest of the kids.
You know, you can only have sis done so many times and then you have to eyes.
Unless you have bladder problems.
And certainly all of those people do.
See them down there trying to swim their way out of trouble?
See them trying to shoot their way out of a paper bag?
Swimming.
Yeah.
Swimming in their own suffering.
Where do they all come from?
Spike stuck in there.
Wallets.
Stuck in their wallets.
Pinning their wallets to their behinds, friend.
As if you got a ten-foot spike piking your wallet into your butt.
Are you staked to that job that way, my friend?
Are you handcuffed?
Are you handcuffed via your wristwatch to that paycheck?
Are you trying to serve two masters?
You can't do it.
Are you trying to juggle a million oranges and make out with that pretty girl at the
same time?
You can't do it.
So why don't you just give up?
Give up.
Forget about it, man.
Just get some...
Multiplier.
You've got to pull back and step away.
Just withdraw.
Just disconnect.
Wait, did I just kind of...
That's it, man.
Bob teaches disconnection, man.
You've just got to break things.
Hope I liked your looking down jokes.
You're gonna break your mind, you're gonna crack it.
You must be like there Bodhisattva.
You must smash the mind for the mind to flourish.
You must crack your skull for your brain to heal.
We're making an omelet, we're breaking eggs.
Get with the program.
Well, cute.
And come on!
We're killing two birds with one stone, man.
We're wiping out whole communities with one stone.
We're putting all our eggs in one basket.
We're making, we are successfully now manufacturing silk purses.
Perhaps in your own town, we're making them everywhere.
We're making silk purses out of sow's ears,
and we're turning pigs into little bunny rabbits with third eyes the size.
Well, we're doing it, friends.
How big is Reverend Ivan's stand?
You can get something for nothing, and it's only $30.
Nothing.
If you just go to subgenius.com right now.
Subgenius.com.
But beware.
Be very careful.
Because as you get closer and closer to the circle, to Bob's orbit,
you are, by scientific nature, pulled ever closer by the four seas of gravitas.
You are pulled in.
As if by magic.
Closer and closer to that looming face.
The grinning dots.
The filthy, stinking pipe.
Have you ever noticed that buildup of crud around that pipe stem near his lips?
What is that stuff?
Is that congealed spit?
Or dog's lip cell?
Dead skin?
Grot?
What is it?
And how does the pipe just hover against his clenched, shut teeth?
He's not closing it.
He's not closing his teeth on that pipe.
The pipe is jutting as if by magic.
Exactly.
From closed teeth.
It's the tar.
We've mined that tar.
And now you can too.
Is it a trick?
No, no, no.
It's the Supernatural.
It's a beautiful product.
We've successfully mined this and made it into really the basic component for all of our products.
Right.
It is a genuine article of faith of the Church of the Subgenius.
And it comes in this attractive little bottle right here.
And how much is that amazing article of faith?
$30.
Only $30?
I can't believe that.
This is blasphemy.
Don't you know that is the talent of Bob's lips that keeps the pipe attached?
It has nothing to do with any kind of artificial product.
You don't question these things, friends.
It's supernatural.
It's magic.
Actually, it is alien science.
But to you, it will always appear as magic because you are mired in this dense earth plane.
Stuck.
In the quicksand of these sad three or four dimensions.
Milling about on your little leg things.
And in your little cars.
Oh, you could follow Bob out into such a grander, more open world.
A new universe.
All yours.
Inside.
And all inside your own little noggin.
Isn't that wonderful?
Bob has enabled you to bell your own cat that is your head.
You can hear it coming, friends.
The bad thoughts won't be able to sneak up on you anymore after what we do to you.
Oh, man, I can't focus anymore, man.
He keeps slamming into this.
My head.
I had another bad thought.
You can tell whether you're coming or going.
Yeah, yeah, man.
I know whether I'm coming or going.
I had another bad thought, man.
You don't know exactly what you think.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
I don't know exactly what I'm thinking when I'm thinking it, man.
That's why.
Not so fast.
You've got to pay.
To know.
And you must pay lots and lots of slow money.
Slow money.
Slow money is accepted by the Church of the Sub-G.
Just as dark matter comprises most of the universe, so slow money comprises our bank
account of the Church of the Sub-G.
Truer words were never spoken, unfortunately.
Although that could change, actually, if you happen to look at my phone, it's still
here.
This is the end of my talk.
I'll see you in the next one.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Do not remember the sins of omission which we have omitted from the earliest Drax brothers
And we see here this perfunctory on the bottom of its glass
Bob's face as we know it now
The universe must squirt in order for us to survive
And that's why we
To fulfill its very destiny
It must squirt
Then my brain let go of it
And we look at these older pictures of Bob in his early stages of squirting
His teeth were quite dense in those days
He had strong forehead muscles
And he was quite a little squirt
Oh Bob might as well be the squirt
The squirt essence
To maintain the equilibrium the squirts must continue
The squirts must need scum
Equilibrium must stop now
There must be a balance of no balance
It's between the match that there must be
It's the end of equilibrium
Things must change
It's a balance
It's a balance of unbalanced forces
And you're expected to join like the lemming you are
The exact science of random chaos
Just how much universal squirt do you think it can take?
Thirty dollars worth
More than you think
How much universal squirt do you get for thirty bucks these days, Dr. Sinister?
Oh wait, Dr. Sinister's not on the air yet
But he will be on soon in this time continuum
Perhaps he'll answer the question now
I forgot what the question was
You can get approximately one metric load of squirt for thirty international galactic credits
How many?
How much?
For thirty intergalactic credits, I'm sorry, you can get exactly one metric load of squirt
Ah, to share the load
Oh, share the load
You can use that one metric load
Master Frodo
Over and over and over again
Master Bobo
And it also causes a foreshortening of the board
I don't know about as much as the same way in the early prescriptions
You squirt, you ingest, you squirt, you ingest
And it allows you to squirt the same squirt
There's no
That's the loop, that's the loop, that's the loop
Look, mine's become oblique
And I need some sort of random punishment or help or something
Well, it's the loop of life
Oh speaking of random cripes
Share the load, share the load, the load, the load
Speaking of random punishment, there's a devival
Devival?
There's a devival in Detroit
Detroit
There's also September 4th
It's at Alvin's, that's it, Alvin's in Detroit
There is some kind of a devival
The amino acids are not necessarily on the bill
But Reverend Angry Larry will be preaching
And Reverend Senator Speck will be there
And I think all of my listeners know what that could really mean
In fact, I should take off this Joe Secretary on the phone
We and I will play at the Beachland on the 17th
Oh, that's right
In front of Ten Huey, probably about three bands in the beginning
But no, Ten Huey will be at September 17th
At the Beachland Ballroom
And?
And Lonesome Cal-men-dave?
And Mondo's Retardo Band
Wow
With the Wii and Mondo's Retardo Band
That's like what it is
Is it Mondo's Retardo Band now?
It thinks it is
That's a pretty good one, isn't it?
That's a pretty good name
That's a pretty good band name
And we had, it's it, that should keep you off the radio out of any
Right, and out of trouble
Out of any kind of money
Any stern discipline which we need
It must be administered
House Chief Administrator for the hospital here
I'd like to thank all the LPNs and RPNs and ZPNs that have gathered about in Bob's head here
And if they'd given us all our support this past coming year
And also the members of the Steering Committee are still on the, still on the line
I'm a little scared on the bottom of the ship, and you know
You know, the only devivals that I'm invited to
I'm not invited to any of the cool ones
I'm invited to, there's one in London, in Amsterdam
Oh cool
And there's one from Annenberg
In Amsterdam
And we're gonna have so many cool ones
In November
Yeah I know
Paris sucks
I know, actually it's quite cold in November
Rome sucks
It's the third annual Fracht Cup is happening in Amsterdam
And this time it looks like we're gonna be able to go and be helped judge
Because we have a couple of people here
the new crop of frappy.
This is not the,
we're not using code words
for common street drugs
like marijuana.
This is habifrop ziplops
we're talking about.
It's a subgenius thing,
totally different.
But the, you know,
it's kind of a fun
party time there anyway.
It's in the pot
from the crop.
Where can people
get information
on this, Reverend Stang?
It's a little bit
of something
just called Tom.
Of course,
the subgenius website.
It's a little bit
of something
just called Tom.
It's a little bit
It's here
in this rough cave
near the artichoke
of Norway
where the fjords
are so deep
that the polar bears
and seals
actually die
from lack of nitrogen
in their hair.
But here we see
the chief seal
marking the doorway
with several spindles
of, well,
these were the spindles
that were originally used
to spin
the very first
doctor band record
which were made
on wax tablets.
It's a strange way
for a seal
to mark its territory.
It was the wax seal,
actually,
and the wax seals
that the wax seals used
were actually made of wax
and were some
of the earliest known
sound recordings
of the first yeti
doctor bands.
Those were the first seals,
but when the seventh seal
is opened
and disemboweled
on that day,
we shall know
that Bob has finally
left the chem camp.
And he has finished
his task
set before him.
The trick is
you need an opener
to break the seal
and only Bob
has the opener.
Bob can work
with any kind of
port-a-potty
that you may have
laying around.
You don't need
the actual old ones,
the Johnny Reds
or the Johnny Blues.
You don't need those for that.
You know,
the modern kind of conveyance
you're going to need
to get out there
past the ionosphere,
is it?
Is it the ionosphere?
The ectosphere.
The ectoplasm is there.
The ectosphere,
the lactosphere.
The arachnosphere.
The morphosphere.
And the morphosphere.
There's a lot of spheres.
Okay, so you've got
all these different...
You've got to get through
all those layers.
Hey, hey, hey,
enough of the science.
Okay, science lesson
is over.
The hour of slack
is coming to its end.
And the...
Ah, you morbid
shite, yeah.
The sad, sad, sad end.
Actually, there's...
I'm sure there's
some sort of
good talk
or good music
coming up.
This is the amino acids
in the background.
But I got that
at Otakual.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
And we thank
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy
for flying in
all the way
from Manhattan.
It's hard to thank you.
I don't want to be
a cynical bird,
but I am.
I'm a freaking bird.
You're a bad boy.
Maybe you're just too slow.
No, I'm not slow.
I hear everything
you say.
No, I'm not.
I hear everything
you say and the other guys say.
I'm not slow.
And I hear it again
in the radio.
I hear it again in the radio.
It's the best of all time.
Bob!
Are you hurt?
Hi.
You faker.
Steve, you know
what this is, don't you?
It's a time-space warp.
I'm not sure
I know exactly
what that is.
I don't suppose
anybody really does.
We've seen some
strange things tonight.
Strange creatures that we know
don't belong on our planet.
God only knows
where they came from.
Jenny and Beth.
The vortex took them.
Just...
Just took them away.
The...
The final...
Do you have a bathroom problem in your house?
It's a very busy place, isn't it?
Where everyone in the family has to brush their teeth, wash their hands...
Take a shit...
Let's get some hot chicks on the phone and talk about Mars or something.
Why don't you get off the phone because our phone lines are pretty much clogged up on
your dumb ass.
I'm a worker, a generator, appointed to work.
If you need help, call an ambulance or someone from your neighborhood.
There you go.
There's a pigeon.
Videotaped the whole thing.
Well, come on.
There's got to be some redheads out there.
Real redheads.
We interrupt to bring you an important announcement.
The world will end at 12 o'clock tonight.
I'll just repeat that.
The world will end at 12 o'clock.
This is not a hoax.
World leaders have been meeting in Washington over the past week
to consider the ever-worsening problems of inflation, overpopulation, racism, pollution.
You name it, they've considered it.
They have come to the conclusion there is no point in going on.
Friends, you're listening to...
This is the end of...