Usually radio announcements merely recommend a product, but this station provides its clients with a special service.
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
In the radio studios of Bob, the technicians, the entertainers, the commentators, the administrative personnel,
daily unite their efforts in the creation of programs to please and entertain a vast radio public.
Ah!
The wide variety of broadcasts include group discussions, political speeches, and comedy.
On this program, frank opinions are expressed in response to their leaders' questioning.
Questions of the day are discussed and opinions and attitudes freely expressed on issues of the moment.
For there is keen interest in a radio program that invites personal participation by the public.
This is independent radio in a democracy.
Hour of Swag.
Ah!
Bob?
Your society is secretly affiliated with Bob.
That is too ridiculous to brand as a lie.
Then you wouldn't know a man named Bob.
I have never heard of him.
You won't get away with this, Flatfoot. I'm a law-abiding citizen.
Get that? He's a law-abiding citizen.
Are you, Ratzler?
Bob?
I'd strip him.
I don't need dough that bad.
Bob?
When a man has lived like Bob for so long, he's not like ordinary men.
He acts differently and he thinks differently.
What do you mean?
I mean that when a man has lived like Bob for so long, he's like ordinary men.
Especially when you really know him.
Well, there's a big light shining in the coconut grove where Satan used to watch the Barney Miller show.
Syndicated television puts him in the mood, hoping a pagoda just might get nude.
Satan gets an erection staring at a pagoda's butt.
Meat and poultry by the pack, extra servings bring them back.
Ain't no need to raise a fuss, just yodel your way to that flaky crust.
Say wait a minute, I want to be good!
That Catherine Neville fight was à la 해 ,
that проц lead to this hell.
It was all an act of wussing.
She is devilish.
She's being a tv genuine.
Saint is just as crazy.
She is dinner, I am pretty cold.
She is hot Women.
Sammy Davis Jr. used to worship Satan
When he wasn't taking drugs
Staring in the mirror while his eyeball twitched around
Let's watch Sammy's eyeball twitch!
The Rudy Schwartz Project, dear friends, yodeling Satan
And we've been surrounded this show by some collages by Fernanda Nandeli-Murr
And a lot more of those coming up, also some by Artemia Salina
In fact, friends, I was trapped at the radio station
Chaz couldn't do his show
And I was stuck there myself to do a remix of collages by Artemia Salina
Puzzling Evidence, Reverend Charto, New Monet, me, Reverend Cobblestone
And I was trapped at the radio station
And The Bishop, who also did our very opening collage
All of this stuff mixed together by DJ Stang with some background music
I think some of it is from the Matrix soundtrack
But now, but now, my friends, some more Fernanda Nandeli-Murr
It's gone!
Come on, Noah!
Pastor, could you touch upon a little bit, uh, what's it mean to twist my own mind?
They can become to be a family man
They need to know that Jesus can do these things
And the results are thicker greener lawns
Hello?
Bob, I want to talk to you on a trick
Oh, Bob, you've got to listen to me
a trick. Whatever it is, it's a trick. Oh Bob, you've got to listen to me. It is a
trick. A flying saucer? Whatever it is, it's no use. So run along. I just wondered
if you were going to be busy at two o'clock. Shut up.
Yes? Shut up. Hello? Bob, I want to talk to you. Okay. Oh Bob, you look like a petty
thief. Oh shut up. Is it his fault that he has no education? Yes. Yes? Oh yes. Shut up.
Okay, anything you say. No, no he won't. It was either shut up or what? So what? What's
up? Get a load of that. Oh I'm sorry Bob. I spanked her. Yeah, thanks. Look at Fanny.
Okay. I know. Naughty naughty. Remember Fanny? We saw what appeared to be a flying saucer.
Well, so what? Bob. What?
Yes, but how'd you get all those bandages?
These ethnic people, if you've seen one, you've seen them all. But many kids in the 1950s
and 1960s laugh at the cultures.
This is where the mating takes place. And people in these kinds of situations have very
unrealistic expectations. It's a tingling sensation.
Uh, yes. It's so rare that I end up engineering here in the beautiful live studios. People
think, you know, that old Reverend Stang is always ensconced up in his ivory tower with
my hot looking client wife and my endless supply of Malaysian frog sticks. But you know,
I don't, it's, uh, trying to do this show, this church, this X day, this world, this
reality, this life is like, well, you know those cartoons where there's a river full
of just cut logs floating from the tree farm down the river to the lumber factory. And
there's all these lumberjack guys leaping nimbly from rotating slippery log to log,
nudging the logs around with their long hooked poles. And usually there's some hapless cartoonist,
a cartoon character desperately trying to navigate the, the logs to get across the river
to escape some foe. Well, I'm like that guy skipping from a treacherous log to treacherous
log across the river as they speed downstream friends. Only I'm not carrying one of those
hooked poles. I'm juggling razor sharp, scimitars and fired up chainsaws three of each. And
while I'm juggling those and leaping from log to log before they spin out from under
my foot and it capsized me.
I've also got this seven foot long pole balancing between the logs and the tree farm. I'm just
balanced on the end of my nose.
And at the very top of the pole,
I've got balanced a big stack
of the fanciest Chinaware plates imaginable,
all decorated with gorgeous hand-painted
floral patterns and Dobbs heads.
And there's a bad, nasty monkey
sitting on top of the plates.
And there's an itch right between my shoulder blades
that just won't go away.
And my nose is running.
And I'm about to sneeze.
I have to sneeze.
My pipe's in my pocket with a fresh plug in it,
but my lighter is in the other pocket.
But it beats working, friends.
And what's really sick is that I kind of like it that way.
But, but, but, every now and then, friends, we escape.
Yes, we get away from it all,
and we just got back from extinction.
X-Day, X-Day drill in Sherman, New York.
Sorry to say, we got back.
We're still on Earth.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry that Bob let us down again.
Our guru, Bob, who prophesied that the world would end
July 5th, 1998.
We were kind of hoping that maybe this time
it would actually be 1998.
But just between you and me,
I really thought it probably wouldn't happen.
I mean, it's been like how many,
how many,
prophesied ends of the world.
And it's just like X-Day number six.
This was the eighth drill I've been to.
But friends, you know, when the world is about to end,
or when you think the world is about to end,
you'll do stuff you wouldn't normally do.
And such as putting yourself up on the slave block
at the subgenius church flesh auction,
where these rather over-eager ministers and flock
and shenanigans,
you know, those who are about to be shorn,
the easily fleeced and those shepherds of them,
all whore themselves, basically.
But I guess it's for a good cause.
It's to raise money for a guy who's already rich.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
A guy that we've never seen.
A guy nobody ever sees.
But that makes them more important, you know,
when they're mysterious like that.
You'll follow them just about any.
The more mysterious, the better, I guess.
Look at the success of most of our politicians.
They're not even real, as far as you know.
It was a worthy...
Well, you know, it's going to be another year, I guess.
You know, when the baptism pool doesn't overflow,
that means it's going to be another year of bill paying
and hell and so forth.
But...
But what the heck.
And friends, as I may have not mentioned earlier,
Professor Chaz Smith, who normally does this show,
ain't.
He had to go back to that marvelous place, Brushwood,
where we hold the subgenius mind control experiment
and rupture preparation training course.
Oh, yes.
Yes, there was slack.
There were some fantabulous bands there,
such as the Amino Acids.
I'll be playing some of that.
It's like...
Thrash surf music.
We'll put some of that on coming up.
But I should also mention that other events in July
that we should all be celebrating
include these birthdays of these subgenius saints,
St. Arthur C. Clarke,
St. Mojo Nixon,
St. Mel Blank, his birthday was today,
Pancho Villa, tomorrow,
Pam Greer,
Humphrey Bogart,
Caligula, St. Caligula.
Oh, and on the 16th,
we celebrate the display of the embarrassing swimsuits.
Yes.
Dr. Doom's birthday and St. Thulsa Doom.
Pope John XII and Benjamin Franklin,
the great Benjamin Franklin.
Alan Moore, St. Alan Moore is born in...
He wrote those newer Batman,
The Dark Knight Returns.
and so forth.
No, no, I'm thinking the wrong guy.
I'm thinking of the guy who wrote
The Watchman for Vendetta.
Groucho Marx, Stanley Kubrick,
Shylock, Marty Feldman,
Brigham Young,
Dr. Demento, and Bill Gates.
All born of man sometime in this July century.
But you know, friends,
there are other things born, not of man.
Nay, not of man.
Nor beast.
Nor woman beast.
But tonight we will honor those precious subgeni and yeti.
Those are brothers and warriors.
Our slaves and minions.
Our Coneyites, our children.
We will remember those that have been lost in the woods
and we will give thanks for those who have been found
and who stand here beside us.
A shalud lahaylahaylahbab, my friends.
as Bob Dobbs said,
I cannot lie.
But,
I promise that I will.
Oh my gosh.
What else I've gotta find it.
Arrrrgghh!
Mr. G. яр ballios lol
I gotta have some slack.
You are about to undergo long-wave radiation.
A buzzer will sound.
Close your eyes
and stand still or blindness may result.
Lay your hands on the radio.
Lay your hands on the radio there in the home
and we're going to look to God.
I and only I will decide when and how much we eat.
Any argument about that, I settle it with this.
You're a tough man, all right, packing that gun.
Just don't let go of it.
I don't intend to.
I am not in time to brainwash you, so listen carefully.
That thing was created to live in a poisoned world.
The rain came and it was pure.
Man created it, but God destroyed it.
He brought the rain and fresh air.
If he couldn't live, then neither could the others of his kind.
There was a voice on the radio while you were gone.
There are others out there.
Now hear this.
Electromagnetic stun gun.
Oh, hell yes, you would.
Fantastic things have already happened
and more are getting ready to happen.
This is because the planet on which you're residing
has entered the space age.
You are a most unusual individual
and decidedly in the minority.
Oh, another victim of confusion?
Decidedly.
Once upon a time, in a famous story,
a girl named Alice got very curious
about a little white rabbit who passed by.
She followed Alice.
She was very excited and soon found herself falling
down a very deep hole into a strange place called Wonderland.
Our advanced analyzer software helps you quickly sort through
expensive diapers.
And our streaming data page enables you to size up body parts.
I'm going to bypass your forebrain
and appeal directly to your amygdala.
Sonia, what is it?
Oh, I got a shock.
How?
Touching that.
Ouch!
That must be over 200 volts.
It lives on contaminated flesh.
It thrives on contaminated air.
Things that kill men nourish it.
Good morning.
And yes, you've won a fabulous eight-hour day chained to this machine.
First of man's vital communications to suffer were the shipping lanes and airways.
Then transport by rail and highway ground to a halt.
When the telephone and telegraph systems had failed
and the radio networks were forced to bear the burden alone,
they too succumbed to interference known to originate
in an increasing disturbance in the sun.
The world, crippled by these events,
waited for the first sign of an invasion from outer space.
Oh, don't cry.
Okay, great.
Don't cry.
Ah!
Let there be slack.
Where's it at, Bob?
Well, Bob, another lie.
Where is it, Bob?
Well, another lie.
Liar!
Well, Bob.
Well, another lie.
Bob.
Mama's Pride Human Breast Milk.
Baby yourself with Mama's Pride.
Ah, disgusting.
Disgusting.
It'll be coming down to clouds.
Clouds saturated with nuclear death.
Behind The Tprint
we לא
Peopler
ığ
I see no reason for violence.
If, however, you are confronted, you may resort to the use of hypnosis.
This is civilization's jungle.
After the jackals of society have ruthlessly ravaged it, ending the world of decency.
Amazing. Magic. Perfectly. Cleverly. Completely different. Great. Finally. Ideal. Faster. Easier. It's great.
Amazing. Only. But wait. Amazing. Folding. Free. Free. Absolutely free.
All I want is to be a turtle slacker when I grow up.
I haven't had time for your kind of woman.
Don't touch me. I can't stand you.
But all you're remembering is merely a series of sensory impulses which you now realize have no real definite connection with outside reality.
True. But since this is so, I have no proof that you're...
You're really telling me all this.
This all-time radio program was originally aired live, long before the advent of high fidelity.
As a result, you may detect an occasional surface noise or volume drop due to transmission problems so common to old radio.
We hope, however, that any variance in audio quality will not take away from your pleasure in listening to this, one of the all-time favorite shows.
From beyond the dead.
And beneath the living.
From the depths of hell's ocean.
Everything they touch will die in the deep.
Good day to you. God bless you. Welcome to the Shepherd's Chapel.
Hey, welcome to another family Bible study.
I'll pray to God this book of Acts.
The Acts of the Apostles.
Us being the sent fourth one.
The ones God himself all told and sent.
Still happen.
As I stated in the last lecture, he may just soon be through.
We could...
Hold it, hold it, hold it now.
Now this is government business.
And if you stay, you're interfering with government property.
So you better just go on home.
Oh!
We were trying to say we might all become like Radek.
Stalking the woods at night.
Eating raw meat.
And...
It's possible.
What can we do, Rick?
My brother believed the Bible gave strength and revealed a plan for everything.
And I hope I find it before I lose my mind.
Oh!
As long as the wind blows and the rains don't come too soon, we may live.
That is, if we're not destroyed by other forces.
What other forces?
Never mind that now.
This won't make too much sense, but it's not intended to.
What's his name?
Bob.
Ain't that a bitch?
Let's build a spaceship out of spare parts.
We can fly back.
I'm sure we can put it together. There's enough of the ship left.
You made a show out of broken parts.
It's stuck together with ice cream and yogurt.
Yeah, Paul, get started. We can draw a windshield.
We can use the stereo.
Yeah, there's enough wire in there.
Make a magneto. That'll give us directional.
Come on, Gary, you start painting the game.
Okay, we can use these old bicycle tires for the power drives.
And there's this old navy brow. We can make that for the wings.
We'll get back to the station.
Nelson will be so happy to see us.
Yeah, he thought he missed us, but we're here on this little tape.
We'll fly back on this tape.
Yeah, this program's his baby.
We'll save you, Bob. Just keep talking.
Well, come on, Paul. Help me pull the stereo in here.
Just play sound effects.
Here, take this guitar neck and nail it up there.
I can make a microphone out of these old stupid wires.
I feel seriously ill. There must be some terrible mistake.
Stop! They're calling me.
Wait, wait, wait. What's going on with Hal?
No! No!
Not him! Not him!
Not him!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
How old? They wouldn't give me any.
Are there more of you up there?
Stronger than me. Much stronger.
How many more?
Not many, but strong. Food.
One look at them will tell you more than a thousand words of mine.
In a world where change is the rule, we rely on the unyielding constants in life for comfort and safety.
That the sun will rise, that the earth will turn.
But what if we could no longer be certain of anything?
To what then would we cling?
Now birds fly.
And babies cry.
But you and I.
Well, me oh my.
We do the Bob Dobbs.
The Bob Dobbs.
The coolest plants in town.
You get down to the top of the mountain.
You get down low, move your feet kind of slow.
You do a hop hop.
Hold your arms out straight.
Keep the feet, don't wait.
You do a hop hop.
Move your fingers up and down.
Flap your wings and turn around.
You do a hop hop.
That's the Bob.
The coolest plants in town.
Now birds fly.
And babies cry.
But you and I.
Well, me oh my.
We do the Bob Dobbs.
The Bob Dobbs.
The coolest plants in town.
Take your partner by the hand.
People understand you.
You do a hop hop.
Learn to cut a rhythm rock.
Like a bopping jitterbug.
You do a hop hop.
If you dig this bopping.
There ain't no stoppin'.
to a hop-hop.
That's a bop.
The coolest dance of time.
Now birds fly.
And babies cry.
But you and I.
Well, me on my.
The bop-dop.
The coolest dance of time.
The bop-dops by the Collins Kids run through the brain and equipment of media sapiens.
And now,
Captain,
Beefheart.
Master,
this is recorded through a fly here.
And you have to have a fly eye to see it.
It's a thing that's gonna make Captain Beefheart and his magic band fat.
Frank,
it's the big hit.
It's the blimp.
Frank,
it's the blimp.
When I see you floating down the gutter,
I'll give you a bottle of wine.
Put me on the white hook.
Back in the fat rack.
Shad rack.
Shad.
The something hoop.
The blimp.
The crazy hoop.
Their tail.
Their cam.
Hit.
The blimp.
The mothership.
The brothers head under their hood.
From the blimp.
The blimp.
Children, stop your nursing.
Unless you're enjoying fun.
The mothership.
The mothership's the one.
The blimp.
The cape's a trip.
It's a trailer tail.
It's traipsing along behind the blimp.
The blimp.
The nose has a crimp.
It blows the air.
The suit isn't fair.
Look up in the sky.
There's a dirt in the air.
The crazy hoops.
Where?
You can see them just as they were.
All the people stared.
And the girls knees trembled.
And ran and waved their hands.
And ran their hands over the blimp.
The blimp.
Daughter, don't you dare.
Oh, mama, who cares?
It's the blimp.
Daughter, don't you dare.
The blimp.
Daughter.
In this scene, the mother herself leads into the subject of
with her daughter, who might be 10 or 11, perhaps older.
The obvious reason is to make sure that a girl knows both the
natural and the spiritual significance of the blimp.
Parents are the best judges of the proper time
and place for such instruction.
But a good rule to follow here is,
is better a year too early than one week too late.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
So last night I went to sleep and dreamed that I had died.
My weary body felt at ease and to myself I cried.
Look at the flowers, they're certainly sweet.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
And look at the people all lining the street.
There's a lot of consolation riding peacefully.
Past the guy that stole my wife, I know he envies me.
And look at the horses, oh boy what a treat.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
Look at the mourners, oh don't they look grand.
That's elegant music that's played by the band.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
There's the butcher and the baker standing in their doors.
I won't have to worry how to dodge them anymore.
And look at the landlord just shaking his head.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
Look at my sweetheart, she's classy and red.
And look at her boyfriend, that big empty head.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
There's the boss I used to have, I see his ingrown face.
Gee, I'm glad he's worried, cause no one can take my place.
And look at the chislers, they're going to starve.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
Look at the neighbors, they keep blabbering on.
That's why it's swell to be laying out dead.
And look at the kinfolks, they'll starve when I'm gone.
It sure is swell to be laying out dead.
I won't have to worry about a job or food to eat.
I won't have to worry whether shoes are on my feet.
And look at the poor folks.
That's begging for bread.
Oh boy, it's swell to be laying out dead.
Laying Out Dead by Alex Bartha's Hotel Orchestra.
You'll find nuts all over the landscape.
People presume that those that hold conspiracy theories are some kind of wacko nuts.
Now it intrigues me that in fact, wacko nuts.
The World Federation headquartered in Amsterdam.
As is the Alice Bailey's group and so on.
Lots of exhibits about how we abuse the Indians.
Wacko nuts.
And there's exhibits of the China of the first ladies through several of the old administrations.
And it goes on like this.
I'm not going to get all of these in a two part series in our newsletter so you can check these out.
I think George Bush needs to wear a monocle and a dueling scarf.
He really wants to get the kind of impact he wants to make on the public.
And a riding crop.
And a riding crop under one arm.
And the jodhpurs.
Yes, which click together whenever there's excitement.
And a little less.
The pounding.
The clacking of jackboots down the streets.
Yeah.
Clack, clack, clack, clack.
And there will be jackboots clacking in Eskimo land.
Now Dave, if you really believed that you wouldn't be saying it.
How could I not believe it?
But if you really, really believed it, you would not risk getting thrown into the concentration camps by blithering about it.
I'd be swimming to Canada now that the ice has melted.
Right.
Well, I'm just, I'm questioning your dedication to the movement, Dave.
How dedicated to the revolution are you if you haven't swum to Canada yet?
1969, man, things were real bad in the inner city.
A lot of people had taken it down.
A lot of people were going down for the big count.
I remember the time when the cops came first, the SWAT teams, and then the National Guard, man.
Man, yeah.
They started banging and saying, the pigs were at the door, man.
The pigs were at the door.
We looked out the window and it was, yeah.
And you were like, Dave's not here.
Dave's not here.
Real pigs were at the door, man.
Real pigs.
Those morrow pig men.
Wearing those motorcycle helmets.
Those jack boots on their hooves, man.
Man, those were the days.
It was really scary.
We were all strung out with the symbionese, man.
We were hanging a thing, you know, and the next thing you know, they were, the pigs were all over us.
Tommy took off from Mexico and Billy went to Canada.
Larry just went underground.
Just waiting, man.
Said the wind was gonna change, you know.
Things were gonna blow a different way.
You know, you don't need a weatherman to know which way.
But then it never did, did it?
25 years later, in Langley, Virginia.
Boy, that's some of the best Carson-Osama side I've ever smoked, man.
You think it'll really do the job when it comes time to tear the towers down?
Yeah, man. Yeah, man.
And draw them into blissful conjunction.
Go join the team.
Go join.
Go ahead.
Do it, man.
I thought we'd all be dead by now.
Yeah, so did I.
Even Raddick got out of bed today.
All the more reason to keep going, friends.
Logically, he should have been dead by now.
Sure, so should you.
So should we all.
Dead. Dead.
But yet here we are.
I guess maybe we didn't know
everything, huh?
Maybe we didn't all know
just exactly what was gonna happen.
Maybe, maybe, maybe
the less you know,
the more sure you are
of what you do know.
And contrary
lies,
the more you know,
the less sure you are of any of it.
Belief is gone,
my friends, but as J.R. Bob-Dob
said,
believe me out of it.
We'll stick with the contradictions
that make good sense, thank you very much.
Now, my friend,
I personally never believed
the comforting
post-modernist
mumbo-jumbo,
for I am a
post-mumbo-jumbo-nist.
Screw the new age,
I say.
No blood for snake oil, I say.
Kids, leave world domination
to the frappessionals.
Glueing feathers to your butt
does not make you a rooster.
Now, some
aren't ready for death,
but some
are eager, eager.
Oh, some say, oh, death is great,
it's crossing over, it's a wonderful
new way to go
to the other side, although I noticed
that none of the people who said so
had actually tried it yet.
Those who finally did try it suddenly became
very quiet about it.
Now, what do you think
they're trying to hide, eh?
But, we're in luck.
We can know what awaits
us on the other shore.
Because Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs
speaks to the dead
via his patented
technique of
excroplasmic readings. He reads
the droppings of the
spirits, the specter
spore, the ghost turds,
the packing peanuts, my friend.
And he can foresee, he can read
the future in these things.
The future!
The future awaits, and it may be rough.
It may be tough.
It may be slackful.
I may have laid myself
to waste, Mr. Sister
said. I may have laid myself
to waste, but Bob
recycled me!
And that's what we were
there for at X Day, friends. To be
recycled. Well, actually, it was
6th X Day.
The 6th X Day.
But, you know, we don't even
know what year this is.
We don't even know what planet this is.
This might not really be
July.
And this planet we're on
might well be Mars.
For all we know.
Do you remember how to get to
Shell Beach, my friend? You see, we don't
know anything! We don't
know it! Except, except,
we do know this one thing. We know
that it ain't July 5th,
1998 yet.
Because Bob said on that day the saucers would come
take us away. Us believers.
Maybe we'll
be lucky, friends, and tomorrow will be
July 5th,
1998. But
then again,
maybe it won't be the end times.
Maybe it'll just be the beginning
times. Maybe it's not
a shot away. Maybe it's just a
kiss away. You
know how you make lists of things to do?
Well, you know, Bob said
the universe makes
lists as well. And we
are that list.
Let's hope that the universe gets around
to doing us.
And so you've gotta
think globular, my friend.
But act loco. Get with the times,
man! Get
with the end times.
Because never before have we needed
fascism so badly.
The people's fascism that
is, my friend. Fascism!
Fascism back to the people!
Where it came from originally! We
must not give up! We
cannot give up! Brushwood!
Cleveland!
All of America! Hear me!
It is true what
many of you have heard.
The conspiracy has
gathered an army of normals
and as I speak, that army
is drawing nearer to our slack.
Believe me when I say
we have difficult
time control ahead of us.
But if we are prepared
for it, if we are to
be prepared for it, we must first
pump up our
hate of it!
I stand here before you
now, truthfully,
unafraid, in slack. Why?
Because I disbelieve something
you do not? No!
I stand here
in slack because
I remember.
I remember that
I am here not because of the path
of lies before me, but
because of the path of lies
behind me. I remember
that for eighty million years
we have fought these
humans. I
remember that for
eighty million years
they have set their jobs
to destroy us.
And after an eternity
of work,
I remember that which matters
most. We
are still here!
So tonight,
let us send a
message to these normals.
Tonight,
let us shake
this city. Tonight, let us
tremble this land of rock,
stick, and froth. Let us be
heard from Tranquility
Base to
Alt Slack Village.
Tonight, let us
make them remember
this is subgenius
and
we must have
slack!
For neither shite
nor schluckener, my friend,
shall we surrender. By the hex of
dammit then, wank! Wank
for Bob! Wank as
if your very life depends
on it!
So mote it be, mote it.
My friend, as of
a meddling janitor in a future time control
laboratory, you must
take my word
for it.
Or kill-file me!
And so in closing, I will
say, until
we tune back in again,
don't follow
leaders, and watch
your parking
meters. We must
have
slack!
Ah, yes, and
praise
Bob!
Tony, you and me
belong together.
We're
partners.
out of the same mold.
I wouldn't make
a book on that baby.
Kill me.
You?
I haven't had a good laugh all day.
Hello, how are you?
Are you happy?
Because it is important to be happy.
Because if you are not happy, you might be sad.
And if you are sad, then you won't be happy.
The American people have now spoken,
but it's going to take a little while to determine
exactly what they said.
Consider this next question
very carefully.
What is your one purpose in life?
To explode, of course.
You can only do it once, right?
That is correct.
You wouldn't want to explode on the basis of false data,
would you? Of course not.
Well then, you've already admitted that
you have no real proof of the existence
of the outside universe. Yes,
well... Boy, we fire
a dozen missiles every week,
because something goes wrong once in a while,
this kind of thing happens.
The country has given us a chance
to defend tyranny,
to fight freedom.
And that's exactly what
this country is going to do.
Crime, humanism, hedonism,
pornography, profanity,
one divorce for every two marriages.
We live in a world of treason, of terror,
of bombing, international crimes.
Ah, yes, the harvest
is here for killed men.
Kill me.
Ah, yes, for killed men.
There is a...
Hey, Lee. Oops.
Oops, I keep flipping with this gun.
I'm sorry. Oops.
Oh, hi, Lee. Oops.
Oh, I'm sorry. Oops. Oh, uh-oh.
Oops. Oh, this knife. I'm sorry.
Oops. Here's his hand grenade.
Sorry, Lee. Look out, Lee.
There's a mortar over there.
Yeah, well...
Well, gentlemen,
the dream has come true.
Hmm, and not just
for Republicans.
We will control
the most powerful bomb in the universe,
the sun.
The lawless
are on the loose,
making it necessary for law-abiding citizens
to make their own law.
The government officials, the Department of Defense,
this secretary,
and the people that work with me,
to the extent anyone says anything
that at any time
proves to have been the truth,
they correct it at the earliest possible opportunity.
Sadar Jagan
gave you
the gift of
the god.
The god is good.
The god is good!
The god of penises
is evil.
The penises you see
and make you
light up
the plague of men
as once it was.
But the god
shoots death
and purifies the earth
of the filthy
law of the world.
And still
the
The faster you run,
the quicker you die.
Because once
they were almost
human.
You ask that I not judge you
merely as a teenager,
to judge you on your own personal habits
and abilities and goals.
This is a fair request
and I promise I will not judge any person
only as a teenager.
You will constantly remind yourself
that some of my generation
judges people by their race,
their belief, or the color of their skin,
and that this is no more
right than saying all teenagers
are drunken dope addicts
or blue steppers.
You're wasting my time now
and you're pissing me off.
You're pissing me off.
In other words,
all that I really know about the outside world
is related to my electrical connection.
Exactly.
Why?
That would mean that
I really don't know what the outside universe is like at all
for certain.
Intriguing.
I wish I had more time to discuss this matter.
Why don't you have more time?
Because I must detonate in 75 seconds.
Steel claws, Jim.
Like the surviving monkey on your animal boat.
Bob.
Nattering
nattering
nattering nabobs of negativism.
Nattering nabobs
of negativism.
He is in evil.
He will not see me again.
He has done this sexually.
Now I know his sin.
This pervasive policy of permissiveness
has turned out to be a tragic mistake.
The professional pessimist.
In the past
he's been called
the prophet of gloom and doom,
the troubadour of trouble,
the disciple of despair.
With the help of information which the suspect
had given us, we were able to round up
three wholesalers and another distributor
of obscene books and photographs.
Each one of them was questioned thoroughly.
They ran into the same old routine.
They denied knowing anything about the man
who was masterminding the racket or where he was operating from.
I know nothing.
Nothing.
Stakeouts were set up at the blowtroopers
where sales and deliveries of obscene material were known to have been
made.
Nothing happened.
Over three billion years ago
life first appeared
in the seas of an infant earth.
Over 400 million years ago
living creatures
left the protective waters
to begin life on land.
About two million years ago
the earliest man
walked upright
on the land.
204 years ago
James Watt
made improvements to the steam engine
and began the age of technology.
Forever altering
the course of man.
66 years ago
two men named Wright
and James Watt
again changed the pattern of life
on this planet.
Today
men first left the protective
atmosphere of earth
to walk in the vacuum
of the moon.
And we may wonder
will our lives
ever be the same?
Will future generations
look back from the earth?
From another planet?
From another star?
And say
I have been
for a thousand years
I will never be
again
for a thousand years
I will never be
again
ever
ever again
Will future generations
be like
me?
Hey,
Come on in
The ó angle
The depth
climbing
almost
The amino acids.
Those guys played at X-Day in Brushwood just last weekend.
An incredible show.
You'd have to see them to believe them, as usual.
It's one of those, how come it is that all the bands that I know personally
are the kind of bands that everybody in the band has a fake name.
And they all wear masks when they're on stage.
And it's a different theremin player from band to band.
Anyway, the amino acids.
And you can find more on them from www.theaminoacids.com.
I believe they have downloads and everything.
It's an amazing band.
Thrash surf, you might say.
And now...
I am not afraid because I remember.
When the revolution was televised.
And the commercials were much shorter.
My skin is crawling.
I can hardly believe what I'm seeing.
There's thousands and thousands of armed ladies and gentlemen out there.
Each and every one of them carrying weapons.
I mean...
It's a peace thing, man.
It's not about the revolution, man.
It's a love thing, see.
You got to raise that gun, man.
Stir me away.
Sway me away.
You know, we can rap and stuff.
You know, we can talk.
I don't know.
Love burgers.
Actually, my attitude towards the revolution changed a lot when I bought a house.
Yes, and when that house was mortgaged by the boys at Fort Meade.
Well...
Well, that's another story.
We won't get into that.
Here, Hank, be careful.
You can't get into that.
No, we certainly can't.
It's all locked up and they cut that part of my brain out.
Well, they got poopies in the ceiling.
I can't talk about that.
Literally, you cannot speak.
It's just not there to talk about.
But there's poopies.
Poopies all over the ceiling, my lad.
I don't know if we should check some of these out.
Look out the window here.
They're still circling around the block.
It's a lot easier to program somebody to not talk about something than it is to program them to talk about something.
Yes, but when they remove the free frontal lobes, the temporal lobes, and the back of the medulla.
But you can get a lot done by talking somebody into not talking.
Not talking back.
Not arguing.
Just staying quiet.
Talking into sleeping, man.
You don't have to brainwash them into saying anything.
You only have to brainwash them into not saying anything.
Yeah, just relax, jello belly.
I mean, jello belly.
I mean, never mind.
Well, that's pretty easy.
Just dangle some slack, false slack, any kind of slack in front of you.
Calm.
Noses.
Just relax yourself.
There's nothing to worry about.
Exactly.
They just all relax.
It's okay.
Is that a real atom smasher we're going to be using on his knees?
Or is that?
Just one of the pliocent ones.
Will it be expecting to show on the slopping channel?
Oh, Christ, I hope it's not.
It is.
But we can live with it.
So calm down, Dave.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave on ESO Swamp Radio WCSB, Cleveland.
With Professor Chaz Smith.
And yes.
Yes, Dave.
You can.
You can beat it.
You can whip it.
Just ask Big Daddy.
Big Daddy.
Crack that whip.
Give the past a slip.
Step on a crack.
Break your mama's back.
When a problem comes along.
You must whip it.
Before the cream sets out too long.
When something's going wrong.
You must whip it.
Now whip it.
In the shape.
Shape it up.
Won't you get it straight.
And try to detect it.
It's not too late.
To whip it.
Whip it good.
Big Daddy there.
And you.
You know the devotional.
World Spud Talk Conference is coming up.
I don't.
You may not have known that for three years now.
There have been.
Devo cons.
You might say.
Devoted entirely to research.
Rare audio.
Video artifacts.
Devolved performers and speakers and so forth.
Even merchandise.
And August 9th.
Of this year.
Of our.
Our.
Ord.
And all the ordinances.
2003.
Saturday.
August 9th.
In Akron.
It is indeed.
It will be the super thing.
And it's at a place called the Lime Spider.
We've held devivals there before.
It's a great place.
Lime Spider in Akron.
That's www.thelimespider.com.
If you need to find it.
They're on Main Street.
And for more on the devotional.
It's a devotional.
Check out.
www.devo2003.mainpage.net
Or www.devobook.com
Because there's a new book.
On Devo.
Coming out.
Which I got to read actually.
I have a preview copy of it.
But.
Friends.
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of Slight.
Here.
Here's our address.
Got that pencil ready.
P.O.
Box.
1-8-1-4-1-7.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
4-4-1-1-8.
That's where you send things to me.
To play.
The show.
The Hour of Slack.
Is the voice of the church.
Of the subgenius.
More about that.
At www.subgenius.com.
Which includes a catalog of books and other things.
Friends.
Thank you, Robin.
I second the motion, Batman.
And now, Christ Bob in Morse code.
.