Listen.
Alright, on one.
Going up in 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
The Strong Genius Power of Squatting.
We'll meet again at midnight.
10-4 Beanie, head full of fear.
Microwaves won't find me here.
I detect a conspiracy smell.
I want to know who's at the wheel.
Who's at the wheel?
Who's at the reins?
Who's the little voice inside of my brain?
Starts with a whisper, ends with a squeal.
I want to know.
Who's at the wheel?
Fidel Johnson, mafia spies.
I don't really think that Kennedy died.
They took him to the moon, that would be so.
But I'm pretty damn sure that they didn't really go.
Who's at the wheel?
Who's at the reins?
Who's the little voice inside of my brain?
Starts with a whisper, ends with a squeal.
I want to know.
Who's at the wheel?
Kenyan Muslims ruin our lives.
Al Qaeda camps, drones in the sky.
A man with a mustache plotting a deal.
I want to know.
Who's at the wheel?
My paranoia's an avalanche.
When I find out I want to crap my pants.
The hard, hard truth.
The real, real deal.
God, I fear nobody's at the wheel.
Who's at the wheel?
Who's at the reins?
Who's that little voice inside of my brain?
Starts with a whisper, ends with a squeal.
I want to know.
Who's at the wheel?
Who raised up brain squelchy, made it glisten with pink,
and served up big stupid so yous all take a drink?
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Who spends Sunday morning praising in church,
then bants from the touchdown when he's doing God's work?
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Look, if I'm laundry, won't you come out tonight?
With your cowboys in the heat and sweet Jesus inside.
Crumphish on pickup trucks, who could it be?
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Who dance around naked with long dangling meat?
Down at the schoolyard, let the girls get a peek.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Who says he's sorry for what he's done?
For being pre-birded and flashing his buns?
He's a good ball player.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Could Roger Stavok be the governor's team?
Illegal abortions and white bread to eat?
Ask Jimmy Creighton, you happen to see,
about the Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
I just want to kill for God.
Who made roly poly, roly poly, roly poly?
Hot dang, it's spicy cheese ball.
Let all them friends and neighbors come a-calling,
cause anything's good if it sits on a wrist.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
What kind of thing is it what's got one head like this?
The head like Andrea Dworkin.
The other head like Bob Tilton.
And two scoops of raisins, cause that's the only way he could get it to
sit up straight at the gawd darn table.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Yip-de-tum-lundry, won't you come out tonight?
Put your hair up in curlers, pull your nipple rings tight.
Stretch your urethra around the sycamore tree.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Yip-de-tum-lundry, won't you come out tonight?
Put your hair up in curlers, pull your nipple rings tight.
Stretch your urethra around the sycamore tree.
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and me.
Me, Jesus and me.
I'm not driving for the touchdown sky.
In case you didn't know it, the world ends tomorrow,
and you may die!
Game from the start to steal my large flat.
They build the vastness, fear of streets, but we never get it back.
This way back.
In 63, Jehovah one-voiced boom.
He spoke the earth through chastity, through a TV tune.
He made a prophet of a simple man, not a stupid bum will groom.
He's brought the beauty and the kindness for the world too.
Whoa!
The union has built a church.
Not put on 10 bus stripes.
For $35 down.
Seeking to save your lives.
It's so tedious.
It's the worst.
Hard time ever, stiff and hard.
And come next day, we'll fly away from the comfort of our backyard.
Whoa!
Slim sumo career of the country.
I'm starting to feel serious.
B.O.B.
Bob.
Wow!
B.O.B.
Bob.
A church of lies, Sub-TDX will help you find your slack
For $35 down, see if you can get it back
Sub-TDX is the word on my membership card
And come next day we'll fly away from the comfort of my backyard
Give me slack or kill me, or kill me, or kill me
Give me slack or kill me, or kill me, or kill
Kill me
Kill me, kill me, kill me
Praise Bob!
And praise Dr. Argus Fox and the Right Angles
who performed that song live at the West End Trading Company in Tampa, Florida.
Dr. Fox, whose name the unenlightened think must be pronounced faux,
is one of the most fiery of subgenius preachers and that band sets the air on fire.
More from them later.
By the way, this is one of those shows that I have to do from home,
so I'm sitting in my backyard recording this.
Before that, we heard a song dear to my heart by the Rudy Schwartz Project,
The Dallas Cowboys, Jesus and Me.
I can't describe how many times I refrained from yelling and flailing and attacking
when my fellow Dallas citizens back in the day
would go into that, so how about them Cowboys routine.
Our buddy Joe Newman, who leads that huge band, Rudy Schwartz Project,
lived in Austin, Texas back when he recorded that.
He has long since moved to Canada.
Who's at the Wheel was by the Rainmakers, one of my favorite bands.
The great Bob Walkenhorst being the singer-songwriter.
And that song is from a Rainmakers album.
I didn't even know it existed until last week.
A 2014 album with the title Monster Movie.
We'll be hearing more from that album too,
because I guess we're on the same wavelength or something.
We might call this episode Ask Dr. Howell the Musical,
because we're basically going to be cutting back and forth between music that's new,
at least to me, and the Ask Dr. Howell show recorded last July
on location at Wisteria Campground at the 20X.
I'm about to play that, but I have to admit that I lost a sound file
and the crisp, clean recording of Ask Dr. Howell from my mix board is just not there.
It's gone.
It's the first time I've ever lost a recording that particular way.
Luckily, we had a video camera also pointed at the stage
just to provide a backup audio recording just in case the thing that happened happened.
So it's a little echoey.
More like the audience heard it, not the way we heard it in the headphones,
but what-evs.
All right, okay.
Ask Dr. Howell.
Now you have filled out question slips,
and while the show is running,
you have the chance to fill out more question slips and send them up here.
We have a tradition also called the side note.
If you feel that the answer hasn't covered your question,
and the way...
Maybe you would have liked.
You can add something, write it on the slip, send it up here,
and it will be added to the permanent record,
which is all part of this show, the Akashic Records.
Oh, is that what the cash part of it means?
The cash is right here on the table.
Cash on the back there.
I just was stupid when I was talking about that Akashic Records.
No, they knew what side their bread was buttered on.
So now we...
We'll begin.
So let's just show how this works
by answering the very first question pre-selected by Ivan Stang.
I selected it on the basis of its placement by random nature on top.
With this $2...
$2, well, that is a very good beginning.
Here's the question, and the gorilla is asking the question,
so he'll say,
Who will win the Game of Thrones?
A marketing...
A marketing executive.
Um, the estate of George R. R. Martin
is the clear victor in this endless combat.
But, aside from that, the most sympathetic characters
are the winners, because they are forever associated
with that particular moment of loire,
that moment of glory, and so therefore,
Peter Dinklage,
the guy who killed his father while his father was sitting on the toilet,
has to be the most sympathetic character in the entire affray.
What scriptwriters call the center of good
should be put in one person,
and it would have to be in our diminutive protagonist.
Does that mean Sheriff Rick is going to win The Walking Dead?
Well, you know, I wouldn't put it past him.
Okay, here's a $5.00.
Here's a $5.00.
Okay, a demon, eh?
Mhmm.
$5.00 demons, but...
The demon asks,
I want some slack.
How do I get that stuff?
The problem is that the demon, being a demon,
thinks of the slack as something which he can acquire like a product.
This is actually the conspiracy way of, uh,
of the demon,
looking at things.
Because, according to the conspiracy,
you're almost happy,
and you would be happy
if you bought the next available item
that is just there,
just out of your reach.
You can almost get it.
And once you get it,
it will complete your happiness.
And when you finally do get it,
it's okay,
and you do like it or not,
but there's another thing
that you don't have.
And so it continues.
Continues.
And thus,
instead of attempting to get the slack,
one must simply have slack.
Since, as we've always taught
in the Church of the Subgenius,
you were born with original slack.
The conspiracy wants to take
your original slack
in exchange for false slack,
which it manufactures,
and sell it to you
so that you will perform work
to support these sales,
doing meaningless labor,
for meaningless results.
So generate slack on your own.
Although, for a demon,
the greatest slack
is a soul in agony.
And not just an ordinary soul,
but a master spirit,
or soul burning.
As opposed to,
well, you know,
angels have cherubs,
and those are like cute little things
that are miniature versions of angels,
and they have to do with pleasant moments.
In the same way,
with demons,
you have imps,
which are tiny little things
that mainly want to make you lose your temper,
and arrange inanimate objects
so just this will happen.
And that is their delight.
But if they ever manage to develop
into a full-fledged demon,
nothing will give them delight
like seeing a master spirit combusting.
geez
These are some of the faintest
to Seitenstern inains
That's every sin
within myself
began
on Christianity
B segundo
Ritual of понятия
of the cultivated
Retail's devils into retail. If your soul's for sale, it's all gonna be gone. Pale politicians hiding in religion. Drag us to the ditch, it's all gonna be gone.
In a monster movie, these monsters are real. In a monster movie, in a house on the hill.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ain't no salvation in a monster movie.
Money nation, greed gonna eat you. It's all gonna be gone.
Dollar bills steeple, all you poor people. Gonna get out, it's all gonna be gone.
In a monster movie, these monsters are real.
In a monster movie, in a house on the hill.
Everything about it is a puzzle. Something's been set. We're all puzzled.
Nobody believes that we'll survive. Probably it's a lie.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Numb out to drama in your melodrama. You're the limited, it's all gonna be gone.
Jesus ain't a-comin', neither is your mama. Close up for the kill, it's all gonna be gone.
In a monster movie, these monsters are real.
In a monster movie, in a house on the hill.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's quite a marching song by the Rainmakers from the album, which, like that song, is called Monster Movie.
I was so thrilled to discover that album, which had somehow slipped under my Rainmakers dar.
It's from 19, uh, I mean 2014.
Uh, but, but it seems like it's ripped from today's headlines.
But now, back to the Ask Dr. Howell Show at 20X Day Drill.
Here's a, uh, now this is a $2 one.
Oh, boy!
A very flowery buildup.
That's all right, flowery buildups are us.
Gorilla voice all the way through, please.
Well, this is a more sensitive gorilla.
What?
Sensitive, new age gorilla.
I have this demon with a gnarled spine and knobby feet.
Fingers.
It possesses hind legs as a kangaroo, so can project itself forward with leaps, bearing teeth as a jackal.
The red skin seems to serve as mere afterthought.
And it carries a kidney balloon to tease me into acknowledging it.
Knowing all this, I ask you,
Why is Greek yogurt so thick?
That gorilla has really nice handwriting.
Yes, well, he took instructions from the best.
Well, you see, this strange creature described by our Simian friend
appears to be what we would call a chimera,
a mythological being comprised of elements of other mythological beings
put together into a new form.
So it was with Greek yogurt when it first appeared,
supplanting the regular little cans that we had seen in the grocery store
for so long in an undisturbed succession of rather limited flavor types and caloric load.
Suddenly it became possible, or financially feasible,
to thicken the upper part of the yogurt,
indeed to produce not the usual puddle
of the yogurt,
full of sugary jam at the bottom,
but a blended form in which the blend or flavoring agent
would stay in isostasis throughout the yogurt.
And this kind has tended to sweep all other kinds before it.
And perhaps its thickness is its strength,
like Samson's hair or the heart of the giant,
which was kept in a distant tower
so no one could kill him while he was on his rampages.
Ah, ooga!
Here we have a five dollar question.
Oh, b-b-b-boy.
It's short, but I...
All right, short.
Short's important.
I predict it not so short an answer.
It's short, but let's see what we can do.
And it has a poem request.
All right. Does it request a specific poem?
Oh, yes. I'll tell you the poem in advance.
All right.
The poem requested is The Skeleton in Armor.
I remember that.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I was only going to do one longish poem this time.
That one I could speed up somewhat.
But what is the question?
The question, and this one is signed by the good Dr. Uncle Onan Kanabaiti.
Ah-ha! Onan Kanabaiti.
The question?
It all fits now. I see.
Is the good discernible from the observation of nature?
Well, sir, I'll answer this question in two shakes of a fish's tail,
ere the Leviathan can swim a league.
I'll put a girdle around the earth in 40 minutes.
The reason is to save more time for the poem.
When one sees nature itself in operation, as Coleridge pointed out in his essays,
one sees beauty because one sees good.
And the good and the beauty that one sees is multiety in unity,
all things in the proper proportion, creating harmony.
But what ain't good?
What would stick out like the sorest of sore thumbs?
Anything disproportionate.
Too much material from a different place.
Something entirely out of size.
It's generally a matter of size with everything else that's there.
Because remember, when you're talking about good and evil,
that evil is not creative.
Only good has that ability.
All evil can do is pervert the good.
And all evil things are things.
That started out as good, and usually by disproportion
of one or more of the elements which constitute a lasting parcel of its composition,
we note an evil thing.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
What's good?
What's not good?
Adamant.
What's good?
When you're done saying the will of the
I like hate, I like to watch.
I like every emotion.
Hook her up, gonna raise the bar
Time's up, show us where you are
Step up, it's time to commit
Plane to sea, we all stepped in it
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Mark my words, time will come
Step up, we're here for fun
We want it now, we want more
We're not the droids you're looking for
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Oh-eh-oh
Hey!
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
It's a joke, it's not funny
Open the cage, I'm not your monkey
Here's a judge, here's the steeple
Open the gates, free the people
Time's up, we won't behave
This ain't your new wave
Step up, it's time to commit
Plane to sea, we all stepped in it
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Oh-eh-oh
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Exposed Foreheads are responsible for the last four minutes.
That's from their new CD, Urgency Squad.
Exposed is spelled starting with an X
and Foreheads is spelled starting with the numeral 4.
They did an amazing live performance of that song,
The Devotion.
in Cleveland last month.
But now back to 20X Day.
Okay, here's a question, a $2 question.
Would it be a violation of subgenius ethics
to breed a cow and an octopus or other cephalopod?
Why or why not?
I'm not sure if ethics would be the problem.
That's octopus.
An octopus, yes.
Well, in this world, it would be a mistake
because however amazing the result of such an experiment would be,
even though Victor Frankenstein himself might approve,
the problem is what happens after you unleash your creation.
And as Frankenstein found out, you're responsible for it,
and you can't just abandon it.
But fortunately for us,
we can indulge in all sorts of genetic engineering,
diddling and shape-shifting
because we're going to be aboard the saucer
where the morality is no more
to tamp down what one might do
because someone might use it for an unsubgenius purpose.
Unsubgenius purpose.
That's right.
Unthinkable.
Unsubgenius.
I know.
Well, we're going to get rid of those assholes
and be all with ourselves in the wonder world of tomorrow.
That was fun.
Okay, we've got one more?
Two more.
All right, let's have them.
Dr. Howell, it has already been asked
how the practice of male circumcision started.
What I want to know is
how were the second and third participants
convinced to take part in this exciting process?
You see, anything that is a new fad
can start to change.
It can certainly be done
when the rich people want to do it.
In fact, the rich people want to start a fad.
So they do something.
And then to be like your prosperous neighbor,
you yourself go in for it.
Furthermore, those who kept the temples
were, as Jesus Christ complained,
all about counting the receipts and the money.
They too were economic players.
Dr. Yeah.
And apart from the Austria and the Dadu
from know-it-alls,
they were also veryɯwerd and potential believers,
so they'd be filled with уп nunca这 turbo
while for our own memory
that people had been very flash.
InSch puedes be a great example of,
done to people and animals in the brave days of old.
So edifying.
You said it.
Here, the final question.
All right.
A deep question.
Okay.
Why did we humans,
why did we bother leaving the woods to begin with?
We're in the woods right now.
Well, the woods are really like a spider's web
where you wait for something to come along.
But humans were able to,
by the virtue of their programming,
go out questing, looking for stuff,
looking for stuff to mess up,
or eat,
or take home,
or have sex with,
or whatever.
But looking, constantly looking,
turning over rocks,
tasting various animals and plants.
And this proved to be an adaptive characteristic.
Yes, this proved to be just what the doctor ordered
for an invasive, meddlesome, and burdensome species.
Nosy parkers involved in the business of all that, that, and all that.
They can see and it can see them.
But that's not to say it wasn't good in the woods.
And some did stay in the woods
because there were different types of humans in the old days.
And some who lived in the woods,
there are those who say,
are there still?
Yep, that's the basis of the legend about the year.
Yet he's still coming in and like in all those jokes
that the apostate subgeniuses find so offensive,
polluting the blood line with DNA from outside
and creating a lasting change,
a synthesis of a new order of beings,
a new beginning and a new order of world.
Like the Nephilim in the Bible
who had sex with the daughters of men
and the Jehovah one and his impatience
washed everything away with a large flood.
But he said it would never happen again.
A flood that is.
No floods.
No flood, no it'll be fire.
They could say that would happen.
Anyway, thanks for listening to the Ask Dr. Hal show.
I think we have another one of these to do tomorrow.
Is that the case, Reverend Stang?
According to the schedule.
Oh, sorry, there I was cleaning my hearing aid.
All right, we're getting ready to wind this sucker down.
And ladies and gentlemen,
I would now like to produce unto you,
the loving crowd of Sanford, Florida, the right angles.
Hurry up, please.
Bye!
I have to go.
I have to be quick and proper before my end due.
Thanks, rude man.
I whiteshilted you figured I'd get it.
There, there.
All right, lovely.
All right, just perfect.
How's that?
Espero bueno, of course.
I missed one.
There we go.
Thank you.
We're at AIER and you'll be seeing a bunch of us at 9 o'clock in the morning, Seattle time.
That's like noon here, so we'll see, friends.
Anyway, I'm going to leave you with that to think about.
And the rest of this show is a fairly timely thing from Starwood.
I hope it doesn't get the station burned down tomorrow.
On this screen may be projected the total scientific knowledge of the crowd from its
primitive beginning to the day of its annihilation.
The brain of these citizens seems quite suitable for our purposes.
We have made the most excellent choice.
The other don't know much as that, but he is not of his world.
Your anniversary should be before years.
Your birthday should be at Starбуш caffeine.
You should go to Zhirei delicious food.
You should be the chief governor of your country.
You should be travelling to what will shorten your difficulty.
You should contribute your time to your nation .
You should donate to Wen Ge.
You should take part in On 관 Vo.
Thank you.