Hey, hey, hey, oh!
Oh, yes, dear friends, you gotta go.
Ruben, you must go. Everyone must go.
Even Joe King must go.
And lo, out of the darkness came a voice.
And it was the voice of the people raising up.
And it was called K-N-O-N 89.3 FM in Dallas, Texas.
And lo, the voice spokeeth across the waters of the airwaves.
And it said, and it said,
Ahem!
And, uh-huh, the voice said,
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to
The Self Genius Hour of Life!
And the listeners heard.
And they said,
Yea, though it causeth my ears anguish and my brain to hurt,
Between my ears,
Nevertheless it is good.
And so they pledged to their station and made it rich.
And likewise the listeners became rich in their poverty, for they were rich in slap.
I heard things.
What things you heard?
I heard some things.
Hey, you heard things.
But you heard nothing.
I do not shout.
I hear nothing.
I do not say.
Master, you must pray?
There must be something in you,
Is there a strict claim to your service to me?
class
We give the
That he hasptions of hishill
That he has no sorrow
Does he do anything you plan
It is we who love you
any fundamentalist will tell you that but first we got a quote not from the bible but from what
we call might call the bauble
what is all this i hear about this youth cult this church of the subgenius
gee uh i don't know well how about you son uh what well what about you it's it's about bob you
know it's bob that's it bob is great but just who is this man bob some call him the slack master
the high epoch the saint of sales others call him liar pimp whoremonger a sleazy con
man
voicing his dangerous scam off on gullible suckers well dear friend jr bob dobbs isn't
some outmoded overused deity from ancient fairy tales but a living bleeding deity for today
the divinely appointed messenger of slack the mystic super salesman upon whose wheeling and
dealing skills the fate of the universe
or
let me tell you
the story
of jr bob dobbs
bread of men in yeti
he walked with the gods
he wore a silly grin
and he smoked a
suicide pipe
he fought the conspiracy
every day of
his life
born to
humble parents somewhere in the
midwest the child bob
who spoth Mamet
experienced a traumatic close encounter with a UFO at the age of three. Soon
thereafter he began to exhibit strange powers of persuasion. By age six he had
made his first million, almost by accident. In college he met and married
his first and still his primary wife, Connie, who is now revered by female
subgenie as the blessed anti-virgin. With Connie's encouragement the young
Dobbs became a salesman of legendary, almost frightening, abilities known to
his peers as the man who could sell anything. He worked his way up to the
very top of the conspiracy ladder and might have stayed there. But late one
night in 1953 while working on an amateur television of his own design an
event occurred which was to become a
milestone on man's mind path to slack. He was suddenly seized up in the spirit
by the hand of Jehovah One itself, the cosmic puppeteer of the Old Testament,
the wrathful alien space god from some corporate sin galaxy. In this timeless
moment which we call the divine immaculation of the Bob, Dobbs received
the first of countless brain-curdling pronouncements
which formed the sacred pre-scriptures of the church. He was shown a vision, a
world where all humanity was equally wealthy, rich beyond imagining, but
without working. This experience combined with his UFO given sales magic led him
inevitably into the religion field. He quickly discovered the golden rule
embodied in his classic saying, they'll pay to know what they really think. This is Bob, Bob's God.
Speaking. You say that you make yourself sure sound dumb. Loosen some of your halos sister.
Praise the Lord. That Beelzebub, that Lucifer, that angel of darkness, he's come.
Don't you know the devil must have been excited? So the devil got all these demons
together. Said let's have a meeting. We've got to have a satanic summer
conference. So he got together with all of his little demons and I imagine
little oriental demon stood up and said, pardon me Mr. Devil.
Just wait until tomorrow. Just wait until next week. Just wait till things get
better and they never get right and they die and they go to hell.
What does Bob do? Does Bob yield? Well if Bob gets wrong and I get wrong that must be
all right. Well if Bob gets wrong and I get wrong that must be all right. That
must be all right. You're not gonna stand up and hear my tape played. You go hear
your tape played and it won't be in a secretary around till
you raise a part of it. You might need just take off and run. Bob's running with
the devil. So you're gonna run way to the other. One way or the other. What else
do you do? I'm seeing a few people talking up in these bleachers while I'm
talking. I don't want no more of that. I'll embarrass you to death in a few
moments. You need to run. That means you need to premeditate your pressure points.
Brother Bob the devil's after me all the time. I said wait really? Because the
The devil doesn't ever bother me much.
He usually puts a demon or two on me.
They can take care of me.
If the phone rings and there's somebody you don't want to talk to,
run from the phone.
I'm glad you came.
You're hearing a preacher preach.
I hope you're listening.
Ooh.
Man, those first few months, I wore out three pair of breeches.
I learned to talk to God.
See, because for a person to get saved and just quit smoking, drinking,
cussing, chewing, and acting ugly, drying up, and dying,
they become bored to death.
They become bored to death.
Some of the most dead-looking, bored, dissipated-looking,
pew-packing papas I ever see are church members.
When they sit on a pew, they so dead the termites move.
That's right, dear friends.
Even the termites get to chewing away on you.
That was cut together by Craig Shropshire,
who used to do the music for a new age show,
Chota, to you KON listeners.
Edited that and several other things coming up.
But in the meantime, as I said earlier,
we're...
We're...
Going to be quoting the Bible.
And these are some lines from the Bible that may come in handy
to any of you who are like the kid in Catholic school
that's always asking things like,
Hey, Father, can, like, uh...
Can, like, God create a rock so big he can't move it?
Or...
Who did Cain marry?
The old favorite.
But if God is, like, all-loving,
why does he let people go to eternal hellfire and damnation?
And whether every atom is in excruciating pain forever and ever and ever
just because they were born in pango-pango and never got baptized,
even if they otherwise lived by the rules of Jesus
without ever hearing from him?
Huh?
And, uh, tricky questions like that.
So, we have a some Bible quotes there, friends.
Uh, here's a good one.
From Luke 14, 26.
Jesus said,
If anyone comes to me and does not hate his own father and mother and wife
and children and brothers and sisters,
yes, and even his own life,
he cannot be my disciple.
Corinthians 11, 5.
But every woman who has her head uncovered while praying or prophesying
disgraces her head,
for she is one and the same with her whose head is shaved.
Behold, I, Paul, say to you,
Galatians 5, 2,
I say to you that if you receive circumcision,
Christ will be of no benefit to you.
Timothy 2, 12.
But I do not allow a woman to teach or exercise authority over a man,
but to,
to remain quiet.
Potentially embarrassing, I suppose, to, uh, some people.
And back, going back to the Old Testament,
uh, Exodus 21, 17.
And he who curses his father or his mother shall surely be put to death.
Leviticus 19, 19.
You are to keep my statutes.
You shall not breed together two kinds of cattle.
You shall not sow your field with two kinds of cattle.
You shall not sow your field with two kinds of seed.
Nor wear a garment upon you of two kinds of material mixed together.
Now, friend, is that shirt you're wearing anything less than 100% cotton?
You sinner.
Uh, Leviticus 19, 27.
You shall not round off the side growth of your heads,
nor harm the edges of your beard.
Now, what is the edge?
Where is the edge, you know?
Leviticus 20, 18.
If there is a man who lies with a menswear,
and a monstrous woman,
and uncovers her nakedness,
he has laid bare her flow,
and she has exposed the flow of her blood.
Thus both of them shall be cut off from among their people.
Deuteronomy 23, 1.
No one who is emasculated, or has his male organ cut off,
shall enter the assembly of the Lord.
Now, I know this isn't against FCC rules,
because this is a law.
This is straight out of the King James Version, my friends.
Uh, in, uh, Kings 2, 23, 24.
This is one of my dad's favorites.
He's a Methodist lay preacher.
He likes to point out that, uh,
because they made fun of the prophet Elijah's bald head,
God caused 42 little children to be torn apart by bears.
And the she-bears came from the woods,
and tore them.
Um, Hosea 13, 16.
Samaria will be held guilty,
for she has rebelled against her God.
They will fall by the sword,
and their little ones will be dashed in pieces,
and their pregnant women will be ripped open.
But on the other hand,
look at it this way.
John 10, 34.
Jesus answered them,
Has it not been written in your law,
I said,
You are gods?
Uh, yes.
There's quite a few things that were cut from the Bible, actually.
From a historical perspective,
it's interesting to see that, uh,
certain books that were written, uh,
then were not accepted as canonical.
Some of these include the books of the Apocrypha
and the Gnostic Gospels,
which, uh, were recently discovered in 1945
by Muhammad Ali Ali,
al-Saman Muhammad Khalifaq,
uh, translated as the Nag Hammadi Library.
And they present a very different picture of Jesus
in the early church than the common Christian view.
Now, many of these writings have an authority equal to
or greater than the canonical Gospels,
because they were written for Egyptians rather than Romans.
So they're free of the pro-Roman bias, censorship, and revision
that the, uh, early mainstream Christian cults used.
These writings lend support to the theories that,
for instance, Jesus was married and had children,
that Jesus did not die upon the cross.
Uh, the Gospel of Philip says,
and the companion of the Savior is Mary Magdalene,
but Christ loved her more than all the disciples
and used to kiss her often on the mouth.
Some historians have stated that the word translated, uh,
companion is more practical.
It's properly translated as spouse.
This same Gospel says,
there is the Son of Man,
and there is the Son of the Son of Man.
The Lord is the Son of Man,
and the Son of the Son of Man is He who is created
through the Son of Man.
Now, you figure that out, my friend.
There is a lot cut from the Bible,
and here's some more lines they cut.
Uh, these are from, uh, uh,
Jesus could hit a baseball so hard
it would go all the way around the world,
and hit him in the back of the head
if he was still standing there 47 hours later.
Ecclesians 6.14,
And lo, on the seventh day,
while God rested and was not looking,
the first bob created him extra beasts of the field,
and among these were the jackalopes,
and the passenger pigeons,
and dodos,
and giant ground sloths,
and flu viruses,
and giant lake serpents,
and bigfoots,
and diasgudises,
and snipe birds.
And he looked upon his handiwork and said,
Lo, it is good.
And on the eighth day,
when God awoke and saw what Bob had done,
he said unto Bob,
Lo, these beasts of the field are unclean in mine eyes,
and of foul odour to my nostrils.
And so I shall let my children,
Adam and Eve,
have brains that they might disobey,
and after a certain time
they shall slay all thine animals
which are ludicrous before mine eyes.
And on the ninth day,
the first bob, in his sadness,
created him certain plants of the field,
such as habifrops,
and zippulops,
and hops,
and grains,
and strange yeasts,
and mould,
and fungi,
that God's children might eat of them,
and fall down and have visions.
And then God saw what Bob had done,
and he putteth his arm over Bob's shoulder,
and they both laughed with a great heartiness
that shook the earth.
For the Lord was glad at Bob's jokes,
and said,
Bob, thou hast shown unto me slack,
so thou art surely my son,
or at least my adopted son,
dearer to me than my shiftless real son,
Satan, that old serpent.
And from that day on,
both the Lord and Bob made merry,
and enjoyed great mirth,
as they made more jokes upon creation
and man forevermore.
The music there was by Art Zoid,
also courtesy of Craig.
And...
Just plain dead!
I'm down here in a restaurant eating a steak
and run up on a gristle,
I'm not gonna give you a hand,
I'm not gonna sit there and fight that gristle!
I'm gonna move around in a hop-over
and get back to the meat!
I don't understand that spot.
Well, dum-dum, jump that spot!
I mean, I'm still glad you came, right here.
And if my heart is made to love,
I want it to love my sponsor!
I've gotta keep my excitement exciting.
Let me give you the truth about exorcism.
And the whole truth about exorcism is this.
Somebody's gonna have everybody.
And the question is, who's got you?
I know a lot of people in the educational field,
they're dedicated to education.
That means they're going to hell smart.
Hogwash!
You better put your faith in somewhere it counts!
Keep your excitement in where it ought to be.
You just go into hell with a bucket on your head
and a fuzz hang off the side.
Ha ha ha ha!
.
I just see some of you right now saying,
well, I don't like this kind of preaching.
Well, big deal!
I know a lot of good masons.
I know some mason men and mason fruit jars.
.
What he'd tempt Bob to do, he wouldn't tempt you to do.
But whatever area you need tempting, he can make it available.
What in the world is wrong with you, woman?
Call me.
.
At 8237-490.
Best way in the world for you and me to be victorious
is to call the manager.
This is Bob speaking.
.
Yes, yesterday's brains are here.
A slow but steady intelligence leading me by the nose.
.
To the table.
This war has spread.
.
You can't eat eagles.
You must watch my feet.
.
First.
And then the crocs shall strike free.
.
Inflicting heavy casualties.
And you're out to lunch.
.
I'll take care of this.
I brought my plastic.
.
Simon Peter assided to me as I flopped out my wallet.
His bulging.
.
Belching.
Bronze tan.
.
Voice.
Carried through the cafe. .
Intentionally.
.
Trying to impress the boss, eh, Pete?
Paul retorted.
.
His bracketed.
Enclosed.
.
Bumshel.
Voice.
.
Blast.
Booming.
.
Across.
The Neverwax.
.
Floor tiles.
Boys.
.
Jesus.
Cleared his.
.
Trout.
Accordionly.
.
Aye, but I like a draw.
Maggie moaned to a greasy pair of glasses.
.
Jesus dawned.
The spectacle and declaimed the onside click.
.
When in Rome. .
Jesus was jousted. .
Indeed the Roman enumerator's bogus man. .
.
John announced from under the table. .
John found his fork. .
.
And thrust. .
His precepts. .
.
In a must unquainly manner. .
Upon his stable-mates. .
.
They called on us for an explanation. .
John jumped. .
But Judas couldn't explain his order. .
And the waitress confused did utter.
Look, mister, you must tell me what you want.
Robin Force abused my influence.
I can't read your mind.
The two of us spent a second fooling in and had a strange vision.
He was holding the bearded lord in his wrists.
Rado style.
Racking to a crazy beat.
Faster and faster than slower.
He heard Cab Calloway singing.
Minnie the Moocher.
He smelled the hearty wrath.
Of twice burned toast.
In trembling egghead earnesty.
He touched and tasted a thousand things.
And was unsure and mortally bounced.
Into the street to find wherefore.
And what not.
On the bench.
That's pronounced guilty.
The others tittered and toasted.
But Jesus savored not the heart.
Savored not.
In the pit.
Of his ugly mug.
The sky rained a million volts.
Of lightning bolts.
And forty buckets.
Of blood.
And beer.
And finally Maggie skittered over.
To our booth.
Heaving and a-hoing.
And the streaming, steaming heap of feast.
She glared straight into the belly soul.
Of our savior.
Cresting.
You order this weather?
Red beans and rhymes in yesterday's brains.
Read the two inch video monitor implanted firmly.
In the forehead.
Of our one eyed waitress.
Maggie Magdalena Witts.
Heh heh heh.
Simon Peter.
Cuffed his face.
To the side of my mouth.
Hey whip.
I told you we should have taken him to the awful house.
Their food is fresher and cheaper too.
But let him look at his men.
You.
Customer implicated by circumstance.
You fresh faced.
Side of bacon.
Too many rowers scraped the bow.
I could see, feel and touch.
His healing glaze.
As it shot clean through the tabular sails.
In Maggie's hot sauce.
The man who was the man.
Sliding side slots.
Thomas touched it too.
And eagerly agreed.
Yes.
They damn well.
Should have eaten elsewhere.
But.
Hell.
Here was water.
Silver.
Leave now?
Why.
They'd look like asses.
They'd break my glasses too.
Maggie recited to no one.
So with their heads.
On their knees.
They broke brains.
In the house of the rising one.
It was over.
Easy.
All around.
Black coffin.
Olive eyeballs.
A rim.
An English translation.
Please.
Mouths watered.
At once.
And as one.
But before feasting.
As always.
Jesus rose.
He ass ended.
And performed a.
A matriarch.
Look faked.
A knowing smile.
Of adoration.
As he had been hoping for his favorite.
The Messiah's interpretation.
Of Chinook's.
Fresh water.
The boys ate.
Feverishly.
Judas.
The joker.
Choked on.
Thirty slivers.
As usual.
He got a big pat on the back side.
Back side.
For his.
Deep.
Trouble.
The lettuce braid.
And everybody.
Said it was Grace's fault.
For extolling the stone.
In front of the shameless.
Steel.
Vault.
The dirty dozen.
Ordered donuts.
In haste.
They ordered bagels.
Dry.
Then they ordered many hundreds.
Of hot dogs.
Then they ordered the tube steaks.
To jump.
Through.
The pastry hoops.
Sit up.
Big.
Roll.
Over.
And pop.
On to their.
Twelve.
Twirling.
Tongues.
Imagine their surprise.
When the dogs disobeyed.
And spelled out.
On Peter's placemat.
The word.
Denial.
Yes.
The instantaneous.
Gnashing.
Of teeth.
Sounded like a lion cub's demolition derby of the soul.
A smoky rabbit's nest arose from the brown.
James.
And haloed them all.
With the foul paw.
That eventually settled.
In.
Surround.
Judy's bulletin purse.
You foot the bell.
They all bawled at the jude.
Who had began to get under their skin.
To make it better.
They all.
Fall down drunk.
And asleep.
In Jesus.
White.
As a sheep.
Knuckled under.
And blake.
I'll never eat out.
Again.
And then he ate his words.
In remembrance.
Of red.
Bees.
And.
Wine.
James.
That was G Don Truby from his album Post Hypnosis.
Actually G Don and Friends.
No telling who they may be.
Old manager.
This is Bob speaking.
I'm Juggler.
Wait up.
Do I sound like me?
Oh.
I'm Juggler.
We got something.
You gotta have some legs to dive.
Come.
I've told it to you.
All gonna do.
Call 823.
74 90.
I was a psyched out on the booger man.
I looked everywhere for him.
I was always taught as a youngster down in Sweetwater, Alabama, that the booger man was
going to get me.
You ever been that.
Now, any of ever been look for.
Alabama.
for him. University of Alabama.
University of Alabama. Don't get me.
Boogerman to get you. You ever been talking to the Boogerman?
I looked everywhere for him.
Bob and the Devil.
We're in space.
Now believe it.
It's real.
Why?
Why is it real?
Do you know where you are?
No.
Now where?
How did we get here?
Does anyone understand what this woman wants?
Have fun.
I love popsicles.
I don't know what it is.
But whatever it is,
it's a property of Soviet Union.
Are you real?
Who are you?
Is it possible?
Yes, it is me.
Mr. Kane, is it you?
We thought you're dead.
Oh, really?
Well, yes and no.
Oh, my God.
Are you upstairs?
Sort of.
Friends,
please feel quite free
to call for information.
Regarding the Church of the Subgenius.
Speak to Will of Dobbs here at 823-7490.
He's ready to answer, well, not all your questions.
Not the ones you really, really, really want to know,
but the ones at least that you have to know.
You can also write for information.
8-2-
Wait a minute.
No. That's when you...
Excuse me, friends.
Bob, the big Bob in my pants got all...
He tried to get out.
Write for information, free information,
from the Church of the Subgenius at...
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 140306
in Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Once again, that's Bob
at...
Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
You have now reached the end of, uh,
side one of your Hour of Slack show.
You may now fast forward to the end and flip it over.
Go down the leader just a little bit and start side two.
Praise Bob and thank you.
Subtitles from the Amara vessel creative team Party
Subtitles from the Amara vessel creative team Party Party
Subtitles from the Amara vessel creativity team Party Party
from his album, Where I Belong.
There's a problem with abortion.
You may have noticed that.
It's in the news a lot lately.
Look at it this way.
If God sends aborted babies to hell,
he is incredibly unjust.
Those babies never had a chance for salvation.
Such a God could not possibly be omnipotent,
omnibenevolent, and omniscient
if he does not condemn aborted babies to hell.
The Christian is taking an exceedingly evil position
by being against abortion.
Since most people who are born do not become Christians,
the prohibition of abortion causes more souls to be created,
which will be tortured for all eternity in hell.
If aborted babies go to neither heaven nor hell,
then the soul must not be created until some later time,
and Christians still have no reason to be against abortion
except among themselves,
as their own children have a much greater chance of achieving salvation.
Friends, that and the other Bible quotes
and rather controversial things I was saying
come from Jim Lippard,
P.O. Box 37052, Phoenix, Arizona, 8502.
Enjoy reporting theerelichford Forbes  our subject.
For an increase on your popularity
you better read over and over Dallas Amen.
We listen to why you writing these books
which has said success is not an easy part.
st preschool, regig is unexplainable.
Is not needed.
It needs to ask for answers,
and ki
brothers and sisters so to speak.
So in the meantime, yeah friends, you know I think the whole idea originally behind this
God guy, he wanted to have fun and they didn't come up with any of the really anti-fun stuff
until human beings evolved.
What a shame, what a shame.
Moses went up to the mountain high to find out the God, why did you make us, why?
Secret words in a secret room, he said, wop, bop, a loo, bop, a lop, bam, boom.
I did not put you here to suffer, I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
And did I have a good time now, now, now?
Let my people go, go, go.
You gotta let my people go, go, go.
You gotta let my people go.
Yeah.
.
Chasing fish to battle the chariot,
it's pretty cold.
You tell the boys with the horns, get down and blow.
They rear back, aim their bells at the stars.
They said, feed me, big daddy, hey, to the bar.
I did not put you here to suffer, I did not put you here to whine.
I put you here to love one another.
And did I have a good time now, now, now?
Let my people go, go, go.
You gotta let my people go, go, go.
You gotta let my people go.
What'd I say?
.
Let people go.
Got to let my people go.
Oh, yes, friends.
That's the Rainmakers.
Old album of theirs.
The Rainmakers.
Good enough.
Whoa!
Call me gullible.
Call me an idiot.
Call me an idiot, man.
The new messiah.
An underdeveloped lighting object.
The things that I've never seen.
But I got to keep the faith.
Got to keep a vision.
And keep watching TV.
But I don't want to hear.
I want to know.
And it's not so clear just to let go.
Let go.
Oh, yes.
Check that dam door
Jesus Calling.
Wake up.
Oh no, it really was him!
A man with a mind.
I must keep saying it.
To myself.
What does that mean to you?
A very long time ago, there was this very powerful man.
In fact, he was more than a powerful man.
He was more like a force, of course, of course.
He was the one who threw the switch.
The switch was wired to the sun's rays.
Then it went right out and it made the earth.
It did it all in seven days.
I did not make this story up.
It has been going around for years.
It first came out of this old book with a capital B, C, C.
They say there's wisdom in that book.
More than you'll find in a bottle of scotch.
And if you buy what's in that book, perhaps you'd like to buy this watch.
Oh God, oh God, you give me such a pain.
When I think of all the things we do and don't do in your name.
Are you love? Are you lighter? Are you just a man?
I just hope I'm on your side when the sh** all hits the fan.
When I was born.
But a little lad.
I stood before the throne of our Lord.
A wide-eyed open bundle of youth.
But not quite on the search for truth.
I saw the water turn to wine.
I saw the church's coppers grow.
I saw more miracles in there than at the circus magic show.
There was this kindly man of the clock.
This man, he took me by the hand.
This man said I should stand erect and wait for God and his command.
This man, he taught me wrong from right.
To love the sinner and hate the sin.
Only words from God.
All I heard was not to be along with this man.
Oh God, oh God, you give me such a pain.
When I think of all the things we do and don't do in your name.
Are you love? Are you lighter? Are you just a man?
I just hope I'm on your side when the sh** all hits the fan.
I've got my crystals.
I've got my chance.
Girls think I'm cool.
And my tight, cheap pants.
All I really want to know is what I have to buy.
So when I kick, I can shake his hand.
And look him in the eye.
There are so many gods right now.
It just could drive a man insane.
And all these people running around who'd slit your throat in his good name.
They all got holy beads and books that make their God the one to know.
But I ain't never met no one who's been up there.
To see his show.
So don't be coming around to me with all your holy cosmic slump.
And don't be showing off your God like he's the latest spandex top.
While Christian soldiers go to war, crusading for the Prince of Peace.
The only preacher you can trust will give the most an ass of peace.
Oh God, oh God, you give me such a pain.
When I think of all the things we do and don't do in your name.
Are you love? Are you lighter?
Are you just a man?
I just hope I'm on your side when the sh** all hits the fan.
Nonsense. Nonsense, nonsense, nonsense.
I don't feel very nice.
I feel as if I'm having a bad dream.
He looks perfectly pitiful.
I think it's just awful.
Awful, awful, awful.
You feel fear.
Come close.
Let me dissect it.
Let me absorb it.
Bring it here.
Bring your brain here.
No!
It hurts.
Who hurts?
My head.
Inside.
It hurts inside.
Shut up, Randall.
Or I'll be nice to you.
Dr. Checker and Mr. Hyde.
Real nice guys.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's the side.
In trouble.
He tried to hide from himself.
Oh, God.
Sad men couldn't face up to the yin and the yang.
Everybody, all of us got a shadow.
Who knows what lies in the hearts of men?
Shame.
We become what we do.
Not what we pretend.
Between the intention and the expression.
Between the emotion and the response.
Who's the shadow?
Who?
Me?
Well, that's a kid, isn't it?
Well, that's a girl.
This little enhanced' mushroom has all kinds of siters.
Sometimes I fail,
to follow the rules.
On things that I want to do
And other times
I find myself
Doing the very things I hate
Reverend Jimmy
And Tammy Bell
Big time pumpers
With a story to sell
Wait a minute
Put your fingers
On that you
Pay attention
Listen up
Don't try to deny it
Or cover it up
Everybody
All of us
Got a shadow
Oh
You could have been a god
Ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha
And we have some wonderful wieners
stuffed with 11 ingredients
11 ingredients
Can you believe it
Tell everybody who did that
Jesus did that
Who
Jesus
Well tell them one more time
Tell everybody who did that
Jesus did that
Who
Jesus
Well tell them one more time
Jesus did that
Tell everybody who did that
Who
Jesus
Well, tell them one more time.
Somebody give Jesus a big hand.
Give the Lord a big hand.
You tell me that I'm different from the other guys
But that's because I see the devil in your eyes
Don't talk about commitment, it just freaks me out
My afterlife is in serious doubt
I'd love to love you, baby, but can't you see
I'm nothing but a Catholic casualty
The way you touch me, it just sends me up
I gotta take a shower cause I get too hot
All my life I'm talking, making love's a sin
We have one night of fashion and you wanna move in
I see my soul burning for eternity
I'm nothing but a Catholic casualty
C-C-C-C-Catholic casualty
I have to kiss and confess
C-C-C-Catholic casualty
My conscientism is
Oh, sweet temptation
Don't you know
You can't take an altar boy from my soul
I'd love to get beyond the bull**** rule
They crammed down my throat in parochial school
But now I'm here in limbo and I'm under a spell
Trapped between pleasure and the fear of hell
I pray to God have mercy on me
I'm nothing but a Catholic casualty
C-C-C-C-Catholic casualty
I have to kiss and confess
My conscientism is
Oh, sweet temptation
I guess you should know
You can't take the altar boy from my soul
Oh, sweet temptation
Don't you know
You can't take the altar boy your omega
Saul!
The true subgenius can learn to think for himself, but only Bob can show him how.
And so, Bob Dobbs founded his church upon a sandy beach of common sense, sense of humor, and dollars and cents.
... and God is pouring out His Spirit, record crowds, the fastest growing church in town.
People are flying in, driving in from all over the nation, and the people here in the Metroplex are receiving miracles.
I minister here. The address is on the screen.
...
Uh, yes, dear friends.
Okay, uh, Catholic Casualty there, and the song, Oh God, You Give Me a Pain, are both by Joe Paulino.
Reverend Joe Paulino, an actor and multi-talented singer.
... and, uh, multi-talented singer.
Subgenius in, uh, I believe San Francisco, maybe L.A.
Uh, you also heard a little bit of Devo in there, and what I'm about to read is from John Shirley's novel, uh, The Black Hole of Carcosa.
There were maybe fourteen of them, earthmen or Jalurians with serious earth damage, crowded around the car with guns in their hands.
Okay, said one of the men, gesturing with the big black gun in his hand, out of the car.
... He was wearing a t-shirt.
... A t-shirt printed with, Do It With Dippy Dog, Drink Dippy Dog Beer.
There was a picture of a rather anthropomorphic dog, winking, as it swilled a can of beer.
... What happens is, the Dippy Dog guy says,
We take this here real nice car for me to drive, and then we take you to the big computer that puts you through your paces, makes you into one of us.
You'll be out fit through and through, and you'll like it or we'll kill you.
You wouldn't like that.
Sorry, boys.
Bob said cheerfully, his grin never wavering, the pipe wagging in his teeth.
Can't oblige you.
The dippy dog guy pointed his pistol at Bob's head and cocked it.
Then kiss your booty goodbye.
Mind if we pray first, Bob asked, still smiling.
Well, I guess not.
Make it quick.
You do a quick prayer unless you're going to try to do some kind of dark land type wizard
hocus pocus and pray to some god awful demon.
Nope, Stang said.
We're going to pray to Jesus.
Jesus, the dippy dog guy said.
He shrugged.
He's harmless.
Go ahead.
I stared at them in disbelief.
They were going to pray to Jesus?
Stang looked up at the sky.
Jesus, I'd sure appreciate it if you'd kind of drop in and escort those who are deserving
through your pearly gates or whatever gates you deem appropriate.
Okay, enough praying, the dippy dog guy said.
He aimed the gun at Bob's forehead.
Then he blinked and looked up, distracted by a light in the sky.
A ball of soft luminescence was descending the sky, coming down directly overhead, straight
and true as an elevator.
In fact, it was an elevator.
A shining elevator without a building.
When it opened five meters over the road, a man leapt out of it.
More than a man.
It was Jesus.
Jesus with a submachine gun in his hand and a burning cigar clamped in his mouth.
When I say Jesus, I mean Jesus.
I don't mean Jesus Garcia of Western Avenue, East LA.
I mean Jesus of Nazareth.
He had the crown of thorns.
He had the stigmata.
He had the beard, the robe and sandals.
He had the halo.
He also looked sore as hell.
And he had that submachine gun in his hand aimed downward.
He leaped out of the elevator, carried him to the air in front of it.
But he didn't fall.
He hovered up there, opening up with the machine gun.
That's right.
The machine gun rattled in Jesus' hands.
He was barking murderous firepower.
Blasting the dippy dog guy into kibblets.
Blowing away a half dozen more of the outfit thugs.
The submachine gun shaking him with its recoil.
The cigar almost bitten in half in his angry clenched teeth.
Jesus was yelling through those clenched teeth.
Yee-haw!
I knew him then.
He wasn't really merely Jesus.
I'd read about this Jesus in the sacred scroll of hyper cryptic icons.
He wasn't your ordinary Jesus.
He was The Fightin' Jesus!
And the sight of The Fightin' Jesus blazing away was inspiring as all hell.
I ducked down behind and between the front and back seat staying out of it but I was
inspired by the sight.
Meanwhile, Bob had let loose the lightning of his terrible swift pipe, electrocuting
two more of the thugs while Stang used their Confusion to stomp the elevator with deaf
jerks of the steering wheel smashing a couple outfits down.
mine clones out of the way using the car as his club. I have to get these darn fenders replaced
from a damn junkyard. Can't get parts for 66 no more, he complained as we roared down the road.
Behind us, the fighting Jesus was turning back to the elevator. He'd killed all the thugs who
hadn't run. Now he punched the buttons on the elevator, waited till the door opened. He turned
and made a gesture of benediction toward us, then a breezy salute of camaraderie. He stepped into
the shining lift and rode it back to the stars. I got up and leaned back in the seat, realizing I
was tired. Tired but impressed. Man, you guys have got connections.
From John Shirley
Popsicle
Praise the fighting Jesus, dear friend.
Joe Paulino here.
The host of Hosanna in the High.
In your super bed.
Good guy.
Having a night.
This is popcorn.
Lord of Macy's.
Christ of Macy's.
Have mercy on me.
Have mercy.
Christ of God.
Christ of Macy's Ann gesagt.
Christ has risen.
Christ.
He feels cortisol because he lost his true nature.
I invite you to get on
I invite you to get under my roof.
So give it up.
Leave him  .
I'll turn him to death.
Turn him to death.
Lamb of God, protect away!
Have mercy.
.
Lamb of God.
Protect away love.
Take away the sins of the wild.
Have mercy.
Most Uhh!
Bless the old.
We believe in the Lord Jesus Christ, the only God, Son of God.
He sits down at the right hand of the man and pops the pulse and got a brand new band.
He's super bad.
Super, super, super bad.
Oh my God, I'm hot inside so have a little baby beef.
And I'm the king of all my sins, so baby, leave your hip.
Huh.
You're too funky down there.
Ha!
Lord be with you.
With you too.
May God bless you.
Bless you too.
Please.
I wanna be.
God's a holy god.
Huh.
Good God.
Mass has ended.
Go in peace, hit me.
Uh, yes, dear friends, that was, uh, Joe Polino .
No under this thing, it always gets extremely, extremely, extremely, extremely .
It's extremely hard.
Mm hmm , and, uh, this is .
You've been listening to The Subgenius by Michael Weir.
radio ministry hour of slack.
You are welcome to recognize or resist us
by writing for free information.
I'm about to give that box number.
Just write to Bob or Jesus or, you know, Rama, whoever,
at Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas, 75214.
It's the same way that it would be odd to talk about it.
It's odd to talk about it, but it's Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Praise Bobby.
Oh, yeah.
...on the New Age.
So what's wrong with the human potential movement?
I mean, doesn't God want me to live life to the fullest?
No.
The idea of developing human potential has invaded our culture.
The Army asks you to be all that you can.
MasterCard wants you to master your possibilities.
Both unwittingly encourage the New Age idea of self-deification.
New Agers believe man's nature can be remolded by human effort.
They would rather you sell your soul for success today
than seek God's will for tomorrow.
Just don't sell cheap.
The human potential movement is not an enlightened choice,
but a doomed decision.
Join us.
Confront the New Age before it's too late.
...
I'm asking you to have the guts to stand up for what's right.
999-9999.
That's Bobby.
Oh, yes, we love you, friend.
We love you, and stay tuned for, uh...
What?
That's right.
Just...
Work it out.
Work it out, baby.
Oh, ah.
And stay tuned for Robert Wisdom's American Music Party.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, rama, hurry, rama, rama, rama, hurry, hurry.
Woo-hoo!