What I'm asking people to do is accept that everything they've based their lives on is a lie.
I'm seeking salvation.
There are enemies of children's souls.
All alone in this world of wickedness.
Search inside yourself for your soul.
In the name of the Jesus.
No, no, no.
Don't be proud of me here.
Fight the real enemy.
Don't you want to be saved?
We're all looking in the same direction.
We're not seeing quite the same thing.
There is absolutely no other possibility.
And now you are ready for the final 200,000 mile voyage
to the moon.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to
the subgenius hour of
SWAT.
And now for this week's verse of meditation.
The dog returns back to its own vomit
and the sow is washed only to wallow in the mire.
We're glad to have each and every one of you at our service today,
especially the young folks.
There's going to be a youth meeting tonight
after the Ascension.
There's going to be a family and all you youths need to be there.
We're going to serve macaroni and cheese,
fish sticks and banana pudding.
Brother Blowforth will speak on dating and mating.
Is it fun or frustrating?
Should be real good.
New Realization,
bringing you best new information for your life.
Not entertainment.
New Realization,
embodiment of concept taught by
Nen Master Nenslow is here to help you.
CIA, NSA, CFR,
Trilaterals, Federal Reserve,
Builder,
Burger, P2, Club of Rome,
International Race Hate Conspiracy,
all means nothing.
Facts are worse than you imagine.
Yeti UFO contactees by thousands.
Cruel, hairy alien dwarfs
slash pickup truck fuel tanks with long sharp claws.
Cute ET, Aryan Space Brothers,
Confederation of Biped Humanoid Worlds.
We'll wish for that when Global Satellite TV reveals to all
that dinosaurs never extinct went underground,
not through polar holes.
To imaginary interior world,
but to abandoned ancient death ray cavern cities
whose unwanted pets dinosaurs once were.
They have advance of us by millions of years
and long ago paid off world governments
creating red herring MJ12,
Area 51 dreamland scams,
releasing vital fragments of actual fact
in foolish fairy tales to discredit serious researchers,
conceal worldwide network of human clone meat farms.
Invisible non-corporeal idiiforms wage war
for possession of human mind.
Showing all traits of life form,
lacking only bodies,
they possess, breed, fight, survive
in non-dimensional idiocosm created by humans,
parasitic fungus brain.
Lowly lichen tells the tale of fungus failure
to infect plant life form.
Alone or with plant form,
fungus is stationary, subject to nature's whim.
Discovery of one cell animal life changes all that.
Mobile host lives, grows, develops, at last the human form,
creates stone heap culture.
Tools creating smaller tools, but then...
Idiiforms develop, controlling animal fungus symbiotes,
creates armies, religions, atom bomb.
Idiiform lives an expensive victim,
breathes, lives though all else die.
Solution, none.
Answers, none.
Nenslow said, beware of those with all the answers.
I have only more questions.
Nenslow said, I never tell you don't listen to him.
I tell you listen, and listen carefully.
Compare, use reason, never decide once and for all
this person is right, this is wrong.
Always leave yourself an out.
A person said to Nenslow,
when commies come marching down Main Street,
I'd rather have a gun in my hand than a philosophy book.
Nenslow said, if commies have philosophy book,
they will never march down Main Street.
Read, learn, work.
Do, dare, and be silent.
New realization, box 86582, Portland, Oregon 97286.
yuanacial briefing made possible by
qi
Should have been left alone to hang and dry
You're in all things too late to scream and cry
Daddy says what can't you sell?
Watch the club
Everything will flow through you
And you're all around
For the good, for the good
Should have been left alone
Now can't decide
Which hypno-tragic role to suicide
Daddy says what can't you sell?
Watch the club
Everything will flow through you
And you're all around
For the good, for the good
New New York
Like hell
Decentralized
New York
Like hell
Decentralized
New New York
Like hell
Decentralized
New York
Let's do it
Watch a generate
We'll be right back.
And, uh, yes, this is why he provided this music also in the background.
This is Nenslow himself leading the Nensletic Orchestra.
Before that, you heard Out of Band Experience,
also known as Kings of Feedback,
a great subgenius band doing Fight the Real Enemy.
And who might that be?
And you can reach Out of Band Experience
by calling, got that pencil ready,
1-617-LICK-O-B-E.
Yes, 1-617-LICK-O-B-E.
Yes, we're taking it easy now at this point.
We've had to do three shows in seven hours,
and we've got two more to go.
But we've got so much great tape,
and we're going to continue now.
With the tapes of the Senate hearings,
originally broadcast on WCSB Cleveland ESO radio show.
When last we left off with Cantor Chaz
and lonesome cowboy Senator Dave, the accused.
We were autopsying President Dobbs,
who actually had just discovered
some key facts about the brain of President Dobbs,
and were, I believe, flipping the tape on the last shows.
This is where the tape picks up in Dave's brain.
Thank y'all.
... had been replaced by spongy mass of pipe tendrils,
which seemed to arrive with an unholy intelligence of their own.
Now, this may explain some of the President's foreign policy miscues,
and the president's own.
Well, we certainly have been exposed to something
nearing an incredible story here today.
I don't know really what to believe,
that the president's wife's brain actually became an out...
... tendrils, tendrils in her brain.
... tendrils, tendrils.
Someone, someone, look, help the senator!
Help the senator!
... get the pipe out!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Too late!
It's broken in too deep!
He'll lose the whole front part of his brain!
Whoa!
Now, how do you feel, Senator Dave?
I feel just fine.
I feel all smooth and creamy like Serena,
or a plate of well-done grits.
I don't feel like napping, though.
He has become...
... Dave has become...
... a great man.
He has joined us.
All one, unite all faith, all moral ABCs, rabbi dogs.
All dogs.
Dilute, dilute.
Okay, okay.
All wagged out.
Hey, is there supposed to be different new flesh growing on my skins?
Oh, that's just one of the side effects of the operation.
Oh, tell us about your dream.
You were mumbling answers as if you were being held up.
I was on trial in some Senate hearings.
I dreamed that Reverend Stang was an evil senator.
And he had claimed that somehow I was investigating church,
and then I had bankrolled, pocketed my bankroll,
that had been given to me by the Senate at committees.
And then he had been doing it instead,
but he had me crucified up there just like Sivana Rowland examining his snakes.
I was going to the cross or the witching post.
And then all of a sudden,
Jackie Onassis' head exploded into a pile of...
Polyphone, kind of like Bob's did when he was exploding.
Did we get all that on tape?
Okay, take it down to the novel department.
Send it off to Simon & Schuster.
That'll be the next subgenius book.
It's worth it.
Those experiments and, I mean, well, the surgery is expensive,
but well worth the results in prophetic utterances by the patient.
As we can see, doctors here,
Dave laying on the altar,
on the operating table,
seems to believe that he is standing upright and doing a radio program.
...shall come a time when three wolves shall walk through the Underwoods...
He's hooked up to the bearing.
...pitches of cheese and monumental artifacts from...
Wait a minute. The lights are blinking.
Okay, yeah.
We can type in behavioral changes,
and we can use the file transfer protocol
to send his behavior changes out over the neural net
so that all the other recipients,
if they can download Lonesome Cowboy Dave's brain,
they are able to take on the courage and wisdom of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
It's a high-tech version of the primitive belief
that if you ate the enemy's heart, you would gain his courage.
In this case, we download Lonesome Cowboy Dave's brain
and gain his intelligence,
which for most of us, of course, is a soporific drug.
It's the only way we can relax.
We run up a little bit of Dave's brain,
and it just mellows us out, you know.
It lowers our consciousness so many degrees.
It feels great! You ought to try it!
Come on, man!
Don't you want to be like everybody else?
Try it!
What are you, chicken?
Try some Dave's brain, man!
This...
I'll try some.
This is pure...
Oh, yeah, come on, little girl.
The first lobe is free.
Okay!
Here, just hold on just a second.
Now, breathe into this sack.
This sack contains some of the essence of Dave's brain.
Go ahead, just huff it.
There you go.
Okay!
She's drooling.
Is it the brain of...
She's growing small.
She looks like a little girl.
Now she's four years old.
Three, two...
Now, hopefully it'll stop here.
We don't know what happens if they keep going.
Oh, don't cry, little girl.
Now, it's okay.
We're your friends.
You're going to grow big.
You'll be a big girl soon.
All right, now she's growing.
Here we go.
It only lasts about 20 seconds, gentlemen.
And isn't that miraculous?
Now, a fully grown test subject.
Just re-grow immediately.
What we are trying to do is to make possible for the person to sniff or to waft someone's brain,
to eat the brain, part of the brain, and immediately accrue all of the attributes of the person.
Imagine the same way he had described the cannibal getting the heart of the victim.
That's right.
And CEO Dobbs has decided that if we can work this formula into the hamburgers in his new franchise,
perhaps we'll just pat it in like we could use some spices.
That's the first burger god, hunger raper, they're called, will be given away free to each customer.
And once they have that first one, we know that they'll come back for more Dave brain-tainted meat.
Ravaged by hunger?
That's a really good brain.
The problem with this brain is the convolutions are completely useless.
There's no information.
There's no information carried in this brain.
It seems to be some sort of sieve or some sort of...
That's not what's at issue here.
It fits on a bun.
That's all that counts.
It weighs half an ounce.
Marty, think of it this way.
And it sits on a bun.
That's right.
It sits on a bun.
And it's 350 for the quarter pounder.
350.
I mean, we don't care if it doesn't really, if it's not really a brain.
We don't care if it's not.
It works.
Look at how well it sits up on the steam table here.
They eat it.
The next part of your purpose is to have an audience who doesn't have the botulinum
on their stomach when you have diabetes.
Yeah.
I mean, my intuition could be that.
That's right.
te obey
Just do it by your instinct.
You have to find sport.
Just be able to 160 Kilos of sugar and you're And this is from the government.
You don't leave anything out of it.
If you leave a lot of food alone, other things will be found.
That's this
You must have been real cool in the 90s.
Yeah, that's no good when you get busted with a trepanation scar.
Yeah, they can tell.
Yeah, they just take a look at you, and that's no job.
You know, you can't even really apply for ADC or anything.
They see that, they assume you're on medication, too, you know,
and it's like, I'm trying to explain to them.
Well, but not because of the church and subgenius or anything like that.
Because, you know, so that's, you know.
Yeah, I mean, half the teenagers in town, I mean,
all the Nine Inch Nails fans have to go out and do the drill thing on their head.
Well, I mean, you know, like there's a lot of people walking around with scars on their skulls,
you know, big, big holes in their skulls, and what kind of, you know,
what are they getting out of this society?
I mean, people think like they don't exist.
What kind of children are we raising?
Children, I mean.
When our high schools have to have metal detectors at the door
to keep the kids from bringing their Black & Decker drills in.
I know it's getting so far out of hand, you know,
like some principals on the Near East side have actually,
and after installing, you know, they find a trepanation scar on a person's head
or a piece of a drill blade on their skull.
They're out.
What's out of there?
In Dallas, Dallas school, I walked in to talk to the kids about drugs and drills and E-means.
That's where I go looking for drugs, too.
Exactly.
And there was a child, there was a fifth grader sitting there
with a fresh hole in his head and a trickle of blood running down the side of his nose
with a blank stare in his eye, quoting Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
sitting there right in the middle of English.
So she'd obviously gone to the boys' restroom and,
like in my day, we might go in there and smoke a cigarette or something.
Now they go and plug, take their power drill with that,
they run on batteries and their beepers and their internet
and they drill that hole and if they're not high enough from the first one,
that means, well, drill a new one.
Make it a little deeper.
Use a gauge four drill instead of a gauge three.
I say one shunt and they should be suspended for six weeks straight.
I knew this dude.
One shunt and no more hunt.
You have found everything you need.
Some people merely blow off the top of their skull entirely.
Those are hipper than now.
Yeah, the ones who take the whole front half of their skull off.
Oh, yeah.
They're so cool.
Yeah, they're like that.
You know, wearing black.
That's the only way they can be cool.
Wearing black and all black and everything and their brains exposed.
Yeah, they always have the little stud on their neck.
Like Frankenstein's monster.
Yeah, like it's supposed to really do something for you, you know?
Like, I really carry that.
Yeah, if you see the ones with the, like, they get their left hand and right hand switched.
Or some have the hand of the gorilla.
You know what works very good?
You know, they're real weak and kind of numb after that.
I only see gorilla hands.
And they're into it.
They like to walk up to normals and shake hands, you know?
With their big, clammy gorilla hands and a normal sleeve.
Oh, yeah.
Let's get down.
Let's cut the hole out of the front of our skull.
Let's go.
Achieve enlightenment.
It's the new cool thing.
It's the way to get high, baby.
Are you?
What's the matter, you fray?
Come on.
The drill doesn't hurt.
Put some Dr. Bronner's on it first.
Aren't you a friend?
Make love to the drill.
Bob's into it, man.
Become one with the drill.
It's God's approved.
Yeah, you'll love the way it sounds.
It, like, echoes across your skull when it's going in.
It's I One Drill.
It's like stereo.
I found the drill last week, and in two months,
I made $7 million.
The drill is your friend.
Open yourself to the drill.
Let the drill open you to everything else.
Have you ever sat on a beach and imagined you were actually doing a radio show while you were in a striped jacket?
You will.
Have you ever imagined yourself locked in a bathroom, crying?
No.
Eating urine-stained cake?
Crying on your birthday?
Did you ever have a dog?
I had a great job down there at the Kaiser Blaze factory, but then the Silanees came in and they laid us all off.
Dogs, when are you going to do something about this invasion of our shores?
Sign a Patreon.
Bob, I'd like to say something about all them damn farmers.
I'm not going to say anything, but I'm going to say that I'm going to say something about the farmers who are coming around here and taking up all the jobs.
You're so boring when I think of you.
You do nothing to my interview.
My doctor's no fun.
Who cares of the pills in a box?
Just can't care for hills.
Can't care for hills.
Can't really care for hills.
I have to say that they are mental positions that lie behind every dimension of longer jobs.
We won't swear.
guitar solo
solo
Hello attention to my room
You can smell it be pain
But you're not there
You're not anywhere
I'll go anywhere
I'll do anything cause I'm bored
solo
Like that
ero
He drove a Cadillac Sedan D.D.Ville
With a power door locks and an 81 grill
It had the cruise control with adjustable seats
And he wore winged toed golf shoes
With retractable cleats
And as he drives the course
He's got a long ball
With his bag of clubs and an 8 o'clock call
Martini's ecstasy with a wooden wedge glue
And he drove a Cadillac Sedan D.D.Ville
With a twist of laminate and an olive tube
He drove a Cadillac Sedan D.D.Ville
With a fuel injection and an iron pad well
He could drink it all down
With a vodka like swill
And he could smile so wide
Like a Cadillac rule
With his little cap and the reason he choose
And he could give a slap
He fulfilled his clues
It took him 40 yards just to fit in his shoes
With that Martini ecstasy
You could pay his dues
And he could drive a Cadillac
With his bag of clubs and an 8 o'clock call
And he drove a Cadillac
With a twist of laminate and an olive tube
From his own point of view
Ah!
He drove a Cadillac
And he drove a Cadillac
Yes, dear friends.
Dr. Bizarro and the disgustos.
They're from iBob Digital.
available from and I want you to get that pencil ready now but that's iBob
digital at P.O. Box 3405 that's Box 3405 Skokie Illinois 60076
listen to the sounds in this room just the hiss just me and the hiss and the tapes
the tapes and the clicks the loud clicks and now this Dave brain
all this
Dave brain laying around here we got to do something with it I'm sorry friends
you know I heard from one person who said I'm not that crazy about Lonesome
Cowboy Dave but I don't care don't care don't care don't care don't care don't
care don't care no sir we're gonna go right back to it we have to because it's
there and and Nenslo
and the evil and the good we can never leave isn't it wonderful
you
I don't know
me
I've lucuma
I've been
eh
how
more
and
well
you
a you
¶¶
Oh, yes, I can feel the spirit.
It's piling up.
It's about washing up the back of Dave's teeth now.
It's going to spill over any minute.
That's a nice one, woman.
He's so full of the slack, it's lapping at his lower lip.
The woman is backing up from the gorge.
Spirits, effluvia, esoteric effluvia.
If he leans forward, the slack will come oozing,
floating out of his mouth like ectoplasm out of a trance medium.
But it ain't no spirit of the dead, friends.
It's the pure essence of slack.
Loves him, Cowboy Dave's slack.
Forming in its ectoplasmotic manifestory existence,
hovering in front of his face here in the studio like a green cloud.
And it's forming into the shape of whatever he's thinking about, which is...
I believe, oh, it's Chelsea from that new rave magazine.
I recognize that pose.
He's thinking of the cover.
We are happy to serve you.
Now it's dissipating.
A cloud of slack in the shape of a naked girl.
And it's pretty...
Dave, that's not exactly like sophisticated or PC.
But it's honest, friends.
And that's what happens.
He hit up on that chicken.
I mean, he had a hit of the chicken.
And the slack splashed out in the form of whatever he was thinking about.
Dave was in Dobbstown for six months learning just that one trick.
Now, anything I think of for long enough time,
using the alien machinery,
which doesn't really exist as machinery,
I can will into existence
any kind of dog-faced boy or miscreant vehicle
or three-wheel bike to wheel around the block
and sleep in a dumpster.
Friends, we just saw a series of images form outside of Dave's head.
It ended with a tricycle.
I noticed he went through a whole bunch of things.
There was a picture of JoJo, the dog-faced boy.
Old, you know, turn-of-the-century photograph.
There was...
There was that picture of Kool-Aid with the face drawn on it.
I don't think he even mentioned that one.
It's a stream of consciousness visualizing.
It externally...
Well, it causes the hallucinations to be externalized,
is what the catalog says.
And you're saying that as the illusions are formed in the mind of the individual,
then they're made concrete?
And then they're...
Well, they're not concrete.
They're just an image.
They're just an image, like a hologram,
that forms outside the head.
But you can't photograph it.
Other people can see it.
But only...
Like, we've done experiments.
Dogs can't see it.
You can't photograph it.
But other people will see it.
Because it's that...
It's on that etheric level.
The slack itself is invisible to the normals.
To the subgeniuses, we're floating in a sea of slack.
We're floating in a sea of pills, for that matter.
But you're just too blind, deaf, and dumb to stick your tongue out.
Just...
Just chaw down on them.
You're floating in a sea of slack, my friends.
But I'll tell you something about slack.
If slack was water, Bob Dobbs would be surfing.
But you'd be drowning.
Mmm...
There it goes, leaking out of Dave's mouth and nose again.
He's all filled up with that slack.
He's got that...
He's got that special trepanated brow.
Mmm...
He took out a hole about the size of a quarter.
Out of the front of his skull.
Didn't even bother to transplant some skin over it or sew it back.
It's just...
The corpus corallosum is exposed.
Supreme serenity.
He sees Bob even when Bob ain't there.
And you know, friends, God is everything.
But Bob has already been everything else.
All the kids in my neighborhood...
Look like Bob Dobbs.
What?
All the kids in my neighborhood smoke pipes.
All the kids in my neighborhood are proud to be Bob Dobbs.
And if they ain't Bob Dobbs...
They die.
We kill them.
I'm gonna kill them.
Kill them dead.
And if they are Bob Dobbs...
We kill them.
We kill them dead.
You're Bob Dobbs.
You're Bob Dobbs, too, aren't you?
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill you first.
You ain't gonna kill me until I get up to you.
Well, I like this church.
Everybody turns into Bob Dobbs,
and they can all sit in the pews and be exactly alike,
and if anybody's different, then they can hate him.
Hate him, hate him, hate, hate.
Oh, I love to hate.
I hate Bobbies.
Everybody comes by me hating fair and square.
Eek, eek, eek, eek, eek.
Er, er, er, er, er.
I'm the good ship Dobbs,
sailing the seas of slack.
The mistletoe.
Pirating and looting of the pig carpet.
Raiders out there.
Looting them on the information highway as well.
Arr.
The Spanish.
We pull our...
Just looting, looting.
We pull our Corsairs up to their modems
and climb right aboard.
Climb right aboard.
We created an interactive CD-ROM game
that hooks your checkbook account up to the Internet
every minute you spend shooting those funny Dobbs figures
rushing at you down that corridor.
Every...
Every penny.
A penny a second goes straight to the home
for slackless children.
Dear friends, look at this little child here.
He's not allowed to play with...
At home, with his human parents,
this child wasn't allowed to play with
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles,
He-Man, Transformers, or Playboy magazines.
No, that's right, Ivan.
This child wasn't even allowed to play with himself.
This child was severely deprived.
Doesn't that just make your heart...
Doesn't that just make your heart bleed?
Doesn't that just make tears well up in your eyes to think,
these poor little...
These children may have the subgenius gene.
It could be triggered by exposure to enough...
Well, let's just call it information.
Pornological Irritainment, we call it.
And, uh, it's...
You know, it's...
It's the...
It's something you can do with that excess money.
The government's just gonna take it.
The government should...
Do you want to give it to the government
so they can spend more on socialized highway buses?
Bridge building. Bridge...
Bridge building.
You want to just let the government take it?
Or you...
Or...
You know, if it has to be gone anyway,
give it at the Home for Slackless Children,
Dobstown, Malaysia.
Tax-exempt.
These children aren't going to cry very much longer,
are they, Ivan?
These children are going straight away to that home
and perhaps find themselves in some sort of
non-mystical, non-experiential way.
Perhaps they don't even really exist, do they?
We don't make those kids...
memorize boring religious passages.
We give them video games.
We give them Wolfenstein 3.0 in 3D.
We...
We give them Army...
We give them the complete G.I. Joe set.
We give them Barbie...
Barbie's Dream House, Barbie's Dream Kitchen.
But, of course, you know,
we don't want to train those little girls to be...
to grow up to be pink girls.
We want them to be subgenius girls.
You know?
And it's all in virtual reality, isn't it, Reverend?
That's right.
So that's why we change those Barbie dolls
before we give them to the girls.
We...
We make them...
We kind of morph them between a Barbie
and the Star Wars characters.
Now, when the ectoplasm comes out of...
Gives them more character.
Yes.
But when the ectoplasm comes out of their mouths,
doesn't that...
Wouldn't it ruin a Barbie set?
Oh, but when you see a room full of kindergarten-age children
with green...
Slactoplasm oozing out of their nostrils, ears, and...
Mouths.
Their eyes rolled back in ecstasy.
Girating them.
Forgetting their evil conspiracy toilet training forever.
Doing their bank statements.
Chewing on their pencils.
We encourage them to chew on their pencils.
We encourage them to break their crayons into millions of bits.
We encourage them to pick on each other,
gang up and bully each other,
and ostracize members.
We want them to learn the way things are in the real world,
where they can do anything but...
But they're gonna have to pay the price.
You know?
It's the school of hard knocks.
If more kids were raised in the school of hard knocks,
I don't think America would be where it is today.
That's right, Reverend.
I think the school of hard knocks would knock some sense into these kids' heads.
Beat them all.
They'd quit huffing paint and Dave Brain,
drilling holes in their heads,
and hooking internet superhighways in one ear and out the other.
Why, friends, I think if you just give your money to Home for Slackless Children,
we could turn America around.
We could sure do that.
We could string up normals from trees like they've been doing to weirdos
for years and years...
for centuries.
For a thousand...
Comes and goes around.
You know who built the pyramids?
We did.
Well, no, well, no.
Actually, a bunch of stupid, normal religious fanatics.
They did it.
But you know who designed the pyramids?
We did.
We stood there and said,
you know, we'd love to be hauling those...
4,000-ton rocks up that slope with you men,
but they need us here,
telling the king that the gods want this pyramid built.
Yeah, now look here.
See, Pharaoh, what we got here,
we got a conjunction of Mars and Venus in the constellation Cygnus.
And Phos and Ra are in conjunction.
Yeah, yeah, Ra and Phos, yeah.
Isis and Osiris are about to collide.
Right, right.
And, you know, when the river starts flooding,
you know what's gonna happen with Asakoth,
or, I mean, Osiris.
That's not really how we should be.
That's right.
So the gods will kill us
if we don't make all the dupes build the pyramid.
Make the dupes build the pyramids in the name of the gods.
But who will design this pyramid?
Will you, the subgenius high priest, design the pyramid?
That's slack.
Uh, nay.
We will get this talented normal to do the actual math.
We will pay him four tamarins, three dates, and a donut.
But we know it wants to be gold.
The gods want it to be covered with gold,
and it has to look like that thing
that the humans will use on their dollar bills,
but without the eye.
The mighty pyramid.
The symbol of the equilibrium between the controller
and the control.
It's a bloodshot eye.
As long as somebody's wielding the whip,
somebody else is gonna walk out and say,
Whip me.
Come on, whip me.
I mean, which one would you rather be, my friend?
Oh, you wanna be that whooped,
huge,
human, feeling the sting of that master's whip, or do you want to be one of the masters?
Those who, or do you want to be the parasite that lives off those evil masters and those
stupid dudes?
I want to be a parasitist.
There you go, kids.
Now you're thinking, like the mighty tick, which kills, does not, the predator kills
the prey, but the parasite kills neither.
It torments.
It torments all equally.
And we, the subgeniuses, are the parasites, the ticks upon the body politic.
A politic.
We made a joke on it.
Anyway, seriously, though, to continue in a more serious vein.
In that the body politic is made of a vermin, shouldn't it be?
We may be called, sure, they call us vermin, and they consider that an insult.
Spermin vermin?
To us, that's a compliment.
Yes.
Well, not the highest.
One of the third, well, maybe the fifth highest compliment.
And in faith, we march these children down the hill out of the home for slackless children
and out to the fields where they learn slack work with little tape decks around their necks
listening to this show and picking, uh, soya beans, cotton, and so forth.
Oh, it's beautiful.
We have little crops up there.
It's lovely.
It's beautiful.
They are taught, they are taught, uh, the slack yoga of service.
But they learn words.
They learn to work.
You see?
As slack.
Great idea, huh?
That was one of Bob's most brilliant.
It was sort of like passive resistance, you know?
It was, right.
So, uh.
A brilliant thinker.
Better than L. Ron Hubbard, I must say.
Much, much more, well, it's, well, he has a squarer face I think.
L. Ron was a sex god, man.
Well, nobody competes with Bob, I know.
Oh, no.
Well, needless to say, you know, you know there's a story, possibly apocryphal, that
when the last time Bob was sent to the hospital.
To hell.
That he cuckolded the devil.
I've heard that story.
Yes, that he was even a better tempter than the devil.
And he cheated too at times, didn't he?
And that he, he put, he put two more horns on the devil, you might say.
Oh my God.
Yes.
And Satan cast Bob from hell.
And since he was never baptized, he can't go to heaven.
So, he's back on earth.
He can try to kill him.
Hell, we did.
We were the first ones to try.
You may hate this Bob stuff, right?
You don't think that occurred to us too?
Oh.
We tried to get out.
We tried to get out back in 84.
But, go ahead, blow him away.
Put ten bullets through Bob's head.
He's gonna come like a cartoon character there.
He'll be again grinning at you.
It never stops.
He just can't die.
My mind always hurts.
It is painful.
It is very painful.
And he just won't ever die, will he?
He just keeps coming back and coming back.
It's phenomenal.
It's kind of like this song.
Well, we have a song about Bob called The Song That Will Never Die.
It's about a man who has a heart that refused to die.
Should we sing it or not?
We've been singing it for the last hour and a half, Dave.
It won't go away either, will it?
No, you can't.
You know, the ironic thing is the song, in a way it wants to die.
But it cannot die.
It just crawls on fitfully.
Sometimes it picks up and really cooks.
And people go, okay, it's gonna build to a halt and it's gonna be over, you know.
And it might be over for a little while, but oh no.
It picks up again.
Just like a mighty stick.
Like a patient on an operating table.
That's right.
And you die and you zap it.
Because the guitar player might die, but some other guitar player will come along.
That's right.
The drummer might die.
Some other drummer.
Or else a car that just blew a tire, the wheel flapping will be the percussion for the song.
That's right.
That's the way we play it.
That refused to die.
And, you know, the audience has changed a million times.
You know, they went away.
I remember when you were a pig.
There's always more.
That pig, very, very tall.
I remember.
I loved that.
There's always some sort of odd.
And they may flee the song.
They may try to kill.
They tried nuclear.
Years ago, back in the 50s, they tried nuclear weapons on the bomb.
Bullets could not stop it.
Flamethrowers, paper cuts, nothing.
Nothing.
No cosmetic has ever been erased.
It would get real ugly.
It would get real damn ugly.
And it would grow 50 feet tall.
You know, it was like the more you tried to kill the song that refused to die, the louder
and meaner and more horrible it would get.
The survival mechanism, mechanism, mechanism.
It was an artificial intelligence of its own.
Of its own kind.
Yeah.
You'd think it was all petered out.
Oh, yeah.
But it would...
Peter on.
Yes.
Peter's out or Peter's in.
It would rise from its deathbed.
It would be like a vampire.
And spring into erect awareness.
More musicians would be drawn in.
It would sap the life force out of them.
Like a glowing bolt of bolt weight.
People...
The song itself tried to warn people about the song.
I mean, part of the lyrics of the song were about how dangerous the song was.
We warned them.
We did.
We actually warned them.
It begged its listeners to kill it.
It begged for them to kill it.
But when they killed it, it refused to die.
They tried to kill it.
You could not kill the song.
The song couldn't commit suicide.
Refused to die.
To die.
The song was just an overlapping rhythmic notation in the back of his head.
Oh, sometimes it wasn't music at all.
Sometimes it was an earthquake.
In San Francisco, sometimes it was a toxic insecticide.
Yeah.
It was a toxic insecticide spill in India.
He remembered.
Yeah.
It might be a secret government cover-up one other month.
But it was still basically the song that refused to die.
Sometimes it would be a radio show.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O.
Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Give me back the burning wall.
Give me a start in St. Paul.
I've seen the future, brother.
It is my dawn.
It is your dawn.
Things are gonna slide.
Slide in all directions.
Move and nothing.
Won't be nothing.
You can't measure anymore.
The blizzard.
The blizzard of the world has crossed the threshold
and it's overturned the order of the soul.
When they say, they say, repent, repent, repent, repent,
I wonder what they mean.
Amen.
When they say, they say, repent, repent, repent, repent.
I wonder what they means.