You may think your husband has never killed a man, but you're wrong.
And before I take him in to face the charges, he'll try to kill me.
I love you.
But first, are you experienced?
Are you experienced?
I'm experienced.
There's a lady who's sure all that glitters is gold, and she's buying a stairway to heaven.
And when she gets there, she knows if the stars are closed.
With a.
Word she can get what she came for.
Whoa, and she's buying a stairway to heaven.
There's a sign on the wall, but she wants to be sure.
And you know sometimes words have two meanings.
In a tree by the brook, there's a songbird who sings.
Sometimes all of our thoughts are misgiven.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tiny Tim with Brave Combo, friends.
And before that, some Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh and some Mr. Fernanda Nandae Lemur.
And some ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
More of all of that coming up, friends, as we OD on far out grooviness on the backside of reality.
Man.
I mean, dude.
I mean, you're not going to make it.
I'm just going to make it.
Baby.
Finally, you're a baby.
Pulverized peanuts.
Rye your own fresh meat.
Forever.
Free.
Chopper.
But then the stranger's path got darker and darker.
And the baby lost his way.
And the baby got old.
And the baby got fat.
And the baby didn't like himself too much anymore.
And he died.
He died.
Yeah, but we have to never forget
We have to never forget that he was a baby
And babies are good
And babies are strong
Maybe the best of everything
None of that Lunk from those Lunk heads
Oh, there's a bunch of those Lunk heads on my block that do they smoke that Lung junk?
Oh, yeah. Oh
There's one of those Lunk heads right now
Hey, man, where do you guys get that that Lung that Lunk? Well, it's just for oh, that's right
It's from the guys who've been smoking
Lunk their whole lives
Well, you could get it a Chinese doctor to from their lungs. That's where you get the Lung
Right, it's actual scrapings of their mustard flavored lungs. Is that how they do it? They scrape it? Yeah, they have to scrape it
But it has to be
Dislocated first. It's very dry
When is this guy gonna run out of semen someday? When is he gonna get around sperm or whatever it is? It's making him do that
That's actually
Something more dangerous to the human race
It's love man
He's feeling me low
Sister, don't you do what your baby sister done
Oh, yeah, baby
Oh, yeah
Oh, solid 100% Amar
That guy irritates my stumps down sometimes. I don't know why he should be irritated
Here comes the pain!
You've got to just do it yourself man. You become the oh yeah channel
Become flow group
They're not even foot with it identify yourself as if like a neural circuit was bypassed here the whole cavity no like one with it one with it
Become an escape for a nation of ignored you many parents too busy to stop
Listen
And love
Now get a job
We're in with a little bit of space. Oh, yes, it's best to use this little mouth for him
Bob said I'm gonna give you drugs
Bob said I'm gonna give you pills
Bob said I'm gonna free him from the false flag of the conspiracy
He's a son of water
He's a god that set fire
He's a pyrocladulator
Three and three year olds can't breathe
Hi there, Mrs. Garibald
Okay
And so she had found the answer to his question
That's right
Tell him all about it
Okay
Bye
Here comes Mrs. Darvon again in her nice soft dress
Hi, Mr. Valium
Hi
Well, today we're going to make sure that everybody feels okay
That's a really long picnic they're having
Yes, they're eating Kool-Aid and pills
Oh, baby, Abelina
Yeah, well
Exy Owl
Miss Valium
How in the world are you?
Well, I'm sad today
Good
Take that
I want to do a warm up
There can be no such thing as a safe pleasure drug.
Even if it had no harmful physical side effects,
it would still be overused by some people who cannot get pleasure in other ways.
That's what's so sad.
Oh, I know smoking cigarettes causes cancer, but I can't stop.
But if them same folks told you smoking cigarettes in your automobile would corrode your engine,
it would be no more smoking in the car.
Now that's kind of sad.
Because they've manipulated us to the extent that these educational institutions ain't nothing but tricks.
Why?
Well, I didn't tell you this before, but he's an egg salad addict.
You mean he's hooked on it?
He's hooked. He's got a chicken on his back.
Yeah, well, too bad for him.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
As far back as educated men have recorded their history,
veils have been lowered to disclose a vast new reality,
rents in the fabric of man's awareness.
And somewhere in the endless search of the curious mind lies the next vision,
the next key to his infinite capacity.
How much did I learn over the years?
How's the start going?
A big piece of information,
That we don't actually know,
Thats, that, that was,
we, we want to know.
Then we want to know,
to experiment.
To experiment with the war in front of us.
ahhh...
on the chemical dumper.
You look puzzled, Peter.
Other than you're still plain Peter Wayne.
But don't worry.
It'll all be crystal clear
as soon as you cross over.
Consciousness expanding.
Properly induced
CE will give a subject full awareness
of capabilities never
known before.
The doses have been somewhat
shorter for me the last time or two.
Music
This is haviflop.
You can smell it. It doesn't smell like marijuana
at all.
It's got a very
pungent odor.
I don't like this stuff.
It is free.
We have to smoke it.
It's one of the rules.
We're talking about a
barrel of have a from we're talking about void a limitless void of have a frog right we're talking
about several alternate realities we're talking about your basic i mean about putting it in your
pipe yeah you take it hey guys yeah yeah over there yeah yeah i i just got a question for you
i saw you smoking and i was just wandering uh they ain't prop now is it uh it is oh oh hot damn
man man this is something i mean i've never seen prop before yeah i mean never tried it or
anything you know of course i'd really like to try it you know
You know, just a little bit, just to see what it's like.
Maybe compare it to something like marijuana or tobacco or banana peels, you know, whatever.
But just take a little bit, not a whole lot or anything like that.
Just enough to give me a hit, not enough to fill up my lungs or anything.
You know, just for me, I can try it? Really?
Ha! Oh, wow, man, that's really generous of you, man.
I think I will, thank you.
Okay, all right, I'm going to do it now.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, man, I'm just really nervous here, you know.
I've never tried FROP before, you know.
I don't know what it's going to do or anything, you know.
Okay, all right, I'm really going to try it now.
Um, it's not lit.
Oh, oh, it makes its own fumes.
Okay, all right.
You know, you don't have to light it for anything.
No, you just, you just suck on it.
All right, all right.
Okay, we'll give this one a try then.
All right.
Here goes nothing.
All right, I'm going to do it.
All right.
Yeah.
Ah.
Oh.
Man, that stuff got on top of me.
Yeah.
It got right on top of me, man.
Oh.
Uh, can I have some more?
You know, just a little bit, you know.
Not anything really major or anything.
Popes Lilith von Frau Mensch, believe it or not, doing frog.
Also heard much old, old subgenius media barrage material,
which included clips of Dick Gregory, Doctors for Bob, Old Outer Limits,
and of course, puzzling evidence.
And now more of that, plus the Firesign Theater
with some of the greatest dope humor of the 70s.
You know I've seen a lot of people walking around with tombstones
in their eyes.
But the push don't cut.
Ah, if you live or if you die.
My boy, if it's drugs you want, the old doctor can help you out.
Right this way.
Hey, get your hands off me. I don't want to leave.
Then roll up your arm and bend over.
Do you want regular or premium?
Oh, this is ridiculous. You guys are nothing but a pack of cards.
Drink me.
It may choke me.
Must be some way out of this.
I'll change the air. That's what I'll do.
Let's see, what have I got left on the climate control?
Uh, dust storm?
No.
Tibetan wilderness?
Land of the pharaohs.
Land of the pharaohs. That sounds great.
Deliciousairl ihren
unsterben.
Mama.
Papa.
Stop!
Where are the helpers?
I'm in my old dimension.
Over there
Where all the evil
wished
G business .
God damn
On the pusher
Oh darling
I remember when the least of your problems
Used to put you right to sleep
Oh not anymore Matt
Today's modern now a go-go woman
Just pops these simple little pills
Called Anger Dream
Swell demonstration eh Sarge
It's routine
Maybe but if the chief ever caught me taking these pills
He'd snap my head off
Here try one of mine
Oh yeah
Yeah the chief himself's been on these for a week
And he's a chump
Good open your mouth chef
No I don't like pills
It really does help take the trouble out of falling asleep
Oh
The haunting reality is
That any one of these addicts
Prostitutes
Or runaways
Could be your child
There was me
That is Alex
And my three droogs
And their enemy
Is the God centered family
Today drugs and alcohol
Have replaced baseball and football
As the national pastimes
We are producing a country
Without a future
Any punk will tell you there is no future
They don't think about it
They uh
They wallow in just now operating
They only have the present
Oh my heart is pulsing too fast
I shouldn't have done that much
Oh man Chase you gotta stop stiffing that stuff
That's mostly for like gay guys
You know
He's a lunkhead man
He's been doing lunk all day
That's not lunk man
Lunk is the decision
K kid
When he dies his lunk will go to the next generation of lunkheads
It'll be passed on down as if
If it were a little suitcase
Or perhaps a pair of socks dad used to wear when he was angry
I did too much M
M
What's M?
Oh that's about four letters higher than K
Oh
God damn
He's on the M mountain
I'm on the
I'm on Z man
I'm on the last
I was hanging out with the N kids last weekend
But that was a little too long
Too much for me
I was hanging out with the
I wasn't ready to go that far
Alpha group
N is
We here at Alpha World don't like to hang with other letters
The betas are negative
It's like null and void there's nothing
It's like you just do the N and there's just nothing
You're not high you're not low
You're not in the middle
You're gone you're on N
Yeah you're gone you're on M
There's no N hole because there's just nothing
There's not even a hole
There's a series of vapid zits and barks and short little unky sounds
No don't even talk about the O room
That's the hole
Oh man
That's when you do an O you go in the hole on O
God you guys are about to make me need to go do some P
You're about to yeah you're about to scare the hell out of me with your
My nipples are already sagging down little kinky letters
Let's go do some P man
Do you really want to
Mommy where's daddy
He's been gone for so long
Come on
seen my lonely knife in my mouth
I see it everyday
seen my ol- ....
Eyes آаааааа
I've got a work
It's like a vortex funnel sucking me down to the bottom of the ocean.
I was getting sucked down.
And you know, as much as I hate to admit it, it felt pretty good.
It felt pretty good getting sucked down in that vortex wave all the way down to the bottom of the ocean.
But God, I hate to admit it.
It felt pretty good.
But I hate to admit it.
Moving on down on the backside of reality.
My bad words on the side.
Riding the wave and stoking on my fine day.
Moving on down to the backside of reality.
Riding on my fine, stoking on my fine day.
.
Mojo can really play the drums.
He was stuck down in this group thing.
He was laying down on the backside of reality on those tracks.
Now how about the song Backside of Reality?
Our audience here is very familiar with that song.
We play it every week.
It was back in our acid days.
Back when we used to consume a lot of LSD.
Yes, I know that about me.
The Swingin' Love Courses at one time was a hippie LSD band.
Yeah, we don't really like that.
We don't talk about it.
We don't really advocate it.
We did expand our consciousness.
But I thought that you condoned contracted consciousness.
We condone contracted consciousness.
Yeah.
Expanded consciousness.
LSD.
So some of your music actually has been LSD.
LSD influence.
Right.
And that is...
What is the similarity here?
I'm reminded of the 60's garage bands.
That's like LSD.
Lollipop sugar donuts.
LSD lollipop.
Mushroom mountains appearing from the sky.
We got high on high doses of sugar.
That's what it was.
White sugar.
And we called it LSD just to cut of a joke.
And you would have visions and get into the backside of reality.
But actually it wasn't real drugs.
It was a pile of drugs.
You would actually drive the curl into the back into the vortex.
Right.
It's like the molecule.
Oh this is my favorite.
This is beautiful.
These vicious junkies and...
Now imagine a world where heroin...
was legal.
But possession of coffee was punishable by up to 50 years in jail.
In other words friends, think of a world where you could run down to the nearest convenience
store just about any time of day or night and purchase any amount of liquid heroin you
wanted.
A whole bottle of heroin would be about 3 bucks.
Or you could go down to a heroin den and sit and shoot up with all your shooting buddies
until about 2 am.
Then you'd get on the expressway and drive home.
Or if that matter folks, in the heroin world.
Where imagine that the authorities making heroin so much a part of their business world
that nobody closed a big business deal without having a few shots of smack with the client.
When there'd be billboards all over the roads for the coolest brands of heroin showing beautiful
models.
Skin popping.
A waterfall.
And on TV, well not only would there be all these ads showing your favorite sports heroes
shooting their favorite brand of heroin.
But in any party scene, any scene of any TV show where people were shown relaxing or having
a good time, well they're always taking a few little sniffs of smack.
Now the leaders of a world like that would have to be pretty insane, right?
I mean it'd be obvious.
It'd be obvious that the leaders themselves were not only heroin users but stood to gain
quite a bit from the whole population aside from a few anti-heroin fanatics leaning on
this substance to relax.
But let's take it a step further friends.
Imagine if these people made coffee illegal.
Cause they said it was addicting and it led to harder stuff like espresso.
But yet untold millions of people had been drinking coffee for thousands of years and
no one had ever OD'd.
You drink it and it sharpens you up a bit and then later you crash a bit.
But it was so illegal that the smugglers are getting fantastically rich having contraband
coffee beans flown up from South America.
And there'd be this whole subculture of bean heads.
People that were into coffee partly as a rebellion against the establishment.
And the whole reason that coffee led to harder stuff like espresso or NyQuil.
Or whatever.
Was because to buy coffee you had to go to a coffee dealer's house.
A pusher's house where you'd encounter people who were espresso users.
And on top of that a one ounce bag of coffee beans would cost like a hundred bucks just
for an ordinary Maxwell House grade.
And people would be arrested and spend their whole lives in jail.
Maybe even be executed for using coffee.
Which is relatively harmless.
While this whole planet of junkies was going scot free.
And that's why I'm here.
And President Reagan would be up there.
You'd see him in the news at, you know, partying with world leaders.
All of them snorting a bit of smack and shooting up.
Imagine what a horrible topsy turvy world that would be, friends.
Where they made a powerful central nervous system depressant not only legal but glamorous.
While an organically grown harmless bean off of a bush could wreck your life only because
of the laws against it.
But, but, we're an enlightened people here.
So just forget that little allegory.
You know, let's not get depressing about it, friends.
Let's just lean back with a good stiff drink and forget it.
CISCANS THAT DO ASSAULT.
ALSO ATTACK.
It doesn't exist.
Also it doesn't exist.
And they are shooting each other because of a new prize.
Billions of dollars in American money.
The hard earned or hard stolen dollars of America's heroin addicts.
If you want any of this junk huh?
Go to it boys.
But this young girl, 14 years of age, in the 8th grade, recently took 50 pills to take
her life.
She has slit her wrist and she's been into heavy drugs.
She's done this.
I've got super dynamic overdrive.
I'm operating in 10,000 revolutions.
My motor is being preserved because I'm operating in supernatural overdrive.
Are you certain you know what reality is?
No matter what I do to change it, normal I remain.
Normal can be just as bad as riding in a wheelchair.
Today, serious heresy is a deviant state of consciousness.
Not so much deviant opinions as having a kind of experience which is different from regular experience.
We are taught what experiences are permissible.
And therefore, if...
A person has so-called strange experiences and endeavors to communicate these experiences to other people,
he is looked at in a very odd way and asked,
Are you feeling all right?
Because people feel distinctly uncomfortable
when they realize that they're in the presence of someone who's experiencing the world in a rather different way from themselves.
They call in question as to whether this person is indeed human.
They look like a human being, but because the state of experience is so different, you wonder whether they really are.
And in rather the same way, in a very everyday kind of circumstance, when you're sitting in a bar drinking, and you find you have a drunk next to you.
And he turns to you and says, I say, uh...
And you sort of move your stool a little way away from this man.
Because he's become, in some way, what we mean by non-human.
We expect a high of about 65 degrees tomorrow, increasingly cloudy skies once again, with some rain in the forecast.
So I found this little dish, crawled in, and I must say I'm happy.
All right, boys.
Bob's got you hooked.
Bob's got a monkey on your back.
Hey, you know that...
Bob's doing something spooky again, ain't he?
That's what you're listening to, right?
Yeah.
That's the kind of Bob that comes up out of the shadows.
It's the kind of Bob that follows you home, man.
It's the kind of Bob that calls you up in the middle of the night and hangs up and suites you.
Hey, Doug, let's kill Bob, you know what I mean?
Yeah, hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
I have an espresso machine in there.
Espresso.
Yeah, what would you do?
I feel the need to express myself into a cup.
And then pour it back into the spot in which I once stood.
Pour it into my shoe, and I will be reborn again.
A man of caffeine.
Y'all get your little whiskey, get your little snort, get your little reefer, get your little...
You serious?
The same people that's fixing to kill you puts the drugs out here for you.
How many of y'all know that?
Let me see your hands.
Some of y'all got your hand up, got a reefer in your pocket.
And we sat in the Corova Milk Bar trying to make up our razzle-dazzle what to do with these guys.
And we were drinking the evening.
The Corova Milk Bar sold Milk Plus.
Milk Plus, Vellicet, or Synthamesque, or Drencrum, which is what we were drinking.
This would sharpen you up and make you ready for a bit of the old ultra-violence.
And they got your head so messed up, everybody got in their hide and don't like nobody else's.
Yeah, the whiskey drinkers have always looked down on the wine owners.
Reefer smokers now got an attitude about whiskey drinkers.
And all at once the cocaine snorters think they're more sophisticated than the reefer smokers.
And the coffee drinkers hate them all.
A lot of the evangelical leaders seem to have forgotten that.
Now we understand the drunk. We know what's the matter with him and it'll wear off.
But when quite unaccountably, a person gives a representation that he's...
suddenly got the feeling that he's living in backwards time.
Or that everybody seems to be separated from him by a huge sheet of glass.
Or that he's suddenly seeing everything in unbelievably vivid, detailed, moving colors.
You say, well that's not normal.
Therefore there must be something wrong with you.
We like you and should ignore you. But instead...
Makes... oh god it hurts, my headaches come back.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
If these headaches keep up...
Fuck. I'll go down in the medicine fish hole.
I'll go in the medicine fish hole if I have to.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Do you have any aspirin?
Jesus Christ, this thing hurts.
What are you guys frustrated about?
A festering? I'm not festering. It just smells a little bad.
He is festering.
Smells really bad.
It's like some pussy festering.
What a fessup, man.
There it is.
Hey, in France they pay extra for that.
Stop fessing, bro, man. You got me wrong, man. Stop fessing, bro.
Come on, you ain't puttin' no wood in my...
When you peel open the...
You open one of Dave's seeming boils. Inside of it there's a little Liberace sitting at a piano with a candelabra.
With a beautiful, beautiful...
Little blue room.
I'd like to...
And he's got a little boil on him.
With a tiny little...
Dave at a radio station.
Right on my Dave-uck.
I'd like to sing this song for my brother George and my...
Ranting insane.
Brother Dave.
Into the darkness.
My new brother.
The boil on my ass I've added to my entrec...
Entrec... entrec... entrec... entrec...
To my repertoire.
There's a little... There's the little Liberace.
Careful not to move around too quickly while I...
Tiny Libo.
Tinkle the high notes.
Now we zoom in on the back of his neck on that boil.
On that left-hand man.
And deep inside that boil there we see...
A little radio station.
A little radio station with loads and loads of...
Another little tiny Dave inside.
And on the boil on that Dave's butt is a little tiny Liberace.
And it goes in a loop like that forever and ever.
Like... Oh, look in the audience's eyes.
The molecular...
Lester Flatt and Earl Scruggs are watching Liberace.
Like super strings.
Exactly.
Stretching through a multitude of dimensions.
And the Johnny Rotten is in the...
All coexisting together.
The one thing they have in common.
The boils of music.
The boils of Dave.
Yes.
All the different octaves of spacers being...
And one day we may even, if our telescopes are powerful enough, see the remnants in the
scattering pattern of the galaxies through the universe.
Of the original big boil that exploded some 15 billion years ago.
And the original lonesome cowboy Dave's ass.
And as the boil expands...
It makes the sound of 15 octaves below B-flat.
It's your time here at Stinky World.
Your time again.
Was there a burst before the big boil?
Yeah.
It's always your time.
What came first?
In Stinky Town.
The boiler burst.
The boiler gave.
It expands as you expand.
It's as light as the hassock around your waist.
And as tiny as your little button.
You can fly now.
Kick up your flings and your damn baggage and fly.
Fly.
You know, Copernicus predicted this some hundreds of years ago.
But the Catholic Church tried to prove that...
The boil came first.
Well, they had the documents and they were in an Alexandria library.
And they had them locked up.
I guess they called him the mad monk.
He found the actual documents themselves and he was quickly burned by his own...
It's the background echo of the original exploding boil.
Background radiation echo.
MLKY expanded from that point.
Andromeda did so itself also.
Andromeda, the great swan.
Cossopia, the lady with all the hair.
And of course our favorite couple in the Tinky Tiny room, Ronald and McDonald.
Ronald Reagan and Nancy McDonald.
Well, I'd just like to say that every night when I see you, I know you're a great man.
And I close my eyes.
I think about you, America.
When I put on my Santa suit and Nancy and I...
It should be more like I think about nothing.
Because my brain is gone.
I'm sorry.
I can't think anymore.
Because I'm a freaking idiot.
And I was an idiot back when I was a governor of California.
It's taken me 42 years to realize this.
Ketchup is a vegetable and so am I.
Well, I'm not sure that...
They should have aired that thing.
Alzheimer's is not like...
They aired it out good.
Look, it smells again.
Like hell.
Alzheimer's is not like being a mindless vegetable.
It's like being in a Burroughs cut-up of your thoughts.
Yes.
Where it's just random cuts from one thought to another.
And you're wearing it on your head, waiting for Burroughs to shoot the apple.
It's like some kind of a bad acid trip.
Kind of, yeah.
Jack Kerouac was a very handsome man when he came back from...
Or a really good one, depending.
I would say that some люди nicely were...
You ain't the granddaddy of all liars
You're the good-natured of nature
They don't know that they're ugly
That's very funny
Happy, happy, joy, joy
Happiness Park
Happy, happy joy, joy
Joy
Happy Joy
We waste a grand many of our lives
Like the little critters of nature
They don't know that they're ugly
That's very funny
Happy Joy
That was Jeff Free
I suspect
His sexy voice
Juan B. His middle name is Juan B. Will B.
Jeff will be free, someday
Or he will be tied down and beaten with truncheons and hog hammers
A hog hammer, boy it's been a long time since I had a sandwich like that
Oh no that sounds like pseudo-homo-sexuality
I was just think about pig sandwiches for some reason
I've been around them
You know, that would be a good name for a bar.
Or a band.
Castro Street.
Hog Hammer.
Castro Street Bar.
Yes, indeed.
There's Cripple Creek, where everyone enjoys dressing up every day of the week.
Well, no.
Hog Hammer would be a real...
That's where the tough guys would hang out.
They'd wear a butcher's apron and a hat.
Yeah, the real tough guys.
And they'd do snacks around their necks.
Yep.
Hog...
Hog what?
Hog Hammer, baby.
Come on over.
It's hot and ready for you.
You know, Hog Hammer.
Yeah, fist to fist.
Hog Hammer, man.
I can understand what's going on there.
I don't think I'm riding down that trail.
Feast.
Feist.
Which way is the...
Faust-y little nightclub.
The clarinet room?
Hershey Freeway?
The Hershey Freeway.
I thought you were asking for the clarinet room.
You get it over on the west side there.
You know, you hang a left.
Yeah.
What?
You hang a left at Lake Erie.
A lonely street.
It's on Cliff Pallet Boulevard.
I guess I don't know my way around here.
Catch that exit off a lonely street.
No, but if you catch...
You carry a truncheon around and a bag of snacks.
A heartbreak hotel.
And a thermos bottle for a long enough period of time, you will find...
Next to a heartburn convenience store.
Yeah, next to a heartburn convenience.
A heart attack hospital.
Now, that woman is wearing a pig nose on her and a pair of devil horns, or am I hallucinating that?
They always come to more shows like that.
What's the difference anymore in this world?
As Pope Meyer used to say, if you...
In the 2000s...
In the 2000s, if you flap your wings and you fly, you're on drugs.
And if you flap your wings and you don't fly, you're in the 2000s.
Or if you have a bottle of water and a glow stick, you're on drugs.
Yeah.
Well, you know...
Well, no, you're just supporting...
You're not necessarily on drugs.
Or thinking of it.
You're thinking of supporting terrorists.
And, you know, in this decade of Big Brother...
On drugs.
Thought crime.
Yeah.
If you've thought about it, you're as guilty as if you don't.
Think about having a breast enlargement operation.
You're helping Al-Haqsa Brigade.
That's right.
Doper, man.
And the Brigadiers.
Thinking of having maybe a...
Not just dopers.
Tip enlargers.
A bunch of dopers.
Tip shrinkers.
Any kind of sex changers.
Opium smokers.
A freeway loader.
A bunch of dopers.
Skaters.
Skateboarders.
Snowboarders.
Snowers.
Yeah.
Boarders.
Puffy and Hooters.
Straight edgers.
I really hate straight edgers.
Dopers.
Bachelorettes with cleft palates.
And if you're not just a pink square of the exact right quota.
Oh, exact right partition.
Ethnician.
Oh, they still have that.
Okay.
Well, it depends on where you are.
You have to buy that down at the...
Wherever you are, you're going to be the wrong color for the job.
You're at the wrong gate.
We're back to chromatic indigens again.
Right.
And next year.
And all the places where you can broil.
It's like...
It doesn't matter what color you are.
This is the race.
You're going to ramp up to the slave loges.
You're going to be the wrong color for that job at that time.
Slavery, man.
The slave loges.
Yeah, the slaves get the loges now, Dave.
Not the balconies anymore.
And not the sidecars.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
It's just getting worse every day.
We complain, but we never do anything.
Like, what could we possibly do?
Could we go to the mirror?
Complain louder!
bach sendiri
barc delle salle
yeah
who's convinced nab
all the юли 같아요
I said I'll stop theriftsorry
the way you treat them when you...
Ehh... Ehh...
Stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby.
I said, stop up-up-upin' that dopey-dopey-moper-down mama.
Can't you see that you're givin' that poor boy trauma?
Because you kick him in the face, and then you punch him in the face,
and then you hit him in the knee and the hell off with what?
Stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby.
Ooh-ooh-ooh-oh!
I said, stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby.
I said, I stopped abusing that substance abuser now, baby.
Stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby
Because you kick him in the face, it's such a damn disgrace
The way you treat him when you feed him and you fuck shit his face
Stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby
Because you kick him in the face, it's such a damn disgrace
The way you treat him when you feed him
Stop abusing that substance abuser now, baby
Lonesome Cowboy Dave with Cinzia, Princess Wee, and Chaz, and Bob,
live at the Beachland Ballroom in Cleveland, November 15th.
Ah, yes.
Before that, lots of ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB.
Happy, happy, joy, joy by Wax, I think.
And we heard some Alan Watts and Doctors for Wotan from 1980,
mixed there with miscellaneous old stuff in the subgenius media barrage number eight.
This music in the background, by the way, was by Help-O-Pewy.
And incidentally, that Beachland revival, friends, we got some good recordings,
and there was no violence, despite Chaz's confident promises heard here on Speaker 9.
The human strange will be...
I'd like to ask one question, if I might.
Sucking the brains out.
Now that sounds like something I could use.
Imagine that.
Now, why...
You suck their wallet out, the human strange will suck their brains out.
Actually, it's...
Bob can have the soul left flapping around on the floor.
Yeah, the soul is really the most valuable thing in there.
That's the only thing that lasts forever.
Hot.
It runs out.
The brains go flat, but the soul is eternal.
They're effervescent, those cans.
Unless Bob huffs it, or sells it to the aliens to...
Remember, one huff off some of the good cans is enough to not only sky you,
but send you on a rocket to the tombs, backwards and forwards into time, space, continuously.
Oh, yeah.
Mortals can't do...
We can't do soul.
No, we can't do...
We can't huff up soul, because there'd be two...
Un-soul.
There'd be two packers in the same woodshed.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
There'd be two humbuckers in the same...
Oh, yeah.
...cabinet of Dr. Tackler.
A man...
A man who has masturbated furiously...
...and without relent for the past 25 hours, he's about to break the gink, gink, gink, gink, gink...
I don't know why you interpret the oh, yeah thing as masturbation.
I think it's more like a mantra.
It's like a...
Yeah, he is...
I can tell his neural circuits are frying.
It's like saying...
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Well, what kind of drugs do you think he takes?
I notice he has like two little holes in the top of his cranium.
Or, well, I don't notice, but I have seen him at a deviable and he has little holes there.
Oh, yeah.
Now, oh, yeah means listen in Espanol.
If you could just get...
Right.
Exactly.
Oh, we could say...
Oh, yeah.
That's why I don't think it's...
Oye, I think it's oye.
Yeah.
Oye.
It's like, listen.
You listen.
But, you know, it's not oiga.
Oye, listen.
Oiga esto.
Oye.
There are two kinds of people in this world, my friend.
Por la carajo, oiga esto.
Those who say oye and those who say oh no.
Those who give thanks and those who go,
take it where it's needed.
Yeah, it's like a ball of spittle that earns and yearns
to come out of your apple seeds.
That's where the lung comes from.
It's like a wholly concerted effort of all the stars and planets
trying to win you over.
That's Bob's secret destiny for you.
And good night.
There's two kinds of people in this world, my friend.
There's a lot more now, Chaz.
Nope.
You guys are going to stay in Chaz.
Those with guns.
There's two kinds of people anywhere.
Those who dig.
You dig.
When you leave this room, the effect will continue.
Inside of your own mind.
Inside of your own skull.
God, these normal souls are amazing.
You can drink them.
You can smoke them.
You can eat them.
I don't know.
Who knows what you can do?
You can even snort them.
I'm rubbing one up under my gums.
I'm going to try a line of this human soul here.
Excuse me.
I'll go.
Now that's what I call soul.
Let me try some of that.
Jesus.
That must have been a fairly intelligent normal.
Oh, no.
That wasn't a normal.
That was some of what?
God, I think I got some of his memories off of that.
How?
Yeah.
It's like I'm seeing this little woman in the 40s.
Just for a second.
That's probably the guy's mom.
Yeah.
God, you can snort their souls.
And these little primal memories.
You've just got to give them final unction and dry them out first.
Okay.
God, how long have you guys known about this?
I mean, was this something the Indians had down there?
Yeah, yeah.
It's too rainy to light a fire to smoke a soul a lot of times,
so they just dry it and keep it with volcanic rock as an absorbent.
Wow.
It's crazy.
They just grind it up and snort it through huge, huge caves.
They didn't have the technology to extract souls.
I mean, how'd they get them under pressure?
How'd they get them into the canisters?
They don't do it that way.
They just feed them the right amount of herbs and plants,
and the soul just drips out of the nasal and anal.
You're kidding.
No.
Why can't we do that?
We can if we've got the right pills.
It's kind of, you know, it's all organic.
I mean, you know, there's two ways you can extract.
You can go high technology,
or you can go with just,
kerosene and a couple of guys with bare hands.
Why did Bob set up these extraction machines?
Well, all you've got to do is you dig a little pit.
You dig a little pit in the ground, you line it with plastic, peg down with wood,
and then you put the body in.
A normal, right?
Yeah.
Any normal?
Any normal.
Any normal that isn't dead yet.
The stole is still in him, right?
Uh-huh.
Okay, then you cover him with kerosene and acetone,
and then you just jump up and down on him until it turns kind of green and thick.
Then you remove him, strain the liquid, then you boil it, and you add sulfuric acid.
But then there's some kind of ritualistic, I mean, what actually causes the transmutation?
Well, there's a group of people around the pit adding a psychic element of the alchemy, you see.
They concentrate.
Oh, yeah, because they don't have the soul amplifier.
Right, so it's done with psychic methods.
It probably doesn't cost them, you know, it costs them.
A couple of necklaces or, you know, a taper.
Well, they don't need electricity to do it.
Their pet taper.
The most expense they've got.
And it costs us a hundred grand a year to keep these things pumping.
Well, you see, we use a lot of...
And not to mention the bodies and the souls and getting rid of them.
See, the body dissolves.
Storing them.
The body dissolves in the solution completely.
Well, do you do up the body, too?
No, they just strain it out with a solid waste.
What do they do with that?
With that?
They press it into little cakes and burn it.
Like for fires and stuff like that.
They usually give it back to the guy's family.
How come this was...
How come the Western civilization didn't discover that?
Well, you see, it's because...
How come they haven't been ripped off yet?
How come we didn't rip them off?
Well, because we can pay for soul and get it a lot cheaper from them than doing it up here.
Because, you know, like down there, nobody complains if you go through four or five hundred bodies in one night.
You know, you can sit around and smoke all the soul you want.
I guess it would be kind of questionable to be digging pits in your backyard and throwing normal bodies in there.
Well, it's just little pressed cakes.
Noisy, if nothing else.
It's just little pressed cakes.
Most people barbecue on them later, you know.
You see?
Well, and then we've got to give half of them away to wherever they're taken on Jupiter.
Well, of course, the thing about...
That weirds me out, man.
A lot of things weird me out.
The fact is that you can't get any good soul here in the States, dry or liquid.
It's always been cut with something.
And I like my soul unstepped on myself, you know.
Oh, yeah.
They'll use monkey souls, chimpanzee souls.
Hell, they just take up crystallized...
It's probably two-thirds...
They just take crystallized emotions and mix them in, for God's sake.
I mean, you get a bad blast of rage mixed in with your soul, and the next thing you know, man, you...
That's probably what happened to me last week.
I think it put a lot of anguish in it, too, you know.
It just makes you depressed.
Whereas pure soul is nothing more than a psychic and, you know, almanic amplifier.
And, you know, if your soul's in good shape when you do pure soul, I mean, it's even better.
But, you know, like, you put...
Stuff that's been stepped on and mixed with monkey soul or alligator.
Yeah, next thing you know, your soul is...
It's tainted.
Very tainted.
Got holes eaten through it.
You know?
Uh-oh.
Running up demagnetized soul, bad golfer souls.
Yeah.
Can you imagine?
Oh, yes, dear friends.
G. Gordon Gordon.
Interviewed there around about 1985, maybe.
And you can learn more.
From www.subgenius.com.
You can also get free information about the Church of the Subgenius.
By writing the headquarters in Austin, Texas.
That's Post Office Box 204-206 Austin, Texas 78720.
For those of you with tape recorders.
For those of you with tapes and CDs to send me, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Send those to Stang, Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 4411.
411.
And our announcer will tell you what else you can get from J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius.
Calcium.
Uh, calcium.
That's right.
Disease.
Yes.
Calcium.
Cancer.
That's right.
Heart disease.
Cancer.
Diabetes.
Calcium.
Yes.
Acid reflux.
And?
Calcium.
Cancer.
Heart disease.
Disease.
Calcium.
Aging.
Yes.
Calcium.
Pain.
Sleeping.
High blood pressure.
Carpal tunnel.
And dizzy cells.
Muscle spasms.
Like a baby.
Pain.
Calcium.
Illness.
Yes.
Calcium.
What are we gonna bring?
Come on, Dr. Stang.
What are we gonna bring now when Church Air is running out?
What are we gonna bring now that Church Air is running out?
Dr. Stang.
What's your prayer, Stang?
Oh, God.
Come on.