Peter was talking the other day, and they were talking about nanobytes and kilobytes,
and I got god.com on my internet.
Hell with that stuff, Dobbs.
Dobbs is the ultimate computer with Dobbs.
It's not Dada, but Dada.
It's not Dada, it's Bulldada.
You launch this bit about how instead of ones and O's, it's B's and O's,
and the B's are kind of curved, and the ones that aren't quite an and and or gate,
or a plus or minus gate, it's kind of a minus and a sort of maybe minus sometimes gate,
which leads you to real strange conclusions a lot of the time.
Yeah, that's how the alien computers work.
Well, it's right, right, it's a stochastic resonant bob.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self Genius Hour of Swatch.
Welcome potential initiates and idiots,
and remain with us for the next...
...hour.
As we delve deeper and deeper into the infamous X-Day Drill tapes.
Yes, a couple of weeks ago, we just finished surviving the X-Day Drill 1996.
They're at Brushwood Folklore Center in Sherman, New York.
And there's so many tapes.
We're just going to start randomly going through these amazing preaching and music tapes
from this astounding event.
Uh, this morning, let us say a big howdy to listeners at WREK in Atlanta.
Praise WREK.
And so we shall proceed with this WOTAN jam.
This is the Swingin' Love Corpses combined with Bill T. Miller and, uh,
I think Pastor Craig, the Luciferian Initiation Fund or something like that.
It's amazing. It's horrible.
And, uh...
Ooh.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Where's that prairie squid?
I wonder if we ought to...
Yeah, if we...
If we put the squid out today, he's going to be pretty used by tomorrow.
And I don't want to have to throw him out before tomorrow
because I think we may unveil the squid on Saturday morning.
Because the squid is, you know, it's not going to live forever.
Yeah, I've got to figure out what to wear.
I really do have the squid, by the way.
I prefer the mountain squid.
Well, this is a Mississippi Delta squid,
which is not the...
They actually smell funny,
unlike a mountain squid or a straight prairie squid.
Well, the smell is an aphrodisiac all in itself.
Well, for some people.
No, the smell of a good rotting squid
inflames your pheromones all the way down.
It can twist up your DNA helix like an old mangled twist tie
if you're not careful, but the trip's an E-ticket.
Yeah.
So, which night should I get naked, Doug?
Huh?
Which night should I get naked?
Saturday.
Saturday night.
Okay, so I don't get...
I don't get the squid on my bustier.
We're going to rape Bob.
Jesus is going to nail him to the cross.
The devil girl for Sunday morning.
There may be violence.
There may actually be violence,
and if you're running around naked,
that would inflame even greater levels.
And we did have violence that Saturday night.
At one point, Dr. Legume brought out a globe of the planet Earth,
a normal, like, classroom globe,
but it was filled with blood.
And he had it hanging from the rafters
and took him a great big ol' hammer,
a big ol' Wotan-type hammer,
smashed that globe open,
splattering blood all over the sex-ecutioner from Guar,
who had thought he was on vacation
from being covered with stage blood for once.
But no, no.
And then following that, Dr. Legume...
Well, let's just listen to the tapes.
We really did crucify, or start to crucify Jesus.
The Lord Jesus Christ, who actually was there at the X-Day drill,
and in fact works in this office now,
and at the last minute decided instead to crucify
our short-duration personal savior, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
So let us continue with those Saturday night recordings.
Yes.
Thank you, brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I got the whole world in my hands,
and we're gonna wipe it out in just two short years.
Yes!
Some of y'all might have got a little bit of blood splashed on you,
but not as much as you're gonna have then.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters,
we're living in an age where you will see
the corpse of the old world and the broken bones of time.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah.
You don't need a weatherman to know which way the wind blows.
All you gotta do is follow the smoke.
Oh, yeah, because that smoke's gonna lead you right back
to J.R. Bob Dobbs' Mighty Pup.
Oh, yeah.
The conspiracy's against you, brothers.
The conspiracy's against you, sisters.
Oh, yeah, they want you to play the game.
They want you to cut your hair.
Oh, yeah.
They want you to get a job.
They want you to behave.
They want you to obey.
They want you to die.
Oh, yeah, brothers and sisters.
It's a sign!
Oh, yeah.
The Earth's going 90 miles an hour down a dead-end street,
brothers and sisters.
90 miles an hour down a dead-end street.
And Bob is just ahead.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Brothers and sisters.
Bob is just ahead.
Don't pass him by.
Run him down!
Whoo, brothers and sisters!
Whoo!
Oh, yeah.
The time has come for our most unholy rituals.
Oh, yeah, time is ticking away.
Time is ticking away.
Oh, yeah.
Got me a little calendar here.
Little visual aid for you.
Oh, my hands are so cold.
Got me a calendar.
It's an inspirational season's calendar.
It says on the inside here,
Upland Baptist Church.
But every day them Baptists
look up there on that wall
and watch the day go by.
There's a day.
They put that little X on their calendar.
But come July 5th, 1998,
it will be the final X.
X day, brothers and sisters.
And we're going to be there.
Can I get an amen?
Can I get a hallelujah?
Can I get a praise ball?
Oh yes, brothers and sisters.
I can see, I can see
the way that this is going to be going tonight.
Bob has lost his mighty pipe.
Whoo!
But we ain't going to let that stop us.
Oh no, brothers and sisters.
We ain't going to let that stop us.
We're going to party on pipe or no pipe.
Whoo!
Ah!
Everybody make some noise!
Legume now points out Jesus.
You stand accused, brother.
You stand accused of being Jesus.
And there's only one way I know of
that I could possibly...
could possibly deal with a man such as yourself.
Crucify him!
Crucify, crucify, crucify!
Crucify!
Jesus is now given the cross piece of the cross.
Grab that board, Pope Fred!
You, your cross piece brother.
You're getting dragged to the Golgotha!
Okay?
Crucify!
Now friends, it's difficult for me to explain the spectacle which now took place.
This crowd of subgeniuses followed Jesus, whipping him, scorching the Lord, yes,
walking slowly up the hill towards the Mount of Skulls that we had prepared up there
at the cost of several Bobby's logs.
Some of the subgeniuses are wearing masks that I handed out.
We had Satan, JFK, the Overman, and one of the Greys from the Gwar tour,
all whipping and chastising the poor Prince of Peace, who now works for me in this office,
all the way up the hill as the sun set.
Listen to the blood.
The thirst, the bloodlust.
Heal Jesus good!
Help him up!
Help him up, my friend!
Heal Jesus good!
Heal Jesus bad!
What is the law?
Oh, we must mend!
That you spill blood?
Now scourge him!
Here!
Crucify him!
Get up, you whips!
Get up, Jesus!
Up you go, staggers!
Come on, Mr. Sleazy, promoter, businessman!
Oh yeah, Jesus thought he'd be a rock star this time!
Get him on down!
Deceive him!
You hear me, boy?
No mercy here!
No Samaritan's hair!
No son!
No!
The pinkest of the boys!
All right, who has the sacred hammer and the sacred nails?
We must make a choice.
Someone must die here today.
Perhaps it could be Jesus.
Perhaps, though, we should give him another chance.
Who has done even more?
Who has done even more harm to our...
Jesus has probably not harmed the...
He's trying to help.
He's trying to make up for what his followers did.
Crucify the boy!
He came to...
He was born again in this world, saw what his followers, his fan club had done, and
decided to try to make amends.
And so came to work for J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Spare him!
But...
Spare or spare?
We need to prove our faith by killing just another messiah, another long-duration personal
saviour, or shall it be...
Shall it be more in keeping?
Shall it give us more slack, perhaps?
To kill Bob!
Kill Bob!
Oh my God, listen to this horrible, even more bloodlust now, when the crowd is given
the opportunity to kill Bob.
The Dobbs effigy, a really good one.
Is...
Applying the sacred nails.
Is hammered into the cross by Jesus and Dr. Legume.
Jesus will get you!
Bob has given up his slack for all of us.
Bob wore polyester underwear.
Nail that...
Nail hard, Jesus!
You know what it feels like!
Jesus is actually more of a plumber these days.
Nail that pipe to his face!
Now Jesus and Legume are joined by Satan, not the person in the devil mask, but the
prophet El Diablo himself.
In their shared hatred of Bob Dobbs, the big brother and the little brother, so long rivals,
Satan and Jesus now cooperating.
It's a lovely sentiment, I suppose.
And now the sacred stump, hauled up here by the sacred slaves.
You all had to be killed, by the way, after hauling the sacred stump.
Now, shall we...
Brothers?
Who here will help me hoist J.R.
Bob Dobbs up to hang and die?
I will help you hang!
Oh, they're all so eager.
A thousand Jews killed him in a minute!
And so the cross is raised and hoisted on high, and Jesus and the overman, Philo and
myself, step forward to spit on Bob, gambling at the foot of the cross, rolling dice.
Susie the floozy was washing his feet with her hair, and then washing her armpits with
her hair.
Burn him!
Here is your chance, friends.
Why have you proceeded?
Are there any among us who would add another?
He thirsts.
Spit upon him.
There's no man among you!
He thirsts!
And they gave him vinegar.
And Dr. Legume sprays down the Dobbs effigy with starter fluid, in preparation for igniting
the gigantic cross.
Where he burned?
And the Dobbs is ignited.
The flames leap into the air, as does the crowd.
It's a gorgeous sight, friends.
The Dobbs effigy, stuffed with children's pajamas by Dr. Legume, so as to be its most flammable,
lit up the eager faces of the worshippers as they watched the flesh of Dobbs melt and
splatter.
The
Dobbs effigy, stuffed with children's pajamas by Dr. Legume, so as to be its most flammable,
lit up the eager faces of the worshippers as they watched the flesh of Dobbs melt and
splatter.
The Dobbs effigy, stuffed with children's pajamas by Dr. Legume, so as to be its most flammable,
lit up the edge of Dobbs effigy, so as to be its most flammable, lit up the edge of Dobbs
effigy.
And then, we had to bring out too many little entschieden-to-be-mentioned subgeniuses with
Also, some subgeniuses brought out weenies and marshmallows and proceeded to barbeque
them off the burning Dobbs corpse.
The hell Jesus, now Jesus, now Jesus, now Jesus, now Jesus!
And then of course that wasn't enough.
And then we had to nail, we nigg'd on our deal and went ahead and killed Jesus as well,
friends.
It was such a lovely way of starting that Saturday Night Devival.
Actually, let's go on and see what else happened as we meandered back to the pavilion
where the Devival and the X-Day drill continued in progress apace.
Thank y'all.
I want you to know, all electronic gear, when I tap into the gear,
and I tap into Bob nightly, let me tell you, I tap into Bob 24-7.
And I'll let you know with our radionic equipment that Bob is doing just fine,
and he's got his hand in all your pocket.
So you make sure you cough up them dollars to Bob, or I'll basically strangle your ass.
He may be serious, I don't know.
He's new in the band.
Bob's jerking us off.
Let's play that song we practiced last week.
Yeah, let's play that one.
That one song that one guy taught us that one time.
Yeah, yeah, that one.
You know, last Wednesday night, we were sitting around on the fourth dimension.
My song, even though we'd never met, but we're so strong and down with Bob,
you don't need to be, you don't need to practice.
We can play through our noses, our Bob and our hearts.
Osmotic jamming.
Down with Bob.
If y'all are down with Bob, we're going to be there that day.
In numbers.
We're not going to be afraid.
We've got tomorrow with Bob in our hearts.
And if you got any frock, we'll smoke that before they come down, too.
We don't want to come down either, you know what I mean?
I don't know.
We don't want to come down either.
Osmotic jamming.
Or ecstatic jamming.
Hey, bring the damn band down behind me, boys.
Add!
Oh, yes, Reverend Susie the Floozy.
I know she's a very shy, withdrawn person,
and I don't want you to make her nervous or anything.
What's she going to do?
Susie's hardly ever been on stage before,
and this is like her first time in front of people.
I'd like to have a piece of her brain.
I know most of you probably came here from Atlanta
where you listen to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
the original Bob's Slack Time Funhouse radio show,
which name I stole from our website.
You bastard.
One at a time or all at once?
Can I stack them with one at a time?
Friends, sisters, Susan the Floozy.
Yes, give me that primetime religion, friends.
Oh, seekers, yeah, it's good enough for me.
Praise Bob.
Yeah.
Well, welcome to the Amy Sempleman Slack
Foursquare Temple Defiable Encounter Mutilation Center.
And Bob's Jack Shack back on Highway 69
on the way into town as our big sponsor.
So we're trying to stop there on the way back, okay?
Oh, yeah, welcome, seekers, to the X-State Drill.
We're just teeming with Oregon energy.
We can feel the Xs coming up over there.
They're rising.
And it's a good feeling because Bob's in the mood for a second coming
and a third coming and a fourth coming,
which is the special down at Bob's after Jack and Shack.
Out of the way.
Although you did still have to spend extra for the 5th, 6th, 7th, 8th, 9th, and 10th coming,
but the 11th one is again free.
Oh, so seekers, yeah, get ready to cook.
Because we're getting drenched in the breadcrumbs of slack.
And Bob's is going to be rolling us up and deep frying us to a nice crackly, crispy crunch.
And we're going to taste good, dip, dip, potty, some honey, butter, mustard.
Oh, I can't wait to eat that chunk of black.
Me neither.
Oh, so lucky upon this kettle of fish, oh, ye mighty, and despair, despair, big, too.
Because X-Day is on the way.
Oh, yeah, you can laugh about it right now, but it's just too short for your seekers.
And what are you going to do then?
What are you going to do when the Krypton lasers are slashing the skies overhead?
Where are you going to plug your laptops in then, huh?
All right.
I've done a little bit of thinking about it.
And now I figure the best way to do it is to take that despair.
Take that despair and fold it.
Double it back upon itself.
Fold it like this.
Origami.
Into a Googleplex of slack.
Slack sent straight from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Yes.
Oh, they may have burned his body, but they didn't burn his baby.
I mean, they can't burn his dream.
And as wet as that dream is,
we've got to follow it, seekers.
We've got to follow it every step of the way.
Because that's what my ministry is all about.
Yes.
I want you to take that despair and crack it like a whip.
Use it against the world.
Because when you're absolutely on the bottom,
there's nowhere else to go but up.
Unless you can dig.
And you're a deeper pit.
And Bob is that divine entrenching tool
that enables you to steam shovel your way out of your troubles
until you blast out the other side.
Preaching.
Oh, preaching.
Yes.
So that's what my ministry is all about, your seekers.
Because I'm handing out shovels, sinners and sinnerettes.
You there, take this garden trowel and see what you can do.
Sister, there's a Bobcat front-end loader waiting for you at the end of the day.
You there, take this hoe and don't treat her too rough.
And let's see what we can do to help Bob along.
Because we need to wake up and smell the slack.
We're all getting older and today is the first day of our last hurrah.
And you better start living like it is.
Because if you don't, you're not going to live.
And if you don't, there'll be nobody to blame but you.
You can't blame the nasty old Amhadona conspiracy.
Because we're down here on the street corner.
We're in that ice cream truck of slack.
You hear that little ding-dee-ring-dee bell ringing.
And you figure, oh, I'll come down later and get on Reverend Susie's gospel bus for Bob.
Yeah, there ain't that whole much that much later to go around, seekers.
Yeah.
You can't monkey with her because the lifetime supply's not that good a deal anymore.
So it's time to get right with Bob.
Get left with Bob.
Get in and out with Bob.
Up and down with Bob.
Yeah.
Yes, baby.
Because if you don't come next day, Neagie is going to be munching your well-buttered butt like a Betty Fwock.
So don't go crying to me.
Praise Bob!
Yeah!
Oh, Susie!
Oh!
Yeah!
Oh, oh, Jesus.
Yes, perhaps the goddess is right.
Or left.
Who, who laid, who put, as Susie said earlier, who put the lay?
In Dr. Lake Hume.
What?
Who put the Hume in Dr. Lake Hume?
Oh, uh, Father Joe Malman, is that you standing over there in the dark?
Yes, you do.
Yes.
It seems how the band members don't seem to have enough air.
All drunk, half-way passed out now already, I guess, after Bill Miller.
Oh, and the Luciferian Liberation Front, of course.
No, we have to leave.
And?
Friends?
You may think it could be a long night, yes.
It could be a much longer two years.
If you don't get straight, get right with Bob and listen to the word this time of the great Papa Joe Mama.
Praise Papa Joe Mama!
Yeah!
In 1941, the German death routine roamed over Europe with difficult efficiency.
Death to the Untermenschen, destruction of all inferior subcultures.
Long live the Reich, the German Reich, that will last for a thousand years.
At the head of that crazed war was one Adolf Hitler, a maniac determined to have world domination.
He started his revolution in the early 30s, carried a plague through the streets.
He was shot by his own police force and hauled off to prison.
Many of his comrades were also shot.
Their blood was splattered on the very plague that he carried through the streets.
That plague was later called the blood plague.
He used it to anoint all of the guidance in the Reich.
When the war came to a close in 1945, the word was out.
Quote Stalin, bring me back the blood plague!
The Soviets swarmed over Berlin searching for the plague.
Even though every major leader in Nazi Germany was brought to justice, the blood plague was still there.
The blood plague was never found.
It's still out there, my friends.
And now, we too, have blood on our legs.
This blood comes from that world, a replica, a symbol of the world we shall conquer.
Only we will not be conquered by any allies, of normals or pinks.
For we have here a sacred document of our own.
A document which I would like to read.
I will read it to you now.
It's entitled, Watering Down Dobbs.
Because it's my sad duty to report to you, friends, that even as I speak, the conspiracy has embarked on a sinister plan of subgenus genocide.
Yes, my dear friends, that means you and me, brothers and sisters in the faith,
are involved in a sinister plot against us devised by the conspiracy
to undermine our great genetic heritage.
It is a true punch below the belt, for that is precisely their target.
To sabotage our seed.
To pervert our progeny.
For the conspiracy is set out to destroy our race by robbing our men of their precious bodily fluids.
Are we going to allow that?
No!
Did I hear a hell no?
Hell no!
Yet, as disgusting as it is to contemplate, it is true.
They ought to inbreed with us, forcing Bob to let the remains of their lineage live so that half of his own flock may flourish.
But they don't know Bob, do they?
He would rather die a fourth time than let the con continue.
They've hogged the hell long enough, and look at the mess they've made.
Just look at it.
Disgusting as it is, it's all theirs, and they are to blame, are they not?
Hell yes!
Only Bob has the courage to take a steady hand in the helm and lead us through the reef.
Only Bob is a leader that can fight the current.
A captain who can keep the ship on course.
That captain is Bob.
And that ship is the Exus Fighting Class Star Cruiser.
Both man and machine are en route right this instant at full light speed.
They shall arrive in two years hence.
But what, you might ask, would good old Captain Bob think if he arrives and finds his crew fraternizing with the enemy?
Hugging them, kissing them, and, Bob forbid, doing the waterbed backstroke.
You simply cannot do this with members of the opposite sect.
This is not a rhetorical question, friends.
It's already happening all over the world thanks to the conspiracy mass marketing campaign to love one another in the name of tolerance.
Oh, the hypocrisy.
The hypocrisy!
How can the conspiracy, who routinely persecuted our people throughout history, even pronounce the word tolerance with a straight face?
They should fear being struck by lightning for daring to remind Jehovah of their crimes against the chosen race.
But no.
No.
Now that the industry, they pretend to be our friends.
Oh, and are they not our friends?
Well, they're not.
And, uh, Papa Jo Mama will continue.
They pretend to be our friends.
They say the subgenies are intolerant because we don't want our children reproducing with their ilk.
They call us old fashioned because we don't want to dumb down to their level.
They taunt us.
They label us.
They claim we're out of touch.
Well?
Perhaps we are out of touch.
Or perhaps, just maybe, they're mad because we don't want to touch them.
But that's not our fault, friends.
It's theirs.
I mean, just look at them.
They're like filthy little rats scrambling through the maze of life in search of the cheese quiz they smell but can't find.
They never suspect that the conspiracy moves the goal every time they near it.
Nor do they notice that the clever ones of them are busy, abducted, and dissected to discover what went wrong.
No, sir.
These lowly creatures actually think they are worthy of our company.
Nay, they are cruel to us all.
Now, now, we don't like to be cruel to animals.
But we don't even really want to hurt their feelings.
But really, what else can we say?
Vermin are vermin and there's no two ways about it.
Hell yeah!
Even if we could love them.
Like, say, a pet.
What would be the point?
We'd still have to kill them once X-Day arrives.
I mean, otherwise the X's won't come.
After all, who wants property that's infested with rats?
Do you want property infested with rats?
Hell no!
Do you want property infested with pigs?
So please, let's be reasonable about this.
I mean, let the normals enjoy the last few minutes.
Let them enjoy the last few days with their own kind.
We'll smile and we'll be patient.
We'll even open the doors for the women.
And we'll let their men cut in front of us on the highway.
But we can't let them taint our race with their own bloodlines.
That just won't do.
If they want to mix their blood with someone else's,
just tell them to wait till X-Day.
There'll be plenty of blood mixing then.
Why, some of that blood may even be ours.
Why, sure.
We expect them to struggle.
We'd do the same if we were in their shoes.
I think it's only sporting.
We'll give them the same chance that they gave us when they were in charge.
Like they say, fair's fair.
So let's be honest with one another.
Our separation has nothing to do with intolerance or hate.
It's just plain common sense.
Why would anyone want to become friends and mix with the mud race
when a storm's coming that's gonna wash all the dirt down the drain?
We can be as sympathetic as anyone else.
But don't ask us to be stupid.
When you lie down with dogs, you get up with fleas.
It's as simple as that.
There's no such thing as safe sex with the normal.
Unless, of course, you're necrophiliac.
We don't believe in getting pinks a single inch of what they want.
Let alone ten.
Because we know whatever's pink on the outside
is usually pink on the inside.
Now me?
I'm just an humble preacher.
But I say it is more blessed to spill your seed
than to plant it on cursed ground.
Stamp out the noxious weed of normalcy
and sow the earth that gives it root.
For if thy penis sins against thee,
cut it off and cast it away.
For what profit the body that perish for the part?
Hearing is the word of all praise, Bob!
Praise Bob!
Felt good.
And now we have a few words from
Who Shall Stand Forth Reverend Stang.
However, those of you who are alt-flaggers
will most surely be ready to hear the
four-dimensional preaching
of the great Dr. Dinosaur.
The silverback,
the, the, the, the
oldest and wisest of all the alt-flaggers,
on there since before the internet even began.
Again, accompanied here by Steve Slack.
I have no earthly idea what is about to happen.
Except for that. I knew that was going to happen.
And so, Dr. Dinosaur is Steve Slack.
And now, the great Dr. Slag.
He is the one who will be
Well, praise Bob, brothers and sisters,
I'm glad to see y'all here.
And I'm really glad to hear you enjoying the Nanjon music.
It's kind of rough for some of the big folks out there,
and even some of the unsaved Yeti,
to understand it all.
And we're here because we know.
Well, now, what do we do about those folks that don't know yet?
Like the book says, there's a lot of unsaved Yeti out there.
Some of this coming on is awful weird, don't you think?
Oh, yeah.
Well, it damn well better be.
You don't want it to be normal, do ya?
No!
Well, they can't quite handle it.
So, sometimes we gotta come on to them in a way
that they can understand a little bit better.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Back when I got started,
coffee houses and whatnot were in vogue.
You could hear all kinds of music from guys sitting down with guitars like this.
Well, it's time we do a little outreach to some of those folks
who think they're still kind of normal.
It sounds a little more normal,
but it's by Bob!
Bob the Worst Slack!
Yeah!
Hear that?
Yeah.
Well, what good would a church be without a hymn?
Yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you a hymn.
For the Church of the Subgenius.
Oh, Yeti sinned from ancient times.
Walk unto Dallas seeking grain.
And was the smiling face of God's on myriad sea rocks seen?
And in the grim and pipe divine,
summon the wool on which to pull.
And, Worse of Genii, I summon Tear to praise Bob and be slack-full.
Bring me my pine with burning gold.
Bring me my salesman's holy fruit.
Bring me my slack, this I must have.
Bring me my saucers of release.
I will yet feed my mental life upon the pigs throughout the land.
Yeti, awake!
Atlantis, rise!
And we shall ponder into sand.
For folks born who can't whiff a thing
Ooh, they got no foot plan
When the saucers land on the roof
They'll stick their heads in the sand
It ain't me, it ain't me
I ain't no human son, no, no
I ain't no little pink one
Some folks are born with no wife at all
All they got's one soul
And when the exes take him on board
They'll be down in the hole
It ain't me, it ain't me
I ain't no me puppet son, no, no, no
I ain't no little pink one
Some folks in Harry's know yet his genes
Ain't like you and me
I say we go grab the chainsaw
Kill that evolutionary tree
It ain't me, it ain't me
I ain't no me puppet son
No, no, no, it ain't me, it ain't me, I ain't a little pink one, no.
Anybody who hasn't heard it, I know this hurts, but 7 o'clock tomorrow morning, 8 hours from now, I'm going to be here for my main little rant.
Actually, you should be here about 6.30, or a quarter of, so we can get the pills passed out to everybody.
As I said before, don't touch those pills before 7 o'clock when we announce that exact time.
I believe I had somebody who had the correct time.
Those pills simulate the rupture.
And it's important that we all be sort of in sync.
If they last exactly 51 seconds, we will be timing that.
And we'll probably do a little bit of chanting and so forth.
I'm saving most of my ex-day stuff tomorrow.
It says here, don't reveal too much, okay?
Put flyers in bathroom, trash, the sacred trash bags, remember your recycling and so forth.
I don't want to have to apologize to Brushwood for the messy, sloppy, anti-ecological subgeniuses.
Yeah!
Should have the iron on wings of slack tattoos tomorrow when the sales table is open.
And as a sort of a contrast, a counterpoint, shall we say, to the good Dr. Dinosaur.
Now, I think the bad Reverend Nikki Death Chick has a little activity planned,
which she may be inviting volunteers up here.
Reverend Nikki Death Chick, the latest new employee of the Great Subgenius Foundation.
Thank you.
Reverend Nikki Death Chick.
I don't really have a lot to say.
I just have a few things to do.
I just want to say a few things about guilt.
Guilt is the conspiracy's way of preventing you from gaining slack.
We don't need guilt.
We need a way to remove guilt.
In the conspiracy's religions, there is a system of punishment that they give to you.
I have devised a ritual in the Church of the Subgenius whereby you not only get your guilt removed by punishment,
purification,
through pain,
but you get slack through the benefits of the punishment,
and Bob benefits as well because you tithe unto Bob
when you donate a love offering to me for administering upon you the Subgenius spanking ritual.
I need volunteers right now.
Scores.
Who will be able to come up here and give me a love offering to spank them and remove?
Their hideous guilt.
Who is it?
Come forth.
Yes.
I am guilty.
What are you guilty of?
Oh, you name it, honey.
I just, I tell you what, I love to be punished.
I really, I really enjoyed being tied up last night by those great, big, strong women.
I like to see strong, strong women.
I don't like weak women.
I'm a weak man.
I'm not a bad man.
I'm just a very bad, sacred.
These are just some of my favorite things.
I'm never going to be described as a right man.
You gotta put your hands up, hands up, on the podium.
Okay.
Do you feel the guilt?
Do you feel it?
I want the guilt.
Harder.
Do you feel the guilt leaving?
Do you feel it?
Good.
More, more.
Let's go.
Oh, God.
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay.
Anybody else?
Come on, come on, give it to me, give it up, give it up, right now.
I didn't have to say what I was guilty of.
Well, tell me, what are you guilty of?
I want to be obeyed by a thousand different women every day.
That's very, very bad.
Do you need more?
Uh, that's enough.
Okay, give it up.
Okay, anybody else?
Come on now, anybody else?
I want another one.
Okay, come on.
Oh, they're okay.
Oh, what?
Oh, if there are any even bigger, stronger women, I still feel a little bit too much guilt.
Time for some violence.
Oh, some sex and violins.
Oh, it's gotta be bad.
Did I court your place for clay?
Yeah.
Can you learn some Phil Washington speak?
Let me get changes here.
Let's see...
firefighter while all other things are this, so...
back to normal.
was that it It looks at
And it's going to
It's going to
he
what do you think?
You'll do great.
that's awesome.
Love you and take care of yourself.
Bye.
Bye bye.
See you.
Bob is a rabbi!
Help!
Yes!
You're a lot closer than you even think!
Bob is the way!
Bob is the path!
Believe or die!
Oh no!
Oh my god!
Don't kill us, you fucking ball-digger!
Jesus!
Bob is not the answer!
And neither is A.J. Graff!
He's ripped me out for all my sake!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, not yet!
Bob, Bob!
You're gonna have to work harder than that!
The power of Bob compels you!
He's a pink boy!
Bob is the apple of my eyes!
He loves you, Bob is kind!
He gets all the crap!
He gets all the women, and he gets all the slack!
This may be true,
but how would you get slagged if Bob
does not first have all the slack?
I want my slack! I want to kill Bob!
Maybe you have a choice, uh, maybe, maybe you have a choice.
Come on, join me! Kill Bob!
Kill Bob! Kill Bob!
Kill Bob!
Bob's a conspiracy patty!
It's true.
Bob faked his own crucifixion so he could be resurrected
and become your personal savior!
We need to kill him for real this time!
Grab your finger, Bob, and whack his little head off!
This is not a joke!
It feels so good!
Bunkie-Doh is lining up for the fight!
Oh my god! He actually got him!
Kill Bob!
Oh my god, his eyes are rolling!
The mannequin head is almost totally destroyed!
A $50 mask is senselessly good!
Kill Bob!
By the power of Bob,
I've cast out the control!
I've cast out the conspiracy demons of the
rude McDonald's clerks!
The conspiracy demons of
blabbering Bobby assholes!
I've cast out the conspiracy demons of
people who don't buy OBE CDs!
I've cast out
the conspiracy demons that have been
holding this man down!
I've cast them out!
The power of Bob compels you!
Save baby!
Save! Save!
Save him, Andy!
High Drop!
Arggh!
It's only one thing to do!
Baseball!
upmauempoparial.com
Please fill me in head first
I promise to have Ylva!
Gratitude!
we have a very special guest
brought all the way up here from Oklahoma
and a crate. Is she still here?
Tarla Stark.
The home of man.
The symbol of the internet.
The Suzie the floozy of old slap.
Do it! Do it!
Yes baby, I give it up.
To Sister Tarla Stark.
Woo!
Ladies, gentlemen, and sisters.
Tarla, Tarla, Tarla.
So let's heat things up. I heard you all like sex.
Yes!
Give us sex!
Well why don't we do this one.
Hot, sweet chocolate.
Dip a finger in and lick it off.
Candied oranges with a jelly bean in between.
Red hots, hot to try.
Gobble it up sweet.
Spicy.
Served on a lace panty.
A neck of wafer wedged in marshmallow.
Fat free, sugar free.
Endlessly renewable.
Have your bonbon and eat it too.
Praline in meringue.
Jordan almond wrapped in divinity.
Don't worry about it getting too hot.
It melts in your mouth as well as your hand.
Woo!
There's a little tattoo on the candy store door.
It says, thank you for coming.
Have a nice day.
Yes!
Sister Tarla!
Woo!
Give us more sluts, sister!
Yes!
Let me do a little bit of a piece of something to my favorite herb.
And I believe yours.
Oh, never cross your words.
Garlic?
This one I call Mary Jane.
Sweet girl, I have loved you for so long now.
You are in my heart.
You are in my blood.
My comfort, my sanity, my red haired vixen.
I love the scent of you.
The taste of you.
Bitter and smoky sweet.
In the darkness, I open myself up to you.
Roll you with my eager fingers.
Swallow you down.
There is never enough.
Those withered men who call us names and scorn our love.
They will pass from this time.
Taking their chains and blindness in tow.
And on that green day,
those of us who have been with you for so long,
who have been true and faithful,
who have cradled you through the nightfall,
shared you in secret and called you sister, lover,
will set you aflame.
Burning, burning, burning.
Yeah!
This is my kind of poetry, man.
This is a little piece I like to give
Stange's daughter credit for too,
because she gave me the title.
This is Wake Up and Smell the Dead.
There's a place I own in Stange,
a place I have hidden inside you.
A place where in retrospect you will believe
that my smile was the brightest,
my eyes the wickedest,
my mouth the most cunning,
and my wit the most cunning and urbane.
My mouth will become in memory
the most cunning creation that God ever laid his hand to.
You came to me young.
What did you expect?
A tabula-rosy girl with an empty head
and a dewy heart,
ready to be filled with lies?
Well, I could have been that.
I could have been a playboy,
a powder puffed tail like a searchlight
to draw your eyes and make you squirm.
I could have been nothing more
than a soft well of cleavage,
a warm wet fantasy
with moist lips,
an easy to understand vocabulary
and a list of hobbies that always included fellatio.
I could have been the kind of woman who pretended
to enjoy the burgeoning bludgeon
inside your heart-shafted remarks.
I could have been there.
I could have been on Oprah or Sally
or Jenny or Montel,
or the trailer park woe,
wearing a hard, thin line of black around my eyes
in my best K-mark
Jacqueline Smith rhinestone sweater,
tawdry but teachable,
a girl to be saved
and molded gently into a tight, quiet prisoner,
afraid of losing everything I had learned to need,
faking orgasms
and making up for it later
with a charge card,
a home shopping network,
a stash bottle of Jack Daniels
and a Panasonic dual speed.
I could have done that.
I could have been so in love with the word
that you would have had to take me in the library stacks
smearing Joyce and Thomas,
yes, Hemingway himself,
with the pearly effluvient of our literary passion.
I could have loved the word so much
that I would have walked around with pebbles in my pockets
mumbling like Virginia Woolf
or cooing quietly to myself
like a pigeon on the grass, alas.
And because I could not stop for sex,
it would kindly stop for me.
I would have been so grateful for your instruction
that I, Easton Inn, would be put to shame
and praised at your research skills.
I could have been that.
I could have been any one of a number of fantasies,
an interesting side path
on whatever idea you had of perfect love.
But I was none of those things and more.
I was the thing you never dreamed of,
the thing that made you wake up in the night
wondering at the newness of it all.
Plaid boy,
all straight lines and intervals
and expectations
you could have never predicted me.
And since you didn't kill me when I left,
I guess you'll have to love me till I die.
Whooo!
Yes!
Can you get a drink of water
before I do one last piece?
I'd like to close this evening's
cultural renditions
with the Industrial Church of
Love and Money.
My ticket to salvation
is a 3 x 2 inch square
of printed white pasteboard
stamped with the name J.R. Bob Dobbs
so that when the time
of rending and pain is upon us,
I will be lifted up
into the safe, soft arms of otherworldly goddesses,
and serve forth the pleasures of all flesh satisfied.
And the squid will anoint me with their perfect
and malleable bodies, till I am rendered quivering
and senseless, a shell of skin housing purest slack.
From below will raft the faint cries of humans
as they ignite and implode.
But please, for mercy, the promises never before
made in sincerity will be transformed
into a harmonic chorale of my vengeance.
And all the while, the squid will anoint me.
The years of swallowing my own bile,
along with the machinations of them,
the hustlers and entertainers, the preachers, teachers,
and government whores, the arbiters of taste,
encouragers of waste, the sanctimonious chaste,
the Barbies and Kens, the little red hens who say,
will you help me?
When what they really mean is, I have no brain.
Please tell me what to think.
You know, them.
Those years will be washed away
in a wave after endless wave of a joy beyond
10,000 simultaneous earth-moving orgasms
as the squid anoint me.
When I leave this place, so unappreciative
of my true genius, on a sunny July morning some days hence,
do not fear for me, for that perfect body, I'm hiding,
that I've been slaving so hard to achieve and maintain
will be mine in the flash of time it takes me to decide
just how big to make my eternally perky breasts.
Yes.
I am going to a place beyond my most monstrous fantasies,
into the realms of elder gods.
Or at least that's what they tell me.
I couldn't read the fine print.
Pass that pipe and pray.
Yes!
Newer!
Newerbox.
all sorts of retarded brothers to love.
Gorsh, Sister Susie,
can I put my finger between your naples?
No, why, Chainer, that's not your,
those aren't my naples.
Uncle Chainer molested you, too.
Oh, Cousin Susie, that ain't my finger neither.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to,
got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Woo!
Pray now.
Pray.
Have faith in God.
You are going to stand up.
We are listening to Jehovah Hates Fred.
Thank you.
What do you like?
I don't know.
You just know you're not.
Have faith in God.
I'm just going to think the tape's put in the wrong way.
It's going backwards.
Have faith in God.
We're filling your mind now with subliminal messages
saying you will give me,
say it again,
all of your money,
if you are over 16 years of age,
and you have the female persuasion,
you will give me.
I'm sure.
I don't know if that's information.
Are you just asking for your opinion?
I'm just going to sit down on the floor
and do what the nice Andrew tells you.
Okay, for our last song,
we're going to do Bob Don't Live Today by Jimi Hendrix.
Yeah.
All right, you go, Andrew.
Strut that stuff.
Will I get slapped tomorrow?
Bob just don't say.
Will I get saved tomorrow?
No.
Well, I know for sure.
Bob don't live today.
No.
He got showcase.
If you get a Die Hard sold.
Whoa, leave it to the
Today, he got shot dead back in LA.
As if Bob Don't lives today.
There's no slack anyway.
There's no f***ing slack in this world.
It's the X's when they come.
It's gonna be in 2998, cause Stag and the rest of the crowd forgot to carry the one from the three scriptures.
Sorry, it's all over. We are not going to be saved.
Bob Don't lives today.
The pipe is broken.
Gone away.
But Bob Don't lives today.
The X's have passed us underway.
The conspiracy is one man.
The words of the swinging love pox is totally f***ing bad ass bummer, dude.