Dear friends, everything you're about to hear is from July and August of 1994.
This is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 457, Lonesome Cowboy Dave in space.
Hi everybody, nice to be back with you.
Well, first of all, I bring a personal message to Dr. Howell, who has asked me to convey his deepest appreciation to all of you for the many sacrifices you have made.
And of course, his congratulations on your discovery, which may well prove to be among the most significant in the history of science.
Listen, Howell.
There's never been a time when you've been so grateful.
There's never been an instance at all of a computer error occurring in an i-1000 series, has there?
Of course I have.
Sorry about this.
I know it's a bit silly.
Just a moment.
Yes.
It's puzzling.
How is old Bob?
Oh, he's doing good.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
Our House Slack.
Welcome potential initiative and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Uh, yes, for the next 30 minutes of wrecked up equipment and crummy tape.
God, and the, the, the, uh, oh, everything's all messed up already, and we have to do so many shows so quickly.
And, where's the tape? There it is. Oh, there, yes.
Yes, and, well, but, all things shall pass, they say.
Oh, listen, you can hear the guard dogs. Listen to that.
That's the sound of the new subgenius house.
It's scary, isn't it?
I suppose I should probably go see who's at the door.
Yes, just go see.
Oh, the phone rang twice more since I went to the door.
Let's see, what's some, some good background music here.
Friends, uh, what an auspicious start.
To another show.
That was a little old lady at the door.
And, see, I just moved into a new skyscraper studio here.
And, and, uh, there was no one else here but me and the guard dogs.
And this little old lady was at the door.
And she went out.
We're, I live with, I'm Miss Barry.
I live on the house I run behind, behind the road there.
And we're trying to get speed bumps put in.
Because people just drive much too fast down that road there.
And, and.
And the fire department says they need it for emergency use.
But there aren't that many emergencies.
And I thought, well, lady, you don't live my life.
I was so charming and sweet.
I'm standing there.
I haven't shaved in two days.
Wearing a Church of Elvis t-shirt.
24-hour Church of Elvis.
With my horrible old gray hair running halfway down my back and everything.
And then, and then the phone rings some more.
And then it was, it was Palmer.
And then it was the editor from New York.
And then it was my agent.
And friends, you know.
Tomorrow and tomorrow and tomorrow.
Creeps in this petty outer space.
From day to day.
To the last tail leader of recorded tapes.
And all our yesterfrops have lighted.
Subgeniuses the way to bad breath.
Out, out brief flashlight batteries.
Life is but a walking shadow.
A poor pocket pool player who struts and frets his hour of slack upon the airwaves.
And then is heard no more.
It is a rant yelled by idiots.
Full of sound and fury.
And then it's heard.
Signifying Dobbs.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack, dear friends.
The voice of the church of the subgenius.
A celebration of peace, love, and understanding.
It just happens to take the form of pain, hate, and confusion.
For this global village of the damned.
Oh, and it's also about slack.
And Bob.
Dear friends, yes.
We mustn't forget.
Those.
Fine things.
Lest we will be indeed the global village of the damned.
Copyright 1994, Paul Malbriti.
Yes, friends.
This old show.
This old show has been through many changes recently.
First, losing the station in Dallas.
And having to rebuild a down and dirty mini studio here at the home office.
And then we had to move the home office.
Oh yeah.
The Subgenius Foundation Incorporated.
And Bullion.
Bulldada.
Time Control.
Not to mention everything I personally own in this world.
And that includes a hell of a lot of comic books, friends.
Has all been physically moved to new digs in another part of Dallas.
A new skyscraper.
And friends.
It's been hell.
And I don't mean no subgenius hell either.
Oh, that'd be a party.
We're not talking about a single bedroom efficiency with flimsy modern aluminum furniture.
We're talking about countless heavy massive antiques.
And the stakes upon which all our flimsy recording equipment is sitting.
Directly behind me as I sit here, seen on screen three, is a 17-foot wall to ceiling.
Floor to ceiling wall, friends.
Of tapes, videos, films, albums, CDs, Cats and Nine Tails.
We've got a new phone number.
A new physical address.
Although, market friends, our virtual address.
The sacred P.O. box.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That, my friend, is eternal.
And shall ne'er change while Bob lives.
And while I live.
But anyway, we had to put off producing the show for two weeks.
And I'm just lucky there's so much tape laying around here.
Screaming and begging to be broadcast.
You can almost hear them.
They're in the background.
But, friends, we're in a new building, too.
And you know what that means?
That means that nothing works.
Because it was made in America by union idiots.
And every single fixture sprang a leak.
Even the electrical ones.
And it was like a Three Stooges comedy brought to life.
I mean, it really was.
But, you know, they say subgeniuses work best under pressure.
And, of course, we always cause that incredible pressure to build up by blowing everything off until the last minute.
And then, then, only then, with total disaster breathing down our necks with its hot breath,
we perform magnificently.
Far beyond mere hume expectations.
It's the fear that amplifies the intelligence, friends.
It's the fight or flight syndrome.
Makes you 20 times smarter than normal.
Unless you're a human.
And then it's just pure panic.
Pure panic.
It's like my daughter's theory about the lucidity of the moment of death.
My little cute 13-year-old says that if you know you're about to die,
like the Mack truck is coming straight at you or whatever,
your brain automatically switches into a higher gear than it has ever been in before.
And not only is your whole life replayed in an instant, complete with smells,
but you also realize you can't do anything.
Suddenly, for the first time, realize the perfect, foolproof, and most of all, extremely easy scheme
that would have saved the planet and made you a billionaire instantly.
But along with that, in those last microseconds of life,
comes the frustration of realizing how utterly obvious it should have been to you all along.
How stupid you were not to think of it.
Eh, too late now, though.
And what's worse, as Vreedes pointed out,
is that if you happen to live through it,
you forget.
Bummer, man.
Anyway, that's the way things are now.
No sooner did we move the entire church coffers and all the gear to a new place
and finally unpack and fix the disasters,
than I get a phone call this morning that basically says
that if I don't fly to San Francisco right now to ensure, no matter what,
that the new subgenius book, Revelation X, Final Layout,
will be done in two weeks, then we're canceled.
Period. The project is canceled.
That's right, that's how late we were.
So, it's easy, friends.
I just have to drop everything else,
spend my life savings getting to the far-off cave of Paul Mavridis and Hal Robbins,
and help them finish a chapter a day,
and do all the corrections,
and hand-carry the material to the publishers in New York,
that's all, that's all that,
and do the five overdue hour of slack radio shows before I leave!
So, this, dear friends, is the ultimate slack of subgenius horror,
or something like that.
It's the hand that dobs Deltas.
Will we then be jokers?
Or aces?
Or, more likely, just pull a black queen and explode?
Only the next fourteen days will tell,
so wish me luck in assembling today
two months worth of tapes into five hours of slack
between now and tomorrow, would you?
And send, after that, your prayers towards the bay
for me and Mavridis and Dr. Howell
to somehow have the energy and brilliance to finish
what we started three long years ago
before the conspiracy.
And, of course, the conspiracy pulls the plug,
leaving us with the greatest unpublished book in all history
and a bill for $20,000.
Amen.
Well, I guess,
first, let's go to outer space, friends,
with lonesome cowboy Dave.
Yeah, I think we'll do that.
That hardly takes any editing.
This was originally broadcast...
Whoa!
Man!
They're coming in again.
I can't believe this!
On top of moving, I have to deal with these!
Okay, this coming up was originally broadcast July
on WCSB radio in Cleveland.
Swamp radio, the show of Chaz Smith and lonesome cowboy Dave.
I've been saving this stuff, friends, for...
just such an occasion.
Praise the Lord.
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
No kind of world for an old man no more.
Well, after this espousal,
I can only wonder what kind of surgery you must have gone under
to get the pipe-like grin
and also some of the weird brain fusions.
Well, they tell me I was born...
I'm not a joker, man.
I'm an ace.
I want you to understand that.
I can't understand the difference between the cards yet.
I know I'm trying, but...
I'm not a joker, man.
I'm not an ace neither.
It's more like a quagmire I'm lost in.
It's just a splattering of 52 different numbers in the deck,
and I can't figure out which one to go with.
I thought I'd like to be a ten of clubs,
but it turned out I was a ten of clubfoot.
Yeah, that'll get you out of Vietnam.
That got me out of Vietnam.
Why did you want to go there?
I didn't want to go.
I wanted to get out.
Luckily, my ten clubs of feet did it.
You can get out of Vietnam by having clubfeet?
Yeah, tell them.
They're going to ship you off if you don't.
Just all you got to do is take your shoes off
in front of the psychiatrist.
Well, I thought they were going to ship me off
to one of those off-planet little spin...
those little spin containers,
those little tuna fish cans.
Well, the...
Vietnam is slang for Venus.
Ha!
The capital of the world.
The capital city, Ritz, right?
Yeah, and Iran is slang for Mars.
We say, oh, we're having a war with Iraq.
What that means is that's North Mars.
North Mars.
Or South Mars.
Well, I thought...
Iran is North Mars.
Vietnam, that was Venus, man.
I mean, they were just...
The media tricked you into thinking
that we're in this primitive 1990s technology
when actually they're shipping people off all the time.
Well, there's colony...
There's slave colonies on Saturn.
Well, not actually on Saturn.
The gravity there would, you know,
make you as heavy as Orson Welles.
Well, was the moon landing real?
But, you know, on the...
Huh?
Was the moon landing real?
Yeah, in 1945.
You mean Oscar Wilde conquered the moon in 1945
with the Mercury Theater?
Or...
No, wait a minute.
No, that was Edward Teller.
Oh, it was Mercury.
Oh, and I thought that was Heinrich Tesla,
who was Tesla's brother
and actually came up with the...
Oppenheimer and all those guys all went to the moon.
Oppenheimer went to the moon?
Yeah, they didn't...
You know, then the thing you saw in 1969 was a...
Roger.
That was fake.
You know, that was like they wanted to...
They had run out of funds for their secret space program.
So they said,
okay, let's tell them we're going to go to the moon
for the first time.
Oh, no, don't...
So they made a big deal out of it.
They made a big deal.
They didn't even really go.
I mean, they already had...
They couldn't have shown that footage on...
There's cities there.
There's cities on the moon?
Well, they're mostly underground,
but you mean you would...
Almost anywhere you go there,
you see signs, you know,
little smokestacks and stuff.
Can you get a good gyros there?
You know, I've heard that some of these places
that had been previously inhabited,
that they just keep on repopulating them
with new kinds of people.
There's always more where that last one came from.
What's the...
People are considered cockroaches to these...
The owners of these bases.
Yeah.
They're just...
Well, what do they want the cockroaches to do there,
other than, like, bug them
and get on top of the turntable or something?
Well, it's a farm.
It's a farm.
This is all a farm.
The whole solar system is a farm, Dave.
You're part of the...
You're not one of the farmers.
You're one of the spuds or turnips
that's being thrown.
I thought I made cheese.
But there...
You had once said that these are beings.
These farmers are too hideous to behold,
that their faces are all squares
and cockeyed angles,
and if they were to come into this world
and were...
You'd rip your face apart
and eat it.
You'd be in terror were you to behold one physically.
How do they make their way through the abyss?
Do they just blow themselves in there,
or do they just, like...
Have they always been...
There is no abyss to them.
It is all...
They are in no space.
All things are touching.
They have cosmic consciousness, man.
There's some bad...
All the time.
...macky-fackies, I guess.
Yeah.
Well...
And...
We can't get away from them?
I mean...
Through Bob, you certainly may.
But only through Bob.
Only by...
And, in fact, no one can get away from Bob.
Not merely through faith or slack in Bob,
but through works.
Money, Dave.
Money.
That $30 is all important.
That makes the difference between those who Bob knows trust him
and those that Bob doesn't even notice.
You can worship him all you want,
but if he doesn't whiff your name on that check,
then you...
You're just another pink boy.
You're no better than the pink.
Now, remember, we are a nonprofit radio station.
Yeah, but...
Bob's a non-profit.
I bet you've said that a thousand times.
That's the first time.
Well, if that was the first time...
It's the first time it ever came up.
Well, I don't know if I...
If I feel like giving some...
Again, we come back to,
Is your soul up?
Is your soul up, dear friends?
Or did you sell out?
Have you sold out?
Yes, I have.
I certainly hope not.
We've done our best to walk that tightrope ourselves.
Well, I just thought I'd take a break here from the swamp radio there from WCSB
and just to experience this lovely music that Nenslo sent us.
A special tape compilation of background music.
Yes, background music that you'll be hearing irritatingly over and over again in the future on these shows.
This particular piece Nenslo calls, quote,
the master control theme, parentheses, seriously, un-parentheses, unquote.
Hmm, let's just listen for a while before we go back deep into outer space with Lonesome Cowboy Dave Show.
Here it goes.
Nenslo!
Oh, Daddy.
Oh, Mammy.
Oh, Pappy.
Oh, Grammy.
Daddy.
Mammy.
Pappy.
Grammy.
Everybody's talking about how sometimes there's a Pop Hope special and Bob sings silver bells.
Walking in the face, no.
Walking with a pinball wrapped in a 40 code.
Everybody's talking about how sometimes there's a Pop Hope special and Bob sings silver bells.
Thank you.
Yes, dear friends.
And that was the amazing, truly amazing Joe Newman there from his tape, Yodel and Sighting.
Yes, Joe Newman.
Joe Newman.
Our musical short.
Just amazing stuff.
And let's go back now into outer space with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and just see what happens here.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And indeed, it's the perfect thing.
Live from the and of course, a yellow line, what we were all over by the sea here on Coney Island,
Bluestone, Colorado, that was asking us about today, this amazing every year, our first Iron
igi ten Figure Work of the International Special Cypher.
It's Peppy, listen.
Wake up, Dave.
Peppy.
I stepped on Peppy.
It'll be okay.
It's just a dream, Dave.
I never had no dog named Peppy.
Your friends are still here.
Me, the Tin Litzman.
Tin Lizzy.
Yeah.
And the Cowardly Lion.
Oh, the Cowardly.
Yes.
It was only a dream.
That horrible, boring world of trucks and sidewalks.
And sausages.
It was just a terrible dream.
And fatal onions.
I've been hearing ahs all along.
Oh, it's my, these flakes on my mouth.
It's so dry.
I've been here all along.
Yeah, you were just, you got knocked out.
Well, how the hell did I get knocked out?
When they dropped that house on your head.
Oh, I thought it was when I was arguing with that bitch.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I think I was.
Don't I?
What his problem was, you know, what the hell.
She was giving me stuff, so I might as well.
Oh, there.
Here it goes again.
Am I in there?
Yeah.
Boy, I think something's missing here now.
This looks like a little teeny tiny room.
Now, how the hell I get in here?
We've been orbiting the whole time, Dave.
You're still in a little tuna can in space, remember?
It's going to be another nine months before we get on all the way over to Jupiter.
Yeah, but when do they hatch?
Do we get to get out before they hatch or we got to wait?
Oh, you'll know when they're hatching.
I thought I'd be in some kind of hibernation chamber or something.
Well, but most people wake up for the last few seconds of their life as the thing is bursting their chest open.
Well, what the hell are we doing this for then?
Well, you signed up.
You signed up.
The contract is in the computer.
Well, I didn't.
You thought the corporation was a great idea.
You said we should all climb into the little capsule and we'd get paid.
By the time we got to Jupiter, we'd be paid a million bucks each.
And sure enough, we will.
It's just that it's our estate that gets it.
Yeah, but it's just...
Because you didn't read the fine print, Dave.
And now we're all stuck here with you for another nine months.
Yeah.
I was never capable of reading a fine print.
I just...
And you just keep having these dreams and going off into fantasy land thinking you're back on Earth doing radio shows.
And every time I have a dream, how come one of you guys changes?
Like, I dreamed my wife was attacking me with a car.
And next thing I know, out there I was out in a side room and some Russian was talking to me.
And a woman was attacking me with a car.
Somehow I think you guys were involved in this.
Yeah, and what are you keeping back there?
What's in that big box anyway?
That's our space hyena.
Well, what's the...
Rover.
And the scorpion rooster creature that we picked up on Mars.
Well, how come we don't get to lick at them?
You can lick them.
You can lick them anytime you want.
Remember what happened last time you licked them, though?
What, the eye socket thing?
Yeah.
Well...
It wasn't easy getting that scorpion rooster barb out of your eye socket.
I thought you said that was another dream.
Give me a mirror.
I want to see if there's anything wrong with my eye socket, man.
Let me look in the monitor.
You can't look at your own eye, Dave.
Yes, you can.
If I look in the monitor, I can look at my own eye.
I'm not listening to you right now.
What the hell?
I have no eyes in there.
Why don't you calm down and take a stress pill, Dave?
I don't see what difference that's going to make.
Now, I'm looking in there and I'm not...
Am I hallucinating or something?
I have absolutely no eyeballs in my...
In my eye socket.
Now, this isn't what happened in the eye socket and before.
Usually, it just, like, ripped out a chunk of the side of my face.
You can't see your own eyes, Dave.
You can't run from your own legs.
Jane told you that a long, long time ago.
Yeah, but you can't talk to your own voice.
You can't...
You can't smell your own nose.
Well, now, wait a minute.
You can't swallow your own throat.
If they pull one eye out, just before the optic nerve severs,
that one eye, just for one second, can look at the other eye.
Yeah, that's true.
If you pull it out, and we did this with Jane.
We pull it out just enough and turn it around.
You have to be very careful turning it.
One eye can actually be seeing the other eye.
But that's not really the point.
The point is, say, a one eye.
You can't see your own eye with that eye that's seeing.
You can see your other eye, but you can't see your eye that is doing the seeing.
You can only see the other eye.
You can look in the mirror, but that doesn't count either.
This is all mirror metaphysical.
You can't digest your own stomach, Dave.
Juggling and juxtaposition.
And you can't hide from Bob, because he's stupider than you.
I can't believe that.
No, it's true.
That's the miracle of it.
That's the beautiful thing.
That's why Bob hates you.
I'll be whipped by a miracle whip.
I didn't want to lose that.
I didn't want to.
Remember what that is?
You can turn into a frog or something.
You never know.
I don't know.
You can't hide from God, because he's bigger than you.
Help me, somebody.
You can't hide from God, because he's bigger than the whole planet.
You can't hide from God.
He's bigger than all the universe.
You can't hide from God, because he's bigger than all infinity.
He's bigger than all reality.
Help me, somebody.
You can't hide from God.
You can't hide from God in a reefer.
You can't hide from God in a glass of alcohol.
You can't hide from God in a...
See?
Because he's bigger than you.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs because he's stupider than you are.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs because he's got more black and white little dots in his face than you do.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs because his face has been mimeographed and put up in more places than yours has.
You can't hide from God.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs because more people worship him than worship you.
You can't hide from Dobbs because he's stupider than you are.
Who the hell is somebody?
You can't run from your own legs.
How you gonna run from your own legs?
Because if you run from your own legs, what are you gonna run from them with?
If you use them to run from them with, what are you gonna run away from?
You can't run from your own legs.
You can't hide from J.R. Bob Dobbs because he's stupider than you.
You can't hide from God because he's bigger than you.
He's bigger...
No.
Realities bigger than all infinity
Help me somebody, she ain't got no legs
Pull the lever down, yo, my legs are on fire
Need some help, praise God
Doctors for Bob
It's a beautiful thing, and we'll continue
If I feel like giving something
Again, we come back to, is your soul up?
Is the magic light gone off?
But there is no up and down in that realm
There's no up and down?
No, there's no, there is sideways
But only in one direction
So it's not a world where we could use the spatula
As frequently as we'd like
No, it's very linear
It's more like the needle
You might be able to use the needle, but never the spatula
The spatula is too three-dimensional
And the beach ball would be out of the question
Yes, and also the
The inclement
The angles are all wrong
This is non-Euclidean geometries
Just the frequencies of this broadcast
Are non-Euclidean
But do they operate on a similar principle?
Is the wave magnetics involved in hearing our voices?
Through this medium?
That's the only way
That's the only thing that hears our voices
In this medium
So are they talking deep into the cervical clavichord
And beneath the subcutaneous matter?
Are they talking inside our
Sure, but it's pointless
Who cares?
It's just all going out into the void, Dave
You're all alone
This vast, huge universe
Spinning around you
Spinning around in this little tuna can
And thirty bucks
Five years from now, you're going to hit Alpha Centauri
You'll be the first man there, though, Dave
It's a great honor
I'll be the first tuna sandwich on Alpha Centauri
You're not just some guinea pig
You're not just some Russian dog
That's been sent up in a sputnik
A guinea pig in a Russian dog
I got that
No, I'm sorry
You're the
I'm a sandwich
You're the vanguard of the human race
Well, the subgenius race, anyway
And if Lenny Reifenstahl were to make my film
And to have me as the top tuna
Above the world
All the rest
Standing below there
Holding flags and everything
And then I forgot the rest of it, too
It'd be really good photography
It would be great stuff
I think we could all get uniforms and everything
And forget Bob
And just
There'd be a million of me
Yeah, just be Dave
Praise Dave
Thousands and millions of him
Praise Dave, that's right
And no individual personalities
Just blend with everything
Like in a big, massive mush pudding
Tuna pudding
They all start thinking that way
When they've been in the tuna can long enough
When they've been spinning through the air
The void
For six months
They start fantasizing that they're on Earth
In a radio station
Taking over the world
With the brilliance of their new discoveries
It's still pretty hot and oily in here
I don't know how much
How much longer I can take it
I suppose you haven't
I just take off these Brazilian slippers here
And relax for a while
Maybe something will happen
Maybe something in.
Just enjoy the stars going by outside the window.
Of course, they don't really seem to be moving.
We're not going fast enough.
It's not like Star Trek.
It's just the same.
And, of course, that window has to be shielded completely.
The radiation, if you stuck your hand out there for a second, it would burn your finger off.
If the vacuum didn't get you first, Dave.
But don't worry.
You know, we spent a lot of money on this capsule.
Well, just as long as I'm protected in here, I can fantasize.
And you've got lots of tapes.
I hope you like mid-60s top 40.
You want to hear good vibrations again?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey.
Remember that one Hendrix tape?
Oh, that was the one that got torn up.
No, no.
That's the one you liked.
Yeah, the Mormon choir doing Hendrix's greatest hits.
You said you'd let me listen to that one again.
Could you just, like, put it up one more time?
Their version of Machine Gun was really original.
I never would have thought I could.
The Mormon Tabernacle Choir doing Machine Gun with just voices.
There's a lot you can do with the human voice.
Help!
It's a good thing his suit provides the medication when he freaks out like that.
I know.
It feels better now, doesn't it?
Everything's computerized.
We've got Dave tucked in, tucked into his little space capsule.
This creaky chair.
His self-medicating space suit.
Just me.
All the buttons in front of him and flashing lights are just props to make him feel good.
Make him feel like he's in control.
Actually, he basically was shot out of a glorified blowgun.
And we kind of, along with about a thousand other people in little tin cans,
and we're just hoping that one or two of them actually makes it to Alpha Centauri.
And we hope it's still there by the time they get there.
Carrying their little letters from J.R. Bob Dobbs
to the kings of any other inhabited planets they might fall onto.
We would have loved to have put you in suspended animation for this five-year voyage, Dave,
but the taxpayers would have had to pay for that.
That's the cruelty level, isn't it?
The committee decided that you could just hack it out.
Tough it out.
Five years of black void sitting here in Orlando,
pretending to be blowed out by a puffed-up dart gun.
You're here with us.
That's the voices inside your head, Dave.
You'll never be alone.
You can't even fall asleep.
Your suit will make sure of that.
Let's see now.
The first duchy fallen was 1264
by a count from the Ukraine named Vladimir Ashbaugh.
Oh, gee, that's boring.
Oh, it's Winoma time in southern New Mexico.
The Winoma Indians are doing the annual Akoma dance.
Oh, oh, there's a new wine bar in Cincinnati.
Now, don't forget, you've got 90 channels of cable TV,
although we will admit there's no sound.
Yeah, but they're all like shopping channels,
and I don't have no money up here,
and you keep trying to get money out of me,
and, hey, wait a minute, you're a voice in my head, aren't I?
You're building up credits all the time back on Earth.
If you ever make it back,
you'll be a very rich man.
Yeah, I'm building up credits.
I'm building up credits all the time.
Of course, if you don't make it back,
they go into the J.R. Bob Dobbs Memorial Fund.
You'll be remembered very fondly
by those of us who had to stay back here on Earth
talking to you by radio, Dave.
I'm kind of connected.
We wish we could be out there with you in the void
carrying on the torch of humanity.
I can feel you.
Discovery, the amazing sense of discovery you must feel.
We all here on Earth envy you, Dave.
I can touch you back there.
I am blown out of here.
You signed up.
You wanted to go for the easy money, Dave.
Yeah, but...
You answered that classified ad in the paper.
Yeah, but it said...
Off-world farming, big future, big bucks while you sleep.
Yeah, but it sounded like such a scam.
Off-world farming.
What could you possibly have to do but sleep?
Sea monkeys are going to be a big cash crop in the future, Dave,
for people on your new colonized planet.
Oh, my God.
I gotta check out the sea monkeys.
The sea monkeys were all bloated yesterday,
and I had to give them their estrogen tablets.
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, third, one, fourth, one.
This hammer is all disconnected here.
I hope the sea monkeys aren't dead, Dave.
They're your only source of nutrients.
Check them, check them, check the sea monkeys.
Try this top off.
Oh, sea monkeys are bloated again.
Are you an invalid?
Hey, who are you?
What?
Who are you?
You're a different voice in my head.
Are you one of the discarnated dead sea monkeys talking to me like the ghost of them?
You posted a WCS feed.
I have to tell you what I want to hear.
Hey, this is getting more realistic and lifelike.
There's like retarded people calling me up and talking in my head.
I doubt if we'll ever be able to resurrect these sea monkeys.
Jeez.
Look at this one.
It's sprouting a whole new head.
I wonder if I mix this solution back in again.
Maybe some of them,
they could take a spore from one of them and reclone the spore.
I don't know.
I'll just go take a nap and write a little report to the committee.
Bob?
I haven't heard the voice of Bob.
There's just something in the background there.
I can't make that voice out.
I'll try on this Mr. Peanut suit.
Yeah, this thing's been laying around for weeks now.
Having any fun with that?
He's hallucinating the peanut suit again.
You'll have to make note of that.
Tell the psychiatrist.
Mr. Peanut used to come to all the fairs
and he'd pass out donuts and give favors to the kids
and bags of peanuts, of course.
I love that monocled eye.
You know what's funny?
All of those volunteer, quote, astronauts, unquote,
start imagining the peanuts.
Something about Mr. Peanut.
Do you suppose the Russians had something to do with that?
Could they have breached security
and implanted the Mr. Peanut fantasy?
Look, he thinks he's Mr. Peanut.
And if it's not Mr. Peanut, it's Reddy Kilowatt.
It's kind of sad in a way.
Oh, boy.
I'm telling all of you.
Mr. Peanut Man.
This is a very, very big, important convention of Mr. Peanut Man.
I think I'm standing.
Do you suppose his suit is over-medicating him?
I wonder if I should still be even taller if I was standing much more from the west.
But why old advertising figures?
I mean, Mr. Peanut's not even used anymore in marketing, I don't think.
It's something from his past.
They're comforting things.
Oh, Mr. Potato Head.
One of the people on the way to Proxima Regulus were all turned in.
Mr. Potato Head.
Around the six-month mark, just like him.
We'll have to remember that.
Yes.
We'll make a note of it.
We'll have to tell the psychology department.
Oh, now I'm glad, Mr. Potato Head.
And now I'm doing red hair.
We ought to tell the cruelty department, too.
They can start implanting evil Mr. Potato Head and evil Mr. Peanut.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's no wonder they gave their shirt off to Mr. Potato Head.
Because...
Now I can stare at each other.
He, he, he, he, he, he, he, he.
I'd rather let them smash me, wouldn't you think?
Ah!
Mr. Tuber costume.
It's the big sweet potato head.
Oh, I love this one the best.
Huh.
It's carved out in the middle.
Hmm.
Huh.
Do you suppose...
Do you suppose he has any inkling that all of his silly antics are being broadcast to
all the people on Earth?
Oh.
On the...
I don't think so.
The crazy astronaut channel?
He's full in love.
Oh, hey, there's somebody watching.
One of these days he's going to switch through those channels and he's going to come upon
the channel with him on it.
Damn, man.
I might as well lift a box.
Oh, wow, this is getting boring.
Dave, your gyros need stabilizing.
Dave, check your computer.
Wait, who?
Who?
Your gyro.
Your, your, your, your, your spinning.
What?
It's spinning.
You're in a spin, Dave.
Whose voice is this?
Stabilize the gyros.
Is this a real voice or is this a real voice?
Turn up the oxygen switch.
Oh, I get lightheaded in here.
Reach for the oxygen switch, Dave.
I think I'll turn on the oxygen switch.
Oh, he did it.
At least he thought it was the oxygen switch.
Eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, eh, uh, that's a wrong switch.
Just green stuff going on.
Uh, go ahead and do it.
I'm gonna go and get you, I promise.
He needed a good washing.
Oh, my God.
They always panic when the suit fills up with the cleansing fluid.
My neck hurts so much.
Right up to their nostrils.
Oh, my God.
It's like he doesn't really...
I think I lost the church air switch.
My hands are clean.
My face is clean.
Hello.
Hello, Dave.
Feeling better now, Dave?
What?
Everything I say itches.
No, no, no.
We're not doing that, it says.
It's just...
It's just us, Dave.
The voices in your head.
We didn't want you to be alone.
I bet I could write a whole symphony on this hollow potato.
That would be something to do for five years.
You'd sit around going mad.
It's that all I'm gonna do.
There have been great symphonies written about hollow potatoes, Dave.
Great symphonies.
Why don't you try it?
It'll keep you busy for a month or so.
Yeah, why don't I try it?
I could, like, make thousands and thousands of little holes, like some sort of chromatic key.
I could just get a little...
Dave, the cat's loose in the spaceship.
Let me check the monitor for her.
Excuse me.
Shh.
Cat's loose.
Damn cat.
It's crawling all over all...
All those...
Faders are...
You better catch that cat, Dave.
It's walking across the control panel.
You're going into a spin again.
It's going right out of control.
You're destabilizing.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna destabilize.
This thing's gonna start flipping.
If I don't get down there right away...
Shh.
Ginger.
Oh, good.
Look, Princess.
We, the cat, mutated.
Just as we were hoping.
What the hell is that?
He let it wander into the cargo hold where it was exposed.
What is that?
What's that? Ginger? Is that you?
Jeez.
What the hell is the slime all over your neck?
What you been getting into?
Just let me get a little closer, okay? What's wrong?
Try to make friends with it, Dave.
I'll try and make friends with it.
Try to make friends with Ginger.
Yeah, Ginger's always a nice little kitty.
She's sick or something. I'll make friends.
I'll pet it and take it back out of her.
Okay. Ginger?
Now settle down, Dave. Try to communicate with it.
It's a new form of life. No one's ever seen a cat spider before.
It could teach us things.
Oh, my God.
Think what it could mean to science.
Go on in there, Dave.
Go on back into that cargo hold with that giant mutated cat spider.
If I could just talk to her, maybe.
It's got to be intelligent if it's mutated.
It's got to be intelligent.
Maybe it has something to tell me.
A little kitty?
What the hell is that?
What's that?
Oh, it just needs to be comforted, Dave.
Your music soothes the savage beast.
Why don't you put on some music?
Oh, Ginger.
I'm just going to play a little song for you.
Maybe you should put out some milk for it.
A little try of milk.
Oh, Ginger.
I'm just wondering, though.
Be careful now.
Don't let it get hurt.
You know, its blood can burn a hole directly through the spaceship hull.
It would create a terrible vacuum and suck you out into space like toothpaste out of a tube.
It looks like it's going through.
And whatever you do, don't let any harm come to Ginger.
The war department is very interested in your little tabby.
Oh, okay.
Deal with this right now.
I think it's just that.
You're out of here.
You're still alive.
Take a look at this.
The war department is over.
And we'll be back to the lonesome cowboy Dave flipping out in outer space channel
after these words from our controller.
Cue up the controller tape.
Dealing with overpopulation involves more than birth control.
That idea will take center stage at an upcoming conference in Egypt.
I'm Steve Pomplin for Earthwatch Radio.
I say kill them all.
Let God sort them out.
I'm into the voluntary human extinction movement.
I say let them eat green cheese.
Let them eat green cheese and let the cat sort them out.
Let the mutated spider cat.
All our problems...
I say exterminate all the sponge monsters.
Everything's...
I have to exterminate everyone.
Stop the...
Stop.
Is there any coffee on this spaceship?
Is there any...
Now, come on, Dave.
I know you got some of that whiskey stashed somewhere
back with the bio...
samples from Mars.
We can't understand a word you're saying.
He's lost in space, friends.
Sad.
But
part of the risks these astronauts take.
Thank God, Creamora,
don't make you sleepy
like some of the other ones do.
Well, at one o'clock,
your suit will put you to sleep.
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for my suit to put me to sleep.
Over the last five and a half hours,
my suit has enthralled me.
My suit has put me to sleep
and waked me up again.
My suit fed me.
My suit evacuated.
My suit evacuated my bowels.
My suit lulled me into a false sense of security.
It's a comforting suit.
My suit talked to me.
My suit made me feel very insecure.
My suit,
my suit expanded and contracted a few times.
I didn't understand what that was about.
It was punishing you, Dave.
The suit punishes.
The suit punishes and the suit rewards.
The suit rewards you, Dave.
My world is in his suit.
The suit rewards you.
The suit is my entire world.
The suit is your friend.
It's a nurturing cocoon.
Oh, look at the cut of my socks.
This is the kind of seasoning that would make
any, any young man in America jealous as hell.
I'm a true hero.
Wearing this suit made me a hero,
and I'm proud of it.
I'm glad I signed up now.
I think my suit's filling me with pride.
Odie, dodie, dodie, Dave.
I'm afraid that's not pride, Dave.
You shouldn't have eaten those freeze-dried beans this morning.
They just had a little.
They just had a little fuzz on them.
I didn't see nothing wrong with those beans.
Yeah, your suit may be filling up with a lot more than mere pride.
Oh, there you go.
He's using the zero-gravity toilet again.
Oh, boy, this is kind of...
Oh, no, he left the flap open.
Look, the stuff is floating around inside the cabin now.
It's coating the windows.
Catch that stuff out on the window.
Way to go, Dave.
Smooth move.
Ha, ha, ha.
You do it.
Oh, no.
Well, now the emergency lights have gone off.
Little robots have to come out and clean up after you again, Dave.
I have to get to the cleaning unit, please.
Hello?
The suit's going to have to punish you again, Dave.
I'm going to clean up on the front window.
Shh, shh.
I think I'm going to be stuck there for weeks now.
Of course, in this vacuous atmosphere, I won't smell much, I don't suppose.
No, just don't take your helmet.
I don't want to take my helmet off.
I wonder what would happen if I took my helmet off.
I never tried it.
No, don't do that, Dave.
Wait a minute.
Maybe something might...
I don't know, maybe...
This is not a pressurized cabin.
Might not be such a good idea after all.
Get a little around with this.
Oh, look, he's trying to light a cigarette again.
He can't get it up to his lips through that helmet.
That must be the 5,000th time he's done that.
Shh.
Huh.
16 cartons of luggage and I can't smoke a damn cigarette.
It was a brilliant move on the part of the psychology department to put that no smoking sign blinking in there.
And those 20 cartons of cigarettes that...
Keeps up the sort of tension that keeps the astronauts...
Oddly enough, it keeps them mentally healthy.
You know, it's so alone out here, the only friend I've got's my own guitar.
Lucio, you've been with me through thick and thin.
Can't smoke.
Can't really eat a good meal.
But I can still sing a song.
I think I'll sing a song about my intergalactic exploits.
Scott can't even hardly touch these fragile, these big mitts on.
Years have gone and years have come
But still I'm a-flyin' by
Oh, someday I'll be back
And I'll get there
And maybe I won't
And I never know the reason why
Oh, oh, oh, ooh ooh, ooh ooh ooh ooh
Oh, oh, oh, ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Shh, it's the worst one yet to form.
Just keep on working and I'll have my opera all figured out by the time I get there.
And then, if I make it back to Earth, some more herodom and fame and fortune for me.
Just chuck that up and...
You'll be the biggest... folk...
Music star on Alpha Centauri, Dave.
God, if I could see it right now, I could be like the Woody Guthrie of Alpha Centauri.
You'll be the only musician in the whole star system, Dave.
Yeah, I'll be the only musician in the whole star system.
You'll be the only music fan in the whole star system.
Yeah, and my head will be shaped like a gigantic fan,
like one of those Komodo dragons, or what do they call them, monitor lizards, when they get mad.
Good, good, we've got him doing stream of consciousness again.
That should keep him amused for a few more days.
I wonder if they got the hot like earth type beige on Alpha Centauri.
The suit is your girlfriend, Dave.
It's clamping down. It's constricting.
It's tightening up.
It's form-fitting.
It's form-fitting, isn't it?
I didn't know this suit could do this.
What the heck is going on?
Alright, that's enough.
Turn off that function of the suit.
Now let's make him exercise.
Put the suit in exercise mode.
There we go.
He's plumping up and down.
He's flopping.
My knee joint is going out again.
What the hell is this music?
It's a good aerobicized music.
We must keep our astronauts in good shape.
He's resisting calisthenics.
Jumping jacks at this time of the morning.
It'll be five years of this if he's lucky.
I mean, I can't do this for five years.
I can't do this for another minute longer.
If he doesn't happen to hit one of the planets,
if there are any in the Alpha Centauri system,
then he'll just have to go on to the next star system
20 years past that.
But you'll probably hit a planet.
Some sort of a planet.
Or a moon.
Or an asteroid.
Or something.
Some body of rock floating around in space.
Think of the romantic cartoon man on a desert island
with nothing but one palm tree and a shark swimming around.
Yeah.
That romantic fantasy will be yours.
Only high-tech style, babe.
I'm a high-tech style romantic hero figure.
Abandoned on a distant moon.
Casting a space like some piece of effluvio on the sea.
Someday I'll be home.
Someday I'll touch the shore.
A distant shore somewhere.
It'll take much longer to wait.
I'll get there someday.
If you get bored, Dave,
you can always just put a note in a bottle
and send it out into the radio waves
like you've just done.
For the last two hours.
This has been ESO Radio.
I'm WCSB Cleveland with my guests,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
the Reverend Ivan Stang,
and the Princess,
Ria Do.
My name is Chaz,
and I'll see you all next week.
Yay for Chaz.
He's the mix master.
I am.
Hay, I am!
You're listening to the subgenius radio ministry
hour of slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the church of the
subgenius, send a self-addressed
Dove to, got your
pencil ready?
Bob.
Post office box.
Or radio radio ministry Orlando doing something all over
and they don't know here.
That's Bob P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Wellman, Dennis locked me in this little box.
I can't feel anything. I can't see anything.
It's totally black.
I have no sensation in my hands.
I don't know if I'm moving or what.
I'm just in this little box.
He said I could talk to you.
He said you'd know what to do if you wanted to help.
Oh, good. Happy Peter Wellman.
I promise I'll pay you all the royalties that I didn't tell you about.
And whatever you want. I mean, anything.
Tavis. You can have Tavis.
Just get me out of this box, Wellman.
Please don't. No.
Don't believe what Paul told you.
It's all a lie. It's all a lie.
Whatever I did, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I let you out of the box, Wellman.
I can't. This is a bad show, Wellman.
This is a real bad show.
Now.
She ibilidad Father Charlie Dzer-
Totale Schmuck.
saol
my
parents