Ah, the one that's not real. That's the one you must listen to, darling. Now, just come over here and sit on my lap.
But it doesn't really make noise.
I know my knee looks a little strange.
It only makes noise when I turn the pages or when I close it or open it.
I had a few additions made. What now? What did you say?
It only makes noise when I open it or close it. It doesn't make noise. And, like, talk to me like I thought you meant when you said that.
Well, we'll try and close it and open it very gently.
Wrap it around your head and listen real carefully to the printed letters on that book.
The Bible is a beautiful story, but this book is even better.
Humans, on the other hand, don't have to. We have a choice.
If you don't like your place in the world, you can get off anytime you want.
Suicide. That's right.
If you don't like the way your life's going, you don't like the way you are in the world, anything around you, you can check out anytime you like.
Animals aren't allowed that thought.
And believe me, if they were.
They would use us.
There'd be a lot of dogs and cats owned by assholes who live in high-rises diving out the windows.
Zebras, if they even had remotely that thought, would take a look at themselves and go,
What the fuck?
Black and white, the green and brown world.
Now, this blows.
I'm just gonna jump in the river.
I don't have a thumb to work a gun or hold a knife.
I don't have a jar of pills.
I'm just gonna dive into the next lion's mouth.
Why even bother?
Now, monkeys have the opposable thumb, so they could kind of do it the exact same way we do.
Now, there's a bunch of people that say, oh, it's against the law.
Well, it's only against the law if you do a crappy job and you get caught.
Other people say, oh, we should save them.
Yeah, well, you know what?
Not everybody wants to be saved.
Not everybody should be saved.
And who are we to force our will upon them?
I mean, isn't that one of the joys about being a human?
Freedom of choice?
Now, it's not all bad.
Now, I'm not saying kill yourself.
But if you're gonna be an idiot and do it anyway,
there's no sweat off of my back.
There's a lot of good that could come from it.
A little bit of bad thrown in.
Some of the things, a job will open.
An apartment will become available.
There'll be more air for me.
They say there's two girls for every guy.
If you're a man, there'll be four chicks for me.
There'll be more Kettle One vodka for me.
There'll be one less idiot in line at the bank
who gets up to the window without their fucking slips filled out.
I won't ever have to go to the store
to buy my favorite salt and vinegar chips
and have the clerk point to you and say,
they bought the last bag.
You won't help change the McDonald's sign
to 100 billion served.
You'll never get AIDS.
You won't have to worry about calories ever.
No more.
Hey, does this make me look fat?
There'll be one less polluting human.
You won't have to recycle.
There'll be one less car on the road.
There'll be more ringdings for me.
50 or so chickens' lives will be spared.
Your fingers won't ever get red from eating pistachios.
You won't be forced to visit your grandparents on Sundays anymore.
No more church.
You'll be saying, hey world, kiss my ass.
No more wet dreams about to come true.
No more about supermodels.
No more Barry Manilow.
For a few years, anyway.
Wondering, am I a loser?
Will be a thing of the past.
Say goodbye to crappy Xmas presents from aunts and uncles.
You won't have to suffer through a motley crew reunion.
Fuck flossing and brushing.
You'll never lose sleep over a pregnancy scare.
Adios, acne.
Worrying whether you fit in or not won't be on your brain.
See you later, homework.
You'll never have to sit through another movie brought to you by the creators of South Park.
School's out forever.
No more paying bills.
You won't have to do chores.
You won't be able to run over toads with a lawnmower, though.
You'll also miss McDonald's french fries.
Bugs Bunny.
The amazing electrifying feeling that surges through your body when you kiss someone for the first time.
You won't be able to watch the letterbox director's cut of Jaws.
Candy.
Living above ground.
Pudding crust.
You'll miss the rush of getting your first apartment.
Getting to the point in your life where you can tell your parents to fuck off.
I gotta make my own mistakes.
You did.
You'll miss sex.
You'll miss thinking about it, looking for it.
Sex by yourself.
Sex with a partner.
Sex with multiple partners.
No more summer nights that seem to go on forever.
Roller coasters.
Naming your kid the name you always wanted.
Making a difference in the world.
You'll miss the experience and pleasure of hallucinogenics.
Watching your neighbors watch.
A wife change clothes with her blinds open.
A lifetime of masturbating.
Watching your favorite team sweep the series.
Music.
You will definitely miss music.
Trying to sneak into your house drunk three hours past your curfew.
You'll miss the blazing glory of the 4th of July fireworks.
The taste of Captain Crunch.
If you're a boy, you'll miss the feeling the first time you reach up a girl's shirt.
If you're a girl, the feeling the first time you reach down a boy's pants.
You'll miss your favorite coat.
Waffles with whipped cream and strawberries.
Beating your friends at video games.
You won't be around to see what shape and color the new marshmallow and Lucky Charms will be.
You'll miss the feeling you'll get when reminiscing about your first love 30 years after the fact.
The joy of giving and receiving at Christmas.
Skinny dipping.
Getting stoned.
Reading Green Eggs and Ham.
And eating like a horse that got loose in the grain bin.
Flying cars.
Hey, you were born.
Finish what was started.
The guy who slagged the football team.
Those jobs were not for him.
He turns into a real estate agent who believes in discipline.
The guy who's first to use cocaine.
The wild boy breaking free.
He'll end up in a court of law as a prosecuting QC.
Remember the school captain?
Success was a matter of time.
I can hear her now as she screams,
Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Forget Snoop Doggy Dog.
Forget old iced tea.
The true word out on the streets is produced by the DAC.
What's the use of striving?
Life's road in front unravels.
We get to do the driving.
Don't choose the direction we travel.
Do your homework and wait for weeks.
Completely the damn, don't lie.
It don't matter much when you hear that scream.
Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Greg, the stop sign.
Sometime in the next ten thousand years,
a comet's gonna wipe out old Tracer Man.
I'm banking on it coming before my end of year exam.
The rich kid becomes a junkie.
The poor kid an advertiser.
What a tragic waste of potential.
Being a junkie's not so good either.
Your folks work hard for what you got.
You are the fruit of their vine.
Who cares what you sow and what you reap?
It's Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Hey, it's Greg.
Home for your daily good Albar,
Home for your daily good sleep.
Home for leaving your books to sleep.
Home for leaving that littlekinера,
You flee 싶ih 있다 log
Home for one Quel Inurita.
Home for приходatib running in the thaw.
Man, could that baby run?
But you know what they always say
There's always a better one
Got a tumor in my brain
It's creeping to my lungs
And I'm searching around in vain
Can't find me a better one
I'm winding to everyone's head
Is the person it gonna be?
Growing up's not a matter of choice
It's a matter of wait and see
So kids, yeah, you can do it
You can be your best
Girls can do anything
You can pass the test
I'm okay, you're okay
We're okay, we're fine
I thought I heard a semi-trailer
Glad you missed the stop sign
Freaky stop sign
Freaky stop sun
The Thousandth and Tenth Day of the Human Totem Pole
The morning was the temper gray of the thousandth and tenth day of the human totem pole.
The man at the bottom was smiling.
He had just finished his breakfast smiling.
It hadn't rained or manured for over two hours.
The man at the top was starving.
The pole was a horrible looking thing with all of those eyes and ears and waving hands for balance.
There was no way to get a copter in close, so everybody was starving together.
The man at the top had long ago given up but didn't have nerve enough to climb down.
At night the pole would talk to itself and the chatter wasn't too good.
Obviously the pole didn't like itself.
It wanted to walk.
It was the summer and it was hot.
And balance wouldn't permit a skinning to undergarments.
It was an integrated pole.
It was taking on a reddish brown cast.
Exercise on the pole was isometric.
Kind of a flex and then balance.
Then the eyes would roll together.
The ears wiggle.
Hands balance.
There was a gurgling and googling herd.
A tenth of the way up the pole.
Approaching was a small child with Statue of Liberty doll.
The
chance to giggle?
all have been ever since came from a
forget it!
and then again travel down across the
Madeleine unhappy犬iv scent magic
Astounding! Captain Beefheart there and the Magic Band.
The 1010th day of the Human Totem Pole from the album Ice Cream for Crow.
Before that, friends, that song, Greg the Stop Sign, is by a British group called This Is Serious, Mum.
That's the name of the group, This Is Serious, Mum.
And you can get more information about them from www.tism.
That's short for This Is Serious, Mum.
www.tism.wanker.com
tism.wanker.com
And friends, before that, that incredible song about suicide.
And why and why not, is by a comedian named Bobby Gaylor.
Dr. Lagune sent me a copy of that.
It's from an album called Fuzzatonic Scream.
And you can check out bobbygaylor.com.
That's spelled G-A-Y-L-O-R.
Bobby Gaylor.
Just amazing.
And it helps set the theme of anti-slack.
As it is taken away from us.
And somehow it always returns back to slack.
Friends, yes, slack.
And for more slack, we're going to go back in time to the old subgenius Media Barrage number 11.
Once a tape, and now a CD.
We're remastering it.
Made from tapes created in the early 1980s.
1980s.
And, uh...
And friends, after that, I don't know what we're going to play.
I ain't going to make any decisions right now.
This music by Tipsy in the background from their album Uh-Oh.
Is...
It just makes me want to slack off.
I'm going to duck the responsibility, dear friends.
As Aleister Crowley once said, if I can't be God, I'm not going to play.
This ain't no video game church.
It ain't no church of bingo.
It's a church.
It's a Bob.
It's a Bob Rice's church.
I don't see what the hell's going on here.
What the hell?
Did you know that heaven, Christian heaven is hotter than the Christian hell?
Yes.
The Christian heaven is hotter.
That's because there are seven sons.
And the subgenius hell is fun.
Oh, yeah.
All your friends will be down there.
No.
There's seven sons.
There's seven sons around the Christian heaven.
This is true.
You can find it in their own Bible.
They admit it.
And seven sons would make it much hotter than the gaseous molten threshold of brimstone.
That means that heaven is hotter than hell.
Hell.
They've been lying to you all this time.
Without anything open, they lie about friends.
They lie about that.
The world isn't coming to an end right away.
In 15 years.
Of course it's coming to an end in 15 years.
It can't last any longer.
It wasn't built to last.
It wasn't meant to last.
It's inferior.
Well, it's a Spartan universe.
The cult is full of superstition and mysticism.
We're scientists.
We're able to argue anything us and ask any questions about ourselves.
In the hands of a human instinct in that universe, our Wall Street odds were across,
All day, you lie about.
So drop your quarters, or hang yourself a column from the wall or notice this paper to find somebody.
I might, I might do it again.
But it can't be.
But we've got to do it again.
But, but how we do it again.
issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end.
Now, that's the same story the cult of the Book of Revelations had been preaching.
Now, when a scientist backs that up, it's news.
Our conclusions have nothing to do with the cult.
Well, today we deal with Bible prophecy.
But the Word of God tells us we can expect nothing but trouble and turmoil in the Middle East
until our Lord returns to be the Prince of Peace.
Bob?
It's been known for some time that the fossil record contains several very pronounced mass extinctions,
when large numbers of quite unrelated species from all kinds of habitats
appear to die out during a relatively short period.
You have, say, an asteroid about 10 kilometers across,
impacting on the Earth at a speed of about 40 kilometers a second.
Did you hear what he was saying?
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps in the form of an atomic holocaust?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
The White House will confirm an order to use the atom bomb.
And our first target will be the initial landing place outside Los Angeles.
Those missiles have all gone off.
They pushed all the punch...
You know what that means, don't you?
Either we fired first and they're going to try to hit what's left,
or they fired first and we just got our missiles...
out of the ground in time.
Either way, we're going to get hit.
So what are we still standing around here for?
Of course, since all human life has been under the surface of Earth for 16 years,
there was no actual loss of life in the sense we know it.
What you see is what you get.
What you get, what you get.
What the hell did you expect?
What you expect, what you expect.
Pretty red roses.
White puppy noses.
Mammoth rubber hoses in his small leg.
Yes!
Oh!
The strange worshippers pull at their faces.
Despite himself, a strangled cry escapes Brent...
Ah!
...as he sees the ghastly heritage of atomic radiation.
Hey, Tony! Let's have some!
Get me out of here!
I mean, hell, this turn, the other cheap thing could be carried a bit too far, you know.
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize those in our sleep tonight.
That is if the crazy Arabs...
...social rights don't get us first.
And the fire will rain down from the sky.
The fire will rain down from the sky.
People die.
The gurgle of a death rattle.
The awful heat.
And I couldn't see...
...the smell.
The terrible rotten smell of burning flesh.
Help me, please.
You're just a bomb!
Yeah! Get a bomb, you son of a bitch!
...
Why did we come all this way?
But the trouble is that all this knowledge I've got hold of is useless.
We're going to come back in just a moment.
We're going to have some strong comments about this.
And we're going to continue with it.
It's no wonder one group of kids said we're a...
...a generation that's been born under the mushroom cloud.
Here on the subgenius death ship, we approach San Francisco.
Our mission, destroy anything.
Somebody help.
Help me, please.
Has this ever happened to you?
Meltdown.
Please remove all humans from container area six.
Doug, pull over. We've got to scrape the collar off the front of the show.
If we have another collar...
If we get another collar on the front of this show smeared like that last one, we're going to be in severe heat damage.
Well, I don't think we should drive the show so fast.
Well, you're right.
It's just stupid to keep wasting fuel running over listeners like this.
There is no collar.
There never has been a collar.
We're listening to tapes. All the collars are gone.
The show was just a tape, right?
Yes.
This joke has been real.
Well, but they did survive and they're willing to give us their wristwatches and most of their...
Imagine listening to this show and surviving.
Internal organs.
Unfortunate. Yes, it was.
We do have some...
The doctors were still here.
Good morning, tiny collar.
Don't drive any faster.
Yes, well, it would have been nice to hear your message, but at this hour we're asking all messages.
Ten minutes left to rotate your message toward the war and off the planet.
So aim high with us. To find out more, all you have to do is speak with your nearest Air Force recruiter.
Ah, that's more like it.
We're all in the Air Force now. We're all heading toward Grenada.
Los Angeles approach control. This is...
No, no, wait. We're over Los Angeles. Don't drop the bomb now.
Oh, look out. It's too late.
...Los Angeles.
Holy cow, that's an L.A. stadium down there.
...five-two at five thousand, especially around control.
Oh, this is awful. What are we going to tell the newspapers?
...Los Angeles.
...and no one can catch anything, but it's exploding bright.
They're congratulating us.
Look at that beautiful bomb pattern.
...as half the Olympics taken out in one final sweep of sub-genius terror.
I'd say that was one of the most beautiful patterns I've seen in the performance so far.
I think that'll get a nine for most of the judges, don't you?
Down there on the floor.
That was a flawless performance on that last explosion.
The Olympic nuclear explosion competition has been a fierce and competitive one with some unexpected contributors.
Oh, yes, the LA Olympics, this certainly...
...smaller countries, but this...
I'm glad I got my tickets there.
...so close.
I got my ticket for my Cabbage Patch Doll.
Well, I hope you left that Cabbage Patch Doll at the door.
The baby's gone.
There's no place in the future...
...because you know they said some of them have a mind of their own.
...the minks of the rich have...
But silence did not follow.
The awful heat.
And I couldn't see.
Oh, ground zero...
I couldn't stand it.
...is the place for...
The smell.
...the smell.
...the terrible life...
No, the terrible experience was far und Adele's Wilcoel.
Ground Zero...
...is the place for me.
images of bunch of people
ground zero
Is the place for me.
I can't believe it...
ground zero
have we met again?
Bon idotif means I'm here for you.
Andy, Marty, andob以
I can't believe it, because Idotif iske
Can someone help me?
irane
that was good.
That's utter nonsense.
The future is always nonsense
until it becomes the past.
I'm sorry, but you see,
it is my curse to tell the absolute truth.
Oh, gloom and destruction.
Despair, hopelessness.
Dark foreboding of consciousness.
Oh, poverty and hate.
Oh, kill little kids.
Oh, Brian De Palma movies.
A world of destruction.
Darkness and despair.
Gloom, chaos, anarchy.
A hopeless culture.
Self-indulgence.
Inter-evil perverseness.
It's like Jones told me that one time.
He said, if you can't X that tractor out of your ass,
you don't ever get to heaven.
Oh, darkness, gloom, destruction, despair, poverty,
and other bad shit.
I fall like a dead man
in the canyons of my mind.
Oh!
In the canyons of your mind.
They're like those wagon wheel rocks
on the bottom of the canyon in your mind.
They're like those tiny little turd things
in the bottom of the rocks in the canyons of your mind.
They're like those tiny little turd things in the canyons of your mind.
Now, these aren't just little valleys.
They're not just little grooves or ditches in the earth.
No, no.
But they're canyons!
Mighty-sized, deep, wide canyons.
Canyons.
Oh, yes.
The swingin' love corpses
with that lovely, lilting tune.
Canyons of my mind.
Or I should say, falling like a dead man
through the canyons of my mind.
The swingin' love corpses.
And before that, KPFA Berkeley radio
with Palmer Vreedy's Gary the Broke Friend
and Puzzling Evidence, Doug Wellman,
with Glass Madness singing.
And all of that, friends,
and the collage material before that
was all from the old subgenius,
Media Barrage number 11,
edited by yours truly,
with St. Byron Werner
and Doug Wellman,
Puzzling Evidence.
Friends, there was also a lot of Devo
and Oingo Boingo clips in there
because it was the 80s.
Now, it's the 80s.
And as the old pass on and pass out
in the fields of Asgard,
the uppity youngsters come along.
Such as,
Reverend Alex Thompson,
age 14.
In fact, we're going to listen to
Reverend Thompson's first sermon,
in public anyway,
recorded live at the 4X Day Drill 2001.
And after that, we'll hear a nice piece
of Connie from Reverend Protectrix Amazonia.
But now, friends,
Reverend Alex Thompson, age 14.
Whenever I interview,
I introduce an unsaved friend,
friend to the church and subgenius.
They'll read the pamphlet number one,
and they'll read the pamphlet number two,
and they'll read through the long, long paragraphs
of confusing and arcane text
typed up by Stang and Drummond
so very long ago.
Oh, they'll read through it as they'll say,
ah, this is what it is, this is what it is,
this is so bizarre,
and off the wall,
but what about Bob?
What about him?
He looks just about as straight as Ward Cleaver.
He looks like your ordinary, everyday dad,
dad-man, father image.
He's got the way about him.
But, you know, and they get this image in their heads
of the pipe-smoking businessman
in the three-piece suit,
chatting up Jesus or the devil or whoever.
The most important thing to remember
about the image of Bob has always been
that no matter where you go,
you see a job saying you know what it stands for.
Yeah!
Slut!
It's simply him, a man, smiling and smoking a pipe.
Yeah!
A pipe filled with the uncut word of himself.
A pipe filled with his holy f-!
A pipe filled with the word of Bob!
Amen!
Preach it!
That the we mortals are only now beginning to understand it.
That's his image, that's his way,
that's Bob, praise Bob,
and if no one else, then by all means,
turn to Connie because, you know,
because let's not kid ourselves guys,
she's the real power behind this church.
You know, she's the one we all know.
Hail Connie!
Woo!
Ladies, gentlemen, fellow travelers,
here ended the rant.
Good evening.
Yeah!
Woo!
Right, Saint Alex, friends,
14 years old!
Woo!
So, don't even think about it, girls,
that's general practice.
Yeah, the church of the subgenius is much older than that young man.
Jesus pointed out we're celebrating our 25th anniversary soon.
As long as it can be distinguished that man is man and woman is woman.
I think you're just a big bully.
I don't care if you like us,
because we don't like you,
and we don't give a flying what you think.
I thought you were trying to French kiss me!
Boys have a vagina.
Girls have a vagina.
Men have a penis.
Man is woman and woman is man.
Guys for girls and men for men.
Hummin' a, hummin' a, hummin' a.
A woman pretending to be a man pretending to be a woman?
Ridiculous.
It's preposterous.
In fact, it's so preposterous no one would ever believe it.
I find it mind-bending.
There is going to be hell.
Medically impossible.
It's not really hard to believe.
It's just hard for you to accept.
Guards!
You can't spread his.
Good heavens!
Ah!
You can't hurt me while I'm here.
I whip this out.
Ah!
Guards!
Castrate him.
No!
Guards!
Castrate him.
This is not a haphazard maneuver.
Careful planning for it started months back.
Beware.
Beware of the big green dragon that sits on your doorstep.
Ah!
He eats little boys.
Please have some of my time.
I'll be downstairs.
Ah!
Be.
That.
Nailed it.
Ah!
Bob is not what you would call a brilliant man.
Hence the word church of the sub-genius.
You notice this isn't church of the genius.
Some geniuses out there may have noticed that by now.
What Bob has been trying to say is that it's not the intelligence that counts.
It's just plain, plain old sense.
Horse sense, common sense, sense of humor, and most importantly of all, dollars and cents.
J.R. Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies
for Time Magazine, and I didn't know who he was.
Exactly.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the church of the sub-genius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Or Bob.
Oh, baby.
Life is grim, is it not?
Yes, life is grim.
And you drive through town and see that a boy who is not a good man is a child of God.
Abandoned factories.
Yes, yes, yes.
The ice caps are melting.
We hate it.
The water is rising.
The world will soon be drowned.
Yes, yes, yes.
The plague is spreading.
Yes, yes.
The bubbles are on everyone, master.
All is lost.
Yes, yes, yes.
Barbarism and inhumanity reign in the trees.
The children are lost souls.
Yes, yes, master.
The world is coming to an end.
Yes, master.
These are all signs of the end time.
Bob spoke of it before.
He wrote of it in the book.
Is your name written in the book of life?
Yes, master.
Or will you be cast into the lake of milk with the pink ones?
Okay.
Oh, they like the lake of milk.
Oh, well, maybe you don't care about the end of the world, the end of freedom, the end of the ability to think.
My master.
My freedom.
They just want the law read to them.
I guess they like Johnny Law.
I guess they ain't going to send in that $30.
I guess they ain't going to play.
Send in Johnny Law's bill.
Thank me, master.
But friend, what will you do when you're called up before the judge?
You know, you tied your shoes this morning, but will the undertaker untie them tonight?
And saw your feet off to fit you in that coffin because your family couldn't afford a big enough one?
Things are bleak.
Things are rough.
Sure, you can try to think positive.
That's just when they're going to come up behind you.
Sneak up on you.
They sneak up on you, man.
You know they're after you.
Oh, yeah.
They're coming for you.
They're not being paranoid.
They really are after you.
They're coming for you.
That means you better know who your friends are, buddy.
You better know where you're going to find Sukor, an aide, when the big hammer comes down.
You know what I mean.
Can't get it with the Sukor.
Who are you going to go to?
You going to go to the cops?
You going to go call 911?
Oh, yeah.
The earthquake's sucking you right down.
The giant volcano's going off in the middle of Kansas.
The mosquitoes the size of dinosaurs are sucking your blood.
You're going to call 911.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
911.
Are you going to go to the...
You're going to know who your friends are and go to the man with the pipe.
You're going to call 669.
669.
911.
Yeah.
You call 669.
You talk to the man with the pipe.
Yes.
Might even offer you a light himself.
Yeah.
Where's that pipe?
Lean back.
Uh-huh.
Big old...
Take a big old hit of that church there.
You know everything's going to be all right.
You get turned off.
You'll be down.
Don't hang down.
Or are you going to screw up?
Or are you just going to say, well, that was a real funny little skit.
It's pretty.
But I'm...
Yeah, sure.
I read in the newspaper that...
That the child murderers are killing their mediocrity parents and putting them in jars.
Oh, yeah.
I read that the ozone layer was almost completely gone.
And that's why me and all my neighbors happen to seem to have cataracts.
I know that the electrical wiring in my home is giving me cancer.
But, you know, well, nothing's perfect.
You know, every cloud has a silver lining.
Tomorrow's another day.
What you know won't hurt you.
Yeah.
You know, Bob's not real.
I don't need slack.
I guess I'll just go down with the rest of them.
Look at these.
Look at these joyous little Morlocks below.
Sure, today the Morlocks are little friends.
It's stunted.
Rather depressing looking as they are.
They love Bob.
They may be pathetic and sad.
But you know that in the future they will be the ones who run things.
Sure, the Pinks may live in their mansions up above ground.
Being fed mysteriously every night somehow.
Fattened up.
And they never grow old.
Because when they turn 30, they're taken away by the Morlocks at night.
And fed to Morlocks.
And fed to Morlocks families.
That is the destiny of the subgeniuses who are left behind on X Day.
Yes, you may...
If you're left behind on X Day, your grandkids will get to be Morlocks and feed off the Eloi.
But if you're truly saved, friend, you ain't gonna have to worry about that.
You're gonna have universal luxury on the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
Universal luxury.
Little boy.
Come on, baby.
Universal luxury.
Little boy.
Come on, baby.
Universal luxury.
below record
What you buy now
The circumstances
Then you cannot go out
Oh yeah
What you find out
The circumstances
Then you cannot go out
Oh yeah
Little girl don't you know
That the stars up above
Are running all alone
Little girl don't you know
That they're blinking at you
Now the sun can sunburn you
But
Not as bad as the lost
Old people do
Yeah
guitar solo
I
Now the sun can sunburn you
Can sunburn you, but not as bad as those old people do.
I want you, once you find out the circumstances,
then you, then you, then you, then you can go out.
Oh yeah, you can go out.
You can go out.
Bay.
I could die.
I know where that jive is at.
One thing I do have on my mind, and it terrifies me too.
Will you call me another guy's name when I try to make love to you?
And you, sir.
I love you.
So if your baby leaves you, got a tale to tell.
Just take a walk down Roman Street to a heartbreak motel.
I've hit the zone lonely, baby.
I've hit the zone lonely.
I could die.
Heartbreaker.
Hotel.
Heartbreaker by Dread Zeppelin.
And before that, we heard Circumstances by Captain Beefheart
and the magic band from the album Clear Spot.
Ah, yes, and a little clip of my life with the Thrill Kill Club.
And a lot of old, old ESO swamp radio on WCSB Cleveland
with Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy, and the band.
Cowboy Dave, special guest princess, we are dough, and yours truly,
from February 1995.
Reverend Chaz Smith there providing the live music.
But now, let us go even further back before the Morlocks and the Eloy and the ESO
to Berkeley, California, the KPFA radio station back in the day
before they changed with Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence,
and?
Glass Madness.
I first had my experience with Bob at a Bob's Big Boy on the corner of Bellevue Drive in
Los Angeles, California in 1959.
It changed my life and I became able to open my third nostril and snort the divine wisdom
of the subgenius.
Every morning before breakfast, I find it helpful to go into my sternutrition room,
as we call them, and sniff up.
Sternutrition.
Yes, violent sternutrition may be observed.
Named after the famous sternio?
Well, yes, the famous sternio does practice sternutrition,
as does everyone who possesses the simple accoutrement of a handkerchief
and a head full of ideas that need to be relieved.
Subdivide the box brain.
Oh, Bob, with your square little gray brain, how do you use that thing?
It's hooked up all wrong.
Oh, Bob, what about this rumor that your pipe is a living organism?
Yes, that has invaded your brain and made everything all wrong.
Yeah, what about that Bob grinning malarkey turkey flunky prop?
What about them aliens, as you say, or us aliens?
We're not aliens.
How about it, Bob?
And who's this anti-Bob?
Some relation of yours?
Some nepotistic cousin on the payroll end?
We dare to question our supreme epopt-Bob, because we have the freedom within the Church
of the Subgenius to question even the basic verities, like whether or not there is a Mokele
Mbembe, whether it's frog-like bellow does echo over the South American or even the African
swamps.
Swamp?
Swooms?
Swamps.
Yes, swamps.
Right now.
That's where they live.
Glass Madness is in that swamp.
Yes, he's gone down.
There's a green hill.
They say Mokele Mbembe lives in Lake Ukabalabonga, which is only four feet deep, but the creature
of...
Balaboomba.
No, Ukabalabonga.
All my other rubbish.
These people are making rubbish.
Let's just keep walking.
That's not stop.
Buy the book of the Subgenius.
Up there it went.
And here...
Oh, wait a minute.
I think it's time for a commercial.
Bob Dobbs, he's no slob.
Bob Dobbs, he's no fool.
He is a hater, he's a hater.
The subgenius church.
That's why he's super cool.
Like Glass.
He's Bob Dobbs.
He's no slob.
Bob Dobbs, he's no fool.
He is the head of the subgenius church, and he is super cool.
Glass Madness, friends, from Media Barrage 11, and now it's time for you to get your
pencils out and start working.
And write down the address of Bob so that you can figure out what the hell this church
and the subgenius thing is all about, and maybe get some free weird little pamphlets
with stuff printed on them.
Or you could just check out www.subgenius.com on the internet.
But to get that pencil ready, friends, while this background music by Tipsy from their
album Uh-Oh is playing, you can write down the address of Hour of Slack at P.O.Box1411.
That's Box 1403-06 in Dallas, Texas.
And the zip is 75214.
P.O.Box 1403-06, Dallas, Texas 75214.
And here now is little Theodore.
And Babushka.
Then, live at the XXX Day Drill in 1999.
And after that, friends, we're going to take some calls.
Praise Bob!
There is only one hope for me.
I want to be Bob.
Sit and smile all the time.
I should've stayed in his grave.
I think every day is a
Don't wanna be Jesus!
You always look so sad!
Ha ha!
He must have had an awful day!
I wanna be Bob!
Tell everyone about Slack.
Let the pigs kiss my crack!
Don't wanna be Jesus!
Don't wanna be no slave!
He should've stayed in his grave.
Don't wanna be Jesus!
I wanna be Bob.
Never have to work a day.
All eternity's a play.
Don't wanna be Jesus.
Don't wanna carry no cross.
Don't wanna speak for no half-boss.
I wanna be Bob.
See everything all so clear.
Shitty to grin, ear to ear.
Don't wanna be Jesus.
Always trying to figure things out.
Who needs all them fucking cosmic doubts?
I wanna be Bob.
Yeah, I wanna be Bob.
I'd even like an InnoJersey.
Yahoo!
Maybe I could go over to...
Back in the days when we lit up...
That was possible.
Good will and see if I could find me a nice pink suit coat.
Find you?
What's with the reflection stuff here?
You're from Appalachia, too, and I mean, you know, find me this, I'm gonna get me that.
You know, come on, man, what's up?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get me some.
Find me this.
I'm gonna get me one of them.
I'm gonna get you one, too.
I'm gonna get them one.
I feel like that I'm gonna get me one of them.
I'm Femskip.
Go out there and get me one.
I'm fitting to get me one.
But if you're...
I'm gonna keep you.
That is one of the most frightening words to any...
Yes.
Hello?
It's a female.
Hello.
How are you?
You're so beautiful.
Oh, thank you.
You sound like a soft spring breeze has wefted into the room.
Oh, it's because I haven't been showering too much.
Oh, you have just taken a shower.
I bet that your skin is still moist and a little bit warm, huh?
Mm-hmm.
And the little evaporation of the vapors come in can smell very well, huh?
You can smell it?
Really?
Oh, of course.
No way, man.
I'm like, oh, my God.
Oh, boy.
That's why it's perhaps the smell of lilacs and diseased ovaries.
No, no, no.
I don't need that.
I'm using my third nostril to whiff-read your psychic stench.
Have you been watching the movie Sinbad the Sailor and eating garlic popcorn?
Mm.
You had many important past lives.
More of a book.
You have had many important past lives.
You are an old soul.
You are a very old soul.
Want some more soul?
Well, what did you call it?
More?
Axe about your old soul.
Show?
Go.
Some more.
Get even, Barber.
Think of the fun you'll have taking Barbie and Ken on dates.
We've already had all that fun.
We're taking Barbie and Ken on dates.
With Krabby and Barber?
No, we've already executed them out in the ditches way beyond Panoria.
You dress them up real pretty and put the caveman outfit on one of them
and sometimes a little skinny tie on the boy and take them out on a little date.
Oh, that would be my favorite thing to do.
That's always my favorite thing to do when I'm home.
I like to take the caveman and take the, you know, the necktie from the business suit guy
and strangle them all up.
When you're home or at the home.
Strangle them with them.
Now when you're home or at the home.
That's before you start burning them.
I have to stay home lately.
Yeah, the home lately?
I have to stay home.
Oh, a shut-in.
And what is your problem there, dear sister?
I have a busted up knee.
Oh, what a bust.
A beautiful bust.
A bust and money, you say?
Yes, when you need your bust.
Busted up money and knee.
I went to the bank and they said I didn't have any.
Knee?
Even more needful.
It seems to have hit the concrete and been pushed to the side in every direction.
That sounds beautiful.
I would like to watch that in slow motion.
So, uh, would you be interested in joining the Bonobo sect?
Um, what's in it for me?
Oh, everything go in there.
What's in it?
For you?
Yes, everything go in there.
What's in it?
Or should I, should I say, what, what will be in me?
What would you say rubs you the right way, my dear?
The spirit, the spirit!
You will be filled.
Will, will, will fill you up.
The spirit of slack.
The spunk of some diseased, mentally ill old gentleman who believe the world is coming to an end.
And course and speed and spray!
In actuality, their own minds are coming to an abrupt halt.
And they will flee at a time.
They'll join you soon in that home.
They'll be there next to you.
The David's.
He just closes his eyes and he just goes.
He's there, man.
He's there.
It doesn't matter.
It's just like, yeah, see, that's why.
That all sounds really, really nice.
It does.
Yeah.
The spunk of an old diseased man?
Yeah!
Don't you get pleasure out of the most mundane things?
I think the old diseased man Dave is referring to may be Dave.
I was referring to you.
But if there was ever a diseased...
That's not Evangela, is it?
Mm-hmm.
I thought so.
I thought that...
I thought it was...
How's the mutated eunuch you're letting live in the basement?
Because I was afraid she'd be great.
Oh, I don't have a basement.
I don't have a basement.
I don't know who you mean.
Well, then how the hell is a mutated eunuch living in your basement?
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're sacking the saddle.
You're back to the wind.
You know all what else.
Hey, thanks for calling, Devangela.
Thanks for calling, Devangela.
Long call, Dave.
Don't you know what they're doing?
You're going to yourself?