Oh
The Self Genius
Power of
Swag
That was a couple of years ago
I went back to reform
school and watched my chance
and this time I finally escaped
But yeah
back to Bob, Bob Dobbs
So yeah
I mean we were quite lucky to get
Reverend Stang so early on
Yes we were quite lucky, he does quite a few interviews
and he never
he's always informed, he never misses a beat
he never misses a beat, so many good quotes
and so much wit, it's incredible
Yeah and the guy's been around for a while
and he's got to hang out with some really cool people
which you'll find out in the interview
and you know he's done a lot of interesting stuff for his life
and this church subgenius is
an institution
that's been around for quite a long time now
Anyway, enough of us waffling on
Let's roll the Ivan Stang interview
Yep, enjoy
What is the church of the subgenius?
You know that is a a great question
that none of us have been able to answer
after 30 years of it
sitä that it is definitely
the church devoted to group
JR Bob Dobbs
the smiling mysterious faces
in the square with the parts
that you see tattooed on so many weirdos
body parts
and Bob started this church back in the
50s as a, I guess you could call it a disorganized religion for non-joiners, weirdos, mutants,
disbelievers, or our favorites, those who will believe anything.
So it's kind of gotten to be a social club in the last few years.
We were surprised that the weirdos would be able to get along with each other as well
as they do, for the most part.
Yeah, nice.
It definitely seems to have been going quite well.
I mean, when did it start, officially?
Well, we first released the secret material to the public in January of 1980, 28 years
ago.
But our guru, Bob, had been developing this ever since his divine immaculation in 1953,
when he had a vision of the alien species.
And he had a vision of the space god, Jehovah One, a sort of a multi-dimensional monster
that has pretended to be God successfully to many cultures over the centuries.
This creature informed Bob that throughout history there's been a conspiracy of normal
people robbing away the slack of all the abnormal and strange people.
I guess this was part of Jehovah One's design to extract...
to extract more agony from the human race.
But then, apparently, this space god wanted to sell the planet off to some other aliens
and wanted Bob to get it into better shape for the sale.
So Bob was commissioned to travel the world and recruit people to build up his church
that would, in turn, build up more slack for the truly worthy persons.
That is, anybody who sends...
sends us $30.
That would be 20 euros, I guess.
It's about 15 pounds, I think.
Yeah.
And technically, you know, a subgenius isn't just anybody who has $30.
The true subgeniuses are the people who are descended from the yeti of the Himalayas, or
the Sasquatch of the Americas.
Um...
But nobody believes that.
And so we found that if we charged $30 for membership, people took us a lot more seriously.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob!
So we've been talking a lot about J.R. Bob Dobbs, but could you give us like a brief
overview or biography of who he is?
Well, yes.
Yes, the great Bob Dobbs was born of a woman, although it was sort of a miraculous birth.
She wanted to get an abortion, but the tenacious child Bob could not be removed from her holy womb, the womb of Jane Dobbs.
So they took her out to a Kansas wheat field and waited for a tornado to come.
And that successfully yanked the fetus Dobbs out of Jane's womb.
But then when she saw the beauty of Bob's fetusly visage, she, of course, fell in love with him and was glad she had not put him to death.
Although, oddly enough, in the Church of the Subgenius, abortions are legal up until the 15th year for any given fetus.
They don't have to be in utero anymore to be aborted in the subgenius family.
So these kids better watch their step.
But Bob, as Bob grew up, he demonstrated almost magical powers.
It was like he could read minds and control the minds of people.
He was rich by the time he was six years old on the stock market.
And it's not that he's brilliant.
In fact, Bob is kind of what you would call retarded.
If you look at his face, he has that vacant grin, almost like a crazy man's grin.
It's not that he's intelligent, but that he is lucky, and hence the term subgenius.
This isn't about intelligence.
It's just the opposite.
We feel like intelligence has been misdefined by the conspiracy of the normals for all these centuries.
And that it's not being smart that counts.
It's being lucky.
Bob is the luckiest fellow in the world.
And for years, he was known among salesmen as the greatest salesman in the world.
He could sell hypocrisy to Baptists, ice to Eskimos, and hate to subgeniuses.
And eventually, he realized that if he turned his gifts to religion,
he could sell and sell and sell without ever really even having a solid product.
That you could put your fingers on.
So he was literally selling nothing.
The belief in Slack was enough.
And so he recruited Dr. Philo Drummond, who then recruited me.
And together, Philo and I in Dallas put together the initial subgenius pamphlets
that were designed to rope in seekers and suckers.
Because we'll take...
Even if somebody's really just a normal who's...
mentalist, or whatever, he's a normal.
He's mentally ill and thinks they're a subgenius.
We'll still take their money.
L. Ron Hubbard taught Bob that although they may be pink of soul,
their money is green in color.
And that's all that counts.
In this country, all of our cash is the same dull color, I'm afraid.
A lot of what Bob says is sort of inscrutable.
You may be familiar with many of his most famous slogans, such as,
Pull the wool over your own eyes.
And relax in the safety of your own delusions.
Now, the fact is, you're still blind.
But it sounds good, doesn't it?
You know?
And it's better than pulling their wool over your eyes.
And too much, he said, Bob said, too much is always better than not enough.
So he plumbered out on the way to the emergency ward getting his stomach pumped.
Sometimes he leans on the floor.
And leaves the not-so-funny ending off of his slogans.
The original was, too much is always better than not enough, but it's almost as bad.
But that doesn't have quite the same kick to it.
You know, college kids don't go for that.
It's too real.
And as Baldwin Lee Primer said, I've had it up to here.
It's that old, you know, I'm mad as hell and I'm not going to take it anymore.
I've had it up to here.
And I've also had it down to there.
And frankly, he said, I like it down to there better.
Oh yeah, me too.
That was Puzzling Evidence imitating me, Reverend Ivan Stang, preaching at Starwood Festival of July 2008.
The radio interview with the real me before that was from the British podcast called Right Where You Are Sitting Now.
A great interview show.
And all their interviews with various counterculture muckamucks are at the website sittingnow.com.
We also heard collage by the great Lee Murr.
There will be more of all that.
But first, let's go to the Puzzling Evidence show at KPFA in Berkeley where Philo, Puzzling, and Dr. Howell attempt to trick yours truly into playing this very clip.
In the darkness of night.
What would happen to these men?
Superstitions.
From earlier cycles.
The shifty and the shifters.
More primitive agents.
That was me doing Ivan Stang.
And in these shadows, coward dark gods.
Whose malefic influence corrupted the innocent soul of man.
Ivan Stang, Ivan Stang, and we all go down to Ivan Stang.
I'm gonna vote for Ivan Stang.
Stang for president.
President.
For vice president.
But what do we really know about Stang?
What do we need to know about Stang?
Nothing.
If you believe everything you read in the book of the subgenius, huh, well, we have a bridge to sell you.
The fact is, no one really knows much about this mysterious figure called Ivan Stang.
He's one quarter Eskimo and one quarter black.
He's one quarter everything black.
One quarter Chinese.
He's the perfect mix of ethnicity.
He will appeal to you and me.
To answer this question, one must go back to the beginning of the Stang Empire at the Slacker Mansion in beautiful Cleveland, Ohio.
Here every year, for the events of the X-Day drill, as it is going to be called, assemble beforehand a historic event which normally transpires in western New York State.
He's a wise old Chinese man.
He's got a beautiful wife.
He's got a beautiful family.
He's a little bit of a
strong-willed.
He's a good man.
sinus cavities.
If we did an hour and a half of singing Ivan's Tang,
do you think he'd put the whole thing on his show?
Like, we could just be one whole show
of him just praising the
crazy Ivan's Tang.
If they do your name for an hour,
you're going to use it for something.
At least a phone message.
And you can hear that phone message
at QuiveringBrain.com
which is Philo's website
full of all the audio that I can't play
on this decent family show.
And you can also hear more
Dr. Howell on his own show,
Ask Dr. Howell, seen at
AskDrHowell.com
And meanwhile,
we go back to England for the
Right Where You Are Sitting Now show
wherein I strive to convince
the world that the Church of the Subgenius
actually can get you laid.
Well, and we hold
events, I mean, this isn't just
a paper tiger church.
We
don't
actually get along with each other all that well,
but once a year,
we hold big events
in both
one in Europe and one in
the U.S. We're hoping to
spread even further to
Oz and so forth.
But every July 5th
we hold the X Day.
So far they've all been
X Day drills where we practice
for the end of the world.
We hope that each July 5th
will be that prophesied day,
but, you know, we're fanatics.
We don't care if we have to wait
8,000 years.
As long as we get our slack.
As long as you get your slack.
And plus, these parties are really fun.
The X Day parties are great.
I mean,
they're kind of like a cross between
a sci-fi convention,
a swingers convention,
and
I don't know,
some sort of twisted lab experience.
I don't know.
It's really a lot of fun.
And this,
the one in Europe this year
is in Copenhagen.
I think around July 5th.
But I'm not even sure where.
So,
we've had people come to the one in New York
from all over the world.
Some poor devil
showed up from China
once.
And we're hoping to get a whole gaggle
of them from Great Britain.
Yeah.
We have a lot of friends in,
well, all over the place there.
There are several British popes
at the subgenius church
in competition with each other.
But all rivals pale
in comparison to Dobstown,
our fabulous walled encampment
in Malaysia,
seen here in this tour of Dobstown
by Reverend Sweetness McGee.
This place doesn't look a damn thing
like a travel brochure.
Now you know why there are only
selling one-way tickets.
If my head wasn't hurting so much,
I'd have sworn I was in heaven.
Heaven for guys who like big tits.
Holy!
Will you look at them hooters?
What is this, anyway?
Bob?
Some kind of goddamn comic book?
We got robots.
We got cavemen.
We got kung fu.
I've said it before
and I'll say it again.
War stories and monster movies
are educational.
Educational.
Praise the Bob.
It looks like a refuge.
It smells like a fart.
Bummer.
Well, maybe Dobstown
needs a little more work.
Thanks to Reverend Sweetness McGee
for that.
So now let us flee Dobstown
for the relative peace and sanity
of the 11th X Day Drill
at Brushwood, New York.
In this case,
a fake hour of slack
being performed on stage
with Dr. Howell,
yours truly,
and the bodacious
Priestess Pisces
discussing the sometimes tortured
sex lives of the subgeni.
Pisces, you look like you...
Would you like to join us?
Up here?
You're welcome to.
I've never known you
to shut your mouth for long.
Take microphone number three.
I could trade places with you
or...
Does that...
Does that look a fair word?
I just...
I was actually quoting Pisces
when I mentioned the hygiene business.
Yeah.
They do for me.
They do.
Well, you might want...
There's a lot of boys here
that come going,
I've heard I could pick up
a mutant girl
that would even like
somebody like me.
And it's true,
although most of the
best ones are taken.
There's some available,
but Pisces,
I think you could give
these boys a chance.
Actually, I can.
I was just talking to
a beautiful,
beautiful uber femme
who was totally dismayed.
She has been out there
and just looking gorgeous
and smiling
and being kind
to all of these boys
and not one of them
would even give her
a shoulder rub.
What uncouth boys.
And the problem is
is that
I had to explain to her
that subgenius men
aren't really used to women.
And when a beautiful woman
comes up,
it's kind of like
if you had that cat
who always wanted to look
in that cabinet
in the top of the kitchen,
was always trying
to get in there
and then you open the cabinet,
and the cat goes,
oh fuck,
and runs away.
That's what happens.
No, meow means me.
Replace every meow
with the word me
and cats make perfect sense.
You know, they don't,
they don't meow at each other.
They only meow at people.
That's a greeting
they have for people.
And it says,
pay attention to me.
That's why it's me.
It's just me, me, me.
It's me yowling.
Essentially.
Yeah.
But yeah, subgenius men forget
that there's all these
beautiful women
who want to talk to you,
you know,
and you guys go,
oh crap, it's a girl.
And you kind of freeze up.
Now on the other hand,
then there's the other side
of subgenius men,
and this goes back
to the hygiene issues
and other issues.
Uh-oh.
The subgenius men
who don't take hints,
if you're sitting...
Case in point.
The microphone wasn't taking a hint.
If you're sitting around a campfire
and people start moving away from you
a lot...
You might need to wash.
Exactly.
And by the way,
sitting in the hot tub
doesn't count as bathing.
You've got to use the shower first.
I hope everybody does.
But a lot of you forget that
and you kind of need to remember
that you do kind of like...
Just because we're out in the woods
doesn't mean that you can go to caveman.
We don't want that subgenius essence
floating on the surface.
Oh no.
And besides that,
the actual...
The habits of that hygiene
sort of amplify.
It's like you have a natural Yeti perfume,
but you have to be clean
for that to come out.
And it's sort of like a Yeti pheromone
sends out that signal
to the appropriate mate
with the matching pheromone
because everyone's like,
everyone has a different one
that works together.
That was very clear.
You give a better lesson than I do.
Easy to remember.
So yes, there's a...
I don't know.
I always...
I have girls ask me for the...
You know, boys ask me for the advice
and the girls ask me for the advice
and I think I understand
the boys' perspective, but...
Well, how saintly of you
to take on all this unwarranted advice acting
and to be the Ann Landers
or Abigail Van Buren of X-Day.
Which is funny
because I'm not at all polite.
Well, but people are always seeking answers.
Seeking they will.
Just as many poor bobbies
are seeking companionship,
at the same time right now
there are some really lonely uberfemmes
seeking not necessarily
a wild romp in the hay.
They're not necessarily looking for you
to last for a four-hour marathon
of yeti sex.
Sometimes they'd just like you
to rub their feet.
They've been walking around
on the hard ground all day.
I'll rub them.
Not at all.
No, there's a lot of tenderness involved
in caring for an uberfemme.
It only stands to reason.
I know Stang is aware of the care
of uberfemmes and space goddesses
and could probably add something
to his personal experience.
Yes, when Stang's memoirs are written,
Casanovas will have to take a back seat.
Those are interesting, by the way.
I recommend those.
Casanovas.
Those are a wonderful, wonderful read.
Many volumes.
When my memoirs are written
in blood and vomit
on a cell wall.
What's playing at the Roxy?
I'll tell you what's playing at the Roxy.
A picture about a Minnesota man
so in love with a Mississippi girl
that he sacrifices everything
and moves all the way to Biloxi.
That's what's playing at the Roxy.
What's in the daily news?
I'll tell you what's in the daily news.
Story about a guy who bought his wife a small ruby
with what otherwise would have been his union dues.
That's what's in the daily news.
What's happening all over?
I'll tell you what's happening all over.
Guy sitting at home by a television set
who used to be something of a rover.
That's what's happening all over.
Love is a thing that has licked him.
And it looks like Nathan's just another victim.
Yes, sir.
When you see a guy
reach for stars in the sky
you can bet that he's doing it for some doll.
When you spot a John
waiting out in the rain
chances are he's insane
as only a John can be for a Jane.
When you meet a gent
paying all kinds of rent
for a flat that could flatten a Taj Mahal
call it sad.
Call it funny.
But it's better than even money
that the guy's only doing it for some doll.
When you see a Joe
saving half of his dough
you can bet
they'll be making it for some doll.
When a bum buys wine
like a bum can't afford
it's a cinch that the bum
is under the thumb of some little broad.
When you meet a mug
lately ordered
by the jug
and he's still lifting platinum
faulty Raoul.
Call it hell, call it heaven
it's a probable twelve to seven
that the guy's only doing it for some doll.
When you see a sport
and his cash has run short
you can bet that he's banking it with some doll.
When a guy wears tails with the front gleaming white
who the hell do you think he is?
You think he's tickling pink on Saturday night.
When a lazy slob
takes a good steady job
and he smells from Vitalis and Barbasol.
Call it dumb, call it clever
but you can get odds forever
that the guy's only doing it for some doll.
Some doll, some doll
the guy's only doing it for some doll.
I feel like the first man who landed on the moon.
You're gonna be the first man who landed on a dick.
Well honey you know that you can and will lick my dick.
It could just be so yammy.
Freaks of any kind give me the willies.
You see Javier is the man all men want to be.
Javier is uh...
It takes a lot of energy.
Javier is the man.
He's the man no woman can say no to.
Yes he's a Rudolph Vasolino type.
And I'm hoping Javier somehow someday trips on this YouTube thing when I get it done.
I know who you're talking about.
He certainly is an oily riser.
Yeah that'll get us done off the air for sure.
I... he goes to bed oily but
I... I suppose that's probably not something one should...
So what you can see up to the north there are the pleasure saucers approaching the town.
There they are?
It's almost next day folks. Almost St. Stupids day.
Just look at these giant glowing vehicles. They're here. They're here at last.
Oh no are we supposed to crawl inside or do we have like...
Settling down.
We don't have to do anything but the bombings will.
They're gonna come out and bring us in right?
When that cavernous opening extends its ramp.
A private vehicle up to...
Well I'm coming to the cocktail party before next day the end of the year.
When is that?
It's just before the end of the world.
Oh okay.
About sunset.
So that'll be the only time you ever go to X day actually.
Yeah the cocktail party. I'll be there and then people...
You'll be there at the cocktail party.
And then bang a comic cocktail.
At the end. No it's at the beginning.
And then people are gonna talk about how they saw me the whole time.
Yeah see how somber it was that they saw you.
I know he was there. I saw him.
It's like...
He was the guy that killed Bob.
La Jetee. You know they see you again and again.
Get him. That's right.
But uh...
Get him.
Dune to relive the last moments of civilization before the nightmarish nuclear holocaust.
No they would throw me in the air.
They were so sad because you...
Poor little Ivan Stang.
He killed their dream before they could even dream.
Staring dumbfounded at the flickering and now meaningless images of Ivan Stang and puzzling evidence.
Every time you have to poo.
Doomed to repeat this behavior over and over to the end of time.
There I would be floating in a little scummy pond next to Ivan Stang who praises we sing.
And the frogs still sing in the scummy pond where Ivan Stang was thrown so long ago.
Sorry man I dropped my drink.
No way dude.
Let's see it.
Well no this is um...
I gotta run the show here.
This is a classified vid and we...
This video doesn't get exhibited except to...
Really?
Select individuals with a G clearance and that is not a viewer clearance level.
If you give a video...
It's not my clearance level.
I can't see this tape either.
What about the video we did...
Well not that video.
When we were down there...
That contains embarrassing moments which...
Oh we have another video.
We did it in the lid.
Oh for we're dead.
Where were we at the overman head?
And we were out there on that point.
Over...
Camping at the end of the...
Of course.
Cause I got some...
Let's see what is...
Oh that's...
I'm thinking of a...
When...
The overman finds the alien one.
There's a...
There's some funny overman scenes but I've already got them...
Well this was out like there on the...
Human soul.
What?
It's a brand new bright Obama day.
What a time to be...
Black.
A girl.
Or gay.
No nothing could go wrong.
So join us in this song of happy days for the gays.
Nothing can go wrong.
Look nobody's watching.
It's time to spread some hate.
And put it in the constitution.
Now how?
Proposition 8.
It's great.
He's a...
That wasn't right.
That's a lie.
But it works so we don't care.
Now you wish we'd all shut up.
But make our clothes and fix our hair.
And our love's not a sin.
Well the bible says it's so.
Well the bible says a lot of things.
You know?
Jesus Christ.
Hey how's it going?
Lil John.
Jesus, doesn't the Bible say these people are an abomination?
Abomination?
Yeah, but you know, it says the exact same thing about this shrimp cocktail.
Shrimp cocktail?
Leviticus says shellfish is an abomination.
Abomination?
What else does the Bible say, Jesus?
The Bible says a lot of interesting things.
Like you can stone your wife or sell your daughter into slavery.
Well, we ignore those verses.
Well, then, friend, it seems to me you pick and choose.
Me pick and choose.
Well, please choose love instead of hate.
Besides, your nation was built on separation of church and state.
See you later, sinners.
Bye, Jesus.
I love you, Jesus.
You know, here's another thought to wrap things up.
Oh, every time a gay or lesbian finds love at the parade,
there's money to be made.
He's right.
It's time to groom, say, paint that wedding hall,
and lavender's the shade.
There's money to be made.
That's a point.
Think of all the carriages and four white horses.
There's millions lost from all your disapproval.
Well, that's not good.
Think of all the lawyers for the gay divorces.
Think of the tattoo removing.
We get it, Merrill.
We've been such fools.
I can see America's calling me.
Yes, gay marriages will save the economy.
Yay!
That doesn't look like me at all.
If you were turned inside out, that's the way you'd look.
I am so sick and tired of these fucking actresses with big piss.
I have to have something to keep me company while you're away.
Sometimes in the night when it does get a little lonely,
I reach over and touch it.
We've experienced a solar disturbance.
It has the same effect as if it came from our own sun.
Shorting TV and communication relations.
The magnetic disturbance that disordered the ship.
But once those particles bounce off, the magnetic field realigns itself.
Now, I can say yes, we're completely removed from that.
You're naive.
I think we turned our original course.
I reach over and touch it.
If you want to be happy, you want to have legs open and your mouth shut.
And your mouth shut.
You're a lousy human.
more than any woman I've met for a long time.
Mike, I think I've uncovered something.
Oh, what?
Girls.
I'm serious.
Look.
Half naked?
Oh, my God.
I'm in a titty bar?
I don't see a thing.
Huh?
Half naked?
Oh, my God.
I'm in a titty bar?
I don't see a thing.
Huh?
If you must copulate,
why don't you go outside and do it?
Why don't you just shut up?
I'm just getting ready to blast off.
I reach over and touch it.
Half naked.
I'm in a titty bar?
I reach over and touch it.
A scene from X-Day, edited by Reverend Sweetness McGee.
Before that, the song was from Proposition 8, the musical.
I found that on YouTube.
We overheard the Puzzling Evidence gang planning their crimes against me.
Me, and before that, the song Guys and Dolls from the 1950 album of the Broadway play of the same name.
By the way, you are listening to the Hour of Slack number 1185 from the church of the subgenius Praise Bob.
You can and will learn way more from our gigantic website, subgenius.com.
And now, the weather report.
Hello from Palm Springs.
Why, hello there.
Hello, Palm Springs. Come in, Palm Springs.
What's the temperature like there?
It's beautiful, actually. It's finally cooling down.
Yeah.
It's a good time to take a bike ride.
I just did a few days from, let's see, Las Vegas, driving up through Tiago Pass.
Hurricane Xerxes is on its way.
It's just like you said. It was all clear and nice.
Clear skies, smooth sailing.
Me too.
I would like to see the top 100 or so people who get written in.
Each election for president.
Who gets the write-in vote?
Yeah, the Ivans.
Ralph Fielding Snell.
See who got the most votes.
And George Stovall.
And then you'd end up being vastly skewed with all those 12 million people that voted for themselves.
The original President Stovall.
The people that the top 100 vote for.
The unknown president.
Bob Dobbs. I always vote Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs? He's no schlop.
Bob Dobbs?
That probably offsets my vote for Ivan Stang.
But I wonder who...
How many...
You wouldn't vote for Stang? That wouldn't be good government?
I mean, no. I never voted for Stang.
I write in Stang as the VP.
The head of the Mormon church might get a lot of votes.
The best government of all is the dominion of the philosophy.
Joseph Stang?
Joseph Stang, yeah, that's the one I meant.
Joseph Stangle.
His great, great, great granddad.
Well, that would be an interesting thing to know.
It would be. That'd be a neat...
That might be really obscure.
I wonder how you'd go about finding some of the early...
Yeah, how would you find that out?
And who would keep those types of records?
There's gotta be records of that.
Yeah, yeah.
By tippy-tippy-tipping your internet, of course.
There's a chance, of course.
Type in the search engine.
Right.
Kiss your sticky notes goodbye.
The thing is, the website somewhere where all the...
The written in...
The write-in vote...
Written on the win.
...getters are...
Check out, like, write-in vote-getters top...
Top write-in vote-getters dot com.
In votefakers dot org.
Yeah, or...
Top write-in vote-getters plus all cities plus...
Yeah.
...USA plus...
...U.S.A. plus...
...goatsuckers dot...
...historical...
...or...
Maybe it's just Schmedley Schmidlap, you know?
Well, if you put that in, you get every answer...
Ralph Fielding Snell and, of course, Byron Harris Bringer.
Schmedley Schmidlap.
...has deaf to jiggle.
Have you gotten by Walgreens to check out those skull rolls?
I have, but I have not.
I don't think I've seen the skulls you am talking about.
Walgreens has some of the best skull stuff.
They're boss bitchin' and groovy.
They still might have some.
And they have screamers.
Don't...
Did you see the screamers?
Yeah.
You mean the movie?
The new screamers.
New screamers?
No, they're pocket screamers.
Pocket screamers.
You can put them in your pocket and they just scream.
Oh, my.
I am.
Well, I am.
Like a woman?
Oh, my.
Like a woman screaming.
Like a rabbit screaming.
Like a little bobby screaming.
Or like the victim of an axe murderer screaming.
Or an alien being disemboweled by a...
An unthinkable thing just disemboweled by a...
...faceless goon.
For the delay trigger.
Yeah, that one.
You walk away and then they leave them in an alleyway.
In a big city somewhere.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah, then the zombies close in on you.
The little poured out bobbies are left by churches usually.
But hope is not necessarily fully extinguished even in those situations.
Their minds drain of thoughts.
And their wallets drain of all that money.
They've been totally cordwangled in their bogle.
And they're still alive.
Yeah.
From their guggle to their zatch.
Then the UFO comes back later and picks up the cartons.
They spend all their time screaming like that.
They use them for fuel.
And now the shrieking starts.
Then the dandos come and stuff them in their gander bags.
Really?
Yeah.
Along with their rucksacks.
Yes.
Then Johnny Rucksack stumbled in his tucker bag.
Under the shade of a couliba tree.
And we wangled with the bunion.
Then we wangled the jumbuck.
We wangled the jumbuck in the air.
And after we snarked the jumbuck.
I snarked the crap out of that jumbuck.
Down came the snark.
Manon walloped the jumbuck.
And then we grunged the jumbuck for a while.
And after we had our way.
We threw it on the gogles.
And we cord wangled our bogles.
And we threw it on the gogles.
And we barfed Matilda with me.
And so forth.
Yeah.
Bob replaces the drugs.
Just looking closely at the dots that comprise his face.
Eats up so many brain cells.
And it's just like using the drugs.
He is, shall we say, the Chinese finger trap of the mind.
That's what Bob is.
But most importantly, above all else, Bob is a short duration personal savior.
We're in a world of planned obsolescence.
And Bob knows that you're not always going to be in the mindset where you definitely need Bob as your main personal savior.
You might have to fall back on Jesus sometimes.
Or whatever you grew up with.
Or some porno star that you are enamored of.
It's revolving messiahs.
You will be one too yourself.
In fact, you might be somebody's short duration personal savior right now and not even know it.
The suching is church is real.
In that if you think about it, it's a hell of a lot bigger than Heaven's Gate, for instance.
How many of them killed themselves?
Thirty-nine.
And then there was another fifty or so that wussed out.
And Jim Jonestown, speaking of interest in cults, had nine hundred people.
This guy got nine hundred people to kill themselves.
Friends, there are like nine thousand subgeniuses whose addresses we still have.
There's more like forty thousand of them who are standing there thirty bucks, but we know no more where they are now than where all that money went.
But!
We have a very active social life.
It's unlike, oh, but there's lots of funny rival cults like the Flying Spaghetti Monster and the Scientologists and so forth.
They're all also satirical takeoffs.
But they don't, they haven't been around this life.
Certainly not the Flying Spaghetti Monster folks.
Praise the Flying Spaghetti Monster.
But they've been around long enough that I run into kids, I run into grown-ups who say,
Oh man, my parents were into Bob.
I hate that shit.
They made me memorize that stuff.
And then I also run into people who go,
Wow, I used to listen to your radio show, Hour of Slack, when I was a teenager.
Man, we couldn't live without it.
We listened all the time.
And that's when I have to go,
It's still on.
I can't believe it.
How many members do you get?
For a year, roughly?
Well, these days, about, depending on the weather, three to five people officially join the church every day.
We've probably totaled up, it's hard to say because a lot of them have moved and we've lost track of them.
I mean, we've been around 28 years.
I would guess that roughly 30 to 40,000 people have sent that 30 bucks.
Yeah.
Although we can only get our hands on about 8,000 of them at any given time.
Now, what's strange about this is look at some of the cults that get so much press.
Heaven's Gate, the famous suicide cult.
Jonestown, another famous suicide cult.
The Branch Davidians from my time.
The Branch Davidians from my hometown in Texas.
Yeah.
And those cults are like maybe 100 to 1,000 people, if that many.
Heaven's Gate only had 39 casualties.
There are so many subgeniuses that we won't even begin to pass out the poison Kool-Aid unless we know we can off 1,000 people at once.
So, you know, the Jonestowns.
The Jonestowns and the Branch Davidians.
There's some end of the world people in Russia lately.
And we had fundamentalist Mormons here once again in Texas in the U.S. causing some embarrassment for the authorities.
And yet the Church of the Subgenius is much, much bigger than most of those.
Yeah.
So I can see why the conspiracy tries not to talk about us.
Because it would only make things worse for them.
Because you're more of a powerful group in numbers at least.
Right.
Well, and that's about all we have is numbers.
None of us are very good with weapons.
We're not really, most of us are not violent except with our dearest friends and loved ones.
So it's not much of a terrorist kind of a cult.
And plus we're into slack.
Yeah.
You know, Bob said the aliens will come in the year 1998 and destroy all the humans.
And save the dues paying subgeniuses.
So we are, every year we wait to see whether this is the real 1998.
But we're not going to destroy the world ourselves.
We're slackers and we're going to wait and let the aliens do it for us.
Yeah.
So.
Hey, let's go down this.
Let's see what's down this hallway.
And remember the bunyip and the whistling tea kettle.
Shh.
Okay.
What's down that hallway?
Can we get down there with this equipment?
I don't know.
Why?
You mean there's something not on the QT?
Hey, this is Kenneth Spoon.
Quentin Tarantino?
I'm just saying that there's something that's a little bit hinky about this operation.
Are we supposed to like.
This is Ivan Stang's office.
Oh well.
This is Ivan.
We don't have any business here.
I have no idea how much the church makes.
Let's look in these drawers.
Oh my god.
What time is it?
It's 11.
I can't get this drawer open.
It's.
Ivan Stang.
Look, there's three locks.
Look, it's glowing.
There's three locks on this drawer.
Uh oh.
Look, there is a, there's a radiant glow coming out from under that desk.
This is the church room.
It's a mailing list.
Oh, that somebody's on the phone too.
Uh oh.
Somebody's tripped an alarm.
There's nobody here.
It's 3 o'clock in the morning.
He's going to be here in here.
He's going to knock you off.
Oh my gosh.
If I could only find the doorknob, but it seems to be slippery and moving around.
That's me.
That's me holding onto your pockets.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well.
All I have to say is.
I thought that was your pocket.
This is a situation which calls for wonder wash.
I think if we keep sneaking along this wall, we'll be able to get out of here.
Before Stang catches us.
Yeah, well.
Of course, we left enough DNA in that office.
Of course, when you say that, the wonderful drug is supposed to appear.
So he'll be able to replicate us in no time.
And he didn't appear, so.
You know.
Really, that doesn't help us at all.
You're Vogel.
You left the Vogel in there.
I beg your pardon.
Herr Vogel.
And there's enough Cordwangle left.
Cordwangle Smith science fiction story.
That I'm sure the DNA can be extracted.
And then our cordless model.
And we can have to worry about clone technology.
Uh oh.
You'll never hear the moan of a clone.
You're going to do it again and again.
Our new generation knows special pseudos are priceless duplicated to provide the very best
in synthetic choice.
If you don't help them, they'll just make instant clone out of you and not be off.
But don't take our word for it.
Toddle on down to the Clonatorium.
Your clone.
And view the models now on display.
It'll teach them to be more compliant.
Their time is your time.
That's the way to do it.
And for a limited time.
You don't do what I say, I'll.
Get Mini Clone Junior.
I'll make a clone out of you who is more compliant.
You'll love him.
An instant clone.
I'm just going to talk about that guy.
That's the clone.
That's the Clone Ranger.
Hello caller.
What are you doing at 346 this morning?
That's our new president.
Party on, Wiz.
um because i haven't looked at that in a while you look at like yeah gosh i wonder what dinosaurs
they would have possibly those are japanese ceramics from the 1960s and 1950s or
bronzes after a while it gets to be what features do you want and what price
what uh price range or they could simply be some contemporary probably chinese knockoff
our best fan ever that's why she's lighting a pipe yeah of course she's a fan is this our fan yeah
it's princess this is a video response to one of your postings yeah to the to the show
toasted in the posting toasted young people what's the toast young person the show we fight for every
thursday night this show right here this one that we're without question i don't have time to talk
about the show i'm not going to show you the show i'm not going to show you the show i'm not going
to show you the show march into hell for a heavenly cause we are at war keep your head down
we are now at work forces only bringing in those extra supplies over here quest we're dawdling
that my heart will be peaceful and diddling while you're dominant to my rest you're dawdling and
diddling your chord wangle again we gotta get these supplies in here we're gonna not we're gonna
run out of ammunition at this pace in no time we still haven't look there's those zombies we've got
zombies zombies
zombies but bobbies gotta hit the zombie bobby where's zombie bob he's the only one that can speak
their language keep your head down those zombies where are you where were you in training you gotta
help us zombie bob you just stayed in the mess room the whole time eating the whole time i won't
help a zombie you idiot you should have been out there learning some stuff and now we take the hand
on you to keep us out of it look out don't pick up the zombies you're not gonna get away with it
up hitchhiking zombies stupid idiot you bring the whole platoon down because you're such a slacker
you're doing nothing but sit in the bathroom reading those bob magazines
should have been out and marching with the rest of us have you seen the latest issue of wichibo
some geniuses are all alive lazy slack masters and if you want to be a lazy slack master too
you can see subgenius.com which will lead you to archives of this show and of all the other shows
which are scavenged to make this show you might want to check out the puzzling evidence show
via quiveringbrain.com or reverend susie the floozy's show on wrek.org you can also investigate
the subgenius printed magazine called quiji bow of which dozens of back issues are available and i'll
give you a real world address for that in a minute quiji bow has everything friends it's got cheesecake
photos of your favorite half-naked connyites open flaming antagonistic personal challenges and
so forth gossip photos proving how we're all so screwed up and some scholarly writing and some
retarded writing and some normal natural writing some drink recipes ads
and some reviews of all the editors friends cds and the address for quiji bow is 18 west
maine that's 18 west maine street greenfield indiana four six one four zero and send a self
address stamped envelope for pricing information which i can't give out on this station oh and if
you want to hear more of the music that's in the background this is the flying ryan brothers from
their cd totality you can find more about that from ryanetics.com ryanetics is spelled with an r y
a n but enough of that now let us hear rubinoff and his violin
so
i think that i shall never see
oh
wow
another uh group of news was there oh oh oh
inside
Insight, Smiling Bob, the dude is going to prison.
He had to forfeit a billion dollars.
He's losing his home and his mom's going to jail.
That's what happens when you try to cop J.R. Bob Dove.
For those of you who don't know what I'm talking about,
on certain cable network channels, you're harassed endlessly by these ads for male enhancement pills
called Insight.
And they're actually pretty funny ads.
But they stole Bob for him.
It's Bob, but without a pipe.
And they call him Bob.
And he grins and he's stupid, but he has a big wanger because of these pills.
Which, by the way, are a complete fraud.
And they were convicted of fraud.
And the guy and his mom are going to be locked up and lose everything.
I've been telling everybody that I get half.
Actually, we didn't even try to mess with that.
Our policy generally is to avoid anything that has to do with lawyers at all.
Because they get all the money.
My dad's a lawyer.
How do you think I became a preacher, friends?
Actually, I found out I'm descended from...
At least four of my great-grandfathers were preachers.
Probably crazy preachers.
So, you never know.
Bob Raskolnikov.
Steve.
Steve K.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you very much.
Good luck to you, and God bless you.
Dostoevsky.
Subgenius.
Come in.
Think you're funny, huh?
Here.
You dirty!
You old hag!
Come in.
I haven't done anything.
You don't want to go.
You dirt.
What's going on here?
Who's that maniac?
Bob.
He's a writer.
Huh?
Oh.
I confess!
Doesn't your conscience ever bother you?
No.
Well, leave me alone.
And now, a touching farewell from Bob Walkenhorst.
Excuse me, I was just leaving.
I hate to derail your train of thought.
Sorry to interrupt in mid-sentence for you.
Hammer and nail me to the spot.
Well, excuse me, I was just leaving.
I used to be the lover that you celebrate.
Now I'm just leaving.
Someone you barely tolerate.
I hate to leave the house in such a mess.
But that's what happens when you bleed to death.
And baby, excuse me, I was just leaving.
Yes, I gotta go.
Excuse me, I was just leaving.
Oh, no, no, no.
Baby, I'm leaving.
Excuse me.
I was just leaving.
Excuse me, I was just leaving.
Oh, no, no, no.
Love has a way of hanging around.
Long after kindness has left town.
Sorry to come between you and your demons.
Excuse me.
I was just leaving.
Fun isn't always of the same size.
Three years from now I'm addressed by a drama queen.
I'll hate the number on the wall.
ologian染으ş legally gangbang gjëz m Jungleいうこと.
Oh no, no, no.
Baby I'm leaving.
You singer that I can't breathe.
Dude, you're on the wrong trail.
Get away.
I've done
Re-lo-
Thanks for coming!
I hate being up here.
We're glad you're here.
Liar, liar, liar!
Thanks for coming.
I also welcome the Girl Scouts who've joined us.
Yeah, I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm glad you're here.
This is the place where Barney likes to hang out.
He came out a little early.
Liar.
As we quarter Americans, also share our blessings.
It's the spirit that moves men and women to be scout leaders.
Liar.
There you go.
Gonna end up on somebody's table.
Thank you all for coming.
Okay, but uh, staff regs probably gonna have some antecedents to deliver to our next meeting.
wife is a very strange, stupid, covered witharl-
f chuyon.