you are about to participate in a great adventure experience you are about to experience the odd
mystery mystery which reaches from the return of mine to the subgenius hour of swag
slack off it's the idea that counts not the source i see that it's truer now more than ever
copyright violation is mankind's best entertainment value the proof is in the pudding for me the
medium is the message i thank you
oh man what people would
what
what a piece of work my friends and welcome
i've learned that there's no place like home and that if i ever go searching for my heart's
desire to travel no further than my own backyard i think that may have been phineas narco talking
just then i don't know i'm not sure but friends welcome to subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
number 606
yes 606 hours of slack and you know that's a sacred number for us my friends because 606 uh
sounds or actually looks kindly like the letters b small b o b 606 equals small b zero big zero
small b it's show number bob i guess you could say yes and in the background here we have the
Ego Plum Music once again.
And friends, I have such a wonderful amount of show ready to go.
And for once, I'm not in a rip and hurry to get it done.
I can take my time putting this show together.
I can take all day long and feel like I'm actually doing my job.
We've got some KPFA Hal and possibly even Jane are on that show.
That Dr. John Casual Media Barrage.
We've got Dr. Legume coming up.
Of course, Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
More from Cleveland.
The lovely Friday Jones.
The lovely Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
The lovely Chris Peterman.
And the lovely Princess Wiardo.
Everything is just so lovely.
The universe is a beautiful place if you just let it be.
And that brings us...
to the news.
Dear friends, I do have...
Speaking of copyright violations,
we do have a newspaper that we steal from.
It's called The Onion from Madison, Wisconsin.
I believe that's where The Onion's from.
It's certainly my favorite newspaper.
Yes.
Let's see if they've got a...
TheOnion.com
That ought to tell you what you need to know.
Well, anyway, according to The Onion here,
the ACLU...
And now for the news.
The ACLU defends Nazis' right to burn down ACLU headquarters.
New York.
At a press conference Monday,
American Civil Liberties Union officials announced
that the organization will go to court
to defend a neo-Nazis group's right
to burn down the ACLU headquarters.
ACLU president,
Nadine Strossen,
told reporters that her organization
intends to vigorously and passionately defend
the Georgia chapter of the American Nazi Party's
First Amendment right to freely express
its hatred of the ACLU
by setting its New York office ablaze
on November 25th,
which is coming up in just a few days, friends.
Quote,
I am reminded of the words of Voltaire.
I may disagree with what you say,
but I will defend to the death
your right to say it.
Strossen said.
While the ACLU vehemently disagrees
with the idea of Nazis torching this building,
the principle of freedom of expression
must be supported in all cases.
If we take away these Nazis' right
to burn down our headquarters,
we take away everyone's right
to burn down our headquarters.
Buddy Carver, president of the Georgia chapter
of the American Nazi Party,
praised the ACLU for taking on his case.
I would like to thank Ms. Strossen
and all the other
Negro-loving, bleeding-heart liberals
at the ACLU
for defending my constitutional right
to express my loathing of them
with hundred-foot-high flames,
said Carver,
sporting a tan uniform
and swastika armband.
We must finish the job
Hitler was unable to.
ACLU associate director
Mel Rosenblatt agreed.
The real danger here is not the American people,
the real danger here is not the American Nazi Party,
he said.
The real danger here is what would happen
to the rest of us
if the Buddy Carvers of this world
were not allowed to commit arson
against Negro-loving, bleeding-heart liberal Jew attorneys.
Making the case all the more controversial
is the neo-Nazis' demand
that the ACLU's entire 315-person staff
be in the building at the time of the blaze.
Strongly opposing the request
are New York City Police Commissioner
William Bratton,
Fire Chief Ed Holm,
and the ACLU's entire staff.
and the ACLU's entire staff
and Mayor Rudolph Giuliani,
who said that all 315 will die
if trapped in the 14-story office building
during the blaze.
ACLU attorneys responded
that they will request a federal appeals hearing
if New York City attempts to stop them
or their fellow employees
from perishing in the November 25th blaze.
Yes, my loving wife Linda
and three wonderful children,
Ben, Robbie, and Stephanie
will be devastated
when I am killed next month.
ACLU attorney Ben Bratton
said,
but I recognize that in a very real sense
it would be a victory for Mr. Carver
and his fellow hate mongers
if I did not burn to death
because their terrible message
of bigotry and intolerance
would be all the more effective
if suppressed.
The Carver case is one of several
controversial legal battles
with which the ACLU has been involved
this judicial year.
In State of California vs. Tubbs,
the organization defended the right
of a San Francisco art gallery
to display
a piece of performance art
in which innocent passersby
are shot to death by gunmen.
In February, the ACLU went to
U.S. Appeals Court
to defend the grand wizard
of the Oklahoma County, Mississippi
chapter of the Ku Klux Klan's right
to beat a black man to death
and spray paint
quote, white pride
unquote, across his chest.
We can have no arbitrary setting of limits
when it comes to the Bill of Rights,
Strossen said.
The Constitution does not say,
you have the right to express
these opinions, but not those opinions,
nor does it say,
you can express these opinions
by word, but not by violence.
For a free society to work,
hatred in all its forms
must be encouraged.
Isn't that wonderful, friends?
And also in the news here
from The Onion,
lifestyle news.
Hot, sexy girls
waiting to talk to guys
just like you.
Van Nuys, California.
According to an announcement broadcast
on late night cable television Saturday,
hot, sexy girls are at this very moment
waiting to talk to guys
just like you.
The broadcast, sponsored by
the Van Nuys-based telecommunication company
Chat Time Entertainment,
urged all guys just like you
to call these hot, sexy girls
without delay in order to minimize
the amount of time the girls
would have to wait.
While the precise number of girls
in question was unspecified,
James Hegel, a spokesperson
for Chat Time Entertainment,
stressed that they are specifically interested
in hearing from guys just like yourself.
These girls aren't looking
for just any guy, Hegel said.
They are interested in a certain type of guy.
Namely, guys who have
working touch-tone telephones
and possess the motor skills necessary
to dial a phone number off their television screen
into the aforementioned telephone
without error.
You know,
guys just like you.
That's the type of guy they're talking to.
Chat Time employee and hot, sexy girl
Candy Lux agreed with Hegel's assessment.
I just love talking to guys
who have cable TV
and watch it late at night,
she said, reclining in a bubble bath.
I just find it so attractive
that when they watch a phone number
come up on the bottom of their screen
and then dial it,
well, it sounds like somebody's just now
dialing in our office.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Fellow hot, sexy girl,
Brianna Kisses.
You know what I really like?
When a guy has a working credit card
and knows how to operate a telephone.
Running her hands over her body,
she added,
when guys like that enter their credit card number
on a touch-tone phone,
it just drives me wild.
Though no specific timetable was given
regarding how long the hot, sexy girls would wait,
Hegel said they very much want
to talk to guys like you.
As soon as possible.
One of these girls' biggest turn-offs
is guys who are indecisive
or slow to take action,
who take a lot of time trying to decide
whether or not they should make a phone call.
These girls want to talk to the kind of guy
who calls right away.
That kind of guy.
What are you waiting for,
said hot, sexy girl, Sandra Pett,
reclining backwards into a pile of soft, lacy pillows
while arching her back
and thrusting her breasts forward.
Aren't you the type of guy
who likes to talk to hot, sexy girls?
Please, don't keep me waiting.
Call now.
Pett added that a nominal fee
will be included in the cost of the call.
And friends, I think,
you know, on that note,
I really should cut over to this
Reverend Friday Jones live.
This is not entirely queued up.
I'm going to mix the music on the fly
and we'll just see how it works.
Say you're new in town
or perhaps just very weird
and you're having difficulty
finding friends and or lovers.
How do you know who to pursue?
Well, to begin with,
if you're a creep,
an ever-whining scumbag
who hates everybody
yet demands attention,
you can forget it.
Otherwise, no matter how shy
and nerdly you might be,
no matter how awkward at meeting people,
there are specific clues to look for
that will tell you whether someone is
worth the embarrassment of being a nerd.
or the embarrassment of getting to know.
Men,
mount a dog's head on a wall
and watch its eyes when a girl walks by.
If they move to follow her,
she's a subgenius.
Ladies,
you can judge a guy by his boobs.
Eyeball his knockers.
That's the secret.
While searching for a true subgenius friend,
you might kill time by using a pink or two.
They're easy to make friends with,
at least for the short term,
if you're that desperate.
They have little or no control
or critical faculties
except those dictated by the con.
And you can quickly go through a long line of normals,
first enticing them,
then burning them out and dropping them.
Having being molded into the me generation system
by the con,
you should be able to so thoroughly out-me them
that they'll eagerly let your me
replace their me.
But be careful.
If you overdo it and become the biggest me around,
you'll end up believing it yourself.
And the next thing you know,
you're just another tool.
Sometimes,
it takes years to find your subgenius mates.
While waiting,
you can always develop an imaginary friend
just like you did in childhood.
Or for that matter,
you can just buy an inflatable one.
A hint,
the ones with simulated hair are worth the extra price.
On the other hand,
maybe you don't want anybody anyway.
19 out of 20 relationships end up being disasters.
But get this,
the ones that do work usually come right after
you've given up looking
and accepted the isness of the now.
Give up and you'll get sex.
There's something else you can do on the pleasure ships
that I forgot to tell you about.
You get to have sex
with the alien sex goddesses.
Yes!
And this is a song just about that.
¶¶
¶¶ Well, now that you know the meaning of fallen sex,
you'll quite often want to get one.
Just take aPRINCY instead
Now, how are sex and entendence related?
It's key to love it.
Plan out when the sex will start.
but it couldn't always lead all the way,
but what do you do
. . .
Ah, sex!
Well, I have no intention of sex.
Now, with the bloody girl.
My, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my.
Oh.
No time.
Oh, stop this crazy thing.
No time
Oh, stop it, bout what?
It's too much
Or have you lost your Citizenship?
If so, even that's R.I.P.
We RB JONAH
With the bloody girl.
Have I lost my Princessänglist?
White woman, save me, please.
There's her.
Yea, stupid.
A little bit.
Whoaaaaa!
But, that's a face.
I'm a sax
Well, I have no reflection
Sax in another dimension
My, my, my, my, my, my, my, my, my
So long
Adieu
Bye-bye
Ah, sax!
Yes, you'll all be having sex in another dimension
When you bore the pleasure
Yeah, if things work out, friends
If things work out just right
Yeah, preaching
Yeah, friends, I'll tell you what
I'm a sax
Ah, Einstein's Secret Orchestra
Talking about the great promise of X-Day
Sure, the escape vessels of the sex goddesses and so forth
But I think we need a sobering reminder here
From Dr. Legume's sermon
At the Cleveland Devival recently
At Euclid Tavern
This is where these recordings come from
Pardon me
I'm going to probably have to do an inordinate amount of cuss word editing
For most of the American stations
Because
Ah
There was this fat, drunken, skinhead, blonde guy
That wrecked
He wrecked the videos
He wrecked the sound
And he actually even wrecked the tripod
Um
He wrecked the vibes
And the whole time
He thought he was just the coolest subgenius there
In fact, he was a shameful
Bobby-like pink boy
Who really is the kind of person
That kind of makes the church an embarrassment
Sometimes
And I'm sure that many of you know what we mean
But let us forget the fat, blonde, skinhead
That everyone who was at that Devival remembers
In a very negative sense
And let us stop being vindictive and bitter
About these amateurs that
Sully the clean and true word of Bob
And go straight to Dr. Kitadon
Legume, thank you
Yeah, actually the guy
Um
Wasn't a skinhead
He told me he was a skinhead
He had a
He had some hair
And he had a little blonde beard
But he proudly told me
That he used to be a skinhead
Oh, God
When X-Day comes
They will all die
He's gone 47 miles above water
Harry Potter
One fine orthogard
He still need a
Knit to take a cut
I know, bros
We want a little more
R traveler
For a snack
Do you want us
So listen
Look at this
I say
We courage and
относ
To, hey
Oh yeah, brothers and sisters, I'm back here in Cleveland once again.
Yeah, I've preached here for several Halloweens here in Cleveland.
This is the third or fourth Halloween I've been out here.
Yeah, Halloween's a good time. I imagine come Friday there'll be lots of little kids out trick-or-treating,
running around in their little costumes, going door-to-door, asking for their little treats.
Well, tonight I want to tell you the story about a little boy who's not going to be going out trick-or-treating this year.
It's a little boy, a little retarded.
It's a little boy. His name's Arthur. He's my nephew.
And a week ago, he was in the bathtub taking a bath,
and my brother-in-law, he went in the bathroom and looked in on him
because he's retarded and he can't take care of himself.
And they found him face down in the tub, and he was blue.
You think that's funny? This is a true story.
This is a true story.
It's a true story.
Yes, it's a true story.
Well, they found him face down in the tub, and he was blue, and he was dead.
And my brother-in-law took him out of the bathtub, and they performed CPR on him,
and they brought him back, and they put him in the intensive care unit at the hospital.
And they managed to get the water pumped out of his lungs,
but it turns out that he had epileptic seizure in the tub, and he had lost control of his bowels.
And some of the water.
So they found out that he had inhaled into his lungs.
Well, it had shit in it.
Well, the doctors didn't know what to do.
He had gotten a terrible blood infection from the shit in his lungs getting mixed around in there.
And they said that he had maybe two days to live.
Well, they gave him antibiotics and everything,
and I guess the doctors were wrong,
because he's starting to pull through.
Well, brothers and sisters,
you know, I could get all morose about this,
but instead I decided to use this
to send a message to you all.
Because when I look out at the group of you
unsaved out there tonight,
I see the face of a bunch of little retarded children
who are being slowly poisoned by their own shit.
Yes, brothers and sisters,
you're all being poisoned by your own shit.
And you're dying.
And you don't know it.
You're dying because you're just too retarded
to know that you're dying.
But brothers and sisters, we're here tonight.
We subgenius doctors are here
to give you an antibiotic
in the form of J.R. Bob Dobbs
to help you clean the poison out of your system,
to help you clean the poison out of your blood,
to keep you from being poisoned by your own shit.
Because, brothers and sisters,
if you don't take that pill,
that Bob pill, that antibiotic
that we're offering you tonight,
well, come July 5th, 1998,
you're all going to be pushing up the daisies.
And it doesn't have to happen.
It does not have to happen,
brothers and sisters.
You do not have to die.
You're damn right I'm scaring you.
If you don't have your membership
in the Church of the Subgenius,
you better goddamn well be scared
because you're going to burn.
That's right.
You're going to burn.
You're going to be burned up in the fires.
The fires.
Not the fires of hell,
but fires a thousand times hotter.
Oh, yeah, because we're one up on the devil.
The devil, well, hell.
The devil's like fucking Mr. Rogers
compared to subgeniuses.
Because we're some sadistic cocksuckers.
And we like to protect our own.
Is there any of our own here tonight
who know that Bob's going to protect them on X day?
Can I get it?
Can I get an amen?
Amen.
Can I get a praise Bob?
Praise Bob.
Oh, these, these saved are the ones
who recognize that they were being poisoned
by their own shit.
Oh, yeah.
And Bob helped them flush out the pipes,
brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah.
He flushed out the pipes for the saved.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
And they'll be trick or treating.
But they won't be trick or treating this Halloween.
They'll be trick or treating on July 5th.
Except for the next one.
Except for all the treats are ours.
And all the tricks are on y'all.
Oh, yeah.
And there won't be egging nobody.
We won't be pitching eggs.
We'll be pitching fucking nukes.
Oh, yeah.
We'll be pitching your fucking skulls around
in the backyard for sport.
We'll be bowling with your severed fucking heads.
Yes, brothers and sisters.
And there's only one thing you can do about it,
brothers and sisters.
You've got to get right with Bob tonight.
You've got to get down on your knees,
stick out your tongue,
and take that pill.
That's right.
You've got to take that pill that we're offering you tonight.
You've got to get right.
You've got to get...
You all need to get yourselves some head tonight.
Can I get an amen?
Can I get a praise Bob?
Can I get a praise head?
Hell yes, brothers and sisters.
Praise the head.
Hey, this is what your head's going to look like
after X day, brothers and sisters.
If you're saved.
But if you're not saved after X day,
your head's going to look kind of like this.
Oh, yeah.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Your poor little mushed head is going to be all over
the steel-tipped boots of the subgenius.
We're not asking for much.
We don't care about your soul.
All we care about is a measly small $30 donation
to the church of the subgenius.
Now, you can take that money,
and you can go see the Indians lose that last game of the series
if you want to go to Florida.
Yeah, you can spend your money on that.
But, hey, all that's up to you.
It's over now.
And, well, this will be the last World Series.
Yes, it's the last series.
You know why it's the last World Series?
Because it's the last year, and it's the last world.
And the only series you all are going to see who are unsaved
is a series of terrible events happening to you.
Yeah!
Oh, yeah.
Oh, and we're going to laugh.
We're going to laugh at you.
We're going to be laughing at you
as we watch the invisible hands of your own dead saints
drag you deeper and deeper to the bottom of an ocean of poison shit.
Yeah!
And you will drown.
You will drown in your own shit.
Even more than you are now.
Even more than you are drowning in the shit
that the conspiracy dunks you under in.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, get rid of your stress.
We'll get rid of your stress.
You won't have anything to worry about.
The only...
Oh, yeah.
You won't have to worry about going to work.
You won't have to worry about whether your children are watching
dirty TV shows on Fox.
Oh, yeah.
Well, let me tell you.
There's somebody else who won't be worrying that night.
The worms.
Because they won't be worrying about what they're having for dinner.
Yeah!
But will the con be destroyed?
Yes, the con will be destroyed.
We will grind the conspiracy under our boot heels.
Yes, we will grind the conspiracy.
We'll grind the conspiracy sheep under our boot heels, too.
Oh, yes.
Yes, fuck the clones.
Fuck all the clones.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck the pink boys.
Hell, yes, brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah.
And they're really all clones.
Walk out into the street.
Can you tell the face of one man from the face of another?
No, they're all just faceless sheep.
Just sitting out there, factory bred fucking chickens.
That's right, brothers.
Crammed into little boxes like veal.
Covered with your own shit and waiting to be slaughtered.
Well, brothers and sisters, I have one thing to say if you're waiting to be slaughtered.
You don't have long to wait.
Yes, brothers and sisters.
The river's rising and you're all going to drown.
Tonight we're offering you a personal flotation device.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters, the supermarket's out of food.
The road's closed.
The roads are closed.
The supermarket's out of food.
Your lawn's on fire.
Your front yard's on fire.
Your backyard's on fire.
You can't get out.
Oh, yeah.
And brothers and sisters, the only chance you have is to hop on that last train out of town.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs will be driving that train.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Can I get an amen?
Can I get an hallelujah?
Hallelujah.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Well, I'm going to end my sermon now with three simple words.
Three simple words that could change your life tonight.
Don't fuck up.
Amen.
Hail Dr. Legume.
Don't fuck up.
Friends, Bob Dobbs promised you that if you spent that $30, you would never, when the escape vessels came on,
on July 5th, 1998, you would never have to worry about the pinks and the normals, the conspiracy again.
But nobody said who was going to protect you from Dr. Legume after X Day.
What happens if he wants to put you on his planet of broken glass?
Now, friends, earlier, you know I mentioned that.
.
This is Dr. Onan Canobite, a new piece of music from the great Dr. Onan Canobite of Dr. Onan's Wotan Band fame.
so
and in more proof of de-evolution dear friends
the Lundarelli family in Udine, Italy said in July
that it would not bow to pressure and would thus leave its Führer wine on the market
joining its Wavara, Lenin and Marx brands
Führer's label has a photo of Adolf Hitler and comes in two varieties
Sieg Heil and Ein Volk, Ein Reich, Ein Führer
one people, one empire, one ruler
and in June the Liquor Control Board of Ontario
cleared local shops
and shelves of a smuggled Chinese wine
that purportedly enhances libido
three-penised wine
deer, dolphin and dog
has such foul ingredients
that authorities wouldn't even dump it in sewers
that was sent in, as was this music
by internet, by Onan Canobite
who was celebrating Guy Fawkes Day in England
at the time, thank y'all
Lee An Normal
was hoping one of you would stop saying
drritis
how could you
unlawful
you know
enough in vain
of that time I reckon
Mark Lambert?
I got him some slack, okay?
Thanks, Bob.
You know, Chaz, I was talking to a young person just the other day.
A young person here in Dallas, Texas.
They didn't even know that we had had an interplanetary war at the turn of the century in the year 1900.
They thought that was a funny science fiction story that had been made into a radio show.
Just like declaring war on the planet a couple of weeks back.
Nobody believed it.
They don't take this kind of seriously.
And the reason they don't is they don't know any history.
You talk to a modern-day...
High school student or college student, and, well, sure, they know about the Gulf War.
You know, they remember the Gulf War, but they don't know about the war in Vietnam.
World War II, they don't know about...
They don't even know we landed on the moon.
No, they don't know that we walked on the moon, and they don't know that we had a war with the Martians at the turn of the century.
It just kills me.
It's like there's these giant Martian tripod museums in Baltimore.
And I think there's one.
It's in Akron.
They've got one of the damn Martian tripods in Akron.
And the people in Cleveland don't even know that we had a war with Mars.
It was...
Admittedly, it was 90 years ago.
90...
Exactly, 97 years ago, praise Bob, that we defeated...
And there's a crashed pyramidal spaceship in Mississippi, and nobody talks about that either.
Oh, they don't pay any damn attention to it at all.
Oops, and unfortunately...
Kaz and I weren't paying any attention at all to the tapes that we were making, and our tape ran out.
But friends, I wanted to...
Speaking of the war against Mars, I ran into some wonderful reading material, memoirs of the war of the worlds, in a book.
New book called...
You'll find in the history section of stores, a cheap paperback called War of the Worlds Global Dispatches.
The Martian Invasion of Earth, as witnessed by various famous people.
Mark Twain, Emily Dickinson, Albert Einstein, Teddy Roosevelt, Pablo Picasso, Joseph Conrad.
And I'm going to read to you from a short section from Jack London.
The author, Jack London, who wrote Call of the Wild, I guess is his most famous book,
was in...
Far north at the time.
After the Martians had died out over most of the United States,
there were still a lot of them surviving up in the north.
And he describes...
It's kind of gross.
There was a...
They had captured a Martian.
Not one of the machines, just the Martian itself.
And had put it into a pit for a dog fight.
And this is what Jack London witnessed.
Doctors for Bob in the background.
It feels like this would be as good as anything else.
What happened next...
Oh, the Martian turned its monstrously intelligent eyes on me and gazed, it seemed, into my soul.
For once there was no hunger in that gaze, no disconcerting look of malevolence.
What happened next, I cannot explain, for words alone are inadequate to describe the sensation I received.
There are those...
Who...
Assume...
That the Martians communicated through clicking sounds of their beaks,
or through the waving of tentacles.
But the many witnesses who observed the monsters in life
all agreed that no such sounds or motions were evident.
Um, indeed, one reporter in London went so far as to suggest
that they may have shared thoughts across space,
from one mind to another.
Such suggestions have met with ridicule in critical circles,
but I can only tell what happened to me.
I...
Was gazing into the pit, at the Martian,
and suddenly it seemed as if a vast intelligence was pouring into my mind.
For one brief moment, my thoughts seemed to expand and my intellect seemed to fill the universe,
and I beheld a world with a red, glowing desert sand,
so strikingly cold that the sensation assaulted me like a physical blow,
crumpling me, so that I fell down into the snow, curling into a ball.
And as I beheld this world, I looked through eyes,
that were not my own.
All the light was tremendously magnified and shifted toward the red spectrum,
so that I beheld the landscape as if on a strange summer evening,
when the sky shone more redly than normal.
I looked out across a horizon that was peculiarly concave,
as if I were staring at a world much smaller than ours.
A few red plants sprouted in this frigid waste,
but they were stunted things.
Martian cities,
walking things that traveled through great maze-like canyons
as they followed the sun from season to season,
were marching in the distance, tantalizing, gleaming.
I craved their warmth, the company of my Martian companions.
I hungered for warmth as a starving man might hunger for food in the last moments of life,
and above me, floating like a mote of dust in the sea of space,
was the shining planet Earth.
One
We are one,
the voice seemed to whisper in my head,
and I knew that the Martian, with its superior intellect,
had deigned to speak to me.
You understand me.
We are one.
Then, a rifle cracked,
the sound of it reverberating from the cabin in the low hills.
Klondike Pete cocked the gun and fired three more times,
and the stinging scent of gunpowder and burnt oil
from the barrel of his gun filled the air.
I got up and looked into the pit at the Martian.
It was wriggling in its own death throes,
twisting and heaving on the ground in its inhuman way.
The Martian
The gunlled,
to estimate its further shrug,
get a class right.
it all depends now
either years down the line
well it's years down the line
I don't know which way it goes
but
one day
after everybody's been
more or less judged
and everybody's ready for hell
or ready for heaven
after all that's been said
and after all that's been done
these angels
which are up there at that church
they will be given
they will be shown
how to become giants
okay
and once those angels
are shown how to become giants
what are they going to start doing then
they're going to start
stomping this earth
okay
they're going to start
stomping it just like a wine press
just like it says in the bible
hey everything I say
is from the bible
it ain't just me
they're going to stomp this plant
just like a wine press
and kill everybody
and crush everything
smash up everything
make it worse
just
just trash
it looks just like a war man
watch more war
war happening in Sarajevo
and places like that
look at the way war looks
and that's the way planet earth is going to look
people are going to be running for their lives
shoot
it's going to be a lot more critical than that
but
just help me man
I need help
I'm getting sick of doing this
I'm getting sick of talking like this
and now
for the news
Bob spoke to me using mental telepathy
Hector Brea told Colombian government investigators
he told me he was a male of his species
just as I am a male of the human species
but Bob didn't act like any male
that's for sure
he acted like a pansy from another planet
the father of three told authorities
the limp wristed pipe smoking visitor
showed up at his home on the night of the day
the night of July 2nd
awakening him and his wife with a knock at the door
he said he thought the subgenius was a human
until he let him in and the light revealed
the shocking truth
a blister on his thigh
Brea described the salesman as at least seven feet tall
with pale green skin
huge eyes
a large mouth
and a long protruding pipe
he had a human-like nose and ears
and wore a thick layer of makeup
his limbs were thin and rubbery
and he wore shiny pointy-toed boots
a blister on the moon
when he walked he sort of minced along and fluttered his hands
Brea said he was clutching a bunch of flowers from my wife's garden
all he did at first was smell the flowers
and spout poetry at us telepathically
he wore a kind of silver jumpsuit over silver and red striped tights
he seemed kind of harmless
but my wife was so terrified
she ran from the room and ran away from the house
and I was in the room
while I just stood there staring
Brea believes the strange visit lasted about 20 minutes
during which the cosmic queen
sashayed around his home trying on his wife's jewelry
using telepathy
the Dobbs told Brea about his long lonely days and nights
aboard a spaceship from a distant galaxy
he told the stunned Colombian
that he and his stoned fellow crewman
had come here merely to see what Earth was like
finally tiring of the small talk
the intergalactic gay salesman approached Brea
grabbed him and kissed him passionately on the neck
I was just about sick to my stomach Brea recalled
I pushed him away and he started to cry
then before I knew it he flounced out the door
and was gone
Brea said he has not heard from his swishy salesman visitor since that night
this Bob thing was a fairy and nutty as a fruitcake
the farmer said I hope he never comes back
friends this is the sad fate that befalls the homophobic
and those who are afraid of the weird the different
the insane and the swishy fairy sissy limp wristed Bob Dobbs
because that was Bob that visited that man testing him
and when he kissed him on his neck
he implanted the device right there
that's all that kiss was
was just a chance to push it one step further
push the envelope
and get a famous article in weekly world news
Bob will push all the way in
he will find an opening
and he will push
he wants your mind now
he will find a crease somewhere
he will moisten it up
he will slobber on it
and slick it up
then he will punch in
he will push and push until he punches in
and then when he is in
you are his
your DNA is about to be injected
with the new viral spiral code
of Bob Dobbs
the spermaceti
of the word sperm
the seed code of Bob
has entered your mind
just now just now
over the radio airwaves
it wasn't what we were saying
it was the hiss in between the words
it is too late now for you to pack out
the sickle will fall
the sacrifice will be made
and that stupid looking head
will rise above the crease
screaming where lies
yes the head
the stupid looking head
floats higher and higher over the gulf green
muttering and singing to itself
dripping blood from a thousand wounds
ever
ever bleeding
and ever flying higher over the gulf greens of earth
the green green greens of earth
and the gulf greens of the moon
where a man can hit a golf ball
or a decapitated golfer head for that matter
five miles
for a hole in one
friends
a hole in one
just like your soul rattling around inside that gas canister of Bob's after
he's gone
got your
whiff read your signature off that thirty dollar check
what I've always dreamed of
ah yeah friends
it's what I've always dreamed
it feels so good good good
when you just let go
and let it all just ooze out
like a forced evacuation
onto that check
just let that signature
ooze out
right out onto that
smooth
unbesmirched check
splashing onto the check
oh you're so good with a riot
that signature
and Bob whiffs that signature
he swishes it around
in his mouth
gets a good taste of it
and then
that is when he has
it's not your money that he cares about friends
it's that one thing
that he wants to whiff off of your soul
he wants to know the real you
the you that you cannot know
because you are inside and he is outside
punching his way in
ooh
ah
oh
ooh
I say Bob
oh
oh you're so rough
oh Bob
Bob is the first and most original rough trade you've ever experienced
and now for limited time only
if you subscribe to this newsletter
you can be introduced to the world of Bob's rough trade
Bob's post office box is a hole friends
I think you know what to do
I think you know just what to do don't you
our next day
that's right
our next day I'll be free
no more traveling around this bitter earth
our next day
I'll shake the manure from my shoes
I'll take that silver ship
our next day
and be with all the babes I never could be with here on earth
don't cry honey
I'm coming back sometime
sometime
someday
our next day
I'm gonna take the time to send my check
to see our next day
our next day
I've got to be a
saint I've got
our next day
the scum gonna rise from the top of the pudding
and reach for the stars
no more bitter tears
all this bitter bitter hell
our next day
yeah I'm going there
I'm never coming back
I'm already gone
our next day
next day
we're never going back
never going back
forever not in slang
church of the subgenius
P.O. Box
1-4-0
3-0-6
Dallas Texas
for our
yes, dear friends, and that's
slack
at subgenius.com
or
you can try the web
at www.subgenius.com
and you
can join us on
X-Day and
Einstein's Secret
Orchestra
for more information on Einstein's Secret
forever
www.wcsb.org
do it
friends
Einstein's Secret Orchestra
room 956 Rhodes Tower
Cleveland State University
44115 Cleveland, Ohio
or just
throw that
donation into a
mailbox and think
about
Einstein's Secret Orchestra
and it'll get to us
that's right
it always does
we'll kind of rub it on your lap first
rub it up real good
I got
I like the
rub it up real good
rub it up
over here
alright well you're all brought here tonight
basically to hear various
forms of preaching
and this song
goes out to the
what's that guy's name?
Tony Irba
i will unlearn
anal Roberts
forevermore
body
eff
the
be
rice
c
with
live
Yes, ma'am.
Yes ma'am.
Is it a nice afternoon?
You're a nice, attracting being.
Yeah, I am.
I am very much so.
Thank you.
Can I put my hands on you?
I have no sin. I have no sin in this part.
I have no sin in the back of a car.
Yes, I have sin.
謎
Can I put my hands on you?
To the lawвинice.
Don't you call the police.
I have sinned, I have no sin, and I've enjoyed it