It's a machine.
Isn't that right, Bob?
What that thing was, was up.
And that music.
It's the hour of slack.
Slack.
Number 1532.
And we're listening to a recording from last night of the devotional of a band known as Rural War Room.
And they're in the house tonight.
We'll be hearing from them.
But for now, we'll just hear them.
Rural War Room.
This is really wonderful.
I don't know what to say.
Rural War Room.
I start to hear the voices of the ocean as well.
Oh, that's so fabulous.
This is awesome.
Yeah!
One, two, one, two.
Praise Bob.
And that was Rural War Room last night
at the devotional of 2015
dedicated to the devos.
But tonight it's Hour of Slack.
Straight here, live from our studios
at KTFT, Fort Worth, Texas.
No, wait, this isn't Slam Bank Theater.
It is the hour.
It's Hour of Slack.
And we had a great time at the devotional.
Stayed up late, watched all the bands.
The headlining band was what you just heard.
That was recorded with my little hand recorder
and may not do justice to the real thing
now that I hear it on good headphones.
But we dragged back with us
one of the members of Rural War Room.
There's only three.
There's only three of them.
And the other two had much better sense.
I think they're at Cedar Point or something.
But Byron Werner, St. Byron Werner is here.
He's an old friend.
And he's also someone we've known for a long time.
He was involved with the subgenius meteor barrage projects
and artwork and all kinds of interesting stuff
since the year of 1980.
And...
You can imagine as you listen to us
someone who looks kind of like a cross
between Moses and Chappie,
that robot in the movie.
So...
That's a surprise to me.
I was going for kind of a Nicolas Cage look.
I wouldn't have thought that.
Hello, everybody.
I've been on board the subgenius wagon
since, well, 35 years.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's right.
It's scary when you think about it.
It's the 35th anniversary.
And it shows.
Oh, God.
I can feel it in every joint.
And also the parts of my body that move and bend.
Oh.
So...
Here.
So we're going to be playing...
It's an unusual show
because usually we don't allow anyone in the studio with us.
And we're going to be playing Rural War Room music.
Back on and off all the...
What was this in the background?
Johann George Albrechtsberger.
Hmm.
Okay.
Sure.
Background.
It's fine.
So what were some of the instruments you were using last night?
Will, one of them was a grunt horn,
which is a deer call with a flexible sort of sleeve on it
that I can reach in and press on the reed.
And on the end of it,
I put a toilet plunger bell, I guess you'd call it,
to be able to use another one to kind of give it a wah-wah.
And it goes everything from a...
sort of sound all the way up to a...
It's both hilarious and tortured sounding at the same time.
It's the best.
Very few instruments are like that.
Yes.
Have you ever heard a coyote call?
I've heard...
Yes.
Look.
It's kind of high yips.
No, no.
It's not supposed to sound like a coyote.
It's supposed to sound like a rabbit in a trap screaming.
It's the most horrendous screaming noise, if it's done right.
I think...
You could probably use that in your band along with your other...
I think that was a jackalope, wasn't it?
No, listen to that Jew's harp in the background.
That's a fine, fine Jew's harp right there.
Yeah.
You know why you don't find a whole lot of jackalopes around these days?
Well, they're extinct in most parts.
They're delicious.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
You know, in West Texas, they look down on...
You know, it's like if you eat jackalope, that's for low-class people.
Well, see, what you do is you get it.
You don't even have to take the fur off it.
Just take it, turn it upside down, stick those antlers in the ground, kind of angle it over the fire.
And that way, you know...
Well, you've got to scan it.
It's all set to...
You don't have to.
Yeah, you have to skin it.
He says you don't have to skin it.
It'll burn all the hair off, and then it leaves that nice, crispy coating that some folks like.
Well, like I say, where I come from, we consider jackalope to be...
Kentucky-fried jackalope.
You know, that's...
Kentucky-burnt jackalope.
It's tasty, but technically, it's illegal.
They're endangered.
Yeah, well, you guys don't eat catfish either.
Well, sometimes.
No.
I mean, we take the hair off of them.
For sure.
That's one thing I know.
I'm not going to eat no catfish with the hair still on it.
That's gross.
There was a guy...
It's crazy.
That's crazy talk.
That didn't make any sense.
Catfish.
There was a guy that said, you know how we cook catfish back in Texas?
I said, of course, no.
He said, well, you get a cow patty.
You put a catfish down on top of it.
You put another cow patty on top of that.
You cook that up for a while, and then you open it up and take the catfish out and throw away the catfish.
And eat the cow patties.
Da-bum-tsch.
Well, like, again...
That's just what I was told.
I'm not saying that.
Some families do that, and some people buy their cow patties at the supermarket already catfish-ized.
You know, it depends on whether you're a po-bucker or what.
It depends on how you take your cow pies.
Hey, I'm getting hungry.
Well, that's the thing.
I hate to talk about it.
I hate to talk about food.
It makes all the radio listeners all excited, and me too.
My stomach's grumbling.
My mouth is watering just thinking of that catfish hair.
So, Lonesome Cowboy Dave should be calling in any second.
Otherwise, I would put on another World War Room cut, which we still could.
Just keep Dave hanging.
Yeah.
We could.
You just handed me that we're going to put on.
It's a cover of a Devo song called I'm a Potato.
Oh, another Devo cover.
You guys do a lot more than just cover Devo.
Yes.
You only do that to get attention in Cleveland.
Well, I'm doing that because we just played this gig, and we're high on the Devo vibe.
Yeah.
That's easy to have.
That's why they do that stuff.
Is we not men's?
Okay, let's go ahead and whip it out, then.
Here it is.
I wish you pretty much knows that stuff.
No, it's not.
Actually, until the song is gone.
Of course it's a scene where I understand why I'm suspecting their kung fu a little bit.
I think it was to Всё とるると安全。
The Government Department, as well.
I'm a potato and I'm so bad
Have a break and wake up
And know my heart
Thickness and everything
Lights in the dark
Fires and all that
a hippopotamus on the cover with a halo
and a big fireball coming out of his mouth.
That's the flaming yawn.
But flaming yawn is actually a pun on filet mignon.
So the next time you're in a fancy restaurant,
ask for a flaming yawn.
And they'll bring you a steak.
Not what you asked for at all.
It would be a big old slab of hippopotamus.
And this is a song called Trouble From Within
which we did with the group Die Alten Maschinen
which is from the Czech Republic
that our friend Jerry Casale also did a song with Die Alten Maschinen.
So this has also got bleepo on it.
Good lord.
It's crammed with subgeniuses.
Yes it is.
See?
I'm planning, you know.
I'm trying to tie in all these loose ends
or these loose cannons.
Dave has had trouble with loose ends today, he told me earlier.
But that's probably more.
We need to know.
Oh, loose ends, yes.
Okay, I'm going to play this song.
Okay.
If this really is a song.
It's song-like.
Okay, here goes.
Standby and action.
Fast.
The times were bad.
Roll us.
Kicking.
Set things right.
They need kicking.
Our best friends helped us out.
Spend our lives.
Enjoy the luxury.
The life's ain't that easy, everybody's been a slave.
Chug, chug, chug.
Then it seems to be a lie.
We became independent.
On all the repercussions.
Chug, chug, chug.
Such an individual.
Seeing many other gays.
Trying to call attention to all the little sense of ways.
We are never limited.
By the very end, it's dead.
May the cozy hand be tapped.
Chug, chug, chug.
Then they flexed.
Their control brought us down.
From within.
We were caught in their web.
Chug, chug, chug.
They're all out there.
Out.
Must.
Some.
Away.
Out.
I took all those scientists.
Thinking of the common parts.
That'll cross another mind.
Chug, chug, chug.
I don't wish to interfere.
We're the world's century.
Then it hit us.
How are you?
Chug, chug, chug.
Magnetic at the head.
Found the intercession.
Flip around.
Coming off a star.
It's all right.
Fumbles on the ground.
Now we both have a chance.
We're all hands on the Russian women.
They look like they do.
Chug, chug, chug.
Chug, chug.
I don't think this mess produced carbon to the underground.
Made a waste out of town.
Chug, chug.
Fill us with the magic we need.
Start to go after the exam.
We're getting at the upper hand.
Chug, chug.
Who says that life is peaceful?
She took the gold she ate.
Make hell a waste.
I need a house.
I need a home to operate.
Who has read up in the end?
Every woman burning a hole.
Yeah, it's trying to overhaul.
Chug, chug.
Who has worked for us once more?
But they're just as certified.
Cause they've all been modified.
Chug, chug.
There is no more scrutiny.
Turn into the paranoid.
Bring us out the androids.
Chug, chug.
Re-introduce obedience.
Special programs any day.
Strip up the imbalances.
Triple-fuck the human race.
Announce the rule by Necrotas.
Nanny S is where my choice.
We're both on the go-back course.
Chug, chug.
Good Lord, Pat.
I wish everyone could have been looking at those lyrics as I was.
Boy, they go through fast, don't they?
They sure do.
I would say it was jarring.
Somewhat remarkable.
A bit twisty and twinkly.
Somewhat unique in the fact that there's nothing you can do about repeating one thing 300 times.
Uh, we just like to do something different.
I think no other song really sounds like that.
Are those lyrics available?
If someone were to purchase that
and they wanted to...
to have the lyrics,
would they come printed with it?
I made up a bunch of them.
I hope they all still have the lyric sheet inside,
because that was very important to me.
And, uh...
It was an experiment to write lyrics for...
for a song where it's going too fast to actually catch it,
but it's all about a robot uprising
and how humanity got the upper hand once again.
A fairy tale, in other words.
Yeah, we're...
We're gonna lose our asses in the robot war right away.
It...
Excuse me, Dave?
How's that?
I'm sure you're ready for the robot war now, is what I mean.
Um...
I'm ready to...
to sell out my race to...
to the robots at any time,
as long as I can get something good.
You know, like a good, uh, stereo set or something.
Speakers.
I just wanna taste a real steak again.
I'm on five minutes with that robot girl over there.
That's all it'll take, believe me.
Well, when they're really well-made, yeah.
Mmm.
Ah, yes.
Love delicious.
Well, uh, there were some strange, strange sounds last night.
I'm, uh...
I don't know how you guys got Ema Sumac in your band.
She looks a lot different.
She's so much younger than I would've expected.
Uh, she...
I always think she'd be older than me by now.
She... she transported in from the astral plane in a new body.
Nice.
She does that well.
Wow.
Now, that's...
You've got an agent that can do something like that.
You're in business in Hollywood.
Uh, they've been activists.
You've got somebody like that working for you.
He has the power of many theosophistic dogs and gods
that we all worship, uh, secretly.
Uh...
You know...
Actually, I had to leave Hollywood under a witness relocation program,
and I...
I'm not supposed to talk about it now,
Now I'm blowing the whole thing.
Never mind.
What you talked about this morning was all the ray gun scenes that you did on all those movies.
Why don't you thrill our listeners and tell us all the different ray gun scenes that you had to...
Probably the best ray gun scene is the big Ghostbuster guns that shoot out those beams with the little things swirling around them.
You're not supposed to cross the beams.
Yeah, I worked on that one.
I worked on the electric beams, the lightning bolts that come out of the gozer's hand.
At the Ghostbusters, I helped them blow away the big Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
I worked on Star Wars, the original one, number one.
You were the guy in the R2-D2 suit, right?
I saw a picture of you inside of it.
I worked on the scene where the giant laser beam shoots down the tunnel there.
You can see all the different layers of the beam.
Boy, that was a mess.
I helped to blow up Alderaan.
The Death Star.
And I worked on Tron and Buckaroo Banzai.
Something Wicked This Way Comes.
Honey, I Shrunk the Kids.
Titanic.
Dante's Peak.
I'm building up to the good ones, you know?
Star Trek Nemesis.
And you were having such a great time working in Hollywood that you decided to move to Little Rock and work for the city.
You were in the city library, right?
No, I decided if I was going to lose my eyesight, my health, and my sanity doing artwork, I was wanting to do that on my own artwork.
And in Little Rock, you can afford to be a starving artist.
Plus, people were feeding you.
When they saw your beard, they assumed you were homeless.
Yes, and I had a number of responses for them all set, but never put them into practice.
I wanted to say, well, ma'am.
I'm not hungry, but I could sure use some sex.
But people were...
Byron was sporting a bit of a Duck Dynasty look for a while there.
And people were pulling over as he was walking to work.
And I had a bag over my shoulder, you know?
People would pull over and go, do you need some food, old fella?
Do you want a sandwich? What?
Could you wash my windshield, please, sir?
Hard to imagine for me, but...
I would urine on their windshield.
And then start to wipe it down.
They'd get all upset. I don't know.
Well, I think that's what any noble, young, human American in the United States of America would do today.
Especially under the pressures of various reasons.
To, like, crackpot regimes all the way from...
All over the place.
Oh, I'm not a young person by any stretch of the imagination.
Well, I figured if you were R2-D2's underwear and stuff, you had to be at least 45.
Uh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I'd make some moves on me, but, you know, I didn't.
But, you know, one night, they got into those cantina masks.
Oh, boy, was that fun.
Posing for pictures.
3-D pictures on the set of Star Wars.
Oh, boy.
Hello.
Um, let me see.
Which one we're going to play here?
Making light of such a salutary career.
It was 30 years in the dark, you know?
Sitting in a little dark room, 10-hour, 12-hour days, just tracing off little shapes.
Boy, does that sound glamorous and fun, huh?
No stars, no flashy stuff.
When they need you, they really need you.
When they don't need you, they really don't need you.
But they want you to hang around so that when they need you, you're all set to go.
Well, but you say you didn't hang around a bunch of stars, but I know that, like,
for instance, your bachelor party, don't worry, I'm not going to.
But you had people like the Devos and the Simpsons.
The Simpsons themselves were there.
Well, not the Simpsons, but we did have one of the creators of P-Dog was there.
And I think it's safe to say at this late date that, yes, Kitten Natividad was the performer.
Oh, we can say that.
Yes, we can.
Go ahead.
I didn't want to get you in trouble.
I'm not married anymore.
We're not going to get in trouble.
Who paid for Kitten?
Was it Matt Granig or my brother's father?
A number of people.
I understand.
Robert Williams.
He put it in.
He put it in some money.
And I think George DiCaprio, Leonardo's dad.
This sounds like a bunch of hogwash, friends, but actually, Byron has been a really big
part of the underground comic book and underground publishing and everything underground that
doesn't get you famous.
Yeah.
Or they're extremely wealthy.
No.
Beyond your imagination.
No, I'm not wealthy at all.
I'm on Social Security now.
That's a blast.
No more Miller High Life.
Woo-hoo.
But you got slack.
You know, more rotoscoping for John Hollywood movies.
Yeah.
And see...
You get coffee, coffee, coffee, and lemon pie.
You just, you know, every day is a different, brand new, really stupid day.
And, you know what I mean?
Every day is a brand new beginning and all that.
And manana is so good.
Okay.
Oh, here's the cool part of Blockhead from last night.
And we're off a quarter.
Okay.
And I didn't agree at all.
Yeah, I know.
Blockhead.
Hey, guys.
My recording just doesn't do justice.
No.
You kind of had to have been there, unfortunately.
You really just didn't taste that delicious voice.
Oh, she's got an ethereal voice, doesn't she?
She does.
I can't believe we had someone who sings that well.
I see.
There's a little snoring in our living room this morning.
I heard no snoring.
That was probably Donovan snoring, I'm guessing.
No, I was just kidding.
Oh, humorous.
I like to think of beautiful ladies snoring horribly because I witness that almost every night.
I think of beautiful women farting.
Yeah, that's a good thing to know that.
That'll keep a man in step.
Knowing that women are not below excreting.
inflations.
They act like it.
Some of them hold it in a long time.
That's why they're acting that way.
Now, boys, boys, let's not get all
Trumpy here.
I'm going to play...
Especially if you're working in close quarters.
You've got to get in the other room
real quickly. What did you leave for?
Where did you go? I went out to the hallway
to make a loud sound.
It's not very...
I've been eating lots of vegetables.
Kill me, you know?
It's going to manifest itself
somehow.
It's another voice speaking.
Alright, what is this
next song that you handed me
that we can play?
This is another one by the Devos.
This is called Auto-Mowdown.
Mutant Mountain Boys did a cover of that last night.
Princess Wee is a new member of the
Mutant... She's a new boy in the Mutant
Mountain Boys.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
That was fun.
And action.
Music
Whoever
Let's listen for a longere
Week
,
guitar solo
Here we go.
Yeah.
I love that one.
I must say it sounds like
the soundtrack of my life.
Unfortunately or unfortunately.
I didn't like the references
to transgender chimpanzees.
I didn't think that was very...
Well, you gotta get
with that, Daddy-O, because that's part of the new age
that's coming. I'm still looking for one
to take on my work.
That was originally on
one of the not necessarily beautiful
but mutated sets, and
we've accumulated
a whole bunch of those and a couple
other cuts on a new CD
that we've got, Rural War Room
Devolved, featuring
Theramina and Pivo,
and you can find out information
about that and about our
radio show at
RuralWarRoom.com
Theramina is the
vocalist, the beautiful female
vocalist, right? Yes.
Does she have an Amy Kamish
like voice? I don't
know. It's kind of...
Can you assume that is?
It's impolite to ask a woman's history.
If she wants to volunteer,
volunteer that, that's one thing, but, you know,
I'm trying to be
polite, you know.
I'm kind of slow to the game.
How did that little funny-looking guy ever score her?
It's a long story.
I'm just kidding.
I could tell that guy said that
he's a sex machine. You can tell
by the spaz style of
his dancing and singing.
Spazier somebody is, the
sexier they are. That's what
we know in the Church of the Set Genius
and the Devo's.
Spaz equals sex.
Spaz is the new black.
That's right.
I mean color, not
race.
Spaz is a race, isn't it, though?
Isn't spaz a race?
Ever since
Bob took over.
There's no first prize
at the end because there is no end.
Of course, that sounds like a
prayer.
A prayer.
Unfortunately, that one was right.
Actually, it was a fun movie.
I'll never forget it.
Byron, I was meaning to ask you
for about 10 years now.
What's with the name
of the band? It's really hard to pronounce.
Rural
War Room.
Well, the idea was
that if we chose a name that was
difficult, and
it looks perfectly innocent when it's
written out. It's only when you go to say it
that it dissolves.
It's kind of like playing with the language
where stuff dissolves as you say it.
And we thought if we can get something
that's difficult, the people
that really are paying attention, they'll
learn how to say it. Once you know how to say it,
it's fun. Even if you say it
perfectly, people are going to go, the what?
And so
I told Donovan, you know,
if we're going to use this name, we've got to throw it off
like it's no problem
in the world. So we
would get together and drink a lot of beer and say
over and over again,
Rural War Room.
I said, let everyone else make the
Scooby-Doo jokes. We've got to
nail it.
And, uh,
well, our slogan on the
radio show is Worldwide Weird
because we play a lot of international
stuff and it's, we
like the weird. We don't think people are weird enough
and we're trying to give a frame of
reference, just expose people to
stuff they haven't heard before. Whether they
like it or not, that's up to them. But
if you don't like it, hang on. There'll be
else in five minutes.
What station? What's the name of that station in
Little Rock? K-A-B-F.
Right. I should know that.
And they never played
Hour of Slack, though, so who cares?
Uh, actually, we do play
some Hour of Slacks when
we exit the
the station and there's
nobody on until the morning we put on.
That's what they do here, too. So we've been
playing some Hour of Slacks, so back off,
fella. Oh, okay.
You've got an attitude.
Yes, I do.
But I just believe that that song,
the name, or the name
Rural War Room, is fraught
with layers. It's filled with
names like, uh,
Decker Poundcake, or
something. You're guaranteed
that people have thought of this
before in advance, you know, not just you storyboard
guys in the PR room.
It just goes all the way to the very
top. And if you consider what
a rural war room might be,
that might be taking all those, um,
co-workers and Sandy Hook guys
off their cheesecake butts and
out to, um,
I don't know, shoot more ducks or something.
I don't know what they've been doing.
Hey, Dave, the music in the background is
you on guitar, believe it or not.
You probably can't hear it.
It's some witch disco
that I recorded. It sounds like
I recorded it because it's kind of muddy.
I love the witch disco.
I swear to God.
I bet that's for the kids.
I recorded it at a winter star in one of those
cabins. Really?
That's what it kind of sounds like to me.
Party tape.
Yeah. But, uh, yeah, that's
the late Chaz and the early Dave.
Ah, Chaz.
I miss the guy.
Oh, that's why you knew Chaz.
Because you came to a couple of X Days
when he was still around.
And I also wrote him a letter
once, and just to warn him
about Mojo.
Oh, right. Yeah, because he ended up
working for Dr. Mojo.
I said, look, there's you, and there's Legume,
and there's Mojo. Well,
you know,
I'm a, quote, friend of his.
That was in those days. I said,
you know, he kind of models his life
after the Three Stooges. Well, he's Mojo,
so he's going to be Mo.
Oh, I never got that.
And then Legume, he's got the bald head, so he's going to be Curly.
So what does that leave for you, Larry?
The schlub.
You've got to remember that as mean as
Mo is to
Curly, that's his
brother. He's not going to hurt him. But you,
he doesn't care. He's going to slap your face
solid until it's like
the sole of a shoe.
So, you know, I went on
and on, and Chaz writes me back and goes,
oh, oh, God, I'm laughing so
hard I can't breathe. I just
really got him. He thought it was a joke.
I was seriously warning
him in gentle
terms that anyone could absorb,
you know, and refer to.
Well, you know, it's
ironic because
he, Mojo,
this friend of ours, he's a rocket scientist
actually, and yet still
a subgenius. He had
worked on that old 3D
program Bryce, which was pretty
popular in the previous century.
And he wanted to make a Bryce
killer. He wanted to create
the new
Minecraft, but instead he created
the new Mojo world.
And it just didn't take off.
The way Minecraft
did wasn't quite the same.
No, it wasn't in real
time. You had to render it,
and it was incredibly complicated
and hard to work. I said, Mojo,
why didn't you do
it? The reason Bryce is
such a popular 3D program
for little kids and old people is because
it's easy to operate.
It's like running a cash register
at McDonald's. It's PICTO's
for everything. He goes, I don't want
I want him to have to learn.
I knew at that moment, oh God,
he expects people to read
the instructions. Well, I know
about how many people in a room full of 10
read the instructions. Me!
And nobody else.
And I wasn't going to read the instructions
for Mojo world, so there, that's it.
Enough said.
The story has been told. Now, weren't there certain
people that just played with it and tried to break
it and did great artwork
with it, just playing
with it, instead of trying to
operate it properly? Oh yeah, if you tried to break it,
you could do some cool stuff. Yeah, I thought
there were some great artworks that were created just
by playing with it and trying to break
it. That's the
only way Philo works any
computer program. It's another subgenius.
That's how you start. Instead of
playing, reading the instructions,
you start off trying to
break it, and then engineer
your way backwards to learning how
it works. It's actually pretty
hard to break a computer program.
So you try.
I think it's a satisfying way of
both the issues involved.
It really does. Just kick the thing, throw it out
the window, attack.
I think maybe attack elderly people
with it, because they don't understand
them quite as well as younger people do.
And I think that would add
a moment of pride to the whole experience.
And you could tape it.
I think part of it is that old
people don't know how to type with
their thumbs.
Well, why
would they not know how to type with their thumb? Because
they're saying it's a more pre-Symeon
type of, you know, monkey thumb?
I say the fingers are better designed
for the typings than
the thumb is. The thumb is some sort of new
monkey science that's come up.
He's talking about how
you have to use the tiny
little phones now instead of the great
big computer keyboards, and that's why
there's no quotes on Bob's name
anymore. It's so modern, it doesn't
work. Sentences don't have periods.
...unless you triple-check.
So anyway, we're going to... All that
punctuation was just a waste of time
anyway. Yeah, grammar Nazis.
We're going to play one
of the greatest new groups out of
Japan.
Autopsy report of a drowned
shrimp. Go onto YouTube and look them up.
They'd be crazy. Okay, now blame
Byron for this, okay? This
isn't my fault. I have no idea what this sounds
like. I'm going to go ahead and whip it out.
Here it is.
.
Thank you.
Good lord, man.
Wow, you're so cute.
I like that shrimp talk.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're crazy.
So what's the deal with that band?
Who are they and how rare are they?
I think they may be made up of a bunch of guys that are in other groups
but are wearing masks because of whatever reason.
And let me see.
It's the brainchild of Yamamoto Kazuki.
They're known as Oro Rita Iba.
You know, they've been around for a while.
I may have the only CD.
I don't know.
Maybe they're probably less than five.
And they got a new one coming out.
I'm very excited about that.
Go on YouTube and watch them.
They are crazy.
Visually crazier than their music.
Wow.
Without seeing them, all I could think of was
Shinji Kukudis.
Yeah.
Kukudis.
I can see how you would do that.
Yeah.
But they're all males, huh?
It's too bad.
It's hard to tell they have masks on and colorful loose clothing.
So, you know, you just can't tell anymore.
Even if it's dressed like a woman, you don't actually know anymore.
Could be.
What do you think of 50 Year in Progress and the Norwegian time belts
and all the different numbers?
They've been trying to pull on people for years,
trying to make them dress up like ladies.
Scandinavia.
That's where it all comes out of, you know?
Damn them.
And the big bustle dresses.
The firmaments and stuff like that.
How come women wanted to have bustles to make themselves look larger in the derriere or smaller?
It's kind of an ape thing, you know?
It's getting down to a body attraction.
And it's getting down near the end of this hour of slack.
The bustle was for a bigger butt bump, Dave.
Well, apes do.
I mean, they try to anyway.
They have a valid code of honor.
They believe the system is fortified by...
Why do you think people go...
When they have sex.
It's that monkey drive, you know?
Speak for yourself, dude.
It's way back.
Okay, listen.
This was once the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
We're recuperating from the Devo convention or the devotional from last night,
which was really great.
And we'll probably have more from that later.
Thank you so much for having me over.
Thank you.
Yeah.
We actually had Byron over to our house.
Reverend Susie the Flusie was in the slacker mansion for the first time.
She sure was.
Oh, and this is my copy of the new World War Room featuring Faramina.
And Peebo.
There's even a Peebo cat on there.
I don't care about Peebo.
You will.
But Faramina is my new chardonnay.
She's a sweetheart.
Okay.
So is World War Room.
We're going to lead out with another song.
It may not be that well recorded, but by golly, I recorded it.
So I'm going to play it anyway.
And it's a rural war room last night at the Beachland Ballroom doing popcorn.
An old earworm that you may recognize.
That's the one.
Yeah.
I didn't recognize it when you guys were playing it.
You explained it later.
So I'm going to play it now.
I watched you sitting there.
You're listening to it with your jaw hanging open.
We have to stop now.
That was because I was asleep.
So long, Dave.
No.
Nice to chat with you.
So long, Barron.
It's been nice chatting with you.
Very good.
Hi, Dave.
And so we've been hanging back up.
What?
We did it just a little longer.
We had our casos for the last week...
You guys...
So very Beendo now.
So this is the Pogo.
Shows the way he бегueron.
Now he's saying hi in Belgian and I'll say bye.
You'll know what it tastes like.
Ya me diri que no es tan rico y lo oigo.
Oh
I am drowning in a cloud of wings
You know it. Popcorn!
Popcorn!
It's a song we put our song
If the song they could not stop
If the song we could not stop, we should not stop, they would not stop.
The song we could not stop, it's the song we could not stop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
When I dream of you, why, why, why, why?
I'm gonna die in a moment