Oh, what's that?
Sounds like an air raid alert.
That's peculiar, they didn't announce it.
Turn on the radio, hurry.
...as well as a press conference to introduce what is supposedly a creature from another planet.
Professor Tomlin is about to speak, and we'll try to catch his word.
And I'm quiet.
Gentlemen, I wish to present to you...
The Self-Genius Power of Splash!
...is a machine.
Probably the most dangerous machine ever invented.
He is telepathic as well.
He can read your thoughts like a book.
He knows exactly what each of you is thinking at this very instant.
Yes?
Do you expect us to swallow this nonsense?
Not without proof, gentlemen.
It's life online!
Join us live!
Call 808-808-4 or log into chat.
And now...
Lead, follow, or get out of his way.
Helping entrepreneurs find the secret to success on the web.
With advice from Startup to Empire.
He's making money, making waves, and he's doing it all with that...
GoDaddy-esque fun.
It's Bob...
What was all that Bob stuff about then?
Bob stuff.
Bob stuffs.
Bob.
Bob!
Bob Bob.
Bob.
Bob!
I say, Bob, I think this calls for a celebration!
How about a game of cup and ball?
And a slap of tea at Mrs. Megan's pie shop?
Bob.
Bob!
Bob! Bob!
We're a couple of fine lads together, aren't we?
Let's get russet and talk about girls, eh?
Hey Taxi Bob, are you
picking up some... some...
some ladies?
Carrying them to their places?
I could, I could go over and
see, but I haven't been doing
that lately. What kind of line
would you give me if you were gonna
pick me up?
Hey baby, do you wanna ride home?
Wow, that's pretty clever. Where's home?
Do you wanna ride home? That works?
Does that work for you?
I don't know.
I get her either my home or her home.
Hey baby, do you wanna
ride home? I'm gonna try,
I'm right, wait a minute, where's my pen? I'm gonna write
that down. You gotta say it just like that.
That's it.
Oh.
Hmm.
What makes me feel funny in my mouth?
It's the sex goddesses.
Oh yeah, when you get the sex goddesses
on the cab, you really gotta watch out.
You gotta watch out.
We have our own sex goddess here.
Our ex goddess.
Ex goddess.
Ex. Ex. Ex.
Ex. Oh my god.
I didn't think of that before.
Do you dare to know the
secret of ex, ex, ex,
ex goddess?
Do you dare to pass through the doorway
and do
ex, ex,
ex, just like we were talking about
Reverend Stang?
What shameful things happened to the women
in Dr. Tar's
tortured
This
is filled with terror, suspense,
and horror.
Dr. Tar's
tortured
will etch itself into your mind
with shock after naked shock.
Dr. Tar's
tortured
If there was torture, that's a crime.
If there was crime, there were criminals.
Who ordered the torture?
That's the problem.
It's political, and the right is going
Go do this for me.
And he'll just do it.
We are America.
I don't give a rat's ass if it helps.
We do not fucking torture.
So the lawyers who would basically tell them
Go do this for me.
And he'll just do it.
It will be done.
Well that's a matter of opinion, Judge.
I mean a lot of that's opinion, right?
We've got Bob saying one thing, we've got a lot of people saying another.
You put them in a confined space with a caterpillar,
you push them up against a flexible wall.
We've had the former CIA director came out
with some kind of cushioning on their neck to prevent whiplash.
The CIA manipulates the Justice Department
into letting it do whatever it wants.
And I read these memorandums.
This is torture.
I mean that's where we are, isn't it?
It's that simple, isn't it?
But here's the point. The point is this.
We are America. We do not fucking torture.
The CIA manipulates the Justice Department
into letting it fucking torture.
Bob was trying to sell books and does a very good job of that.
I agree.
Hot poker through the eye, pulling your ass off the pliers.
So you read it, how was the experience?
I'm only about two thirds of the way through them
and I'm having trouble getting all the way through them
because Shep, I've got to tell you,
as Judge McCall Tanner says,
You need to read them. You need to read them.
Absolutely. You know it when you see it.
What this is about is a series of dots
which people are now mentally connecting
in a backward fashion.
I'm afraid that there's a lot of truth
to what you're saying.
It makes no sense whatsoever.
What we need right now is more information
about who, how, when, what permission.
We don't torture people. We don't torture people.
And the moment that's not the case,
I want off the train.
We're joining America.
And it's full of
lying, thinking cocksuckers that you can't trust at all.
Governors,
commissioners and what not.
And by God, that's just a new way of things
and you're just gonna have to get used to it, John.
Alright.
You're gonna have to accept it and learn to control yourself.
You get no argument from me!
What is your opinion of Bob?
I refuse to go along with this
I want to know all your lies, lies,
lies, lies, Bob you wicked
wicked devil!
Shit!
AAAAAAAAAAH!
Lies, lies, lies, lies!
FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU
Shit!
I love Bob, that's my favorite of all the pretenders.
What do you have to say about Bob, the man, the legend, the saint of souls?
That's dick.
Shit!
Bob, sort of hurt me and I had to see a doctor.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
That's dick.
Shit!
Reptile Newt porn.
That's dick.
Yes.
I can't have an opinion on something I've never met.
Never met.
We can sing some really dirty songs.
Oh, God.
Get lost, creep!
Hello there, Bob!
Bob.
Well, Bob.
Welcome on board.
I like you, young Bob.
You've got balls.
Is he making fun of me?
That and more of it to come was by Dr.
Slackjaw, also known as Reverend Royal Decapitator, who also did many of the collages in this episode,
although not the ones just now, which were by Reverend Exister and Sweetness McGee of the
Ministry of Slack Show podcast.
Also, we heard the Puzzling Evidence show from KPFA Berkeley with hosts Puzzling, Philodrum
and Dr. Howland, special guests Chaos, McBob, Kat, Princess Wee, and me, Reverend Ivan Stagg,
and Phineas Snarko.
Those shows are available in full, by the way, for the KPA.
And from QuiveringBrain.com.
The music in the background is by the Flyin' Ryan Brothers album, under the influence found
at Ryanetics.com.
R-Y-A-N-etics.com.
Friends, X Day is a-comin', so we're talking about that a lot now.
But before we return to that subject, we're going to take a short side trip to Austin,
Texas during the winter's subgenius family vacation.
Princess Wee is laughing because I have already said this once, but with the recorder not
on.
So we're digesting a fine, fine Waffle House meal.
Mmm, that food was restorative.
It was Princess Wee's first Waffle House experience.
I will live now.
We're heading for Austin, down the very, very boring highway of the city.
The I-35.
There could not be a more boring highway than the one from Dallas to Austin.
Except possibly the one from Dallas to Little Rock.
Anyway, we're going to visit the great G. Gordon Gordon, former bodyguard of Dobbs,
the late Bob Dobbs.
Or rather, the late several times and then resurrected.
I guess you could say he wasn't much of a bodyguard.
Um.
And, uh.
And Sphinx Drummond also lives in Austin.
We'll be visiting him and slacking off before we head out into the wilds of far west Texas
and rural New Mexico and all the state parks and stuff.
This will be our last visit with friends and family until we get to Los Angeles.
Where the liquor stores are big, grand, and majestic.
There are Lone Stars everywhere.
And lots and lots of elephants.
You see elephants on cars.
Are you talking about L.A.?
No, I'm talking about here.
Texas.
I've seen.
The elephants are almost crushing the cars.
Yes.
And yet it's a fad in Texas.
They love to stick an elephant on the back of their pickup truck even though it almost destroys the suspension.
They're usually baby elephants.
Yeah.
And, uh.
And it's true.
All the liquor stores that I remember from when I lived here 15 years ago are still there.
Although nothing else that I remember was.
Well, they're huge.
They have these enormous signs and sometimes big figures.
Yeah.
They're giant liquor store cowboys.
Neon cowboys.
Well, the liquor stores in Texas are the size of many towns in other states.
Yes.
That's what I was getting at.
But so are the cow droppings.
So, anyway, we'll report back in case anything interesting happens.
So it may be a long time before we report back.
Be our time.
Be instantaneous your time.
Praise time control.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, it sounds like the party just entered the room.
G Gordon Gordon is here.
G Gordon Gordon.
Big drum, uh, drumming.
All right.
Yeah.
Give them all my best.
All the best.
Just singing another to Rocknar.
Is this, is this the Austin Clench?
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah.
They're beautiful.
You know, speaking, well, changing the subject to Rocknar Winacorton, uh, I made a new Facebook
friend on Friday on my birthday.
Yeah, this is the life.
This, this, well, is this something that'll compare to your 24-hour marriage from the last
X Day I saw you at?
Uh, maybe.
Uh.
Rocknar's got a girlfriend.
Yeah.
I hope it's a girl.
It is a girl.
It looks like it.
No, she's the, she's the CEO of Rocknar.
You know, on the internet, on the internet nobody knows you're a dog.
That's an old New Yorker cartoon.
Now, uh, um, this girl, I don't know if I can say the name of her kind.
She's a CEO of a company, and I don't know if I can, I'm not gonna say her name, obviously,
but she's a CEO of an offline to online dating company.
Oh my God.
You, I've got men, you have scored.
She's probably a millionaire.
Dude, you're, you're dating a CEO of a dating company?
That's like, that's like having Bill Gates come over and fix your computer for you.
She has her pick of men, and she picked Rocknar.
Well, I did get my hair cut, and I was wearing my blue suit and tie.
I'm sorry.
I bet you even took a shower, didn't you?
Oh yeah, I took two.
Whenever I go to court and I take a shower.
Rocknar went to court and he did right.
Crab bones.
They lost him.
I got to see Skull Rock at Joshua Tree National Monument.
My son said, Dad, I've always wanted to kind of go there, but I don't want to just see
a bunch of trees.
I know what a Joshua tree looks like, and I had to explain, well, it's called that,
but really the attraction is the twisted land formations and long stretches of desert.
The Joshua trees themselves, raising their arms to heaven as they are, most of them.
Well, the Ernesto trees are much more beautiful.
Ernesto's?
Ernesto's, yeah.
One nestles gently in them.
Well, we got hugged by a lot of those teddy bear jumping chollas.
Hugs, not drugs.
Really?
You got cholla?
Yes.
That's terrible.
Those things are nightmares.
Actually, we only, Princess Wee and I only had to pick spines out once in the whole trip.
You know how to do it.
You get two sticks and you just rip it off because if you touch it, you'll get them in
your fingers.
Yeah.
And then when you touch yourself, you get it right.
It's sad.
I'm from Texas.
I know how to handle a damn cactus.
Where are those jumping?
We eat cactus.
We eat cactus in Texas for breakfast.
We call it nopales.
That's right.
We had, Princess Wee had her first cactus.
No nopales.
When we went to visit G. Gordon Gordon.
You poly?
And Sphinx Drummond and Mrs. Gordon.
Oh, did you have migas?
Migas.
We had migas in Austin with the Drummond brother.
And we've got a caller from an Austin number now.
You're on air.
Hey, I've just been listening to your show and I just want to tell you, I think it's
pretty good.
I like what you all are saying.
And the way you say it.
Why, thank you.
That's the nicest thing anyone's said to me all year.
You say words all year.
I'm sure somebody, unless you're just really a bad guy, I'm sure somebody will say something
nicer before the end of the year.
And then this won't be the nicest thing anybody's said to you all year.
You know what though?
I got to tell you like why maybe I am a bad guy because I think that is the second time
I've told someone that's the nicest thing someone said to me all year.
And I think I'd probably say it again if I heard the first thing again.
Oh, man.
But the first thing I thought was on that level.
It was on that level.
Hmm.
It's just a friendly level.
That changes everything, man.
Well, the thing is though, like you're just a person that I don't know personally who
was calling up this radio show and telling me you like it.
Hey, that's a very nice thing to say to me.
And I like that.
I appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
And I hope to continue living up to the standard or living down the standard, whichever it
is.
He's a colonel.
We live up to our standards.
The guy that called in, he's a colonel.
I know.
Like a colonel of corn?
He used to be in the Swingin' Love Corpses.
He was the main vocalist and horn player at the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Hello there.
Is this true?
And that's how far he's fallen.
I think he's still here with us.
Is that true?
I don't know what the hell's going on.
I just want to say I'm enjoying the show a lot, but I don't think I have a lot to
contribute.
So I'm going to hang up now and-
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't do that.
I'm good.
Why not?
I am.
I really am the main vocalist in the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Whatever.
Well, I heard a click.
I think they just lost the thing.
No, no.
No, he's still with us.
Still on his-
I don't think so.
I just need to listen to this other guy for a while because-
I just need to listen to this other guy for a while because that's why I called
Ben.
I don't want him to hang up.
Bob.
We're all going to go to hell because of you, Senator.
Oh, you were going to hell long before you met me.
Yeah, but I just now done found a girlfriend.
Thanks a lot.
It is safe to surmise that we are all going to hell.
Yeah, this is hell.
What do you mean going to hell?
Earth is hell without me.
If you're going to sin, you might as well be original about it.
We're the original sinners here on WCSB Cleveland.
Oh, that was the original seniors.
Get that in the bob.
What's the deal?
So what else are we talking about here?
What's the thing about the bob?
How much we covered my birthday?
It's all about you, isn't it, Rockhead?
Huh?
What?
Pete Bob?
I heard someone in the background in Austin.
Yeah, there's kind of a fair enough to call it a party
that's going on here in Austin.
At the Dostown 4.
Well, I recorded that streaming by laying this microphone on the keyboard.
It was tuned in on my laptop and surprisingly loud.
I just laid this right on the keyboard.
How's it sound?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Not as good as a direct recording.
Let's listen.
The whole thing is so incredibly stupid.
We're all going to be embarrassed.
It's so Escher-esque.
Maybe you won't.
I don't embarrass easy.
I can copy it.
Or it's stuck.
He's getting, still gets AOL.
Solicitations in the mail.
When you pull the pieces apart.
I do not get AOL.
That's what I keep old files and porno in.
I use them for rolling tries.
I use them for the containers.
Marvin says he's going to stay out of second-rate nursing home.
Because every time they send him one of those, remember the giant, for like 10 years, he
just saved them all unopened.
He has a stack this high of AOL.
How's that going to help?
Well, I don't know.
He's going to sell it on eBay.
You know, I don't know.
Ancient AOL mailings.
A complete set.
People will pay good money for that worthless thing.
I got every AOL promotional from time immemorial.
I got one every time.
Oh, they came forever.
And I like these because these you keep, you know, you throw the AOL shit away and you've
got old, I mean, it's a nice little hard box.
I have a box of metal.
A bunch of metal boxes.
But these I like.
They're paper and you can put like two or three CDs in it, depending.
CDs?
No, you put your frappy in there.
No, you put your, you know, you put your, you know, you put your, you know, you put your
frappy in the little...
I forgot about that.
You have a strange idea of porno, Dr. Gordon.
What, that?
Yeah, those objects.
That's not porno.
Here.
Some people paint beautiful women.
I'll show you.
And then pop their legs off.
Some photograph beautiful women.
Here.
Most of them don't pop, cut their legs off.
Where are we?
I don't even know.
This guy makes these spiky...
That's good that most of them are dope.
Sex monologues.
You mean like 51%?
That's all so fat.
Oh, wait, let me go see my...
When you say most, you mean like 51% or like 90%?
51.
So more often than not.
Yeah.
I'm not looking.
Am I hitting the right button?
No, boss, it's always the same.
Here we go.
More often than not, then I always call him out.
You mean like 51%?
Stop pissing me off.
Hey, that's an obvious cactus vagina.
Yes.
It's called...
The Sin of Marriage.
We'd put a big price tag on it with a title like that, it'll probably sell for thousands.
Yes.
Slow down.
So you've got a February 6th court date in the courthouse and it's 420 Blount...
What?
How do you pronounce that?
Blount Avenue.
Blount Avenue, chewy for the
site refético.
Basically, it's Blount.
Blount Avenue.
Jimmy.
recreational.
May 21st, 2011.
The world will be coming to an end.
The world will be cracking apart.
And we're going to have massive earthquakes.
Judgment Day.
Don't forget.
There's billboards all up over the Bay Area.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, get those guys down from that building.
What was that date?
In Berkeley.
They're on top of your building.
What was that date?
Hey, you guys.
Hey, I'm standing right across the street from your station there.
It might be one of those armies of women.
Oh, really?
That's just maintenance.
It's moving around.
I'm going to take out my rocket launcher.
Okay, good idea.
That's some maintenance people.
Put that rocket away.
Those are plumbers.
We just hired them to fix the...
Those are the roofers.
Sink stopped up?
Call Pete the plumber.
Don't worry about it.
Really?
He won't be on issue at May 21st.
You've heard of Joe the plumber.
Pete Goldie is a plumber.
Is he a plumber, too?
Yes, in fact.
I want to write this down and put it in my...
They call him the tile doctor.
There he goes.
He fired his...
Wait, did I miss?
No, no.
I'm going to mark this down for May 21st in my...
End of the world.
Now, what time of day is that?
I want to make sure nothing intrudes on them.
Yeah, what time of day is the end of the world?
Is that going to be like before noon?
Am I going to have to worry about eating lunch that day?
This is doctor's orders.
Oh, I don't hold with this newfangled doctoring.
Plenty of problems.
I'll go to the wise woman.
Very well, then.
Three other...
Paths are open to you.
Three cunning plans to cure thy ailment.
Oh, good.
The first is simple.
Kill Bob.
Never.
Then try the second.
Kill yourself.
And the third?
The third is to ensure that no one else ever knows.
Ah, that sounds more like it.
How?
Kill everybody in the whole world.
What?
Listen, Bob.
I said, Bob.
Besides, I thought we were friends.
Well, we are friends, Bob.
Of course.
Good night.
Bob.
That's right.
Are they singing about Bob in the background?
The laying on of hands.
Yes.
Yes, as we do at the lake.
Eh, Reverend?
Well, we really weren't talking about the way you lay your hand.
I beg your pardon.
I'm talking about our holy ceremony at Exeter.
As we waste our way into the future, it's better to give others slack.
As soon as we...
The bobbies come hopefully trooping into the water.
Moving forward to some obscure utopia.
At some distant time when we all shall hold hands together as one.
Even though the...
These simple children of nature have a great fear of old Sequaw.
Thinking as one.
Lost head of clunker at the bottom of the endless shaft.
We didn't have old Sequaw at the old Exeter place.
No, no, no.
Old Sequaw's a new feature of Exeter.
Unless he commuted from the frog pond.
Boy, it was a great Bob-tism too.
I kept my glasses on for that and turned on my mental recorder.
I'll have...
All memories to take me out to the end of my days.
The endless Bob-tism.
Or boob-tism in one case.
Reverend Back It On Up got boob-tized by having the breastages of Sister Decadence.
Which are sizable.
Commendable.
To save a week.
Those were dropped upon Back It On Up's little head.
And pushed her underwater.
And that was her boob-tism.
So great.
Quaint and merry.
And gay.
So gay and happy.
I've never seen a sad boob-tism.
No.
I can't even imagine that.
Boobs.
Bob's one O short of boob.
Yeah.
And everybody loves boob.
I'd like to crawl over an ocean of them on my belly.
Yeah, yeah.
A thank you Radio Synesthesia and WCSB Cleveland.
Before that we heard a billion clips from Royal Decapitator and the Puzzling Evidence Show as well.
And now we go from talking about X Day to an actual recording from 14X Day Drill 2011 during a so-called live hour of slack.
The Grindhouse today, friends, if anyone gets completely bored with everything else that's happening.
And if you don't like sex with a beautiful live girl.
The Grindhouse, it's a...
Oh, the Turkish Superman rip-off.
It's a rough double feature.
Has anyone here seen the Superman, the Turkish Superman movie?
It's really amazing.
An old serial, part of a serial called The Phantom Creeps, number five, part five, that has a robot in it.
An ugly one.
Radar Men from the Moon, part five.
That's an early Commando Cody chapter play.
Devler Gilojur, or Iron Fist.
Which I assume is a foreign film.
Phantom Creep 6, Horrors of Spider Island.
Ah yes, the Horrors of Spider Island.
This is a German film and the horrors are not the exceptionally large spiders who bite the people who go to the island, but what the people turn into afterwards.
I've never seen that.
Yes, the Horrors of Spider Island.
And finally, the incredibly strange creatures who stopped living and became mixed.
The zombies.
Oh well, if you want to wallow in bad film with that one.
It's a monster musical, folks.
And friends, the greatest thing about the Grindhouse showings and Dr. Dark's drive-in, Mystery Science Theater 3000 will not be there.
You'll have to be your own snarky silhouette to make your own comment.
You get to be the snarky bastard.
We need no mediator here.
We're at the church of the subgenius.
Uh...
Yeah, bring your own puppets.
Well there's our co-star, Father Joe Mama.
It's Papa Joe Mama.
He doesn't look very priestly today.
He's rushing, I see, from one of those sweat lodges.
He's rushing in haste.
Hail Papa Joe Mama.
Oh you, he gets to take his shirt off.
Well, uh...
Somebody's gotta bring your 80s.
Scoot in as close as you can, because we've hung Bob in such a way that he's not going to be able to see us.
He blocks whoever is the third or fourth, uh, big bullshitter.
Well that's the problem with this church. Bob is always blocking all the stars with his swinging corpse.
Of love.
These notes I'm looking at are my big rant sermon for Starwood.
Right, right.
I never get to do a rant here because it's all preaching to the saved.
I have a big binder of notes for ranting too, but unfortunately it's filled with...
notes of things not to rant about.
Well, look at those pages and think of the opposite of each quiddity and you can come out with something.
Oh, thanks. Changing the subject. Have you seen Cowboys and Aliens yet?
Uh, I saw enough of the trailer that I feel like I saw the movie, yes.
No, no, no, no. Watch the movie.
I mean that. Watch the movie. It is really a good movie.
Of course we can't make any calls to action.
Yeah, right. Get those toothpicks.
Rock on!
Okay, Robbie.
First we'll call the action.
The action is thang, though.
Have you ever read a book called The Bobliographons? The Encyclopedia of Slack?
That was the original Cowboys vs. Aliens, wasn't it?
It was Cowboys and Indians vs. the Aliens was produced by J.R. Bob Dobbs in the 1950s.
And believe you me, when we heard that Hollywood was making a movie by almost the exact same title,
Reverend Chris Lee and I both got a bit concerned and had our fingers ready to call a lawyer
when I then read that they had based that movie on a comic book neither one of us had ever heard of.
So I guess, you know, when it's Cowboys and Indians vs. Aliens time...
Which is what this movie is. It is Cowboys and Indians vs. Aliens.
Cowboys and Indians vs. the Aliens.
When it's steam engine time, you get steam engines.
What I like...
When it's the power of slack, I get steam engines.
I get to put my disease in you.
And my disease, I'm happy to announce, is now in everyone hearing my voice.
And mine is Cowboys vs. the Paleontologists.
I vote strictly on that ticket.
There was a series of books by Harry Turtledove about Nazis and Communists vs. Aliens.
Really?
I never heard of those.
I know he's an expert in...
Harry Turtledove is known for alternate histories.
Yeah, this is one where these lizard aliens visited the Earth sometime in the 1200s.
And they come from a planet where everything happens very slowly.
And all their galactic travels they had never encountered a civilization that evolved at a pace any faster than glacial.
So they come back expecting to be, you know, fighting knights in shining armor.
And then they discover that, you know, when they first get back to the planet in the opening, there's like,
Well, this is very strange. We're picking up wireless signals from TOSAV-3.
And like, what? How could they possibly have wireless?
Right.
Wait a minute, that eluded me totally.
They breathe like bugs down there, those humans.
No, they went away for 800 years. They figured they could come back 800 years later and we'd still be riding horses and fighting with swords.
Oh, right.
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
Well, if they do come back 800 years from now, it'll probably be true again.
Yeah.
Wasn't it Einstein who said...
You know, sorry to say.
Wasn't it Einstein who said,
I do not know what weapon I'm using.
...日本's World War Three will be fought with but World War Four will be fought with sticks and stones?
Ah.
Well, if you think according to the prophecies of Nostradamus,
We're already in the middle of World War Three.
You can have my voice.
We are.
He says that World War Three archG question about 27 years.
Shutup.
Shutup about Nostradamus.
A form of yammering indeed.
I don't know.
NostroDAmus
NostroDPus opened up the third nostral.
We were martyred, too.
great-great-great-great-grandfather.
Nostril, damn us.
He was a lot like my great-great-uncle, Justice.
I mean, damn us.
That's right, that was your family that started the whole Mormon thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, my.
Yeah, we're good at it.
The Mormon Menace.
Mormons have become very prominent in public life.
And the Mormon Church seems to be well aware of this.
They've got a new ad campaign out.
There's no doubt about it,
and I think the Church is really trying to capitalize on this moment,
and they're using this campaign to position themselves
in the mainstream of American society,
in which they're saying, you know, we're just like you.
We're bikers.
We're surfers and rock stars and moms and everything,
and we're Mormon.
And so we're just like you.
We're your neighbors.
We're your coworkers.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
We might have some distinctive beliefs, but so does everybody.
And ultimately, we're just like you.
My name is Jeff Tecker.
I'm a father and husband of four,
and sculpt motorcycles for Harley-Davidson primarily.
And my passion in life is historic racing motorcycles.
I never give myself enough credit for having enough in life,
but I think that's false.
I strive for false balance because my family,
because I'm so polarized that I find refuge in the Church.
Lots of people just sort of talking about how normal they are,
how they're just like everybody else.
I think the two messages that the Church really wants to get across right now
is one, we're Christian, and two, we're normal.
Normal.
Norman.
God and Jesus.
Holy Ghost.
Flesh and bone.
Deep respect.
Deep bone.
God and Jesus and the Holy Bone.
And love for their prophets.
Bigotry and persecution.
Group mentality.
Cult.
Persecution complex.
Or a siege mentality.
Cult.
I got an alternate history story for staying.
Elvis versus Hitler.
In like an actual boxing match and stuff like that?
In the Moon Garden?
Sort of.
All right.
It supposes that Elvis was born 20 years earlier than he should have been.
He becomes the same.
He's a kind of musician.
Actually, he becomes more of a crooner, like Bing Crosby type,
but he's still a world-famous musician.
He rocks the house.
He's recruited by Frank Sinatra and the OSS
to take out Hitler on Hitler's birthday in a special concert in Berlin.
And the ending of which would be,
Elvis's grave isn't at Graceland,
but it's in Arlington National Cemetery because he died a hero.
He took out Hitler.
Wow.
Well, that would be an interesting story, wouldn't it?
Elvis versus Hitler.
It's only a joke.
I was under the impression that Hitler took himself out.
You know, you could make a short film about that.
Like, you could actually make that into a short movie, probably, for not too much money.
I've already written it, dude.
I wrote a detailed treatment called Harold and Maude and Kumar Visit Hitler.
And I'm not going to tell you anymore because it's actually a pretty good idea for a movie,
so I'm going to leave it at that.
Yeah, but you've got to include each of them.
One of these days, Harold and Maude and Kumar go to Hitler.
Okay, I'll look at it.
The main idea is they're going to buy his artwork real cheap
and then bring it back to the future and sell it, you know,
because it'd be a lot.
But you've got to throw NPH into it.
What?
Really?
Right, right.
NPH.
Neil Patrick Harris.
Oh, okay.
Well, of course, it's Harold and Maude and Kumar.
Didn't he come out of the closet, Neil Patrick Harris?
I'm sorry, I don't watch...
I'm not quite as learned as you are in the world of...
Or wide-nostril.
...verily important sitcoms and television shows,
so I often sound ignorant that way.
Is it more important to be ignorant or wide-eyed or just wide-nostril
as we bring it to the future?
I agree.
The perfumes and all those different concepts...
What's important is to know that you're ignorant.
As a genius pretender, so to speak,
I'd like to know why, how, I mean, actually how,
that it comes about.
Television destroyed our greatest minds
and it's too late now to turn it around.
I can say one thing.
If you think your IQ is anywhere close to,
Dr. Seuss,
Sinister's IQ,
you've got another thing coming.
I would say that...
Well, he forgot more than you'll ever know.
That's not true, Joe.
His IQ qualifies him as a sub-genius.
Yeah, I do not have a genius level IQ.
Not that IQ means all that much anyway.
He's got a good mammary, I'll tell you that.
And quite a set of mammary glands to go with him.
Oh, man.
Some knockers on Dr. Seuss.
He's a real sinister.
That's what makes him so sinister.
Circumcision is indeed profit if thou keepest the law.
But if thou art a transgressor of the law,
thy circumcision becomes uncircumcision.
Therefore, if thy uncircumcision keeps the righteousness of the law,
shall not his uncircumcision be unrighteous?
Uncircumcision?
Be count for circumcision.
Yea, the uncircumcision that is by nature fulfilling his law
shall judge thee who by letter and circumcision transgresses the law.
I want some puzzling evidence.
Well, who is this sexy voice with puzzling evidence?
It is puzzling. The evidence I have is puzzling.
Wow.
Tell us about it. Maybe Dr. Howell can explain it.
Oh, I would try.
There is some jello and cotter pins all over the place.
What? Jello and cotter pins?
Yes.
That means Bob has been there.
That's the worst sign.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you.
The people love it when Bob shows up and then leaves before they get to see him.
Yes, and he leaves the so-called jello as well as cotter pins.
It was like Outer Limits or something.
It was. It was a journey.
You know her first notice that Bob left jello and cotter pins behind him?
To the Outer Limits.
The late John Stakely, the science fiction writer who wrote Armor.
Yes.
Vampires with a dollar sign.
Is he listening right now?
No, he... well, from heaven.
Do we know he had some knowledge of the corporations and jello before?
What, a friend jello?
A friend jello, though.
A friend jello?
Friend Jellica.
There's evidence of jello and cotter pins before now.
I see.
It's...
Yeah, it's sticky.
Jello by...
It's sticky and sweet.
It's sticky, but it's not the brand name product.
It's usually grape jello.
The last couple of X days, we found the cotter pins with grape jello around the pulpit.
Grape jello in the morning.
And the pulpit knocked over.
Like Bob had come up there and went,
I'm casting the money changers out of the temple.
Ain't changing enough money into money for me.
And he kicked the pulpit over.
The very heavy pulpit.
Not the little pulpit.
Not the altar.
Yeah, the big altar.
The giant thing made by X-Train.
Holy dagons.
The one you can launch a head from.
It's so sturdy.
Neck way lectulous.
Neck portico acapit.
Yeah, Dr. Hallis has watched Bobby's Hall thing up hills.
I've seen them.
Yes.
Like Prince Geraldo.
Dedicated their bodies to straining under the effort.
Their young flesh quivering with exhaustion as they attempt to heave this massive Bob object up into its place of prominence.
It's a sturdy pulpit.
That's what we're watching right now.
The first thing that we...
Above the plotted plane.
Ed said, I want to make you guys a pulpit.
What's the first thing you need?
And we said, it needs to be really portable so you can take it on a plane.
So he made something that you can only carry in a van.
Pulpit fiction there.
So what is this about the rape jello?
The leg jello?
Imagine how heavy...
You have to talk to Philo about that.
He has that problem chronically.
I didn't think she was...
Imagine how heavy it would be if you asked him to make it heavy.
Well, it's just going to be the volume and weight of a human leg.
And I guess that's about all.
Except of course to say that what is advertised as a jello may actually be...
Something else.
In the long run, it's always better to look before you leap.
Yep.
Watch out for the ass pick.
For Goofball Radio, this is Dr. Howlandow.
Better to eat the jello than drink the Kool-Aid.
Or a flavoring as the face may be.
Eat the jello.
Or not.
Man, those sheep are like, they've eaten the jello.
They'll believe anything.
The hungry sheep look up and are not fed.
With care.
J-E-L-L-O.
You still hear the crying of the lambs, don't you?
And full grown lambs loud bleat from hilly bourn.
I'm calling on my cello phone.
Cello?
The jello phone.
That's the softest, jiggliest form of smartphone.
It's a mellow jello phone.
Soft and jiggly and smart.
I understand the connection is there.
But the jello phone is sort of wiggly.
It's a little bit hinky, it's wobbly.
But there's always room for more.
That's the important thing.
Room for one more, honey.
Jello, of course, is just the conspiracy's name for hell.
Hell.
Oh, get it?
In Spanish, it would be pronounced hail.
But it is jello.
It's like hell.
Jello.
Help me, Bob.
I'm in hell, Bob.
I'm in hell.
It's not what you said it would be.
Where's my $90, Bob?
Help me, Bob.
Maybe we're dead, Bob.
Maybe this place is hell.
Did you ever hear of a railroad in hell?
I got injured in the course of X Day During That Doctor Jam.
Like, my hands were bleeding.
After playing the game.
I played the drums.
What?
I played the drums until my hands were bleeding.
Literally.
Cool.
Oh my God.
You mean the drumsticks were holes in your hands?
I got some blisters from that.
I don't know.
Maybe I have to build up calluses.
Or maybe I'm just holding the sticks the wrong way.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
He shed blood for Bob.
That's right.
Well, I'm sure that Reverend Angry Larry set that up.
Because for the first time, he didn't.
Normally, Reverend Angry Larry, somehow, he would have been able to get the money.
I don't even know.
All right, we didn't see you two together.
Do you?
Yeah, ladies and gentlemen, white
men.
open. He looks all
scarred up and ugly like he does.
He gave a lot for Bob. He gave
his face for Bob.
I just thought it was because he was from Detroit.
What was that?
I just assumed that
was because he was from Michigan.
Well, you'll get that in
Michigan. That's true. Okay, Reverend
Stang, I had a question for you.
Yes. Okay,
you might have heard earlier
in the show, Dr. Spencer was talking about
feeling let down because Bob failed to
show again.
He's done this year after year.
I'm just wondering, what did Bob
have to do to get you offended enough
to leave the church as a subgenius?
Now, what?
Say that again?
What would Bob have to
do to get me to leave the church?
Right, exactly.
All he would have to do would be
to wish it for one instant.
Just the slightest little whim.
Oh, I'd wish Stang would go away.
That'd be it.
Yeah, that's
one of the dangers of being
that powerful. We all the time find
ourselves saying, God, I wish this or that
for a second there, but you don't really wish it.
Well, with Bob, those fading wishes
come true.
That happened to me the other day.
That happened to me the other day because I was
staring at the power transformer that's right
outside the house on the power lines,
and I was just kind of putting my psychic energy
into it, thinking, wow, wouldn't it
be cool if that power transformer
blew?
Two days later, we heard a loud
pop outside in the middle of the night
and 1130 at night.
Power went out in my neighborhood because that
power transformer blew.
Oh, that wasn't kind of blue
I was hoping you would say, but
I was expecting
a different kind of blow from the
transformer, but...
Wow, man.
Those transformers are more than meets the eye.
You've got to be careful.
You've got to be working for Michael Bay on those transformers
movies.
You know, Autumn went to see that...
I will defeat you!
Optimus Prime.
Autumn went to see that and said that
they stole my artwork for
transformers.
Oh, you ought to see those.
If you just skip past all the human
parts and just watch the robot fighting,
it's psychedelic
as hell. It's great stuff.
And they do look
very similar. They're so detailed.
Some of them have like
10,000 moving interlocking
virtual parts.
Oh, there's a character
just like you in Transformers 2.
He's like
a Decepticon who's
so old
he's been damaged and he's
become...
He's become
deprogrammed and he's joined
the Autobots.
But he's
got a Scottish accent to begin with.
So he's like Sean Connery.
He's actually...
He transforms into a...
stealth bomber
that's in an
aviation museum.
And the hero comes and awakens him
and he unfolds and he's this
cranky old
revolving-haired bearded...
He's like a transformer that reminds you of
Ian Anderson.
You know, kind of this...
Did you throw Tully in Anderson?
Yeah.
An old shaggy-haired guy with a beard.
He has almost a cane
type of thing.
And he's...
Cantankerous.
Whoever voices him is great.
And he's
one of the good guys
who used to be a bad guy.
You know, a Decepticon.
But he's kind of...
Be nice to your little furry friend.
That's great. Yeah, Transformers 2.
I haven't seen any of them.
The animation is astounding.
Everything else about him is just
about what you'd expect.
You know, kid stuff.
I'll send me pawns and days.
Show you some...
I'll suffer my infinite wrath!
You little spinal cord-based organisms.
Bugger it!
Behold!
The eternal glory of
the Empire!
Prepare for about systems override!
I tell you, this guy did not age well.
There's really nothing
more satisfying than getting to
make music at all.
And then getting to make music with musicians
you know and respect.
That just compounds the...
awesomeness.
Well, I will try to have that
Sunday night X-Day jam
rendered and flensed
and available in all media
as soon as possible.
Rendered unto the sinister...
You were amazing, Rob.
I keep on...
Stop, stop.
His bloody hand was cool.
The blood splattering.
I wondered who had bled all over the stage.
Well, apparently I wasn't the only one
bleeding on stage.
I'm not sure if I should say this or not,
but Pisces mentioned something about...
something about...
something happening.
Like there was like blood fueling the whole thing.
Cool.
See, we don't have a fan of these cult...
No.
...rock and roll shows.
No, it was true blood.
It's doctor music
because the doctors are surgeons.
They use knives of sound
to slice the flesh
and cleanse the blueness of the wound.
Oh, yes.
The patient's dying.
We better bleed him some more.
I'm on a mission.
He got fired.
What do you want?
Look, we just...
We just want to talk.
I have no time to talk.
I'm on a mission.
I'm a mercenary doombringer.
What planet am I on?
Earth.
Earth?
Terrible name for a planet.
Might as well call it
Dirt.
Planet Dirt.
Oh, that was the former Decepticon
representing Dr. G. Gordon Gordon
here on Hour of Slack number 1,355
from the Church of the Subgenius
about which everything can be learned
including all past shows
at subgenius.com.
If you look at the front page,
there are buttons,
buttons for all kinds of stuff.
For instance, radio
leading to all subgenius shows.
Videos, graphics, books.
We have a whole book online
that we did with people like
William Burroughs and Robert Anton Wilson,
Three-Fisted Tales of Bob.
And under events,
you can learn about the X-Day Festival
and Starwood,
both coming up in Southern Ohio
this July 5th week
in hopes that this is the year,
the last year for the humans,
the year Bob called
1998.
You said 98.
I mean, for me, that's a huge year
because it was written
and involves 1998 as being this sort of
crossroads of time-space
where this was like a major shift
in time-space.
Who's the guy who does
the time travel technology?
I was listening to an interview with him
where someone called in asking about
if they had noticed
a shift in 1998.
And he said, actually,
we have a lot of,
we hear that a lot from people
and we think there might be something to this.
We have some evidence to suggest
that 1998 involves some sort of time travel
or time shift.
When are you going to X that tractor up your...
Well, now let's not get personal here.
X-ing requires practice.
You can't just X something right away.
You have to work up to it.
You can X it up and X it when?
Well, X is the third time.
It's the third to the last letter of the alphabet.
Z?
And because of that,
I said the third to the last.
Y?
X.
No, Z.
Y.
W.
We're talking about X, not Y.
Don't you see anything?
Why?
Do you see nothing?
I'm trying to make this into some kind of
Abbott and Costello routine, I think.
First the X's come, then the Y's come,
then the Z's come and clean up.
Costello.
Well, that's true.
It is an organic mathematical sequence of preordained events.
Now, there's no point in kicking against the traces there.
That's the problem with knowing the future.
There are no answers.
I'll take my nose.
We just don't know what time or year it is now.
Let's see, I'll take that one and that one.
So we have no point of reference that's accurate.
We know what's happened in class.
Ye know not when the master comes.
I'll take that one.
Right, and that one.
Prophecy becomes a bit of a problem because it's...
I've picked all my nose now.
...not always accurate.
You can pick your friends and you can pick your nose,
but you can't pick your friends' noses.
Not in a state park.
You can choose a nose from this table of noses here.
Who would want to chew a nose?
Only a desperate individual.
Well, you know there's a website out there for it.
A Donner pastor.
There's a nose chewers website out there somewhere.
Yes, that's the NoseChewer.com.
NoseChewer.com.
That's a domain name that I'm going to try to get real quick.
While the demand is low.
I just read on Scrub Genius, I read that Reverend Popo discovered that the domain name largemanhood.com
was not in use and he bought it and re-mirrored it so it goes to subgenius.com.
So anyone who types in largemanhood,
it goes straight to subgenius.com.
That's great.
That just saves us a little bit of organization.
It only cost him like 50 bucks a year for that.
Praise Reverend Provo.
How much does it cost to renew a domain name now?
This is Provo.
About, it depends.
About six arms and a leg.
Yeah, yeah, it depends on what kind of a domain it is.
Once it's gone, it's gone.
Subgenius.com.
I think I pay about 35 bucks a year.
60 bucks for two years.
But then there's a monthly fee on top of that.
Oh man.
So we need every donation that's allowed to be discussed on the public right now.
Which is none.
We can't discuss it at all.
All you can do is donate to your local radio station.
But the good thing about none, the good thing about nothing is you can ask for all of it that you want.
On the other hand, on pirate radio, you can make outrageous requests for money and perhaps...
But we can request nothing.
And we want you to give us all the nothing you can to send in your donations of nothing.
As much as possible.
Open your heart and open your arms wide and...
Inada creeps in this petty pace from day to day to the last syllable of recorded masking tape.
You're supposed to wash your problem?
And all our yesterdays have lighted fools to dusty depths.
You should clean your problems off.
Keep them problem free.
Out, out, brief phylo.
Your problems should be free to...
Show us but a walking shadow.
A poor, extremely poor player who struts and frets endlessly.
His hour upon the stage.
And then is heard only in real life.
She can go on like that for hours.
Tale told by an idiot.
Full of sound and fury.
Why would you stop something so sweet?
It's like the sound of angels laughing.
Great.
Another religious nut.
Hmph.
Welcome friend.
I don't even know what I'm doing here.
You believe in...
Mob?
Yeah, sure.
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
Mob?
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
Mob?
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
Mob?
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
Mob?
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
Mob?
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
A doing here.
That's what you do in here.
What I'm...
Mob?
Thud.
That's what you do in here.
Thank you.