The Self-Genius Power of Bob
Ah yes, dear friends, and this one gets really weird.
It's a new arrangement of pretty old stuff, all from late 2000 and early 2001,
all from Chaz Smith's ESO Swamp Radio at WCSB Cleveland.
Every month back then, I used to compile the clips from that show that I used on our Slack
just in case I might need ways to reduce show production time in my old age.
And this is the fourth, actually, of those compilations.
I did go to the trouble of taking the random parts and organizing them
so they sound less random and more like we meant it to be that way.
We, being the late Professor Chaz Smith,
who was the host,
producer,
mix board operator,
and guiding star,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
who had been doing radio and music with Chaz for many years,
and me, the new guy.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy has also heard on this one a lot, calling in.
And we really miss our old friend Chaz
and those days at the WCSB studio.
Heck,
before 9-11,
you could frop in there.
You weren't supposed to,
but you could.
Well.
Yep.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's
trying to get here.
Good night, boys and girls.
Oh!
Good night.
Look out for them gopher holes, Dave.
Boston, Texas, wherever you are.
Oh, Dave.
Dave, look out for that barbed wire.
Look at that.
Look out.
Look out for those mud puddles made of sulfuric acid, Dave.
Don't put your foot in there.
Dave, look out for that nuclear testing range.
Dave.
Don't drive too close to the perinuclear power plant.
We've told you that over and over.
Dave, look out for that canyon.
Dave, look out for that mountain.
Oops, a cactus.
Oh, a heel monster.
It's Billy.
Oh, a giant tarantula crawling up from behind it.
Then mute.
And let us come together
under the auspices of the show.
ESO Swamp Radio.
I am plugged directly into the show
and to the listeners
by way of a series of wires and transmitters.
Once again, I'm...
It's almost as if my brain waves...
We're intermingling with those of the unfortunate listener.
Well, I'll tell you what, Dave.
You, the listener.
You, the individual one.
The one I'm talking to.
Not everybody in general that might happen to be
all ten of the people that might happen to be listening.
Here, Dave, give me your tape.
But you.
You.
Those ten people are not...
The one.
True individuals in the way between...
No, no, no.
He's not...
That's a dumb old radio joke.
He's not really talking to me.
He's not talking to you.
In this one case, this one instance,
you have to be wrong.
It's not generic.
It really is you.
You.
I guess he was going to call the insecurity police.
Remember when we had that whole fan club of...
That is true.
...13 and 14-year-old boys in high school,
junior high and high school kids?
We semi-raised a generation in our many years here doing Thanksgiving.
I still get emails from some of them.
Of radio freaks who are like in their 20s.
They're all rich now.
Yes.
They've moved on.
They're all...
They grew up with brain rot radio theater.
And they said it did something strange to them.
It lubrilexed their interior their whole life.
When I was eight years old,
I heard you on the radio.
In scabby days.
It's like, I believed in you.
Psychopath.
I believed in you, man.
You let me down.
What we used to hear the most was...
I've been watching you.
I know what you're...
Kid.
...name's are and where they go.
I know how you slept downstairs.
I listened to you when I was eight years old.
And you told me about Bob.
And you let me down, man.
I know how you slept.
My slinky let me down.
The pinkies are dancing little slinkies down there on the dance floor.
Just look at them.
They don't know that they're in for the special showers after the dance.
A loner in pairs and makes a sleeky sound.
Yeah.
Look at those slinkies jiggling, springy down there.
Little do they know.
Oh, they're having fun now.
Slinky, it's slinky.
For fun, it's a wonderful time.
Down there dancing, doing coke, locker room and bullets.
And that disgusting...
Those people are just shipping me alien dice.
Anybody who would go to a children's toy store...
Makes a great sound when you pull it around.
If I was an old money fellow...
Slinky, that's a slinky thing.
You don't want the best time to go to a...
Children's toy store.
Christmas Eve.
Go to Toys R Us at Christmas Eve with a home video camera and a tape recorder
and watch the...
Record the parents going stark raving mad.
We'll see you there.
You're going to raincoat?
It's Christmas Eve.
Did you go on a raincoat or is this like, you know, a form of debauchery like you were talking about?
Go in and watch the yuppie parents panic.
Just buy this old Christmas.
I haven't done a thing.
Don't even have a Christmas tree.
I am panicking.
Most lots are all sold out.
I search until the night.
I end up with the grubby shrub with the case of life.
Christmas is almost here.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle but Satan Claus?
Oh my gosh.
Dang, come on.
Whose father, Paul Bunyan, and whose mother, Big Sister, created the conspiracy.
Did they have Christmas before there were malls?
Before there were malls, there was no such thing as Christmas.
Yes.
The Pilgrims were big.
There was a down-home Norman Rockwell style, it's a wonderful life type of Christmas.
It was a kite-flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas, not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
No.
It was a...
When your little brother broke through the hole, fell through a hole in the ice sling,
and you went and saved him, you didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
But today, Christmas is lost its meaning.
So, Stang, are you up there?
Are you in some huddle on the side of a freeway somewhere?
I am in both places, for I can travel to any part of the universe without moving.
I would say you're there now.
You're there now.
Huh?
I have folded...
I can tell he's there now because when you guys, you know, both put your fingers
and your sphincters at the same time, you can read each other's minds.
And that's how he knew what you were going to say.
No, that's the way we sign for the deaf.
Yeah.
Ha ha.
Signing for the deaf.
I get it somehow.
No, I made it all the way up here through the snow.
I had my dogs pull the Travoy type thing.
Well, can I ask you a question about your voyage there?
What really is Great-Grandma Dummy Up's Ice Cold Titty Wax?
Can we use it on a winter night like tonight, or is it just like more of a psychic medicine?
You know, my people do not know of such things.
We don't even have a single word for snow or illness where I come from.
Well, your people, um...
Travel to any part of the universe...
Which people are your people?
The people there from Alpha Centauri?
The people who can travel to any part of the universe without moving.
Okay, then they're astral traveling pigasus peoples.
Is that what it means?
They are those who can fold...
...in space as you would fold a soiled handkerchief.
But don't the dimensions around them bend and undulate as they travel through the mall buying their, you know, Christmas shit stockings and things that they wear?
Well, that's what we promised the girls.
Well, I can imagine you'd get some probably...
If you were the magnet, you know, any... like that, you know, I imagine that you'd attract a lot of horse hair, if you know what I mean.
Well, and plus you also have to use some form of...
...of spice.
Which could be metaphysical in your case.
A metaphysical spice?
Or sort of like the stuff that comes off of that handkerchief that you fold like space in order to travel from one side of the handkerchief to the other without moving.
So then we're presented with the universal problem.
God's daughter or dog butter, who put the condoms in the pie pan as the cosmos expands?
Travel to any part of the universe, Dave, without moving.
Pierce the pinhole in the rubber of space.
You can feel the phony cyber stocks and the surveillance groups...
Dave, we want you to do this. Here's what I want you to do.
Drift away from your body...
Dave, listen.
I'm listening.
Okay. You have to go to sleep.
Okay, I have to go to sleep.
And then you're gonna dream.
Must I concentrate on my navel or must I look at my hands?
You're gonna dream.
You have to look at your hands in your dream.
Okay, what if I'm pawing at myself like a dog?
Okay, then try not to look at your genitalia.
Okay, well, I can't see them anyway, must I?
Okay. Well, okay, and then dream your body here.
Dream yourself here to the radio show.
Okay, but that would be like...
And then you're gonna transfer your dreaming body into your real body and your real body into your dreaming body, and then you'll be here.
So I will physically be there, but I'll be dreaming that I'm here.
You are a mongrel.
Dream walk through dream time.
Do I have to knock the coconuts together and wear one of those weird things on my head?
Of course.
And go rub my back against a red rock or something?
Come on, that's why I didn't even have to mention...
You don't even mention that.
Make sure your kneecaps are shaved, too.
The mongrel must shave kneecaps and suck on the death bone.
Just as if it were so easy to shave your kneecaps in one breath, and then the very next lung-shocking breath to so deftly do that other thing that you used to do.
You said what I can't... I can't really remember what it was.
Just don't worry, he's only the beard.
Travel to any part of the universe without moving.
What you will notice is a temporal distension and also an increase in the size of the pubic area.
The number of brain cells affected is marginal if done correctly.
Oh!
Dave started to materialize just there.
Oh, did you see that, Chad?
I saw him for a second and he looked like a sleeping man on the floor.
He was like starting to nod off and he...
I can't... Am I...
I feel her body.
Oh, it's gross.
Get it away from me.
No, no, wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
God, wake up, Dave, wake up.
I can't really wake up.
You traveled through dream time and did bad things.
Okay, we got a little bit of a problem.
Come on, Dave.
Your body is there.
And although I can smile like an oily jackaniche, I can't really more or less wake up in a way that, you know, it looks like my mouth is moving there.
It's...
Quit drooling.
I'm stuck kind of like in this...
Here, let me try to wipe...
Ooh, my hand went...
I tried to wipe this face and my hand went right through it.
No, no, no, don't worry about the de novo jurisprudence monkeys.
Just keep on pushing down further and further until you get to the Versace pants.
I'll just get to the floor.
Huh?
It's gross.
You're gone.
Oh.
Oh, good.
You're just a voice now, Dave.
Yeah, but I'm still in here.
Okay, now I can't feel my body anywhere, you guys.
Huh?
I can feel my voice, but I can't feel my body anywhere.
You mean you're like in between the phone lines and the radio airways?
I don't know.
I'm stroking my fake beard.
I just...
I pulled out my plastic eye and it didn't...
I didn't feel a damn thing.
It's just like I'm just...
Tug on the beard.
Huh?
Oh, you can't feel yourself?
I cannot feel my physical acupuncture.
There's no acupuncture.
I'm just like, you know, sensations are...
But you're talking.
Of course I'm talking.
I can't even...
Well, can you feel your lips with your tongue if you're talking?
I mean, can you...
Oh, I see.
You're saying like take it back step by step?
Yeah, just start...
Yeah.
Okay, I'll have to make a sound first.
Or you could just strap on those big sticks on your feet and slide around in that snow.
Babe, you don't know how long I've been...
Long as to slap some big sticks on my feet and slide around, but I don't know if it's
gonna get me out of the monitor box.
At least as long as you know.
He doesn't have feet right now.
Right.
You're looking for...
He wishes.
He wishes he had feet.
The one which put the shoes to slide.
I got some like electron dots, some, you know, like photovoltaic things going on here.
Some, you know...
What can you see?
I cannot really see anything.
It's really a strange sensation.
It's just if I was looking, but all I am getting is like an impression of like this long tube
and this other like tube of light.
They're both like two tubes of light and they're like next to each other.
I'm in this larger one and there's this like smaller one and things are going through it
and then all around it's black.
But I can't really say, you know, describe it.
It's just like so proto and so, you know, so geometric.
You're talking.
Is there air?
Can you smell anything?
Well, maybe that would help if I skeet shot backwards with one of the big George Bush
balloon heads on myself, you know, or something.
But I don't know.
I could try it, you know, or something.
I could try something anyway.
Smell first.
Think later.
Can I feel your fingers?
My fingers?
Can you feel your fingers feeling your fingers?
That would be your fingers.
Sniff your fingers.
Your thumb though.
I have a sensation that I am sucking my thumb right now, so I must pull it.
Huh?
Pull my thumb.
Okay.
I'll try.
Wait a minute.
Let me, let me try and see if I can pull my tongue.
The center of the tongue.
Okay.
Now I feel another part of my body.
I pulled my thumb while I was sucking it.
Now I can feel another part of my body.
Does it itch back there?
Of course.
It feels like it's full of like these weird like little neuron hairs or something.
These little, little dendrites poking out like electronic things or something.
Follow the itch and the hairs back there back.
Okay.
I'll follow back.
If you want to come back.
Maybe you want to stay there on the edge.
Wait a minute.
I'm picking up another, it looks like it says muni light intake station.
What the hell does that mean?
And who's that woman with you?
I said what?
There's a woman with you, Dave.
She's got to be like an electronic woman because all I can see are like these like weird little electronic images that like kind of remind you of female, but they don't really look like any human woman I ever saw.
It's just like, you know, things that go by and they're like, they're like, they're looking at me like they're trying to stay, I don't know, hidden.
The spirits of the dead, perhaps, Dave?
I don't know.
I haven't offended the dead, have I?
Maybe.
I'm sorry.
Maybe you've joined the dead.
Maybe you have.
It's been 3,000 years since my last defection, but I can't remember.
Maybe you died inside your horse.
Maybe I died in there?
Shivering.
And maybe the horse, after the horse died and cooled down, you cooled down and while you were talking to us on that pay phone and maybe you've crossed over.
Okay, since all I can feel is my thumb sucking itself.
That's kind of like a proto-existence thing, right?
So if I go back to being in the horse's butt trying to stay warm, then that means that.
Or go the other way.
Maybe you'll come out of a new mama.
Maybe that's who that was that we just heard speaking.
What about those little air fish that everybody's seeing?
I've heard more and more sightings of air fish.
Well, I didn't see any while I was out there.
What the hell?
I just thought it was snow.
No, no, no.
People are seeing like, you know, they'll be walking around and like in the air around them, they'll see little like tropical fish.
Well, no wonder we are.
That's a hallucination.
That's a common hallucination in white outs.
Yeah, no, no, but.
That's part of it.
He's on the first bardo, the air fish on the first.
That's the first thing you see when.
We must help to lead.
When the snow.
To help Dave cross over.
Yeah.
To the second bardo.
Those are snow fairies, bleepo.
Snow fairies?
Yeah.
I've seen snow fairies out of a horse's arse?
Come on, man.
That doesn't make any sense.
But what does.
Okay, what does ginger beer mean?
Oh, ginger beer.
I don't know what ginger beer means.
I don't know if it has a meaning.
I think it has more like a psychic reference point.
What?
What do fluids mean?
Fluids don't have a meaning.
They have like more of a psychic reference point.
I have to keep repeating myself, but like, okay, you think of a fluid.
What's the first thing it relates to a feeling, doesn't it?
Air fish.
There's another feeling that just like drifted in and drifted out.
No, but I'm serious.
I don't think it's ever going to get me out of here.
You know, if you think of fluids and feelings, then you have air fish because, you know,
fish are like swimming through like the emotions, you know?
But are they lethal or predatory?
I don't know.
I put all my scrotal essences in phony cyber stocks.
I was going to say, I got the bottle.
You sent me the bottle and I've been able to do all kinds of things with that.
Well, see, I was a failure.
No, no, no, but it worked.
You sent me the bottle of your essence and I'm telling you that it worked here.
Well, why doesn't my essence work for me and why doesn't anybody else's work for me?
Well, the thing is, you're probably just like, I don't know.
Well, I don't know.
Do you boil it down?
Do you boil it down before you use it?
Well, yeah, but I was hoping you weren't going to say I'm unessential, if you know what I
mean.
Do you use the cheese cloth?
Do you like double strain it through the cheese cloth and do the thing with the clay and the
candles and the little, you know, the little onanistic ritual and the, and the, and the
wall with the clay and everything?
See, those directions were so confusing.
I didn't know how to make the clothes out of a piece of cheese.
And I assumed that was in other words, alchemy jokes you guys were playing on me, right?
But I kept the cheese and I kept the...
I'm not saying, I'm not saying, I'm not going to say whether it was, but go on.
Well, isn't anybody going to give me kind of illumination of some kind?
I mean, what am I just like sitting here like Rudolph the Red?
Dave, you had your chance at illumination when you were on the first Bardo and were
able to, had the opportunity to cross over to the second, but instead you listened to
the babbling devil and now you've gone back to the negative first Bardo.
Which is why that cheese is so effective.
It's getting colder, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's getting oilier too, just like that cheese.
You're going down, down, down, down.
I can feel my wisdom eye teeth draining themselves like a little, a little thing like one of
those little radio tubes.
It's too small, it's like a little crystal now.
Going down, sir.
But first the word go for F-ing.
Want to take this out down in paradise?
Which paradise?
Mars?
Brushwood?
Amsterdam?
Or Black Rock City?
Palm trees, white sand, clear blue water.
At least not the kind of name I want to raise its children to know.
Dave, that would be like some insane author who's made a big lot of money and he's down
there bothering the people who just want to hang out on the beach.
We're in Papua New Guinea or someplace?
Yeah.
Like if you were to become a prize-selling author like Stang.
Hey you New Guinea Papas, how about you read Book of Subgenius?
We write big books, make big money.
Yeah, yeah.
You have to talk pig Latin like,
We make love long time.
If me gay that, uh, okina kate.
Bob love you, sell Bob book.
And then the ceremonies begin.
As Stang is about to learn his first lesson in the Cathedral of Sax.
Why, certainly I'd like to undergo your strange rituals here on this island, uh, folks.
What just you got me?
Let us wash your feet.
Ritual circumcision?
This costume's so ugly.
Wait just a minute.
You can circumcise a couple of them, I guess, sure.
Yeah, you can circumcise a couple, but you can't circumcise them all.
And so Stang was cut by the medicine man while the dancing girls tiraded around in order to, uh, help accelerate the process.
Now what the hell was that confabulation?
Was that a kind of congruent movement or?
Well, it's kind of hard to find.
It's hard to find the skin when it's like a cluster, like a, a, a cab of kale.
Have you ever lit your skin, pour oil by pinching your skin and then you hold a lighter close much the way you'd light an orange on fire.
And it makes something.
When you, when you hold a light, when you pinch a bit of your skin.
Yeah, it's like an old hippie trick, you know, like the first time you ever got high on having a frappe.
Yeah, and from your elbow, it'll burn kind of greenish oil.
Right, it's more like that.
And from your knee, it burns like kind of purplish.
Yeah, it's more like transmission oil coming out of your elbow.
From your forehead.
From your forehead, it's kind of a yellowish glow.
Yeah, but it does, it looks like castor oil or something.
Very, very piggy incentive.
I bet a lot of people didn't know you could do that.
And there's a big scab afterwards and you get an infection and.
Well, not always, you know.
Down by the old lake, we pulled the canoe up and walked inside.
The band was playing already.
We waited a little bit too long out in the canoe.
We got our bottle of hoochie and went inside and the whole gang was there.
Tinas Wang, Cloris Leperitis and Betty Clitoris were all standing around in a circle,
laughing at the misshapen-headed boy.
We had so much fun with him.
His head was so big.
Little did I know he'd become the head of the Republican National Committee.
Oh, honey, I hope you like what's been going on so far, if you know what I mean.
I can't get enough of it.
Just put your head right over here.
Whoa!
Hey, it's gonna be sunny tomorrow.
Sunny and bright.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
Would you like to dance?
I've got some Crisco oil.
Oh, don't mind if I do, dear.
Let's get down and slather, baby.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
It's so romantic.
Well, the band played on for hours and hours and Bob and Connie got closer and closer.
It wasn't much of a matter of time before Bob and Connie decided to walk out in the woods after him.
Still here, the muted strains of the band in the background.
Now the lapping of the lake was much stronger.
And in Bob's mind, the lapping of the water on the sand was a reminder, a reminder.
Ah!
Ah, yes, loiterers and Germans, that's the first installment.
And you can get an installment every week of this show.
Thickening, perhaps even a curtailment of your normal activitudes.
Just by sending a skip love bracelet and a lack of interest to Tricky and the Preeminence.
And also, this week only, you're gonna get them all absolutely for free.
That's only a 3.9 lack of interest this month until January 1st.
Sha-la-la.
Many, many, many, many, many, many miles.
As we return to Lake Winnicott,
we see Bob's long proboscis,
the phallus of a frightened dog,
entering the safe harbor of Connie's womanhood.
And here's my final question before I go, because the spaceship is taking off in a minute here.
How can I get tapes of this show? How can I tune in?
Well, you hear a lot of it on the computer.
You're on the internet.
We're on the internet in many different ways.
www.wcsb.org
.org, I like that word, org.
Yeah.
Right.
That's a good word.
And then you just click on the, uh, audioactive thing, and if you don't have it, download it.
And, uh, do what you have to do.
You can hear excerpts from the show, uh, any time of day or night on www.subgenius.com.
Now, that I, that I have done. That I have done.
I have streamed in MP3 as well as real audio.
That is good stuff.
Praise David Botner, the greatest Canadian who was ever born.
But there were plenty of Canadians before him who starved to death in the snow.
For it is he who made the MP3 broadcasts of Swamp Radio and Hour of Slack possible.
You know, it's good when you're back there, gotta get out, you know where it is.
You know nothing of these wet, gotta be black.
Alright.
No.
The change is coming.
The change is coming, Dr. Spanx.
Wake up, Dr. Spanx.
Look up my nightie.
Look, look, look, look.
Look what I've got.
Isn't it pink?
Wait, hey, am I still in Dobstown?
I bet you've never seen me.
Yes.
It looks all...
It's, it's some...
It is Dobstown.
Don't worry.
It's so slackful now.
Oh, just, just lay back down.
It's so filmy and downy and slidey and...
Look out the suit, the suit stained window.
It's latched.
Flowing and...
Look at the smokestacks rising.
Sir, sir.
Look at the smoke descending into the heavens off an horizon.
And those beautiful singers.
The swirling of the leaves around your ears.
Flying winged pipes.
This is how I envision Dobstown.
Yes, your exotic pants.
Tell me I'm not hypnotized or something, Doc.
Look at those capri pants.
Oh, man, I feel, I don't feel like my old self anymore.
I feel like, like, like a new man.
You staying?
A new, a new man.
Dave.
Get your hand out of my pants, man.
It's freezing out here.
Dave, what are you...
Oh, God.
Hey, man.
Dave.
Oh, damn it, Dave.
You think you're taking a nap?
I thought you froze today, man.
I was cruising, man.
I was in the zone.
No.
Hey, Chaz, Chaz, slap his...
You just brought me down.
I'm gonna...
Check his pulse, Chaz.
...least another five minutes out of that temper, Dex, you bastard.
He's talking pretty fast.
Man, you were almost there, bro.
God, it's freezing.
I was, it was like I was in Dobstown and I had a chance to get out of that temper,
and he's full slack to miss him.
No, man.
And it was like there was still a church at St. Eustace, and the new year and the new
world were all real, and it wasn't still this old.
You passed over, man.
Oh, the world...
We thought you was dead.
You were asleep there in the back seat and there was so much carbon monoxide, and the
snowbank was up so high we...
Man, it's freezing.
Well, we had to dig you out.
It took almost like...
Man, my hands are still freezing.
You got a coffee over there?
Hey.
Now, this is crazy.
This is crazy.
Did you hear about the sun activity, too?
The sun is going through a total peak time right now.
Yeah, George Jr. is really...
He's as popular as the father was.
But it is.
There's a website.
There's a lot I've heard.
They're more like little pubescent rockets than flares.
It's a really cool website, too.
That's all about it.
You can get a real-time sun screensaver now.
I waited long enough for this.
You used to put up four or five different pictures of the sun.
I should have sent it to you.
We quit doing that because it was so disturbing.
It appeared that huge, gigantic shotguns were blasting away at the sun about half the time.
I think those were Masonic subliminals from the Masonics who are running the NASA corporations.
Wait a minute.
The engine that...
Creates all warmth for the whole solar system is having a little trouble right now, did you say?
Supposedly.
It's more than a little trouble.
Now, could this possibly be the coming of prophecy?
Of all the prophecies of every primitive...
It's a rich form of frothy tabulency when your mom and dad and everyone who you don't even know is going to want to...
The prophecies of the homies.
Of the Aztecs.
The Incas and the Subgenii.
Like a bird in the sky.
Like a little little lantern.
That all things, that the great carpet of reality would be rolled up...
So smooth and soft.
Taken outside, hung over a tree limb and batted by a gigantic old hag with a broom standing on the back of an infinite number of turtles.
And that she would spray it with an anti-lice sort of lotion potion.
Right.
And then it would be rolled, laid back down and all things would begin anew in the new age.
Or the new...
Oh, I forget the...
Well, how about...
The new Navajo Trail.
The new Navajo Trail?
And the Church of the Subgenius...
That leads off into the cosmos.
These silly primitive superstitions are understood in a scientific way as the time intersection,
which will happen when the great Mobius strip or infinity sign that is the road of time...
It has to cross in the middle, right?
Well, we're nearing that crossover point.
See, I can refuse that.
I want to set up a little deli.
Right there at that crossroad.
Chad Spankengold.
A little general story.
It's like, well, I think the exes are kind of wondering what the hell's going to happen when the time intersection occurs.
Listener.
What are you doing about it?
Are you ready?
You was ready for it.
Hey, hey.
Stop playing with the machine.
Hey.
Over and out.
Their froth was stored up for Y2K.
Now, they're not worried about nothing.
They ain't worried about X-Day.
Ain't worried about time intersection.
Ain't worried about divine rupture.
Ain't worried about...
They don't care about nothing.
About time.
They're going to get drunk and party.
Why should it?
And how can it?
They're just going to get drunk.
Softly.
RG by radio.
You think you're going to go out there and get drunk?
I know you.
I don't want you up for my beer.
Well, what do you know?
That don't cut no ice with me.
Speaking of ice cutters.
I don't hear that far address.
Do you remember the time Jack and I were out?
I mean, we were so far.
Damn far out there.
That when we dug the hole, you know, and stuck...
Squid gigging?
We were squid gigging.
And we stuck the little shack over the top of the little hole in the ice, you know.
And we're sitting there popping back a few beer, you know.
And I guess one guy...
This guy, you know, he's talking about Mario Lemieux and all this hockey crap all night.
And I said, I don't like hockey, you know.
So, I pulled this little like harpoon device I got.
You know, it's about four and a half inches long.
You get it from K-Telronco.
Any of them guys, you can order away for it.
And I said, I don't like hockey.
And he shoved it right into his thigh and ripped those, you know, those real thick muscles near the top of his knee, you know.
You're a prankster, Dave.
I tell you, we had a good laugh after that.
We had years and years of stories about that.
And I guess, well, it got him a little railed up, you know.
So, did he kill you then now, Dave?
I think I know where the nano-aliens live.
What do you think of me?
Why, they're the leprechauns of Celtic legend.
They're the wee folk?
Pink penises.
Red hearts and purple...
The Dave brains.
Brains.
I see, I see.
Frolicking over the hillside of the Emerald Isle.
Emerald Palace.
Emerald City.
Emerald Mushrooms.
That dirty, perky, sharkaback, black-bucked-a-burton,
important, fill-up-bucked-a-burton,
perkaluma-burton-bucked-a-burton,
don't you watch that.
But think...
Think if you could go back in time, Dave.
I am what I am right now.
I'm just wishing I hadn't come tonight.
Because I...
Because you did come back in time to get here?
Well, yeah.
Because I'm...
Well, I'd have to be here already now,
or else this part wouldn't make sense.
The rest of it...
But I'm already full of oblique little passages of time
that don't make no sense.
How about yourself?
I...
If I could...
If...
If time control,
as...
As prophesied by Dobbs,
were ours now,
what would...
What would one do with such a power?
If you could go back in time,
would you...
Go back in time, for instance,
and kill Hitler
to prevent terror,
or...
Or kiss Hitler to prevent...
Or kiss...
Right, to make him...
Because some people said, you know,
Ava Brown was just like his front
because he didn't have a girlfriend
to hang out with Berkscott.
He'd rather be hanging out with Goring or Himmler.
Really?
Yeah, they said...
Oh, that...
Well, you know, he has a lot of enemies.
The old frustrated rage thing, you know,
like he must be wanting to be with boys.
You know how he used to kiss those Hitler youth,
those young men on the cheek, you know,
these 12-year-old boys?
Well, so did I.
So did I.
I saw you do it, too, David.
I was forced to.
I was a political dissident,
and that was one of the jobs they made us do
besides ripping the clothes off the stiffs.
We'd help gas the stiffs,
pull their clothes off,
and then we'd have to go and kiss the Hitler youth boys.
And believe me,
that was not hell.
Well, would you go back in time?
Would you dare to change history?
Because say you did kill or kiss Hitler,
maybe the world would be a much better place
for lots of people,
but perhaps,
Hitler was the man who also killed
the one who would have been worse than Hitler,
the one who would have won.
What if Hitler, at some point in his career,
was indirectly or directly responsible
for killing someone else
who might, in fact, have destroyed the entire world?
How could you have had someone...
But Hitler was going to go for it.
Would you play God?
If you could go back in time,
would you play God?
I would probably play God,
or I would play Henry VIII.
What if you could turn back the clock,
even on Earth,
and start over again?
You know, would the same things happen?
Wouldn't you go back in time and kill Hitler,
even though he might be the very one
who killed the man who would destroy the entire world?
No, the first lizard.
No, say you could go back in time.
Okay, I would risk.
I would go back in time.
Say you could go back in time
to when the first lizard evolved.
Kissed Hitler.
Because we're really evolved from the lizards, right?
Okay, we're still...
So you kill the first lizard,
and it's some other form of life that comes out.
Not a lizard.
Not specifically...
Maybe a polyp.
Not specifically a lizard.
Perhaps an insect-based intelligent life.
Polyps come out sometimes.
A hybrid, a Friday John.
Okay, say our polyps were evolving
at a rate that was so rapidly fast
that we could not control it.
Would you go back,
as in a Hitler suit,
like one of those first characters,
a one-shell creature,
start your own jail,
and kill the polyps?
Would you step up?
On that butterfly
to make everything be spelled wrong
10, 60 million years later?
And you, as Americans...
Would you do it?
Brace yourselves together
with these mighty hernia braces
designed by my cousin Lou and I.
Would you play Frisbee with God?
Stand firmly and fastly
in front of the rest of your renegade crew
and laugh like dogs
until the cows return.
Even fish do it.
But what do they do?
In today's modern world,
in the year 2006,
fish not only do it,
they do it in style
at the downtown arena
for moms and dads and kids alike.
In the water that you drink.
It's done regularly
in the water you're drinking right now.
So sit back, plop a nice cube,
and put those feet up on the schizolone.
It's time for the...
Sponge Patrol.
The fish are doing it, huh?
I don't like to watch the fish do it.
The fish doing it reminds me of Bob
in his more recalcitrant,
more flaccid days.
Oh, I remember Bob and Connie
on Valentine's Day.
The little bat-winged hearts,
you could almost see them,
well, psychics could see them
flying between Bob and Connie
as they walked on the...
sidewalk hand in hand.
I could hear, uh...
Pantsless and panties and skirts.
Ah, the boat's going up and down the Seine.
You can hear the singing of the boat guys.
Bob with his funny little beret
cocked on the side of his...
Ah, look, he's wearing a funny little shirt
with a nipple cut out
so he can drink the wine
and let it fall where it may, huh?
No.
You know what I'm trying to do.
Or shopping for butt plugs.
A lonely sacre de mer.
Ah, le sacre de mer.
Let's go over to Montparnasse
and see if we can find those...
green butt plugs with his sequins.
They're so hard to find.
Yes, and we shall commit some paintings
and some artwork.
Ah, we will commit...
And we will go to see Jerry Lewis movies.
Ah, the Jerry Lewis movies.
And we'll listen to Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He also is a genius.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I love Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
True American stupidity, huh?
Oh, what an idiot.
The Americans could be so brilliantly stupid.
I listen to the audition all the time
and believe me,
for my limited anglais,
I can tell you these people
have no idea what they're doing.
They're talking about
what makes them so funny.
Oh, la, la.
More truffles?
Ah, hey, now.
David?
Let's stop down by the river
and have our feet crushed
and sing a morality song
from the Middle Ages, eh?
Oh, la, la.
Ah, I remember those days well.
I remember when the...
the Saracens attacked the city.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm going to flap my fingers.
Are you ready, Sia?
Oh, oh, oh.
Sit down and stop yourself.
Sorry, I was wool-gathering.
The virtual moment is almost expired.
I wonder if you want more time.
Oh, yes, please.
One thing, waiter.
What country is this?
Well, the current time
with the checkpoint and also...
That's the other thing.
What time do you have?
And what day, by the way?
Well...
I'm afraid I have to make
a terrible mistake.
I don't recognize those cars.
What year car is that new one
over there, waiter?
Is, uh...
It's a brand-new 1934 Escalade.
Oh, uh...
See, the show must go on.
Brand-new, eh?
Oh, man.
Time control.
It was just like the old man said.
Time control must always go awry.
I was a fool.
I was a fool to follow Bob
and his insane plans.
He was like a madman
throwing these glass beakers
and his Tesla coils
back across the laboratory
in a rage,
trying to bring life to the battery.
Then finally, he got it plugged in.
Then...
Oh, my God, man.
I thought he...
I thought that surely he was just
a crackpot, a kook, a madman.
A madman.
But yet...
Here, I find myself in 1934.
Some little town in France, I guess it is.
Ah, whistle while you work, monsieur.
I spill the wine in my forehead
all over my lady's lap
and all over your forehead.
What is that in your forehead?
Oh, what?
Oh, my God.
It's a little clock.
Ah, a bigger mess.
This is wonderful.
Wait a minute.
Let me look at this mirror over here.
The clock is...
It looks...
Why does it...
No, it looks right in the mirror,
which means it must be installed in my head
backwards so that it will look right in a mirror.
What have they done?
What did Bob do to me?
Bob did nothing to you, my friend.
He put this stupid clock into my forehead.
Just relax, monsieur.
Everyone has this stupid clock in their forehead.
What kind of a...
What?
What kind of insurance?
It's supposed to be a show!
It's not a show.
Miss, I am afraid you have used up your entire virtual moment.
Please get out of the...
Bob was like a pornographer on the internet.
And he said, go over there and push the button.
Next!
And I pushed the button and then...
Next, monsieur.
I'm sorry.
Your virtual moment is over.
No!
Leg-gator bend over that trapeze.
Flippin' and flappin' it in the air like a dark-headed Cochise woman.
Yes, uh...
No, I think, uh...
Wait.
There's the ellipse.
It's come back again.
Yes.
And now my forehead is back to its usual shape and size.
And so is yours out there.
Everything has resumed to normal.
Ah, feels better, doesn't it?
It's slack.
Strap ourselves back in.
That's what we call slack.
That's the problem when you unbuckle your...
Just let your...
Unbuckle your...
Seatbelt.
Forehead cave right in.
Just deflate, baby.
What would be better than...
You've been tight.
You've been inflated.
You rose earlier.
Now it's time to just flop, baby.
Just...
Let it all out.
Every brain cell, let it melt, melt, melt down into a little puddle of gray matter soup.
Gray matter soup.
Bend over.
Bend over, human, and let us help.
And get ready for cultural warfare.
We're coming to your town.
Jesus is coming to your town.
We're the colonial purpose.
Get down on your knees and cry.
We're just here to help.
Praise Jesus.
And now...
And to help you better, we must destroy you.
To save the town, we had to destroy it.
To save democracy, we had to destroy it.
To save the world, we must destroy it.
Destroy!
One, two, destroy!
And die.
Hey, man, why don't you save the world?
Why don't you save me a little piece, you know?
And then you can, like, blow up the rest and let me have some fun.
To carve up...
A world.
To carve a worm.
To carve a worm as neatly as one might carve a stick of boater.
To carve up a world between the corporations.
Which means between my friends.
And my friends' friends.
And here they are at the Monaco Parlor Ballroom.
This is a very exclusive place.
There's this builder.
Inhabited and frequented by...
Only the one percent of the one percent.
There's Mrs. Rockefeller.
Oh, there's Mr. J.
Oh, look, his skin cancer's much better now.
Look, there's Mr. Morgan.
He's getting on in years.
Yeah, he's still got that terrible club foot, though.
But he'll be fine.
He's got more money than I need.
Oh, there's the Anheuser-Busch's.
I think we have one of the business underneath the Bushes.
There he is.
He's by the curtain.
He's hiding in the Anheuser-Busch.
Sir.
Don't let him...
Get out of the way!
I get tired of people telling me that they're tripping all the time when it's so obvious.
Their faces have changed.
Like, blue and red things are coming out.
You know, wearing green.
Yeah, and one eye is dribbling down the side of their face.
And they've got this kind of...
Ripping.
My clothing is all...
And they're giggling.
It's cute.
You can tell they're high on something.
You know, the wall behind them is kind of, like, melting.
Yeah.
And they...
All the blacklight posters around them are fountaining.
And, yeah.
And very disturbing to the environment.
Try and get them in your car and have the windshield start melting and have the radio
playing.
It looks like toothpaste is coming out of the radio.
Man, you want to throw them right out of your car and they still laugh as they roll down
the freeway.
It seemed like everybody I looked at was tripping because they were all just melting.
And they're...
You know, they put on this music that tasted like ice cream.
The air was tripping.
Hey, man.
Um.
One of the crackers.
Is that what you...
Is that what you called them?
I thought it was...
Okay.
Hey, man.
Am I still sweating?
Hey.
Hey, I heard...
No, you're in New York, man.
You're in the Greenwich Village.
I heard that you had...
I heard that you had shrooms.
W-w-w-w-w-w-wanted a pound of flesh.
They wanted that which makes you alive.
They wanted your soul.
That's what they do want.
They want a piece.
Could you...
Could you make some coffee for us, man?
We've been walking out in the rain.
It's cold, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Sit down.
Sure.
When'd you get up?
Um, I don't know.
It was like...
I think it was yesterday, but...
This one kid died.
I think he died.
Um...
They found him in the woods.
Well, yeah.
That's where we found him first.
Down by the lake.
Oh, man.
Yeah, man.
He was, uh...
Checking out...
He almost got ran over by a...
A pontoon boat.
Looking from...
He came to study consciousness.
Yeah, he wanted to...
But he ended up...
...beating inside your...
With his pants around his ankles down by the lake.
With the...
Freezing at dawn.
I had...
Wondering what had happened.
Stop that!
Is there...
We heard this really, really, really bad.
Now, did you ever, uh, play Hoppin' John or Magic Footy when you were a young lad or any of those other...
Or...
Impale your head into...
Into the telephone pole spike?
We used to...
Well...
We used to play, uh...
Uh...
Bash the cat to death with your forehead.
But you had to use an actual little baby child.
You couldn't use a cat because that would be unhuman.
No, of course we used cats.
We'd nail them to the post.
Oh, man.
In the center of town.
And then the young men would...
Would vie to beat the cat to death with their heads.
The cat was nailed to the post.
You know...
But still alive.
And, you know, it was difficult because there's...
It's like...
This scratch...
You're trying to scratch your eye.
Right.
They don't want that to happen.
Of course.
And you've got to bash it to death with your head without injuring yourself on the nails
that are holding the cat on the post.
Or the...
Or the cat's claws.
Teeth, too.
Yeah.
What I just described actually was...
It's still...
Of course, that's what we do at Subgenius Shows, but...
And campouts.
But that was commonly done all over Europe in the Middle Ages.
Well, did you...
That was a common...
That's what our civilized ancestors did.
Think about it.
Civilized ancestors.
Even Europe.
Yeah, think about it.
I did.
I did not believe.
Enough genes to go wrong.
I do not believe.
Of any...
If one...
The lads would go out and do...
Nail the cat to a post.
Did you...
Did you ever, like, go to, say, for instance, to, you know, one of the outpatient things
at a hospital, and there's, like, maybe an elderly World War II or Korean vet there in
a wheelchair with one of those...
Breeder-type things on.
And what you do is...
You just come up to him.
He says...
You start talking to him, like, maybe you want to talk about the big one.
Kiss me.
You know?
And you sit down on his lap, which is kind of painful, even though the legs are pretty
well gone, you know, and they just feel like little stumps and stuff.
You sit right on his lap and put your arm around and start talking to him like he's
Santa Claus, only you're real drunk and, like, 40 years old.
And I tell you, man, this...
What?
Well, it's just great fun.
I don't know.
I find my fun where I pick some cheeses at a bus station.
You know, like, a lot of people in the parking lot of a mall.
Come on, man.
Haven't you ever goofed on your elders?
Self-amusing personality, or S.A.P., really does not require fancy toys, cars, stereos,
DVD players.
Nay.
It's the ultimate performance art.
The true S.A.P. can enjoy the loftiest heights of sublime, aesthetic entertainment just by
by looking at the dirt under its fingernails.
And they can also enjoy gastrointestinal intercourse
at the same time if they're shaving right.
Just feeling the bubbles in their own intestines
can be a form of slack
for the truly aware man or woman.
Nourishment.
Up.
And up.
Uh-oh.
Look, man.
He's opening up his escali
and you can't actually see a brain.
That's what happens when you turn to the left too quickly.
It's a whole other scene now.
Yeah, man, I'm too sure.
Well, at least we got out of that one, though.
You don't want to...
I really hate when this happens.
You don't want to swerve, man.
You don't want to, you know,
cause any covenant errors, if you know what I'm saying.
Are we even still on the road, man?
I can't even...
You call this a road?
I mean, you better slow down.
I can't see anything.
Hey, man, nobody's going nowhere.
Calm down.
Look, look, see?
Anything going by, it's in your mind, man.
This is an illusion, man, created by the windshield frost.
I think I've got caffeine poisoning, man.
No, no, no, that's...
I'm seeing weird fringing around me.
That's the tip of your skull.
The edge of my vision.
This car, we shouldn't be...
Shouldn't the road be bumped?
Where is the road?
Are we even on the road?
Jesus God Almighty, wet your pants.
I can't even tell if we're moving.
What's that voice?
Dave DeLuca.
I think I know who you are.
Dave DeLuca?
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I think I don't...
Are you there?
I'm not really here.
Buh, buh, buh, ah, ah, buh.
It's luminous blue.
It's...
What is the next great frontier, Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
The next great frontier is the frontier of the human mind.
Delineated and demarcated, sans frontiers, but only its only limited image...
We've been there, done that.
Imagination.
And...
Okay, all right, then I'll just forget about it.
Can I get...
The mind has been completely mapped and explored.
The mind is still a vast frontier where very few have ever truly tried.
Your mind, maybe.
The mind is still a place filled with cavernous muscles and tiny little tissues
which no one can reach except for their own share of bones.
The human or normal mind has been completely worked out by marketing companies
and conspiracy medical science.
The last hundred...
The last hundred years, they've had it down, down, down.
Don't you believe what the ancient Rishis have told us?
That by properly using our minds, we can even fly as if gossamer on wings of felt?
Is that what the ancient Rishis told you?
Not the Rishis, Monk.
It's the Rishis of ancient India.
You gotta lose your tish in order to fly.
Anybody who finds himself that far off the ground without knowing why loses their tish.
And that's a truism and a falsehood.
Tish, tish, tish, boys.
Fish, fish, fish.
That's the real lie.
Good God!
The prediction came true!
Now, what's that?
It's Bob Pipe!
It's a young, hipster teenager girl with a Bob Pipe in her mouth
and a broomstick inserted just the way Bob predicted would be the new fad of the...
Now, speaking of things that come and go, speaking of fads,
is that a real broomstick or is that what...
When you see a broomstick where it shouldn't ought to be,
whether it's...
Whether it be inserted by New York Police Department or...
or Bob Dobbs himself, friends,
you know the end times are coming.
And so are a lot of gross perverts out there,
of which I am not that kind myself.
Nay, brother.
And I only look at these things.
Can I get a witness to...
You gotta know the enemy!
You gotta know your enemy!
And I get a witness, brothers.
I...
But seriously, you know, if we look at...
at prophecy, like, uh, as many do,
the Weekly World News there at the checkout line,
as we thumb through Revelation X,
the book of the subgenius, we...
Using our second or third horsekin thumb...
We're entering a glorious new age,
a new era of diseases,
of volcanic eruptions...
Praise diseases.
...that decimate entire states.
Praise eruptions.
Earthquakes.
Uh, incredible man-made disasters
of gigantic stockpiles of nerve gases
released into the atmosphere...
...and confused...
...flowing hither and yon.
...all flapping amongst the small union children
as they gathered by the gates to sing songs...
The madness of the Middle Ages will pale in comparison
to the marvelous, futuristic new age that's coming.
...scarier than it is now.
We know that you, the listener,
are interested in the future.
Or you wouldn't be listening to this show.
You who are hearing my voice now,
those of you who live into the new age,
will see such wonders as rubber cities.
Gigantic dominoes the size of skyscrapers,
all set to go off and fall at once on July 5th, 2001.
...at Brushwood Campground in Sherman, New York.
Devices are all dying, master.
All is in order now.
You see?
One such wonders as glass lipstick.
Growth books.
We like the glass lipstick.
Sin pills.
I have taken many, master.
What shall I do now?
Other miracles of science,
such as the robotic butt puffler.
The eye condenser, the amazing eye condenser,
takes what you see or what you have seen
and procreates into a small proclivitis package.
It can be owned by a member of your family unit
now for a limited time, but not in the neutral space.
These are completely designed for a modern you today
in the neutral space.
If you care, or if you dare, just step into the box,
reach your hand out, the influence will go on and on.
Are you ready for this future?
Is this really the future that you want?
This is food for thought, ladies and gentlemen.
And until next week,
the box is doxed.
You can keep your hat on tight.
Don't dare.
You're dark to the wind.
You're deep to it.
And you're sagging the saddle.
Think about it.
That's how we got the red nose.
If everything is lost, it's me.
Then he'd pick you up, because you were really small.
He'd pick you up, and he'd whirl you around his head
around and around and around over and over and over again.
Remember that?
But neither one of you make any sense.
Because, yeah, I mean, I think that's the same.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
And this illustration of 10-dimensional string theory...
I would have loved to have heard what that said.
I would have liked to get in there.
Well, that's why you got to do that.
I'll be featured in the test tomorrow.
And you're like, listen to it later.
And analyze it.
In four dimensions?
And like, yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
One guy on one side, and another guy on the other side.
But you can get a degree on what Dave says in the background on these shows.
There is a degree offered now?
It's like really complex fractal mathematics or something, though.
Well, combined with history.
Because the strands just keep branching off.
It's like the James Joyce form of assembly instructions.
Well, strands...
Very simply put...
Strands after strands.
Do your eyeballs roll in the back of your head?
Strand after strand.
After strand.
Travel to any part of the universe without moving.
Without moving.
In a slowly undulating fashion illuminating...
They are standing still, about ready to drive home a balloon head.
And the sub-lives stride up.
You and the car are static, but the wheels are rolling the world under your sarcophagus.
I can hear the snow, Sirius.
I can hear them all.
Just as you suspected.
That's how it really works.
The dark!
I can hear the dark now.
Yes, my friend.
But who is holding the steering wheel of the car?
I don't know.
Go into the void, kids.
It's time to go into the void.
I will step in first.
I've been bad tonight.
I want to confess my badness.
I will go bye-bye for a squib.
What are your sins?
Well, I was controlling and dominating and selfish and piggy.
Oh, no.
No, I wanted to hear what you were saying.
You were saying that you were a selfish and piggy.
I didn't know.
And nobody would shut up and not...
We didn't know.
Well, we got to go, though.
When you die, you shut up like hell.
Okay, starting again from the very beginning.
Don't shut up yet.
Okay.
You're still entertaining everything.
Just start the whole thing from the beginning, from right before I came in.
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind and your sack in the saddle.
Well, we're back here at the annual George Bush Airplay Balloon Headed Shoot Show.
This is just a practice run.
This wasn't on the air.
Balloon Headed Shoot Show.
Well, we can edit it all.
Okay, so this is like...
That was take one.
Take two.
I'm Ken Smart.
I came on the air.
All right, guys.
We'll do this again.
Let's do it all again.
Merry Christmas.
Happy Christmas.
Have a good holiday.
Happy Chinookish.
Happy X-est month.
What's the other...