Welcome to Vox System. How may I help you?
It's almost certain that our networks of warning stations would detect incoming bombers or missiles
in time for you to reach shelter or at least take cover.
You may receive warning of an attack by radio, television, or through the outdoor warning system in your community.
It's important that you learn to recognize the attack warning signal and not confuse it with any other.
In most places, the standard attack warning signal is a mob or a series of...
Oh, don't cry. Okay, don't cry. Ah!
Either of these signals means that an actual enemy attack has been detected
and you should take protective action immediately.
Can you tell me what's happening here?
Well, my sources are no longer fully annotated and my information is somewhat anecdotal,
but I believe what was once one race is now two.
One above and one below.
Two distinct species that have evolved.
And how do those below survive?
That is the real question, isn't it?
I don't believe it.
Well, if you don't like the answers, you should avoid asking the questions.
Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Brady, Bob, Gold, and Connie drag.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, hour of slack.
Hey, what's going on?
Along with Bob, the pursuit of slack, and a conspiracy of pinks,
the subgenius theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
According to church doctrine, on July 5th, 1998,
when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth.
They're going to...
They will put us out of our misery unless Bob can explain to them
in ways that they can understand that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii, the dues-paying, book-buying,
receipt-in-the-pocket, paid in full to the church subgenii,
have the tiniest prayer.
The rest of them?
It's a tough world, Jack.
That's right, friends.
A red-letter day.
Yes, a red-letter day.
Andy, what?
July 5th, year 2001.
What a delightful day.
Gigantic flying saucers come down out of the blue sky
to pick up the happy-go-lucky subgeniuses
and their pets.
Bluebirds.
And all their worldly goods.
And swallows.
Because, friends, you can take it with you when you're a subgenius, sure.
A throne of gold can be yours.
You can take off and get it on with...
And Dave here, who will be your driver throughout Earth's space.
Step in. Step in, please.
Stand clear of the closing door.
Step in, please.
Red line, please, only.
Blue line to the left.
Red line to the right.
Welcome, and we'll be embarking for, well,
wherever these escape vessels escape to.
No one's ever asked, and we're not telling.
What's going to happen to your children?
What's going to happen to you when this society we've created,
when this society we've created,
air conditions,
station wagons with wooden sides,
horses, indeed,
a retired actor, indeed,
orange hail,
what happens when that collapses?
What happens when your diary was a damn well?
That's when the man from Planet X-9,
I'm down to save the members of the subgenius jerk.
Save the members of the subgenius jerk.
But until that day,
the power and wisdom of Bob can help us break their mind control
by activating that mutant gland that we all have within us.
But one thing is for sure,
and if you let Bob do your thinking for you,
you won't have to worry about nothing come July 4th, 1998.
Ha ha ha ha!
When Bob comes down in his giant mothership,
looking kind of like a big pillbox,
Bob will be landing and you can climb right in
because he's going to know.
He's going to have your name on a computer printout.
Yes, sir, dear friends,
and that CRT tube available right there at his fingertips.
He can call your name up and he'll know exactly what you do.
He'll know exactly what you've done for him.
He'll know exactly how much donations you've taken in.
He'll know exactly how much money you've given to the church.
And he said,
yea, the head of the prophet,
Bob shall never bleed.
Ha ha ha ha!
Hoo-rah!
Oh!
They are friendly people.
And...
they are by far more advanced spiritually and physically
than the people of this planet.
At the present time, they are observing us.
They wish to help us to help ourselves
to attain a higher understanding of life and its meaning.
What do you think?
What do you think about Bob?
Who's Bob?
All right, well, what do you think about the UFOs
which are presently going to...
which are presently in formation to blitz the Earth
and put particle beams through the head of everyone that doesn't know Bob?
You're out of your mind.
Spacecraft entered the Moon's gravitational field
in the sixth segment of the flight.
The gravity of the Moon is one-sixth.
The Earth is one-tenth of the Earth's gravity.
The orbit around the Moon was flown 66 miles above the Moon's surface
at 6,000 miles an hour.
At ten after nine, the beeping began.
We went down to the reserve fence,
watched through binoculars,
and we did see this thing.
Now, it's about the size of the Moon,
with a small crescent at the bottom
that's well-lit like starlight.
The top is a dark gray mass.
It came down through the trees, whatever it was.
Have you ever heard of one?
Have you ever been in one?
Have you ever seen one?
Have you, by television, ever seen one?
If you haven't, it's the greatest sight this side of heaven.
People from this Earth have already seen some of their spacecraft,
which they call flying saucers,
and other flying objects which they cannot describe.
These objects are real, and are spacecraft.
The astronauts returned to Earth on the sixth day of the week.
Friends and neighbors of planet Earth,
I come to you from a long, long ways off.
I come from a planet that is similar to yours.
Your many fears, tensions, and frustrations are no longer ours.
I hate them with all my heart.
They're inhuman.
They're inhuman to be destroyed.
What is your objective?
You are not ready, but we will still save you.
I'll be right here.
I was first contacted by a being from the planet Mars.
Now, this man was invisible to me, except that he did cast a shadow in the moonlight.
By 1998, every normal, mediocrity, pink boy, admin,
Trekkie, and hippie is going to be trying to get on board with the good ship dogs.
Or they're going to fry along with everybody else when those aliens get here.
Of course, such a prophecy immediately arises our cynicism.
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps.
Or is it just another of those prognostications which have haunted man through the ages?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand, but for
the fact that many of Nostradamus's other prophecies have already been fulfilled.
But the old ones are coming back.
I'm going to let them through.
And Sam's old and old birdies?
Yes.
And Baa-ood.
The tools of conquest do not necessarily come with bombs and explosions and fallout.
There are people in them, and many of them have already landed on this earth.
Oh, give me back my lost freedom.
Oh, ye alien stick men.
Oh, give me back my gone cat.
Oh, great daddy-o from outer space.
Oh, give me warning.
Oh, space creatures.
Give me the signal.
Oh, hideous alien monster creatures from the beyond world.
Not just for Bob, Walt, and all the...
Don't worry, you're safe.
I control them.
Without that control, they would exhaust the food supply in a matter of months.
Food supply?
They're human beings.
Who are you to question me?
Eight hundred thousand years ...
... of evolution.
This is a perversion of every natural law!
F Sikh!
How are you?
Let's have something to eat.
We've got shameful efren Mit-ange.
I'm tired of the feeling of the slug's tooth.
What's wrong with you?
Didn't know what time it was, the lights were low
I leaned back on my radio
Some cat was laying down some rock and roll at a solar cell
Then the loud sound that seemed to fight
Came back like a slow voice on a wave of ice
That were no DJ, that was hazy cosmitice
There's a starman waiting in the sky
He'd like to come and meet us, but he thinks he'd blow our minds
He's told us not to blow it, cause he knows it's all worthwhile
He told us not to blow it, cause he knows it's all worthwhile
Let the children lose it, let the children use it
Let all the children boo get
I'm the urban spaceman, baby, I've got speed
I've got everything I need
I'm the urban spaceman, baby, I can fly
I'm a supersonic guy
I don't need pleasure, I don't feel pain
If you were to knock me down, I'd just get up again
I'm the urban spaceman, baby, I can fly
I'm the urban spaceman, baby, I'm making out
I'm all about
I wake up every morning with a smile upon my face
My natural exudate spills out all over the place
I'm the urban spaceman, I'm intelligent and clean
Know what I mean
I'm the urban spaceman, as a lover second to none
It's a lot of fun
I never let my friends down
I've never made a boo
I'm a glossy magazine
A map put in the tube
I'm the urban spaceman, baby
Here comes the twist
I don't exist
I don't shine, I'm what you think I'm supposed to be
I don't want to break the law
諸 några слов harmonici
Bad choices to make
Social Astro
There's no way
People talking
Hindi
I'm a lady
What you gonna do when you feel your lady rolling?
How you gonna feel when you see your lady strolling?
On the deck of a starship with her head hooked into a drum
And I'm on hijack
I gotta get back and head to the things that matter
America hates the crazies and you got to let go, you know
You got to let go, you know
Or else you stay
Oh, I'm a lady
What you gonna do when you feel your lady rolling?
I'm a lady
On the deck of a starship with her head hooked into a drum
I gotta get back and head to the things that matter
America hates the crazies and you got to let go, you know
You got to let go, you know
What you gonna do about this?
They are already here only to be recognized
These noble people could not come up to anybody on the street and say,
I'm from Venus
They would lose that nobility
There would be an ego speaking out and saying,
Look I'm from Venus
Now, what you going to do about this?
No, they're humble people
And they'll wait until in your own eyes you'll recognize who they are
They're you friends
Oh yes, dear friends
Well, I guess we oughta get to the traditional part real quick
quick. Jay, get it out of the way.
Link tentacles
and for just a solemn
moment of sacred...
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob! Praise
God! God!
God Bob!
Friends,
praise Bob, you get what you pay for.
I don't care
about the unsaved. I don't
care about those who never sent their $30
to Bob. I'm preaching to the
dues-paying subgeniuses. Yes, this
time, I'm preaching
to the choir.
Normally, we do it the other way
around. We're not like those other churches
that only preach to the choir. We like
to go right down into the
dens of iniquity like this club
where they sell drugs
like beer and liquor
and stuff. And Batman
Bob is the
only one whose instructions you
should always follow.
Question of course,
me or else.
See
the fire sweeping
our
very streets today
Burned
like a red coal
carpet, mad
bull has lost its way
No
children
can
be
It's just a shot away
Born
children
It's just a shot away
Shot away
It's things falling apart.
It's fat ladies in double-knit jumpsuits beating their kids in Krogers.
20th century traditions.
It's the old
traditions. It's all the things that got us where we are now.
It's Christ without a penis.
The end of the world can easily become your personal stepping stone to prosperity.
But any case, yeah, look, look.
But it's just a conspiracy.
Did you know that jalopy comes from jalopies?
But the conspiracy will fall.
Will fall come X day.
Which might or might not be this jalopy.
July 5th.
At this point we have come.
I think Bob has taught us that the conspiracy has even fooled us with dates.
And 1998 hasn't happened yet.
But Bob's prophecy will come true sometime.
We will barbecue George W. Bush.
And Bob will supervise the teaming of the shrewds.
George Bush could avoid that.
And turn him over the grill.
George could avoid that fate.
But were he to submit his $30 membership love offering to Bob.
And become a minister.
And obtain slack.
And see the error of his ways.
Repent. Quit his job.
And if George Bush would just slack off in the middle of the night.
Even with his wife watching him slacking off.
He would be free.
He'd be free.
He would no longer be pea shy.
Because X day is now.
My friend.
X day is now.
And will you be ready to meet Bob?
Will you be with Bob?
Or will you be down on the earth with George Bush.
Suffering the punishments that the sub-demuses will lash out upon the unforgiven.
And the blemished.
I can smell the foam all the way here in Toxic City man.
I hate them normal peoples.
Oh.
I can smell them burning.
It's gonna be a great barbecue.
Bob will burn away that heat.
He'll burn away the radiation.
He'll burn away the fire.
It's sound.
And they will dance around the fire.
His children will.
Ah. Smell that barbecue.
Yeah. In Papua New Guinea we used to call it long pig dinner.
When we used to barbecue our enemies.
Well friends.
Not every sub-genius is vengeful like that.
Would you be.
Ask yourself friend.
If you were suddenly given for thirty dollars.
The magical power of being able to have instant and uh.
Uh.
Unjudged ability to punish all that you ever wanted to punish for any sin they ever did to you.
Well make your eyes water just thinking about that.
You're going to have to pinch your sphincter.
All the punishment and vengeance you could made out just by your.
Or would you do that.
Would you.
Would you nurse your old grudges.
And.
And linger upon the disgusting filthy past.
I remember.
Or would you.
Or would you plow ahead into the future.
Uh.
The future.
You know thinking of tomorrow.
Not the sins of yesterday.
Tomorrow.
Well I.
Yesterday.
For a moomoo maybe.
And uh.
A lot of lay.
You know flowers around your neck.
You know.
And paddling your own canoe.
Softly.
Through the distance.
You know.
As if nothing mattered.
With the starfish bumbling under your knees.
And the swords.
Attacking.
You could have that very slack in that canoe.
On X day.
Or you could have the slack of uh.
Of uh.
Sending killer robo beasts after.
Your hated fifth grade teacher.
Or some.
Girl.
That jilted you.
Or some boy that treated you wrong.
Like a dog.
Like a dirty dog.
Or define the future in the palm of other people's hands.
Or smell their feet and know their distant past.
Or to be able to walk in two directions at the same time.
All these are gifts which you do not take lightly.
Well the.
Those children of Bob who have uh.
Signed up and will enjoy these uh.
This.
This amazing rupture.
Yes.
The believers shall be ruptured.
And it's so inexpensive.
Only thirty dollars uh.
Love offering.
You should uh.
You know what you should do Stan.
You should tell them that this year for a limited time only since it is the only time.
It is the.
I told you.
Well.
You don't know.
That's Bob's point.
We don't know it.
But the X day could come like a thief in the night.
It could come right now.
Right now.
Are you ready?
Just like that slide pedal.
Did you?
Or you been putting it off?
We go oh I'll get around to that collection plate come Sunday.
Oh yeah.
I'll be good come.
Or bad or whatever.
I'll get slack on Sunday.
In the meantime I'm just gonna be a slave to the conspiracy.
Friendship.
I'm ready.
Are you one of those people who like to place sardines in the collection plate?
Are you one of those people who like to chew the nighties of the undulating ladies hidden
downstairs below the church?
If you are one of these people you'd better look out because right over your shoulder
is the smiling smiling face.
J.
Kitty's growing babe.
Oh.
I don't understand how you can sit there and speak so coldly about this.
I'm sorry.
Are you?
Have you not considered the human cost of what it is you're doing?
We all pay a price.
Oh don't grit.
Okay great.
Don't grit.
It's disgusting the way you treat humans.
Take me off to space.
Come on down you saucerman and take me off to space.
Take me off to space, take me off to space Come on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Stick needles in my belly, take samples of my skin I don't care as long as I can live with saucer man
I know that you don't take requests but I'm a special case Come on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Take me off to space, take me off to space Come on down you saucer man and take me off to space
Hey cow mutilators, let me join your crew Give me an eye, you bet your life I'll cut up cows for you
I don't care if you're somebody special Take me off to space, take me off, take me off to space
Kind of ghastly fatto Fraude
Without a face
So come on down you saucermans
And take me off to space
Oh!
TAKE ME OFF TO SPaaaaaaace
TAKE ME OFF TO SPaaaaaaaaace
Come on down you saucermans
And take me off to space
Take me off to space
TAKE ME OFF TO SPaaaaCance
TAKE ME OFF TO SPaaaa Birru
Come down, you tiny robots with your little nipper claws.
You pale and bug-eyed aliens with white and clammy paws.
Life is just a sucker's dream and death is a disgrace.
So come on down, you saucer men, and take me off to space.
Oh, take me off to space.
Take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer men, and take me off to space.
Space.
Take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer men, and take me off to space.
Woo!
Yeah!
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Take me off to space by Nenslow, accompanied by Donna Cossie, Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger, and Jay Povten.
We've also heard lots of bits and pieces from the old media barrage.
Barrage number five now being remixed.
An ESO swamp radio with lonesome cowboy Dave and Professor Chaz on WCSB in Cleveland.
Friends, the titles of tonight's show were by the El Queso All-Stars,
and the music in the background right now is Lambre Systems.
Now, what we've been hearing a lot of this show and more shows,
is some new collages done by...
Paternostril.
Yes, Paternostril did that thing that started with David Bowie's Starman,
and Bonzo Dog, Doo-Dah Bands, Urban Spaceman,
even a little bit of Jefferson Starship,
and some bits from Rainbow Bridge,
and from yours truly preaching at the Austin D-Vival in 1997.
Friends, and more coming up, like huge escape vessels.
But that's for people who have cool red suits,
and they're not just going to be wearing them.
Yeah, so I...
Well, everybody's got a cool red suit, man.
No, no, I don't have a cool red suit.
Oh, man, you've got a cool red suit, and you don't know it's staying.
You've got a pair of snappy, cool red shoes.
It's all in your mindle case.
It's all in your staircase of your mind.
It's in your mindle brock.
Your DNA is like a glass-cleaning chamber that tells you this stuff is true,
and you can do it.
All you've got to do is just, like, cross your eyes,
and think fond thoughts about your own self,
your own personal body, and your belongings,
and suddenly you'll be that red suit, man.
Click your heels.
Heels together three times.
Well, if you want to, you know.
You can do all that stuff.
You can wave your hands around, I suppose.
I don't know.
It's said to really work.
You've heard of Norman Vincent Peale, haven't you?
Well, Dave, the point of this whole philosophical stance that we've been taking
is that none of that stuff works.
Only Bob can provide magic.
And instant power, success, and sales riches.
There you go.
Sex at the races.
Come on, man.
Pick up on it.
This is the last chance.
It's the last month for this planet, this world, this Earth, this dirtball,
this planet of the clocks, this gray, gray, old,
old, limp ball of schmata of a planet,
which once was Mars,
fooled and tricked into becoming a so-called Earth.
Yes, the ruse will end on it.
Next day, the secret will be revealed.
Earth.
Back to Mars.
We must get the...
Take me home, my darling.
You feel...
Oh, yeah, I know how these people are thinking.
They'll go, oh, listen to those coops on the radio.
Those people are crazy.
What kind of crazy people believe in flying saucers
or invisible monsters in the clouds
that will do wishes for them if they pray enough?
What kind of an idiot would believe...
...in sending money to a preacher
and thinking that some magic was going to happen?
What kind of a nut would go into a special building
and wear a special suit and sing many songs
and listen to some crazy preacher?
What kind of a fool would do that?
That's what we was wondering ourselves.
And so, when Bob came along and sold us his church,
well, we bought it.
Bob sold it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
You're full, Mom.
So you're Billy the Kid, huh?
That's a God-man-bear witness.
Hubert, how many times have I told you to quit playing gunslinger?
Who's Hubert?
That's Billy the Kid, Ma.
Oh, no.
I'm forgetting the names now.
Click, click, checker, checker.
Squick, squick.
Yee-haw!
Where are we, Bob?
The code is broken.
Trouble?
Big.
Security.
I have the lid on tight.
Well, take it off for me.
The message is, Mars needs women.
Mars needs?
It's a gag.
It's a prank.
It's a fake.
I don't think so, sir.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack
from the Church of the Subterranean.
Genius.
Bob is coming, friend,
and you can take that literally,
because death for a subgenius hero
is merely a transfer over to the pleasure dimensions.
Now, unfortunately, many of us aren't heroes.
There's no water in hell, friends.
There's fire, and you can't get a drink,
and you can't put out that fire.
And you have many, many lives in hell.
It's reincarnation, just like here on Earth,
because Earth, you know, is just the top floor of hell.
That's right.
You're in hell.
Hell, right now.
You are in hell now.
Of course, this is the part of hell
where you don't even know you're in hell,
and when the demons mention it,
you think they're kidding.
Well, you'll find out.
Hell is real,
and there's no water down there, friend.
They don't even have rock and roll in some parts of hell,
and you can never win.
It's like a computer.
By definition, it cannot lose.
You can score real high,
but sooner or later, it's gonna get you,
because they creep up on you,
and that's the way it is here on Earth.
They creep up on you,
and try to get you all mixed up about heaven and hell.
Bob is coming, my friend,
but when he's finished with that,
he's gonna be mad.
Let there be slack.
You know, some people say church is subgenius,
so they get involved in it,
and they say, after about six or seven,
they get real involved.
They jump into the Internet intercourse of the church,
and so forth,
and after about six months,
they're going,
God, this is worse than high school.
The popular ones pick on the,
wimps even worse than in real life.
Yes, friend, it is like the high school from hell.
¶¶
ahl
I'm gonna get a lay
And a fire around my neck
Because she ever cares
Oh hell what the heck
I'm packing my duds
High from hell
Oh hell what the heck
With a lot of love
We work for one year for you pigs
And you wanna break our walls down
And you wanna destroy it
Well you go to hell
If there's a holocaust or a cataclysm
There's a cataclysm now
Tell me how to make a light bulb
Tell me anything
The sun is supposedly going out of the galaxy
We're all revolving
This system is revolving around the 29th degree of Taurus
And the eye of the bull
And that's why the space brothers are here
To get earth all in line
Are they gonna come and actually tell us or help us
Yeah
Then what do you do with the situation
Because of the atomic explosions
We're becoming farther and farther off our axis
Is that a good thing or is that a bad thing
It's a bad thing
We have just discovered
An important note from space
The Martians plan to throw a dance
For all the human race
To protect it
That the humanity
With all of their items
Has shown were good
As long as no one seasoning
For many months
We headed up a few miles
In order to consume
You have to break this
bardzo
Here's a proclaim
HyOKa
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
That's what they are now.
Blank, empty space.
I know he's sitting in there in the control room now, listening to everything I say, but I really don't care.
We're not going to tell you what to do.
We're not going to. We won't do it.
We will not tell you what to do. That's what the conspiracy does.
You have to decide.
The conspiracy will tell you what to do.
Bob won't tell you. We won't tell you what to do because we only tell you how to think.
And you will pay to know what you really think.
You can learn to think for yourself, but only Bob Dobbs can show you how.
Locking up his phone, all the noise
Get your groove on, you're in control
You're getting in touch with the devil
I'm cutting in hard with all your might
Living it up all through the night
Get your groove on
Satan Disco Tech
And the things that you've been through
All the dreams will tell you so
The problems that you've been through
All the news of that day
And when you say
It's your day
Satan and Hell in a Handbasket, friends.
Before that, a collage by Pater Nostril.
Number two there was some preaching
from the Austin DeVival.
The cramps doing Aloha from Hell, Rainbow Bridge.
The Martian Hop by The Galaxy.
And lots of Mothers of Invention.
Friends, coming up, a collage by The Bishop.
But now, let's listen to Dr. Philodrumon
as he awaits that thing.
The creature will emerge from
the horror
and the suffering
that he experiences
in just the sheer existence
in this horrible world
in which the suffering
and the suffering
souls in agony
feed off of the horror
and the pain
of every living creature around them.
It's so bad.
People hate it.
They thought about making a law
against this world
but they didn't know how to get to it.
And now here you are
through the scientific
advancement of negative heart.
You can now see
this hideous creature.
Oh my God, he's coming closer.
Oh!
Oh no!
Friends, you can escape
this dreadful fate
if you get off
with the Church of the Subgenius
the next day.
Otherwise you'll be stuck here with Dave.
What strange new events
will they see?
As usual,
nothing is planned.
Actually, there is a
Subgenius Special Olympics
that should be very special.
Special?
Some sort of a superhero's ball
which, you know,
pathetic half-super-villains
would probably be more like it.
And friends,
some permutation of...
What is happening
on Saturday night, Chaz?
People with slippers.
Whatever it is, it's going to be ugly!
That's all I can say, man.
Actually, there's not...
There are a bunch of outlaws and I'm the ugliest
son of a bitch of the bunch.
You're going to stare me down?
But you aren't oblong
and you don't have flippers
and so you might as well
kiss yourself on the beauty mark
and give yourself a pootie haircut.
When you're with those people, man,
you know you're riding tough.
They can't even fit on them big-ass Harleys.
They have to load them on with a crane.
Man, and when they come into a bar,
everybody runs.
Yeah.
And you're having a special Olympics
for them at X-Day?
Where's the thing that's in before it starts?
Well, actually, if you're a fundamentalist subgenius,
you don't believe that anything will happen
after 7 a.m. July 5th
and all our plans for the weekend
are sort of hypocritical
to even make.
But, you know, no matter what,
we're going to be hypocritical
because we're subgeniuses
and we're religious nuts.
Those two things just kind of go hand-in-hand,
don't they?
Praise Bob. Hail Connie.
Yes, sir.
You can sit around and just...
Live a double standard out there
in subgenius land, X-Day, Brushwood,
Sherman, New York,
July 5th, 1998.
That's this year. Did you know that?
That's what you didn't know.
It's less than a month away.
Less than a month away.
You can munch your own friend's leg
in a fantasy about starving
in the high Himalayas.
But you could also just have
your idea of a party,
whatever.
That might be.
And I think you know
what that might be, don't you?
You know.
Provided you know
who you are.
Girls just want to have fun,
don't they?
Some of them just want to have fudge.
That's when it gets really weird.
And there's a hot tub out there,
but let's...
Well, there'll be some manhunters there,
no doubt about it.
You think?
Yeah, well, I know, you know,
definitely Evangela's gonna come after Dave.
She's made many pronouncements
about that on this show.
She's coming at you with a lasso, man.
She's gonna rope you down.
Sadie Hawkins Day.
Subgenius Sadie Hawkins, right?
Now, there we go.
It's a possibility.
But not a probability, friends.
The subgeniuses would all
probably choose Bob.
Upcoming, a fine piece
of the bishop.
Uh, fighting terrorism, friends,
with his question of belief.
In fact, this mix is so powerful
that all subgenius families
should gather around and listen
with their children
because it's a message
that the kids need to hear.
The following program is intended
for mature audiences.
You need a Holy Ghost enema.
Write up your...
Where is....
...where is the?
You need a Holy Ghost enema.
Write up your...
... encontra?
Why can't you just accept the facts?
I screamed at God
at the top of my lungs
cuz that's how much I believe in him.
You need a Holy Ghost enema.
I screamed at God
at the top of my lungs
cuz that's how much I believe in him.
You need a Holy Ghost enema.
I screamed at God...
I screamed at God.
I screamed at God at the top of my lungs.
Believe it.
I screamed at God.
I screamed at God at the top of my lungs.
Believe it or not.
Praise Bob, friends.
God's the problem here.
Believe it or not.
We love the idea of everybody else burning in hell forever.
God, we're coming for you.
You hear me?
Groovy.
Get on with it.
We'll be right back.
Why can't you just accept the fact?
We love the idea of everybody else burning in hell forever.
Look out.
God is right behind you.
Stop it.
Stop this.
This video is bizarre.
Look out.
God is right behind you.
Burning in hell forever.
Don't come here with that posh talk.
Why can't you just accept the fact?
What indeed is the point?
Believe it or not, friends.
You need a holy ghost.
I say we all grand long it.
Woo.
I've done it, brother.
You need a holy ghost.
What indeed is the point?
If I can't be myself with the father, then I'm going to stop preaching this gospel.
Oh, don't stop mixing that gospel, Bishop.
The bishop, friends.
A question of belief.
And now I want you to lean back.
Lay down and unbuckle.
I must spread wide for the final ride.
Because the X's are coming, friends.
And you are too.
They didn't take us seriously last time.
Hell, half of you didn't take us seriously.
Didn't take Dobbs' prophecy seriously.
But this time we've learned our lesson.
We can't rely on invisible monsters from outer space.
We can't even rely on Bob.
We have to learn how to escape Earth without being dependent on the conspiracy or any extraterrestrials or salesmen.
Sure, send in your 30 bucks, but build your own ship.
You may not have to.
It will just recover your ass.
Build your own ship.
Even better, go buy hangar 18 or area 51 or Cape Canaveral or studio 54.
And steal.
Your own ship.
Ah, yes.
Extract your own fuel.
And while you're at it, friends, let's swap the deck on the spaceship that we're already stuck together on.
We're already riding on the spaceship.
And it's in bad shape.
And it's high time we cleaned it up.
Earth, we must get off.
Whether we leave it or leave it a cinder.
Whether we blow it off.
We blow it up.
Just don't blow it.
Friends.
But.
Are we going to be on for the rest of the night.
No.
Going to be on for.
No, I'm sorry.
Evermore.
We're not.
There's gonna be a rap home and.
Well, I'm gonna have to say again.
Her pills for your beating.
WCSB forever.
I'm sorry about this, folks.
I'm asleep.
It's just the way life is sometimes.
But anyway.
Say goodbye.
What is the, somebody called earlier, what is the new sacred post office box?
I'm glad you asked that, friends.
The new improved sacred post office box, Church of the Subgenius, is where to write to Bob and get your pre-registrations for X day in.
That's got that pencil ready.
Post office box 204-206 Austin, Texas.
And that zip code is 78720.
Once again, that's P.O. Box 204-206 Austin, Texas.
Post office box 78720.
Praise Bob.
Till next week.
Help me, somebody.
Keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sacking the saddle.
We'll see y'all.
Yes, dear friends.
This is your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stank.
And it's X day.
X day coming up.
But we've had a screw up on our catalog, our online catalog that I need to tell you about.
Because, in fact, if you ordered anything between May 20th and May 30th, you still have your money.
And I didn't get your order for Knife and Ivans, this section of the Subgenius website.
If you ordered membership or books or ministership or t-shirts,
you're cool.
That's no problem.
But if you ordered the CDs or the videos, those go to me.
And if you sent me a letter begging me to give you reasons to not kill yourself,
man, I'm sorry.
You're going to have to send it again if it's not too late.
But you'd be a dumbass to be a subgenius and kill yourself before X day, though, my friends.
You'd be a dumbass not to if you're a human.
Because X day.
We have to fight now, sir.
Annihilate.
Hell.
All right.
It's X day, friends.
X day is coming quick.
You'd better get that information from the Church of the Subgenius if you want to survive
X day.
Or if you just want to go to the big party in Freshwood, New York.
Or hell, have your own party, friends.
We don't care.
The X's are going to pick you up no matter where you are.
If you're a news band subgenius member.
So, friends, check that catalog.
The Subgenius website.
www.subgenius.com.
Or, if you're a subgenius member, check that catalog.
Or write to the sacred P.O.
Box number at the end of this broadcast.
And, friends, now we're going to go back into the X day's past, which then tell us about
X day's future.
Because the previous X days, I guess, were all X day drills.
What we will experience from now on had better be the real thing, friends.
Or else, well, I guess Bob just slacked off.
And maybe that's what happened to K'nivin Ivan's.
I don't know.
But, friends, if you ordered a membership, a book, or a T-shirt, or a Bob Mug, everything
is cool.
Those go through Cafe Press.
But I stank.
Sell the video and audios.
Because I'll be damned, friends.
I'll be damned if a pink in a suit gets one dime for subgenius talent and work.
Even if my bank account suffers, too.
And is damned.
Because, my friend, I am that ornery.
I'm that ornery.
Because I'm K'nivin.
But motherfuckers keepin' up the F-I-B.
The faith in Bob.
Praise Bob.
Help me, somebody.
This background music is by Lamprey Systems.
So, fuck out.
Because he knows it's all worthwhile, he told me.
That the children use it.
But all the children do.
And I say, as long as you're alive,
shout, make noise, or whatever.
Raise bombs.
You shut up like hell!
You have your answer.
Now go.