I bring you a warning.
Every one of you listening to my voice, tell the world.
Tell this to everybody wherever they are.
Watch the skies.
New from Dobbs Cove, tasty prairie squid spread.
Salted and unsalted varieties available on the East Coast only.
The radioactive cloud is now over Little Rock.
The craggy shat piercingly.
Get your things out of this house right now before I throw them into the street and you're with them.
Bye, June.
Get out before I...
Yeah!
Oh, my beloved spermulites.
Before destruction overtakes us, we must flee to another planet.
I have consulted the universe.
I have consulted the universal viewmaster and found a tiny distant sphere.
No more than a napturd in the mind of God called Earth.
The intellectual capacity of its inhabitants is so low, we can easily enslave their feeble minds.
But there is another, even easier way to bring these hideous bipeds to their knees.
It is their weakness for a disgusting physical act called sex.
To describe the erotic practices of these sex-ridden morons, at once lewd and ludicrous,
would make even an incorporeal vapour lose its lunge.
And so, I summon into my presence a chosen group of elderly and experienced spermulites.
Come to your big mother, oh creatures of the mist,
ye who will go forth as a vanguard to prepare the way for the rest of us.
Your venerable ears alone are wise enough to hear these vile human practices without alarm.
Your all-knowing minds alone can contemplate the hideous flab of the universe.
Can you emanate or destroy the universal practice of human form without screaming in horror at what you see?
Know ye this, that through all the ages of evolution, the earthlings have failed to reach the stage of auto-reproduction.
Two beings are required to join in repulsive physical union in order to bring forth others of their kind.
Though their wise men are slowly perfecting methods of reproduction which do not require this ridiculous practice,
or the humiliating preliminaries which lead up to it.
You will assume the form and function of one of these beings.
The space is speaking.
stronger, more intelligent, more vital and aggressive creature called woman.
With the power of her sexual allure, she rules over her weakened spineless victim called man.
His pathetic sexual organ rises and swells at her command
and shrivels and wilts when she is drained out its strength.
Man is a slave to this absurd biological reflex.
And when you assume female form, you will have him in your power.
Now take on that form, oh chosen spermalite.
Dwell in female flesh.
Look upon yourselves and tell me what you see.
Women everywhere are having a love affair with Bieber.
Rated PG.
I believe deeply in your taxes.
All my life, I fought our land, water and people.
That's what I'll do in the Senate.
I approve your vote.
I want to be your senator because I want to change things.
And especially the middle class.
We all approve this terrorism.
The federal government might soon be headed to the United States.
Now here, we immerse the eggs into a warm bouillon containing free swimming spermatozoa.
Immersion continues until the eggs are all fertilized.
Ah, and over here, here is where we bottle the alphas and betas.
Are there any questions?
Uh, sir, will you explain Bob?
Bob?
Oh, I like Bob.
You asked that?
But his reputation.
You're heading for trouble.
Now boys, come with me.
Come, a bee gives a golly gosh and better puke your peat on full throttle potent teat.
Elsewise your wants will be wagging down on mammy's hind nanny.
Why can't your peeser pop a squeezer when the gushers are going all normal like?
Got you no geyser sense?
And your sneezing chamber, boy?
Hiced in an empty platter in your bean bag?
Where's your roller balls, eh?
I can't grok me no love grow on this loo-joo moo-joo bad.
You're gonna have to spreech English, Jake.
Get right with your muscle snake, snunk monkey.
Quit spritzin' your plizzerer lessen its snowing white lute juice, baby.
Elsewise your pleatin' bleeder's blowin' hot water.
You go blind or please your neether tryin' not to.
Either way, you're gettin' up on the wrong orbit for this kind of free-kneadin' bleedin' side trade, eh?
Well, won't you go and stand there like your dammy nickel slug or you gonna plus your plimper and righteous hargany, pee-boy?
Got weenie ribbers and your fluter tubes, don't you?
Join gumption's with the true and the see brave.
And pee for Bob, man, and send your jeans.
Buy out the gland owners with what you earned with your skinny peelin' face of pain.
This has been your enunciator. Thank me.
Amen.
Well, fun day.
Thanksgiving
After you, you did it
Went up the river, shoot from my head
Buried a hatchet in your riverbed
Got my car over the cliff, saw myself lying dead
Tortured me while you watched on TV
Sour of darkness, everything's turned gray
Now it's time for all good things to pass away
Ask me why, why, why, we all must go, go, go, go, go, you did it
Now the time has come
My tears run from my eyes
But it seems like there's no running from the lies
My poor heart, my poor heart lays trips on my mind
Love, love, love, love
Sour of darkness
Just before I say goodbye
Like a Teflon cigarette
I chew my cyanide for chlorate
Write down a fake confession
And then send it off to you
Sour of darkness
Everything's turned gray
Now it's time for all good things
To pass away
Ask me why, why, why, we all must go, go, go, go, go, you did it
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, this song introduces a new genre.
It's called Gospel Hell.
It's a new genre in country and western music.
We call it Gosp-Hell.
It's gospel music for people who know they're going to hell anyway.
It's a little thing called Legs of Fire.
Well, I thought I could get away
With Sondra on our wedding day
Preacher Man said, Boy, better put away your song
But I said I don't cotton to no God's county law
But that song was stolen
At least that's what they said
So I wrapped up in asbestos
From my waist up to my head
I wrapped up in asbestos
That I got from Greg's
I only wish I had enough
To cover up my legs
So I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Oh, my head's dry and cool
So's my arms and tool
My torso, even more so
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Well, I was selling heroin
At the elementary school
Preacher Man said, Boy, you know that isn't cool
The good Lord come to me
Said my time was up
When I asked why God
He said because that horse was cut
They were shooting up in the bathroom
Yes, you know it's true
But they were not getting off
And that's why my soul is through
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Oh, my brain ain't in no flame
And my shoulder ain't in pain
But my toes need a hose
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Well, I was stealing cars
For God to try to get in well
But when my judgment came
He said, You'll have to go to hell
It's true I gave my son, he said
To pay for all your sins
But when you brought me that limo chain
Or the door was dented in
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Oh, my head ain't on the line
And my arm is doing fine
But my knees are crying, please
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Well, I was bashing Grandma's head
With a railroad tie
The good Lord come to me
And said, Why did you lie?
When I said, What lie?
God, he said, You must confess
That ain't your grandma's head at all
It's just a bloody mess
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
My legs, my legs, my legs are fire
Say, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
My legs, my legs are fire
But I ain't no liar
God, he said, Why did you lie?
That's New York Hell and Edge.
I'll speak, I'll speak.
I think I
You will die
Die
You go to hell and you die
I have just seen someone I know die in the most hideous, hideous way
Why am I Mr. Pink?
Mr. Pink
Why am I Mr. Pink
Why am I Mr. Pink?
Mr. Pink
P-r nieuwe Meechains will die!!!
Prepare to die
Meech released a horror movie
You must die.
Why am I Mr. Pink?
Prepare to die.
You gotta pray and pray and pray and pray and pray.
Pray when you're feeling low, when the ill winds blow.
Don't forget to pray.
Pray when you go to bed for your daily bread.
You can awake to a beautiful morning.
When you've got troubles, remember this warning.
And pray until judgment day.
Got the devil to pay if you never pray.
Open up the devil's warning page.
That's okay.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, Bob.
You love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll bob you out.
Only if, you know, if he...
There's gonna be so many reverend stangs, Kyle.
There's gonna be more and more and more reverend stangs.
Get rid of me.
How many stangs can there be in a pudge, friends?
We need that money.
Relative to most of my fellow kooks,
and crackpots, I'm...
I was called by possibly divine powers
to be a skeptic.
A disbeliever.
And I know that sounds...
I even have paranormal examples
to back up why there's no such thing.
I actually...
The most vivid one was when I alone couldn't see the UFO.
It's a true story.
Everybody else, and I'll make it very short,
but everybody else in the trailer court,
saw the UFO.
Well, I was there,
and they...
When they asked me what I thought it was,
I had to say,
what the hell are you talking about?
And they all looked at each other like,
this guy must be nuts.
He didn't see the UFO.
Well, I'm not saying that the UFO wasn't there,
because I was really outnumbered.
And I'm sure that that thing that...
I mean, it was a classic UFO sighting
at a trailer court.
What can I say?
In South Dakota.
On an Indian reservation, in fact.
A long time ago.
Classic thing.
But I didn't see the UFO.
So, it's like I was chosen to be a disbeliever.
It's almost like...
Well, in fact, for that matter,
not just the aliens told me,
but God, God Himself.
Yes, God told me not to believe in Him.
I'll go ahead and admit it
for the first time ever here at this stage.
I spoke to God.
Yes?
And, oh, by the way, God, before I forget,
He did mention that you can now,
as of this moment,
you can now do anything you want,
period.
He just...
Even if it hurts somebody else,
go ahead and do it.
That's what God told me.
But, no, He said...
God said to me,
He goes,
Stan, you know, if people...
He said,
I just don't exist the way people think I do.
And if they knew the way I do exist,
they'd...
they'd puke.
He said,
but they...
But, Stan,
they just couldn't possibly understand it
unless...
Well,
hmm...
Nah!
That's what God said.
Now, when I saw that bit of hesitation
and uncertainty on the part of God,
that's kind of disconcerting.
I've been wondering about that ever since.
It's really...
really kind of been...
been worrying me.
And we...
you know, we...
Churches of Genius started in the
South among the Baptists and so forth.
And they were telling us we were going to be...
going to go to hell.
So what else could we do but start our own religion?
And...
and we mock...
we try to mock pretty much all the religions,
including atheism.
Definitely including atheism.
As far as I'm concerned,
those people are the biggest kooks of all
because they're...
they are totally sure.
Well, I'm sorry, man,
but I don't...
I don't know for sure whose aquarium
I might be swimming around in.
You know, to your fish,
you're a cloud
that rains food down on them.
They don't know they're a fish in an aquarium.
I remember sit...
watching Beavis and Butthead with my son.
And Beavis and Butthead were making fun of MTV.
And my son and I were making fun of Beavis and Butthead,
making fun of MTV.
And then we both kind of went...
You know, like...
So...
that's...
that's where...
that's where I stand on the belief thing, man.
I'm from the Church of Bob's Scientists.
Well, actually, Bob Hobbyist.
Or...
But to tell the honest truth,
it's really Bob...
Church of Bob Crackpot.
Bob, Crackpot.
And we deliberately created a net
to catch weirdos in crackpots.
I met my wife that way.
Right here at...
Right here at Brushwood, in fact.
Thanks again to Jeff Rosenbaum.
But we deliberately set out to attract weirdos.
And friends,
yes, some of them scare even us.
Our weirdar has a very wide range.
But even then, you know,
there's some that you just want to back away from.
The people who don't know...
They can't tell when they're being humored.
You know what I'm saying?
The ones who don't respond to you doing like this...
You know, making gestures of needing to escape.
They just talk louder, like I'm doing.
Well...
I spent years, actually,
like many of you, I'm sure, have,
reading up on the paranormal
and searching out weird things
and studying religion, historical religions, and so forth.
And after a while, it all starts to sound the same
and none of the weird stuff ever works in the lab.
And you get bored with the phenomena,
which is always just out of reach
and kind of a dog chasing its own tail.
But you meet the most interesting people.
The kooks themselves, the visionaries,
become so interesting that that...
And friends, becoming one yourself is even more interesting.
Ah, I love it.
And so I collect photographs of orbs and rods
and crop circles and so forth.
Last year at Starwood, we had a crop circle artist come out
and show us how to do it and show us how to do it.
And I wrote his photographs that the believers had all...
Only the believers can afford to send helicopters up,
take pictures of crop circles,
and put them on a website instantly,
and that's how the artists get pictures of their art.
And when they try to take credit for it,
they get arrested, like our friend Matthew Williams did,
the one who came here and spoke last time.
Or it's like those crop circle artists
can take a videotape of themselves,
shot with night vision,
working with night vision,
making the crop circle.
It takes two or three people,
maybe two or three hours to do.
If you've got a good designer and know what you're doing,
it's not that hard.
But the people who write the books
about the crop circles and the aliens,
ah, God, they're unbelievable.
And I've seen this in person.
You can show them the movie of the crop circle they're standing in
being made, and they will say,
no, you faked that to discredit the whole new age.
Why are you trying to wreck everything for us?
They can't let go of this belief
right in the front of their faces.
Now, friends, I'm not really that much of a skeptic
because I do believe in magic.
I've seen incredible, unbelievable miracles happen every day.
Miracles that I could scarcely believe,
but it was happening right in front of me.
And the most common one that I see,
the real miracle,
the most fantastic, amazing, magical thing,
is that so many people can believe such dumb shit.
It is absolutely...
Friends, thank you.
That is a miracle that never stops happening.
So if you want to believe in magic,
just stop talking and start listening, man.
But,
at the same time, though,
you can't expect love to be logical or magic
or any of that kind of stuff
to really work the way you want it to.
There's no logic in...
By definition, of course there's not.
As Bob said over and over again,
you don't use your mind to think about your religion.
He added, you use your mind to think about my religion.
But, you see, Bob had two...
has two hemispheres in his brain,
but they're not exactly like ours.
In his left, there's nothing right.
And in his right brain, there's nothing left.
And so, what Bob can't just wait for magic to happen,
he has to get out,
he has to do the first rule of Bob magic,
which is to get off your ass.
However, he only...
He does things, but he only does what's easier for him.
He surfs what we call the path of least resistance.
And you can't be just like Bob,
because he's getting your slack.
You'll never get as much as he...
Where do you think he gets his slack?
So don't go seeking Bob, friends.
He's going to suck it right off of you automatically.
But it's like spitting and wishing, you know,
the whole magical thing.
You can spit in one hand and wish in the other,
and the one will fill up with spit.
And...
And the other one will, in fact, fill up with wishes.
It's just how much you can sell them for.
Those of you who know my songwriting style
know that I specialize in humorous angst,
and I write about songs that...
about things that piss me off.
So this song...
is dedicated to a supermarket...
that I go to in my neighborhood.
You have one in yours, too.
Yeah, you'll recognize the...
spirit instantly.
It's called Rude.
Rude.
So many people...
here in this place.
Most of us try to get along.
But there are always exceptions to the case.
And to try and deny them, well, it would be so wrong.
Rude.
I see you everywhere.
You're all the people who just don't care.
At every station, every occupation, you're rude.
You're rude, so rude.
You got a really shitty attitude.
I wish you would go away, but I'm screwed.
And you're rude, so rude.
Now when you steal my parking space and utter insults to my face,
I think that's just the way it was.
But I can't help but feel the world would be a better place
if I ran you over with my car wheel.
Whatever happened to just plain courtesy?
Hearing a thank you, saying please excuse me.
Now it's not.
Nothing but noxious noise.
And it's nasty.
And you're rude, so rude.
You're so rude, yeah.
You're so rude.
You got a really bad attitude.
Oh, I want to build me a big barricade.
Maybe load up a shotgun.
Maybe sharpen a blade.
Yeah, it's you.
You who put me in that mood.
And you're rude, so rude.
You're so rude, so rude.
You're so rude.
I never saw you in my life.
I'm not your child.
I'm not your wife.
So why do you treat me this way?
And I can tell you you were crass, sullen and crude and had no class.
But you wouldn't understand.
Oh, you'd ignore every word I say.
Yeah, that's life.
Oh, jump inside and get me away from here, now.
We gotink.
We got a take hat.
We got to take it.
It all be done.
I got to like it.
You got to lose.
Your attitude
You're so rude
Everybody
So rude
You're so rude
So very damn rude
And every supermarket
And every checkout line
At the airport
So rude
All those people walking so slowly
In front of your car
While you're trying to move
And let's talk about people with cell phones
So very damn rude
And people with children
And children in general
So rude
And people who don't have the correct change
And people who are in
The shower house
For an hour
And a half
So very damn rude
You gotta lose
Your attitude
You're so rude
So terribly rude
So very damn rude
That's a song you can relate to, right?
No.
Victoria Ganger and Revelry
Dear friends, also known as
Sister Melodious Chops
And Princess We
And M.A.
Recorded there
At Starwood number 24
Which is also where my sermonizing
Was recorded last summer
See
Rosencomet.com
For more on that
Or Revelrychicks.com
For Revelrychicks downloads
But about this next upcoming music
My friends
You must see
Heart Ignition
And the name of the Lord
And the name of Jesus
We got the power
And we know we're right
It's gotta be us
There's gonna be none of us
Checkmate, stay with me
Come on, let's fight
Christians, Christians
All the hairy Christians
Line them up, shut them up
Tell them what to do
Church can you stay like me
And my brother
We don't wanna know each other
But we sure as hell do
In the name of the Lord
In the name of Yahweh
We got the power
And we know we're right
It's gotta be us
There's gonna be none of us
Checkmate, stay with me
Come on, let's fight
He, Bruce, He, Bruce
All the hairy Hebrews
Line them up, shut them up
Tell them what to do
Church can you stay like me
And my brother
We don't wanna know each other
But we sure as hell do
In the name of the Lord
In the name of all
And we got the power
We know we're right
It's gonna be us
There's gonna be none of us
Checkmate, stay with me
Come on, let's fight
Most of you
Muslims, Muslims, all hairy Muslims
Line them up, shout them up, tell them what to do
Churches and state like me and my brother
We don't wanna know each other but we sure as hell do
In the name of the Lord, in the name of Krishna
We've got the power and we know we're right
It's gotta be us, it's gonna be none of us
Check this, tell me, come on, let's fight
Hindus, Hindus, all hairy Hindus
Line them up, shout them up, tell them what to do
Churches and state like me and my brother
We don't wanna know each other but we sure as hell do
One, two, three, one, two, three
Ask the girl what she wanted to be
She said, I want it
Bob?
Repeat, quit your job, SWAT off!
You have been driven to the brink of insanity by the conspiracy!
I'm gonna tattery, tattery, tattery
Bob, if you owe me a hand
You're a lot closer than you even think
Bob is the way, Bob is the path
Believe or die!
Bob is not the answer
And neither is anything else
Bob, screw Bob!
What does he know?
Don't believe anything Bob knows you
Blasphemy! He represents for the anti-Bob!
That's right, Bob is a loser
Bob ripped me off for all my SWAT
Because Bob is a free-for-all!
Bob is a peach boy!
Bob just takes it all for himself
He gets all the women
He gets all the rock
He gets all the SWAT
Bob!
Kill Bob!
Bob is a conspiracy patsy
Bob faked his own crucifixion
So he can be resurrected to become your personal savior!
Bob is in the back of his limo right now
Getting ahead from your girlfriend!
Grab your favorite dog pup and whack him head-off!
Whack him!
And place it in the trophy cage right next to the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer!
That's right, Bob is a sinner just like you!
The second coming to Bob will be a slaughter!
With the false promise they are robbed of leading the flock!
Bob!
Kill Bob!
Forgive me Bob!
Oh Bob, I have served against you!
I was possessed by The Anti-Bob
Please forgive me!
Praise Bob!
If they would love him, much to do money, we would never have any problems.
He is the king of all kings.
The king of slack kills Bob there.
King of slack, Bill T. Miller.
You can get entire albums by Bill T. Miller, king of slack, by downloading them from BillTMiller.com or KingOfSlack.com.
And I think now we will let Mr. Fernando Nandili-Mur have a say.
Oh, dear, anything interesting happen around here today?
It's sad when a mother has to speak the words that condemn her own son.
Sure, Mom.
But I couldn't.
I couldn't allow them to believe that I would commit murder.
Well, gee, no, Mom.
They'll put him away now, as I should have years ago.
Boy, that sure is a shame, all right.
He was always bad.
Yeah, I suppose so.
And in the end, he intended to tell them I killed those girls and that man.
As if I could do anything except just sit and stare like one of his stuffed birds.
Oh, yeah, kind of.
Well, they know I can't even move a finger.
And I won't.
I'll just sit here and be quiet.
Yeah.
Just in case they do suspect me.
They're probably watching me.
You're too young to be seeing so much of one girl.
Well, let them.
Yeah, you're right, Dad, but...
Let them see what kind of a person I am.
Well...
I'm not even going to swat that fly.
I hope they are watching.
They'll see.
Okay, Mom.
They'll see and they'll know.
And they'll say, why, she wouldn't even harm a fly.
We wonder who she was.
It was just my mom.
For the children, turn this world around.
Remember, you must cook or smoke while under the influence of alcohol on every level of your home.
So please, test all members of your household to make sure they're in good working order
and change the batteries if necessary.
Then review your escape plan during this festive season.
Remember, always put your fit, poisonous hands over your eyes.
Then crawl low to a neighboring home.
Remember, most people die from breathing in nothing.
Why me?
Senators know firsthand the threat of biological agents.
Something we can never have too much of in this post-9-11 world.
Wow, protecting me, right?
Hmm, well...
Well...
Did you know?
Think about it.
They don't know.
What if they do know?
We're working to promote voluntary AIDS around the world.
It happened to me.
The air detector in your home.
The smoke bag in your car.
You hope they're there.
Just as we protect an accident or a fire,
the Connecticut Department of Public Health,
along with Connecticut's tribal nations,
are natural public health.
We're a national health emergency.
If you're a rancher or farmer on your tractor,
you're out of control.
I'm proud that our government shocked babies somewhere in the world.
If you are too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too,
a new baby shocked every minute for just pennies a day.
Yeah, um, my brother and my twin sister are getting married in the next few months.
I'm wondering if you have any advice or wisdom from Bob that I might give to them.
Your brother and twin sister?
My brother and twin sister are getting married in a few months.
Move to Alabama.
It's legal for them to do that there.
I think.
Well, you better become a subgenius minister,
and then I charge 200 bucks to do a wedding.
You could get a, you could, yeah, it's family.
You could charge them half price and still make 200.
200.
The divorce is just as expensive as any other divorce,
even though our marriages are cheap and perfectly legal.
Again, the lawyers, man, they're the ones who got it figured out.
We have a lot of subgenius lawyers.
Lawyers love the Church of the Subgenius because the written material is thick with a jargon.
It's like we created our own priesthood and speak our own jargon.
And lawyers and doctors appreciate that.
They don't have, they don't know that much more than you do.
They do have the jargon down.
And that's all it takes.
And that's why they think we're all so stupid.
They do look down on us.
And I don't blame them.
Oh.
I was sitting here by the garbage can.
I've been, I've had a revelation.
I've been fist slapped by the hand of Bob.
And I'm wondering, hearing all the bullshit, you're saying,
how am I going to go out there to all my friends who believe in me?
And even a bunch of stupid kooky crap.
And interact with them without them thinking I'm a foolish asshole.
Well, what does it matter?
The point, if you're a subgenius, they're already going to think you're a foolish asshole.
You've got, it's like you lost your credibility when you walked into this room, dude.
So, quit worrying about, that's the, the only problem you have is you worrying about what they think.
You are a foolish asshole.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
You know, eat the, don't just be a foolish asshole.
Be the hell out of it.
Look at me.
It works great.
I get paid to do this.
Be a foolish asshole for pay.
Yeah, I could give a whole lecture.
I should give a workshop on how to run your own cult.
But that would just be more competition.
We did the, this is the stupidest cult in the world.
It really is.
We consciously created an anti-business business.
And an anti-belief religion that also happened to be an anti-science science project and an anti-art art project.
Designed for non-joiners.
Designed for non-joiners, that's right.
A membership thing designed for non-joiners.
Now, do you see why we called it sub-genius?
So, you'll have to get your enlightenment somewhere else.
We do have excellent in darkenment.
In stereo and full color sound.
Pull the wool over your own eyes.
Like we said, you'll still be just as blind as a bat.
But it'll be your wool.
And there's nude pictures of Bob Dobbs printed on the inside of the wool.
So you're always getting a little shot of porno all the time.
What I told, when I started this, I said, what do we have to offer?
Lofty words, feelings, pablum, and lies.
And yet, isn't it sick, that that makes this the one true religion?
The only one.
Because it will admit that it's completely and utterly bogus.
From the ground floor up, it's the only one you can trust.
That's fucked.
Praise Bob.
Listen.
Never is it to be thought that man is either oldest or last of the masters of earth.
Nor that the greater part of substances walks alone.
The old ones were.
The old ones are.
And the old ones shall be.
They walk calm and tribal, of no dimension, and to us unseen.
They walk foul in lonely places, where the words have been spoken, and the rites howl through with their seasons,
which are in the blood and differ from the seasons of man.
The winds shiver with their voices.
The earth mutters with their consciousness.
They bend the forest.
They raise up the waves.
They crush the cities.
If not forest or ocean or cities, beholds the hand that smites.
As abounders shall they be known to the race of man.
Their hands are at the throats of men forever.
From the beginning of known time to the end of time known.
Man rules where once they ruled.
Soon they shall rule again where man rules now.
They shall return.
An army's returning.
Shall great Kapuru be freed from Raya beneath the sea.
And him who is not to be named shall come from his city, which is Tarkosa near the lake of Ali.
And Shabnukurush shall come forth and multiply in her hideousness.
And Nyarlathotep shall carry the word to the great old ones of their minions.
And Yod-Sothoth, who is all in one, and one in all,
shall lay his hand upon them who oppose them and destroy them from the black-litten caverns within the earth.
Where all this chaos and destruction shall come.
The noxious Azathoth.
And together they will take possession of all things that live upon earth.
That man is mad.
The cometh as one who shall be won.
But where there shall be title and name.
Behold...
What's great and new to Valhalla.
There shall be
the citizen of the blue seasangan allen.
tob
to outwit death?
Or has he created another?
Where can people get information on this, Reverend Stang?
It's a little bit of something just called Tom.
Of course, the subgenius website.
There are people broadswinging their arms,
screaming, where is Stang when we need him now?
You're throwing away amputated arms and legs
trying to figure out what to do next,
involving local community people,
and yet, while we're under a state of orange alert.
It was pretty weird.
Are we in orange alert for that thing?
No, I heard they moved it up to Valencia orange alert.
Valencia orange alert, which is a lighter shade of orange.
I need it down. It's closer to yellow.
Or did they move it to...
There are plenty of navels at X-Day.
I think they moved it to burnt...
It's a burnt sienna alert.
The blue and the green, I think, was the next step up from the navel orange.
I don't know. Some people tend to focus on the wrong areas.
I thought they were the fuchsia.
I really don't understand your whole terror coding system down there.
That's always kind of blown my mind.
Blue means all is well.
Oh, we're going to have levels of alerts.
Blue means everything's wonderful.
We have to have those for forest fires at National Park.
You know, like the don't throw your ashtray out the window if it's at, like, orange or higher.
But we don't have that for terror.
We have the amber alerts.
It's so preposterous.
It is.
Well, maybe eventually they'll have little badges for each person that will show each person's hate alert.
They have those.
They have the one you're going to the airport.
Sister Mary Magdalene, she has an orange.
She gets tagged when she flies.
Oh, right, yeah.
Well, yeah, they are after proof.
Yeah, it's like a little lie detector thing.
And if you're nervous...
If you're wearing an apple on your head, though,
they'll get you, too.
If you're neurotic, you get a certain color that shows up on your name tag.
If you carry a golden apple that says Caliste on it.
They give you a whole different color one.
Right.
Collect them all.
If you carry a golden apple that says Caliste on it, you are most certainly unmasked.
Right, I mean, some of us would have a regular rainbow on our little alert pad.
Rainbow alert.
Well, your medication actually is color barred.
Actually, no, we're going into a rainbow alert right now
because they're going to vote on the gay marriage amendment this week.
So that's the rainbow.
Rainbow alert.
You guys aren't 21st century enough to pass that one.
I dare you to pass that amendment.
Uh, people are predicting that it won't pass.
Capitol Hill insiders and, uh, experts are predicting that, uh, it will not pass.
They're not even sure it will get a simple majority when, in fact, it would require a
two-thirds vote to really pass.
If it does pass, indeed, they may, uh, suspenderate the elections this year because of the crisis
that it causes.
Well, actually, the Constitution doesn't say anything about elections.
It's, uh...
They're not the only people out therey.
Yeah.
There's, uh, the loo-lo-loooots and all these other b-looo
crap out there that, uh, are really locked in.
The only people out there are the formerRAC politicians that so bother about the moment's
Yeah.
The formerRAC politicians,ifferently.
make sure that every cow is counted.
We've got an Ohio company counting votes now.
Diebold election systems of
Canton, Ohio. They make the computer thing.
And they're guaranteed to win the election for whoever gives them
the most amount of money. And if you've got a
cash forward, listen, buddy, we're going to put those
things up front. Yeah, the CEO
of the... I'm working on them all the time, if you know
what I mean. Wink, wink, wink. The CEO of
the company that makes voting machines
is an ardent
Bush supporter, campaigner,
fundraiser, says he's committed to delivering Ohio's
electoral votes to Bush this year.
And he's the CEO of the company
that makes the election machines.
It is a question. Is it half
a statement with the end half a missing?
Is it the groin and socket of the underdog?
Is it the vast whiteness
under your linen pillow sky and
the tea bag under the apple house in your
mother's mansion in which you can find the end of the
world lying in wait for unwary travelers
from the dyke's mis-existence, flying
over the remnants of a dream once lost
and never found again by the masses?
Or is it just me dancing in my
underwear?
If you desire forums,
then you'll have to get two extra attached
because most mere humans in
subgenii only have two.
Or else you'll have to cut yours off and get
robot wheels, which are almost as nice.
But don't worry about it. The operation
is painless, even if you're penniless.
The whales keep form-hungry even though the
noses of the celebrities fall off into my
coat and are half-drowned by the waves
of my discontented checkbooks.
So don't spare the criticisms
and exorcisms when the four
horsemen come riding out of the deep with
ultrasound blasters blazing their way
into the hearts of all admiring ceiling fans.
And don't worry about the
ceiling wax either. It's guaranteed
for a thousand years.
Or until X-Day. Whichever
comes first.
A reverend self-slayer
did that. A piece called
Questionus Informatus.
And before that,
Radio Synesthesia
with Dr. Sinister.
And a call-in by St. Bucky,
I think. And Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And now,
now a subgenius.
Okay, this guy is
Georgetown Party, right? And all the
Illuminati and Illuminoids are all there and all these people
who work for the State Department. The guy's kind of a little bit
of a liberal and so forth and everything. And he's just
making some jokes to people. And he walks up to
a lovely young couple sitting by the punchbowl
there and he says, hey man, have you heard
the latest funny thing that came out of the White House?
Man, check this out. The guy says,
very high-rated, he says, I'll have you know I work
for the White House Press Corps. I am
a man's plane of the
White House. And the guy says,
alright, I'll say
it very
slowly.
Did you hear the one about
the horse's ass and the cowboy hat?
Yeah, I did.
Okay. Yeah.
Man, tell me a new joke, man. Tell me a joke I haven't heard.
Senator
Leahy was on the floor and he bent over because
he thought he'd seen a, you know, he dropped
a piece of tissue out of his pocket
and he just lonely, ripe snot
and he didn't want to dirty it
before. And so he reached over to pick
it up and Dick Cheney
appeared on the scene and said, hey, listen,
I got a good one for you.
Chicken walks into a bar
and it's got a little growth coming
out of the side of its head that looks like I'm staying
wherever I'm staying.
Chicken walks into a bar and
the, oh, she's not in.
I would have to tell you where the bartender says.
You're in safe harbor.
The bartender says, hey, listen, buddy, we don't
serve free tea here. And the little growth
on the chicken's neck says, hey, don't blame me.
I've been trying to get rid of this guy for the last half hour.
That's very logical.
That's very logical that.
It could have been in the communication device,
he was just portraying it to me.
It could have been an appliance.
qual
to another
way,
I don't know.
Yes,
still
this is
minor
to
the
east
Leave me, I ain't got stuff.
This is Miner Mountain.
The sun's tarnished.
Ah, so went my whiskey time.
Survive, he said. It was the name of the game.
What I give a shit about these people.
Subtitles by Subtitle Workshop
The amino, uh, destruct, destroy the warming sun.
See theaminoacids.com. That's theaminoacids.com and praise the...
Subtitles by Subtitle Workshop