The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects is intended only as humor
and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
We must adjust ourselves to the level of our audience, which is pretty low.
The following commercial has been seasonally updated for broadcast at this time.
I found my exact feelings expressed in a greeting card.
Easter's a very special day for me.
And I say, wouldn't it be great to have all of the churches full?
You know, packed churches all over our country.
Wow.
The trouble is that people believe that garbage can get themselves in trouble.
Of course, just a general statement.
By the bad planning committee.
They were doing it late December or early January.
Trying to draw a happy face from the map of the United States.
We'd probably be coming around about early spring, which is the beginning of April, the end of March.
Spring is here.
But, I mean, damn, if you spend all your time in your house watching videotapes of whatever it is.
But you've got to go out and get you some.
Click.
I would love to aim it right at Easter Sunday, so we're open for church service.
Is that true? Is that possible? Or is that false?
I think it's possible. Why isn't it?
How many of you believe that? You believe that?
Packed churches.
You believe that?
Yee-haw!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
Pew Packers!
I'm a Pew Packer. He's a Pew Packer. She's a Pew Packer. We're all Pew Packers.
Wouldn't you like to be a Pew Packer, too?
You come.
I'd love to have it open by Easter.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
I don't think that's anyone's problem.
Thanks, church!
And the congregation said?
Amen!
Amen.
Now, as you're dismissed, shake the hand of your neighbor before you leave your pew.
Aaaaaaaaaaahhhhh!
I love that golf game.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm!
Mwah!
Our country wants to die Easter Sunday. That would be a beautiful thing.
Woo-hoo!
What is that? The Calvinist view?
Calvin and Hobbes? Hm?
Yeah.
If you got it, you got it.
There we go.
Accidents happen.
Yeah, accidents do happen.
Ah-oh!
Ah!
Ahh!
Do a gift that'll still be around for many...
Aprils.
... to come.
A gift that keeps on giving is wicker furniture, or wicker baskets, or even a gumball machine!
Remember that the most unique gift ideas for all year are at Baskets & Things.
There in the Kenwood Plaza, just behind Hershedi's.
Baskets & Things wishes everybody a merry...
Easter
... and a happy...
Memorial Day!
The preceding commercial was seasonally updated for broadcast at this time.
We're still working on what to do with the 4th of July.
What was your idea?
Why? What's doing?
Just the usual thing.
We go into old Susie's place.
Hell of a nice place.
Old Susie's a laugh.
Always cracking jokes.
Like she says when we come up on the front porch last Saturday night.
Susie opens the door and then she yells,
What the f*** do you want?
Sweet Susie.
She'll beat you to death.
The diary of a wicked lady.
The memoirs of a bad girl.
Sweet Susie.
Slamming, crashing, banging action from opening scene to mind-bending climax.
She ain't no lady.
This motion picture's rated R.
She's a cold one, all right.
More stallion than man.
I never seen nobody like her.
She got the eye going all the time on everybody.
Rat head?
A whore.
I'm picturing a rat head.
She's a whore.
I don't know what the hell she wants.
She is undermining our civilization.
One woman, Sodom and Gomorrah, if you will.
Rape her.
A slimy, slithering succubus.
A concubine, a streetwalker, a tramp, a slut, a cheap whore.
Good grief.
There she was, parading around in clothes that couldn't keep a titmouse dry in a drizzle.
I mean, it was next to nothing.
I'd say it was next to plenty.
She's gonna make a mess.
There's gonna be a bad mess about her.
She's a jailbait all set on the trigger.
That ranch with a bunch of guys on it.
Ain't no place for a girl, especially like her.
And yet half the teenagers in town writhing around to that jungle music.
Gentlemen, it's time to present the person you have all come to see.
Please welcome Miss Susie.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ha.
But I'm prettier than she ever was.
Go hug your floozy.
She's right here.
Uh, here is relative.
She knows I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
That's okay, so am I.
Ha, ha.
That redhead.
That's the worst customer she's called conned with a karate punch.
She never talks dirty, neither.
What the f***?
What once you said you're back?
Two and a half.
Susie got nice chairs to sit in, too.
If a guy don't want to flop, why, he can just sit in the chairs.
Have a couple three shots and pass the time of day and Susie don't give a damn.
She ain't rushing guys through and kicking them out if they don't want to flop.
Might go in and look the joint over.
Come along.
It's a hell of a lot of fun.
Her cracking jokes all the time.
Like she says one time, she says,
I know people that if they got a rag rug on the floor and a cupid eye lamp on the phonograph,
they think they run in a parlor house.
And Susie says, I know what you boys want.
She says, I know.
My girls is clean, she says, and they ain't no water in my whiskey, she says.
If you guys want to look at a cupid eye lamp and take your own chance getting burned,
why, you know where you can go.
And she says, these guys around here walking bow-legged because they like to look at a cupid eye lamp.
What's so unappealing about sex?
Yeah, yeah.
I ain't had sex.
Well, Susie's place is clean and she got nice chairs.
Don't let no goo-goos in, neither.
What is that supposed to mean?
Ah, gulp.
I might go in and sit and have a shag.
But I ain't putting out no two and a half.
Well, a guy got to have some fun sometime.
Well, Susie, homewrecker, dip yourself in flour and make a skank biscuit.
Oh, man, it's so hard being me, but it's showtime.
Oh, welcome, Seekers, to yet another freaking episode of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Ha!
It was the nicest little whorehouse you ever saw.
It lay about a mile down this old dirt road, and if you just happened to stumble on it,
you couldn't help but notice that the barns were painted, the fences were up, and you
might think to yourself why folks that live there might just do to run the river with.
What a lie.
Sure, but...
And welcome to Watchdog with yours truly, Melvin P. Thorpe.
This week's spotlight will shine on a situation that has been allowed to exist right in the
shadows of the state capitol.
Let's get it out in the open.
Isn't this the age of telling it like it is?
Well, here goes, and God forgive me!
Yeah, it probably will if you slip on the big enough pill on the collection plate in
the morning.
Oh, welcome, Seekers, to my favorite time of year.
Yes, it's spring.
When even the flu's gone.
Shut up and shut up.
Has everyone got ink or something?
And it's giving me a frightful feeling that I'm going to die if I start wearing the
homaya out that's made of cut
Tintin's easyunden.
You know you can.
can survive a night in the embrace of a subgenius hellbitch?
Are you yeti enough to take it?
Because I'll spin dry your biogram
like an inside-the-egg-shell egg scrambler,
and your DNA helices will look like spin art
when I'm through with it.
Because it's a spring-fall, baby,
and I'm finally in the mood for some sex!
And it's about damn time, too.
So, Connie, bar the door,
because we ain't taking no prisoners tonight.
In order to keep our broadcasting license,
we devote Sunday night dead time
to public service shows of limited appeal.
No!
In that spirit, we bring you Gabin About God.
No, no, no!
I want sex!
Sex!
Now, we in the church, you know,
we're good at having things.
And to pour out drink offerings unto other gods,
break in a few more,
these are our traditions of men while you're at it.
A little rapture here, a little fly there,
fly away, it won't matter.
That they may provoke me to anger.
That's what your father thinks about the celebration of Easter
as it is presented by most Christians today,
rather than the Passover
with the focus upon the lamb slayer.
You still wake up sometimes, don't you?
You wake up in the dark
and hear the screaming,
and you're like,
the lab. Shut up! They have confused themselves whereby they don't know if an Easter egg belongs
in God's word or on a table somewhere or in an idyllic, heathen, organic orgy or festival.
It's all one and the same to them. Those egg council creeps got to you too, huh? Oh, you got
it all wrong, Homer. It's not like that. It's supposed to be told. It's supposed to be repeated,
not rolling idolatry, heathenistic Easter eggs. Well, now you're going to mess around and take
a lot of the children's fun away. I'm going to take a lot of the heat from God's anger away
from them. If they want to roll Easter eggs, let them do it some other day, but not on Passover.
It's an insult to the bloodshed on the cross.
You better run, egg! Well, are you saying that because they roll Easter eggs that they're going
to hell? No, I didn't say that. I said it gives Satan one of the greatest victories he's ever
accomplished, though. They want to hang on to that one little bit of sin, because I guess it feels
good to roll Easter eggs, not when you recognize the insinuations and the innuendos of filthy
orgies.
That it's symbolic of, and to even relate it anywhere near Christ, or Christianity,
or the church, is an abomination. You're an abomination. Easter orgies. The day Christ
rose, they're all screwing one another. And the poor kids and the middle class kids,
they're all copying the rich kids. They're all going the same goddamn screw America way.
He sees the ignorance.
He sees the injustice. He sees the mistừM
Error.
He sees the punishment, the Scolding. It's
a승
Error.
you've had a few little baskets.
You see, rabbits don't lay eggs.
They don't raise legs at all.
They're quick like a bunny.
This is the city, Jerusalem.
It's righteous.
A lot of people live here, most of them good.
But when they fall from grace, that's where I come in.
My name's Friday.
Good Friday.
I carry a badge.
The story you are about to hear is true.
None of the names have been changed because only one was innocent.
Gee, goody, mind if I knock this time?
Sure, Frank. Live it up.
So, hello, officers.
What can you do for me?
Your name, Thomas?
Uh, yeah. Did I do something wrong?
We just want the facts.
You know a man named Jesus Christ?
Yeah, I know him. Uh, what's this all about?
What's this all about?
Says he's the son of God.
What do you say?
Well, uh, he's a great guy.
You should see the miracles he does.
We just need the facts, sir.
Just the facts.
Well, son of God.
Yes, sir.
I doubt it.
Reports say he's at a garden in Gethsemane.
What do you say?
Gethsemane. I know the place.
I doubt it.
Hmm.
Kind of makes him a doubting Thomas, doesn't it?
So, you write your own material?
Uh, they say this Jesus is the king of the Jews.
What do you say?
Well, uh, that I doubt.
Calls himself the light of the world.
What do you think?
Uh, I doubt it.
They claim he's mankind's salvation.
How about you?
Well, I doubt it.
Right.
You gonna be available for any further questioning?
Hmm.
I doubt it.
2.18.
Frank and I stopped at a fish stand for lunch.
8.
Got back on the donkey and headed out to the house
with yet another Jesus follower.
We're gonna have to get him back.
He's a goody.
He's a great fish.
Only $1.50 a bucket.
What a deal.
Must have been a good catch.
You got some coleslaw on your nose, Frank.
Yeah?
Uh, could you turn down your stereo?
My what?
Your stereo.
Oh, okay.
Uh, honey?
Could you turn down the stereo?
What stereo?
The thing next to the dishwasher.
I want the dishwasher!
Yeah?
Your name's Simon, also called Peter?
Yeah.
Which is it?
It's both.
Listen, Peter.
What do your friends call you?
The Rock.
How are you listed in the phone book?
I don't have a phone.
What's it say on your driver's license?
Uh, I haven't got a donkey, either.
What's it say on your fishing license?
Retired.
You know a guy named Jesus?
Jesus?
Uh, no.
Never heard of him.
Look, we've got over a dozen witnesses here
having seen you with him on a number of occasions.
Now, what do you mean you don't know him?
Well, maybe it was just somebody that looked like me
because I don't know him.
Hey, uh, Rocky, you got a tooth in your mouth.
Look, I don't know him.
3.42.
When we arrived back at headquarters,
a farmer was waiting with a 402 complaint.
Willful destruction of private property.
Frank went to call his wife.
I went to question the farmer.
Well, I can't get mine, I got a bowl, honey.
You can lie and I got a bowl, buddy.
You can lie and I got a bowl, honey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
You the farmer?
Sure am.
You the officer?
Love whistles.
Will you get me one of those?
Yeah, I'll get you a whole box if it keep you from singing.
What's your problem?
Well, it's this, uh, Jesus fella.
Jesus again.
What happened?
He killed one of my fig trees.
What'd he do, tear it up?
Nope, never even went near it.
He just cursed it.
He what?
He cursed it.
Oh, I see.
Look, uh, just give me the facts.
Well, I got these five fig trees down by the fence, you know?
Yes, sir.
And this here Jesus fella comes sashaying along, figuring he's gonna mooch one of my
figs.
Mm-hmm.
Well, sir, and he saw there was nothing to be had, he cursed it.
I see.
Well, we'll get right on it.
We'll let you know if anything comes up.
Hey, hey, listen here, bullet head.
Now, I'm a taxpayer and 20% of my crop's gone.
Now, what am I gonna do?
I got a wife, I got a kid, I just bought a dishwasher.
All right, all right.
Uh, did you see what he was driving?
A donkey.
What color?
Uh, light brown, Galilee plates.
Did you get the details?
Did you get the donkey number?
Nope.
Why not?
Tail light was out.
445.
Frank and I headed back to the fish stand.
The donkey made a wrong turn and proceeded down an alley behind the temple.
We ran into still another Jesus follower.
Gee, I don't know, Goody, maybe we're lost.
Boy, it sure stinks back here.
Hmm.
Maybe we should have sent Sergeant Laverne his beat anyway.
Hey, wait a minute.
Isn't that someone up there?
Yeah, pull the donkey up here, Frank.
Uh-oh.
Oh, well.
Hey, buddy, you know the way back to Goldstein's fish stand?
Yeah.
Want to tell us?
Okay.
Go to the end of the alley.
Hang a right.
Go down two blocks.
Can't miss it.
Big fish going around in the sky.
Thanks.
By the way, uh, what are you doing back here?
Me?
I got a meeting with the Pharisees a little later on.
Pharisees, huh?
So who are you?
I'm a priest.
My name's Iscariot.
Uh, Judas Iscariot.
You one of the twelve?
What's it to you, gumsandal?
We're looking for Jesus now.
Do you know where he is?
Maybe yes and maybe no.
What's in it for me?
I got some more fish back in the donkey.
No, I just ate, uh, spare change.
Hmm, let's see.
That's my bowling money.
I got some change here from the confirmation.
Here's 20 silver pieces.
I'll get another 10.
That's 30.
That's 30 pieces of silver, do you?
That'll do.
Okay, you gotta promise me one thing.
What's that?
Don't tell Jesus that I rat on him, okay?
10-4.
No one will ever know it was you.
Now, how do you want to set this thing up?
Well, let's see.
It's gonna be the Passover.
We're gonna eat about 8 o'clock.
Mm-hmm.
You pick him up in the garden about 10-30.
10-30.
Fine.
How are we supposed to know this Mr. Jesus fellow?
I'll point him out to you.
That's not good enough.
Why not?
We need something more definite.
What if we get the wrong guy?
Okay, uh, I'll go up to him and I'll shake his hand.
That's still not definite enough.
Why?
What if someone shoots you?
It's not definite enough.
I'll go up to him and I'll shake his hand.
Well, what do you want me to do?
Kiss him?
Sounds good.
Okay, well, see you tonight.
Where are we supposed to meet you?
Don't worry.
I'll be hanging around.
That night Frank and I busted the Son of God ring and arrested Jesus Christ.
6 AM the following morning we turned him over to Pontius Pilate.
Jesus is our only king.
Not anymore.
Huh?
What?
That's amazing for a Christian.
Alwyn.
Excuse me.
Have you seen Alwyn anywhere?
Who?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Alwyn.
I don't know, Goody.
I've been a cop a long time.
This time I really think we did the wrong thing.
I mean, this Jesus guy didn't look like a criminal to me.
Hmm.
Even Pilate and Herod couldn't find anything wrong with him.
I wonder what the Pharisees have against him.
He was so nice and gentle.
You know, I even think he smiled at me.
Yeah.
Well, that's how it goes in this business, Frank.
We don't make the laws.
We just enforce them.
I'm kind of tired.
I think I'll take the rest of the day off.
I'll see you Monday.
Aren't you working Sunday?
No, Frank.
Sunday's Easter.
Friday, April 7th, in the apartment 6 of the Jewish Supreme Court.
Jesus Christ was tried and convicted of blasphemy.
Later that same day, he was crucified for the sins of the world.
In a moment, the results of that crucifixion.
This club better be worth it.
Oh, hey, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Well, it's such a strange world that I'm living in. She was my woman and he was my friend, but I was wrong again.
It's such a strange changing that you put me through. Like a fool, I'm still in love with you. What can this poor boy do?
Well, the way things go, don't leave me alone. Never let me entertain. Don't leave me laying here.
What will they do?
In two thousand years.
It's such a strange time that we're passing through. I thought you'd tell me when your time was due. I guess you thought I knew.
Oh, strange way to keep from waiting me.
Why did you lie? How could I help?
I'm so happy. Oh, won't you help me?
Well, the way things go, don't leave me here alone. Never let me entertain. Don't leave me laying here.
What will they do? In two thousand years.
Well, the way things go, don't leave me alone. Never let me entertain. Don't leave me laying here.
I think so too.
Well, they'll have to tell me so I don't have to stay Vargas.
It's the way it is.
So, who are you and what did you do?
I met you one day.
After three years.
This is one of those things that seems a little silly.
What does he mean?
What is it?
These fringes, tassels.
All right.
Now, in modern day, you can find something else that will take the place of it.
Oh, yeah.
I want you to make a note.
I'm not going to turn there.
I don't have time at this time, but make a note of numbers 1538.
What were the tassels for?
Every time you saw him jiggle, it reminded you to follow God's law.
Because usually a man, as long as the tassels are not jiggling, he's not breaking too many laws unless he's lazy.
So, do all you guys play for the same team or what?
Oh, no.
It sounds like that.
I've risen and I can't get down.
Stuff is over.
Excuse me.
If I gotta be anywhere at all, I'm glad that I am here with you.
Now, you know sex is my philosophy, though I may never make history.
I know making it is no mystery from my point of view.
I'm glad that I am here with you.
Now, the golden rule in my motto of one, do unto others as long as it's fun.
I never look before I leap.
I only sow what's fun to reap.
So, get out and live because I believe it's as blessed to give as to receive.
If I gotta be anywhere at all, I'm glad that I am here with you.
Now, the kids are here.
I only thought since I turned 20 is to share the wealth and I've got plenty.
I only live by a simple creed.
And he wants my friend if he's a friend in need.
Life's too short.
Not too far.
I don't like to have a ball.
Why behave?
Why one if you can have them all?
I gotta be anywhere at all.
I'm glad I'm here with you.
Welcome, Seekers.
Welcome to Bob's Jack Time Whorehouse.
The show that makes black women white hot and white men black out.
Oh, but the pinks keep on getting pinker.
Oh, hell, I can't change everything.
Oh, I'm your hostess, Reverend Susie the Floozy.
I'm afraid I'm the only girl working the house tonight.
Oh, so I'm afraid there's a problem.
A bit of a lie.
Yeah.
But you've caught me at a good time, sport.
Oh, man.
Damn this Easter.
My stigmata put out my cigarette again.
Damn.
I'll just slip on these rubber gloves and change them when they start looking like a five-lobe blood blister.
Ah, there.
Oh, yeah, these pinky cheaters just might be a good idea tonight, Seekers.
Because we're drifting into some unsavory waters full of strange body fluids and even stranger noises.
That's right.
It's a sex show just dripping with carnal content.
Better get out the drop logs, too.
That might be a good idea.
Yeah.
Because with my little shows, we can never be sure just where we're going to wind up.
Because I don't even have the slightest idea myself where we're headed.
Oh, but if we're in luck, we're going to have an obscenely good time.
So let's peel out of some of these clothes and get comfortable.
And then strap yourself in nice and tight.
And don't cheat, because I'll be coming by at a check.
Check those straps.
And they better be the big red ones if you know what's good for you.
Because tonight, Seekers, we're going to wallow in the baser side of our psyches.
Because when you get down to the nasty, nitty-gritty, deep, deep downside,
we're all nothing but a bunch of sexies.
Sex junkies.
Hey.
Whoa.
Here we go.
Woo!
Make your feelings cool.
While you don't get enough, it's called Sex Junkie.
You bring your black tassels and your cell phone.
You are the lowest, the lowest, the low.
Bang for me, girl.
Whoa.
I'm underneath
You're all so chunky
You're too fast I feel
I'm underneath
Secrets of us that you keep
in your mind
Things looks like you are
so easy to find
First name is jerk
And your last name is Lee
Is your hot sex junkie
You're too
as I believe
I'm
shorty master
Take this part to me
For the ideas
they just clog up your brain
These stress and fights
for you just focus
and it will be great
time for us to live
Just for this
your hot sex junkie
You're too fast I feel
One faster
One faster, one faster
Two hundred for the battle's over
Keep them walking to the light
And their flesh is hot
Eat to them, she is dead
Keep respiring
To your glory
Your victory
And your glory
Sex balls surround
Out of the sky
Fill the orgasm
Until the time
Screaming flesh
Begs for more
You make the sex
There is no more
That's true love
Is to love enough
That you'll dedicate your life
To teaching the truth
Regardless of what people might say
Regardless of how offensive
It may be to some
Because you only want those
That care enough to love you
Enough that they want to know more
About their father's word
Instead of a bunch of polished off
Powder puff
Penny laced
Frills and thrills
Back scratching
Make you feel good
Men that say things
To get men to feel good
Rather than teaching the word of God
Are unfit and they're nuts
Okay, I'm off of it
Well it means you can sin
I mean
And the more you do it
The more you sin
The sin nature really doesn't have anything to do
With you failing God
But here's what happens
If you fail the Lord
All of a sudden that sin nature explodes into flames
Now whenever this happens
And that sin nature explodes
And we find ourselves
With sin reigning
Notice what Paul said here
Well we belong to God
We belong to the church that rolls eggs
Ball them up
You know and we get out and hippity hoppity
Chase these two bunnies
You know heavy stuff friend
I mean forget about Passover
God we like bunny rabbits
And Ishtar
Oh just have a big meeting
I mean you know
Everything in him became sin
It became degradation
As long as we're in a flesh body
Especially if you can't define sin
Sin is to
Let's take between the two sexes
Oh that sounds dead he likes it
Sin is to lust
Or to be very plain
To put the make on
Every type that you come across
That's lust
But to admire God's beautiful creation
In Christian love
That's not a sin
And if you tell someone
If you were to say
If you're holy
You're not even going to look upon a woman
Well that's
We are human beings
And there is no sin
In appreciating
Our sisters
Well because if you believe that
Then you can do anything you please
You can just live your life any old way
Say well live it up now
Might as well enjoy it now
This is all we have
Might as well just make the most of it you know
You only have one time around
Like the beer commercials tell you
So live it up with a lot of gusto
My bible says different
It says that the point on the
Never man wants to die
And after this he does
Now in this satanic bible
There's a chapter entitled satanic sex
In the chapter entitled satanic sex
It says this
Satanism condones any type of sexual activity
Which properly satisfies your desires
Be it heterosexual, homosexual, bisexual or asexual
Satanism also sanctions any fetish or deviation
Which will enhance your sex life so long
As it involves no one who does not wish to be involved
Now that's the same thing as the new morality law
Of liberal preaching appraisal
Anything's okay
As long as everybody that's involved is consenting to it
And nobody gets hurt
May I help you?
Hey don't touch me lady
I'll punch your face off
I didn't touch you
Well you better not
Or I'll tear your legs off lady
Now that we understand each other
Why don't you sell me one of those whips you got on sale
Whips?
Leather whips
Just a second
Now if you're out of whips
Maybe you got some leather rope with little barbs on them
I love leather so much it hurts so much
Oh we do have leather on sale
But not what you're looking for
I definitely want the white leather ones
I contrast with my black rubber suit
See
Hey close that will you?
Oh yeah sure
Now where's them white leather whips?
Shoes
Shoes to who?
No only shoes
Converse All Star genuine white leather basketball shoes
Just $12.88 while they last
Converse shoes no whips?
Sorry
But why don't you try these shoes?
Let me look at them here
Yeah nice leather but does it hurt?
Let me try it on my face here
Oh
Wake up wake up
Where am I?
You're at Ben's Department Store 8th and Central downtown
And you just got some Converse All Star basketball shoes
For you
Hey that felt good hit me again
Oh never mind I'll just take these shoes home and wear them on my face
Well I'm weapon in style with my
Some people think little girls should be seen and not heard
But I think
Oh bondage up yours
One two three four
I'm a soldier of all
I want to be a choose who you are
Oh bondage up yours
Oh bondage of yours
Change that case though
I can save you all
Change it change it
I don't think at all
Oh bondage of yours
I'm yours.
By the
God's
name,
I may carry you to the wall, I wanna play your save-for-you-all.
Abandon, no more! Abandon, no more!
Wicked, bad, naughty evil Zoot!
Oh, she is a lowly servant, and you must pay her penalty.
And here in Castle Anthrax, we have but one punishment for setting alight the grail-shaped eaten.
You must tie her down on a bed and spank her.
And spank me! And spank me!
You must spank her well, and after you have spanked her, you may deal with her as you like.
And then, spank me.
And spank me. And me. And me.
Yes, you must give us all a good spanking.
And spank me! And spank me!
My friends are into everything, and we have it all on tape.
Big breasts, eager virgin, menage a trois, spanking, masturbation, anal fetishes, sex in unusual places.
Adultery, fornication, uncleanness, lasciviousness, idolatry, witchcraft.
Verse 21 ends up this way. It gives a long list of sins.
And lots more.
Strange love desires that make a mockery out of marriage will keep you wedded to your seat.
What kind of superb love is that?
What kind of superb and sin have these housewives of tomorrow said, I do too?
Find out firsthand. See the smut peddler.
It's so cute!
And I've secretly taped some of my friends enjoying their wildest fantasies.
First, you'll meet a very oral girl who boasts that she gives the best.
I know you don't!
I did not have sexual relations with that woman.
I didn't do it.
How many times have I heard that before?
And then again.
And again, and again, and again.
I could hear the cheerings in living room all across this country.
Right on! It's the I didn't do it guy!
But you'd do it again, wouldn't you?
He's mine! I own him! And all the subsidiary rights!
I spoke to the president just a few minutes ago.
A Ph.D. in the obvious is he's quite pleased.
Arnie.
John, how could you?
I, uh, didn't do it.
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha!
It's just a political marriage. He doesn't love her. He never sticks his hand up her dress like he does to me.
You think you are so grand.
The president's whore. How many women do you think he has?
Paula, Jennifer, Monica, Linda, Kathleen, Elizabeth, Dolly, Sally, Perdue.
There's no Republican or Democratic way to pick up the garbage. It either gets picked up or it doesn't.
Literally.
I disagree. I don't understand how come they always dine in the president. He's doing his job and all of them women that's claiming him, they're ugly!
He's got a beautiful wife! They're ugly women! They're ugly!
I did not have sexual relations with that woman.
Oh my God!
Now, the I didn't do it dancers!
Don't move, dude.
This is totally a gun.
I didn't see you didn't do it.
We want to seriously diminish the threat posed by Iraq's weapons of mass destruction program.
He has already said that he intends to expand. He invaded his neighbors. If the world community lets him, then so many people could be at risk.
Once you get gray-headed, you can fess up to that.
What I want to talk to you about today is that we have to continue that until every American is a part of this success story.
To determining whether we can in fact teach every neighborhood, every block, every family, every child.
Ah, you almost had me.
It's just like a sad excuse for your strange perversion.
You're screwing, you're screwing the head.
I can't believe I'm here.
There's got to be a third way here.
What's the hubbub, bub?
It's the president pressing the flesh, both animal and human.
Tonight, Ion Springfield takes a look at the secret affairs of Kennedy, Eisenhower, Bush and Clinton.
Did fooling around on their wives make them great?
We'll find out next when we play Tales of the Chief.
The allegations are false and I would never ask anybody to do anything other than tell the truth.
What's the big issue there?
His attitude was, we stick together, we all lie about it, we'll be okay.
We found a way, make some innovative partnerships.
We want to be your partner and we want to be a good partner and help you be a good partner.
Ah, the term disappointed has a whole new meaning in my life today.
I did not have sexual relations with that woman.
I didn't do it.
Hey, proper.
Now that would be some very good advice for our commander in chief at this time, but I assure you it would seem that he is fond of handling abominations.
I'm going to the White House to get my presidential knee pads.
Yes, this hinged knee, low cut dress for you.
Wearing baby fatty, phone sexing, psycho valley .
Intern .
Yes, in fact, she was frustrated by the fact that this person would not have what she termed regular sex with her.
Ah, a man after my own heart.
A gentleman with a taste for the low life.
Uncensored, without a kiss or a comma missing.
Let's assume that this is the guy.
Who's been sexually active for a long time and then got it that as president he'd have to not have to shut himself down.
You would then expect a variety of things which would be quasi sexual in nature, but which would fall short of it.
And phone sex might be one of them.
Fantasies might be one of them.
A close emotional relationship with a young person might be one of them.
After the thanking, the oral sex.
The oral sex.
Those all could be real things without actually committing adultery.
Where the rubber hits the road.
I can report to you tonight that it's working.
Guys, I know this has a very high ick factor.
Which two politicians in this room went to the greatest lengths early in their career to cover up the fact that we can do it?
Roy.
Oh, you're right on that.
I know.
They don't call me sleep early for nothing.
And I thought, well I don't think that's true.
I think you can slap the President of the United States like that.
Why?
We had the same type of feeling with the people that John Kennedy had, I think.
Sit down, ho!
Sit down!
Oh, you ho, sit down!
Oh, .
I would very likely expose myself to legal bills and subpoenas and all manner of other hurt.
Because that's the nature of this proceeding that they're under.
I couldn't in good conscience just say, well, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to sit on this stuff and not tell the authorities what I know.
I, oh, yeah, I can't, oh, sit down.
I want you to listen to me.
I'm going to say this again.
I did not have sexual relations with that woman.
I didn't do nothing!
Uh, isn't it, I didn't do it?
Yeah, whatever!
Uh.
Do it!
I did not.
And now, boys and girls, here he is, the boy that says the words you've been longing
to hear like the salivating dog that you are.
I didn't do it.
Huh?
Uh-huh.
I didn't do it.
I can go back, uh, now and continue the work that I'm doing.
You awful man.
Speaking of one-trick ponies, whatever happened to that I didn't do it kid?
Boy, did that get old fast.
Whoa!
You know, if you want to last in this business, you gotta stay fresh.
I can report to you tonight that it's working.
Now, let's get to work.
Let's imagine the future.
Hello.
Hello, seekers.
I'd like to take this opportunity to say a few words about our leader.
I'm very concerned about the way the whole thing's been going for a while, but I've been
afraid to speak.
Seekers, there's a very serious sexual addiction running rampant here, and it gives even me
cause for concern, so you know it's gotta be bad.
Oh, I'm not talking about that two-bit laundromat Lothario Bill Clinton.
Oh, I wish I were.
That guy's just another glad-handing, grab-ass hick.
Oh, no.
The leader who made me a leader.
And the one whom I'm referring to is our own sweet, dear, beloved Reverend Ivan Stagg.
Or is he?
Oh, as one of the church interns, I've put up with the repeated inseminations by the church
hierarchy.
Oh, just a rite of passage, they said, but this hallway never ends.
Oh, I figured I was ready for anything.
Well, anyhow.
Things have been real intense for a long time, but oh, lately, Stagg's sexual excesses have
reached such horrifying proportions that it may endanger the church itself, and I can't
sit on this any longer.
I'm gonna turn you all my kids to hell.
Oh, my God.
They're all gonna get it.
I can't sit down.
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
Oh, I feel your pain.
Oh, yes.
Is this indeed our Stagg doing this?
And doing it?
The Stagg does resemble the old Stagg, but, oh, there's something about this one that
isn't right.
It's more than just our little sister.
Our good old staying with a beard.
There's something about the eyes.
Oh, like those small ruby red dots in the middle of each pupil for starters.
Oh, I'd never noticed those before.
But the first thing I noticed was his weird behavior.
It used to be three, maybe four call girls a night.
Oh, and then the stakes got higher.
He needed new thrills.
Ordinary human women weren't cranking his tractor anymore.
Oh, and then the disappearances started happening around Dallas.
House pets, livestock, Christians.
It was getting bad.
Oh, but our staying was a busy man.
At the same time, he began to assemble an elite cadre of bimbos, a la L. Ron Hubbard.
Oh, and they helped keep up with his rampaging perversions for a while.
Oh, how he kept him out of jail just with that, I don't know.
Oh, but then last week, Stang.
Oh, if it is Stang.
Went on a colossal bender and took a whole busload of 38 drugged and bound and half-corps church secretaries off a bridge.
And...
Chained.
Kappa squinted.
And now I've got a mess of monumental proportions here to cover up.
Oh, I managed to plant Tammy Wynette and Wendy O. Williams in convincing death scenes.
But...
Oh, I'm working from the wrong end of the alphabet here and I got 36 to go.
And how he had Vince Foster on board, I'll never know.
Oh, I can't figure out...
Who was the poor jerk they found shot?
I mean, I've got a bunch of people out in the park and...
Gee, would it really confuse things all that badly if I just used that same setup again?
It worked once and it sure would be convenient.
Oh, but anyhow, Seekers.
This is where you come in.
You need to pray to Bob that our beloved Reverend Ivan Stang is okay.
Whoever the hell this Stang is.
Because one little mass murder like this could compromise our chances of making it to X-Day.
And we're only 85 days away, Seekers.
Yes.
However evil and horny this new Stang is, we need him to get off this planet.
So let's rally behind him, whoever he is.
Because that way he can't point them laser beam eyes at us.
And yeah...
Let's get back to going on about...
Sex again.
Oh...
Yeah, that damn Bill Clinton.
Oh, when Willy showed his Willy to Willy, that was my shut-off point.
Oh, but that cheesy weasel is taking us off the beaten track tonight, so...
We're gonna have to do some beating to catch up.
And hey...
That sure does sound like a good idea to me.
So why don't you just go and get out your ritual items?
A little cold cream, some Kleenex, some favorite pornography.
Because we're getting back down to business.
Because face it, baby...
You know you want to.
You know you need it.
You might even deserve it.
And one thing's for sure...
I ain't cleaning up after it.
So enjoy...
And let yourself go.
There's evil in your town, though you may not know it's there.
It never makes a sound, it just creeps up your underwear.
You can find it in your restaurants underneath the tablecloth.
You can find it in your old haunts in a can of chicken broth.
Sometimes it shows in daylight for everyone to see.
We gotta join the fight against S-M-U-T.
S-M-U-T.
It's deepening your mind.
So easy to find.
S-M-U-T.
It's wicked and it's foul.
It's enough to make you high.
High.
Foul.
My daddy was a baker.
His buns he liked to show.
My mama was a cosmo girl.
She sucked up daddy's dough.
My girlfriend is a call girl.
She makes my carrot grow.
She doesn't like a tractor.
That's why they call her hoe.
S-M-U-T.
It's deepening your mind.
So easy to find.
S-M-U-T.
It's wicked and it's foul.
It's enough to make you high.
High.
S-M-U-T.
SUB CREDITS
Good morning, boys and girls.
Ah, I see you're alone.
Well, turn your stereo up real loud.
Make yourself real small.
And let your mind drift away to poetry corner.
Are you small enough to read between the lines?
Well, here's a poem you can really get into.
I like little pussy.
Her coat is so warm.
And if I don't hurt her, she'll do me no harm.
So I'll not pull her tail nor drive her away.
But pussy and I very gently will play.
She shall sit by my side and I'll give her some food.
And she'll love me because I'm gentle and good.
I'll pat little pussy and then she will purr.
And I'll show her thanks for my kindness to her.
I never will bex her or make her displeased.
Puss doesn't like to be worried or teased.
I like little pussy.
Her coat is so warm.
And if I don't hurt her, she'll do me no harm.
Oh.
SFUG.
It's seeping in your mind.
It's so easy to find.
SFUG.
It's wicked and it's foul.
It's enough to make you high.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Oh, goodnight, seekers.
SFUG.
Ahem.