Slack, my friends, is like energy. It can neither be destroyed nor created. It is
just present everywhere in some form or another.
Slack can be transmuted. Slack can be fine-tuned so that appeals only to you
and it is your personal form of Slack. But Slack is always there. It is around
you everywhere, even in this miserable pink world that we're forced to live in,
surrounded by Glorps. There is Slack, friends, and the way to Slack is to
remember the way of Bob. Bob can give you Slack. Bob can help you find that
particular kind of Slack that fits you best. Remember, it's always out there. You
and Bob can find the Slack you need.
Red, can you go? Where shall I go? What shall I do?
Frankly, my dear, I don't...
I'll give it.
Some genius. Power of Slack.
From PR News in Washington, I'm a mass of cold penguin food rations trying to adapt
to a rapidly changing marketplace as people gathered to celebrate pummeling PR News.
This is going to be sort of a...
It's up to...
Win the titles and expect rid to both.
Power companies say they're already arranging explosives for next week.
And another milestone is also within view.
It's a...
The world program says it plans to provide monthly flying in PR News for one and a half people,
at least until the middle of a mass of cold air from the north.
The assailant escape. Police infiltrate. Strike troops. Troops true. Kill. Attacks.
Shooting. Attack. Shooting. PR News.
The National Hurricane Center in Miami says this is PR News.
PR News.
Germany calling. Germany calling.
The witches attempt to keep mum in this cathedral.
Ah, sorcery, kidnapping, and desecration.
The solution is...
The Soul Genius. Power of Slack.
Did I hear a flash?
Because the crabs he had were awful, dear.
Go on, I said, have a nice bowl of liquid paraffin jelly. It'll loosen you up.
Oh, no, he said.
So I turned around and said, look, a warm half pint of olive oil and a funnel.
I don't mind doing it, but not him.
He got unrest with the light off.
Here you are, dear, I said, do it yourself.
Shove a pellet of soap up with a good squirt of cucumber juice.
Mrs. E.
When I require an evacuant, I swallow 30 feet of toweling and wait.
Death night. Death night. Death night. Death night. Death night. Death night.
I must have some booze.
I demand to have some booze.
If I had all the money I'd spent on drink, I'd spend it on drink.
You know what makes you feel helpless sometimes?
Spaceships rushing by.
Bombs. Bombs.
Big enough to bury continents.
Men and women.
Ordinary men and women like you and me.
Able to press a button and bingo.
Everything's finished.
And that boy, he wants to know if everything's going to turn out all right in the end.
I hope so. I certainly hope so.
We'll just have to see what's going to happen in this...
Hey.
enamored
This red payback is the jack of the cop.
Heh heh heh.
quando
These drugs are going to blow my ass off.
Five, four, three, two...
People run to the edge of countries and stop.
And look above the water.
You can tell the edge by stones.
Some are small like sand.
Some are big like pebbles.
Then they usually sit down.
Some on man-made cushions.
The rest on newspaper.
Except for a few who don't care where they sit.
Stones are so unique.
People get bored by being unable to find two the same.
And anyway, the differences are superficial.
Though the stones don't think so.
In this way, stones are a bit like people.
Except they think more and say less.
And don't complain.
God bless.
Stones.
And that includes pebbles and sand.
I have a macrocosmic view of things temporal.
No order changes.
Yielding place to you.
God fulfills himself in many ways.
And soon, I suppose,
I shall be swept away.
By some vulnerable little tumour.
Oh my boys.
My boys, we're at the end of an age.
We live in a land of weather forecasts.
Breakfasts that set in.
Shattered by Tories.
Shoveled up by labour.
And here we are.
We three.
Perhaps the last island of beauty in the world.
I don't know.
Which of you is going to be a splendid island
and the damping abodes for the rest of the plane?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
We'll try our best to find best ice-b LEO.
.
That's telling usiotou triples of a world.
See you in the fire.
I wish you ease of anguish.
My ed Thrones island.
ир
Subsamu land.
I want to join Islamic Jihad
I just want to kill for God
Praising Allah is the life for me
I'll use pipe bombs, what the fuck?
Killing Hebrews brings good luck
God will make all maybe proud of me
Load a car with dynamite and drive it to a synagogue without any brakes
Nothing could be better than this
Better than impaling your intestines on a big rusty stake
Pack grenades and cattle prods
Let's go out and kill for God
I can hear Mohammed calling me
Yowza, yowza, yowza
Let's go out and kill for God
I want to join Islamic Jihad
I want to kill for God
Praising Allah is the life for me
I'll use pipe bombs, what the fuck?
Killing Hebrews brings good luck
Let's go out and kill for God
Let's get the hell out of here
Let's kill for God
Ha ha ha!
Ah, looks like it sucks!
Firing up the ol' bulldozer!
Though the Corinth seems quite odd
I still want to kill for God
Praising Jesus is the life for me
Fuck those pagans, they're such cynics
Let's bomb the abortion clinic
Jesse Helms, he is my cup of tea
Never thought I'd make it big by selling God to idiots on cable TV
What the fuck?
It's not true!
I'm a G, but still a better way to use my business degree
Use a rifle, spare the rod
Let's go out and kill for God
Baby Jesus, pass my AKG!
Friends...
It's gonna be a rough time and I'm gonna...
I'm... this is...
à Cartier
The pounding action
Kiss the buyer
Have no fun
Son, I realize
All my money
Call me
Be a grown-up
And always knew
That present
If this little murder
Was never meant for me
Indeed more
No, no
My love
If this little heart
For the heart
Was a seraglio
Be my du polyn enhancees
You're alive. You're healthy.
Your life's insured.
There's little money set aside in case of accidents.
What more could you ask for?
These are good times.
Easy money, easy sex, VCRs and Nintendo to keep your minds occupied.
You know, they say that the golden age is never the present age.
They really do say that.
But we look all around us everywhere, and what do we see?
Golden opportunity.
Well, friends, that's just calm before the storm,
because tonight's sermon is entitled,
X-Day 1998, Day of Reckoning.
We all know vaguely what X-Day is.
Bob told us himself that it shall occur July 5th, 1998.
The X's shall land and whisk the good subgenies off
to a never-ending pleasure cruise of the cosmos.
But what of the peaks that remain on Earth?
What will happen to the A's?
What will happen to the B's?
Well, friends, as much as I hate to gloat over those less fortunate,
the fact is, they'll get exactly what they deserve.
Now, to any real subgenie, giving the normal what he deserves
is about the cruelest fate a normal could ever receive.
After all, these are the same normals that have supported the conspiracy for centuries.
These are the same normals that have tortured us with their ignorance
and defiled the name of Bob.
These are the same normals...
that have taken the most free country in the world
and turned it into an ever-growing bureaucratic governmental monster
that feeds on taxes, committees, laws, statutes,
buck-passing, and fill-in-the-blank.
Then, once the creature's rot-filled gut
sprues out the digested combination of all the vices
before mentioned by the lawyers and liars that created this filth,
what's the result?
Why, the conspiracy, of course.
And this pile of stinking defecation
we're supposed to kneel before and worship
and serve?
Never!
Bob will avenge us for the years of conspiracy rule
on that most dreaded of subgenius holidays,
X-Day 1998.
Dreaded by them,
but not by us.
Let us look at Bob's prophecy
and see what the normals have in store for them,
shall we?
Bob's word comes in many mysterious ways,
not all of which are immediately recognized
as divine in origin.
Indeed, since Bob transcends time,
so does his word.
This revelation popped up in a 1938 radio drama.
In this story, the Martians,
then a synonym for aliens,
later to be known as X's,
have landed and started to round up the normals.
Two of the unlucky survivors
meet to discuss the future of man unkind.
The smarter one asserts, quote,
I've thought it all out.
Right now,
we're caught as we're wanted.
An X's only has to go a few miles
to get a crowd on the run,
but they won't keep on doing that.
They'll begin catching us systematic-like,
keeping the best and storing us in cages and things.
They haven't begun on us yet.
Not begun.
Later, he goes on to say,
all those little office workers
that used to live in these houses,
they'll be no good.
They haven't any strength,
no stuff in them.
They used to run,
run off to work.
I have seen hundreds of them running
and catching their commuter trains in the morning,
afraid that they'd get panned if they didn't.
Running back at night,
afraid that they wouldn't be in time for dinner.
Lives insured and a little invested in case of accidents.
Yay, and on Sundays,
worried about the hereafter.
Well, the X's will be a godsend for those guys.
Nice roomy cages,
good food,
careful breeding,
and no worries.
Yeah, after a week or so of chasing around the fields on empty stomachs,
they'll come and be glad to be caught.
Now, this is 1938, mind you.
He goes on to say, finally,
that's not all.
These X's are going to make pets of some of them,
train them to do tricks.
Who knows, get sentimental over the pet boy who grew up and had to be killed.
Yay, and some, maybe,
they'll train to hunt us.
Yes, they will.
There's men who will do it gladly.
Well, friends,
how much more obvious does Bob have to be?
When he gave this brief preview of the future in 1938 on CBS,
it sent millions of normals into the streets screaming for reprieve.
They repented.
They begged forgiveness.
And yet, just a few days later,
after Bob Orson Welles in the War of the Worlds broadcast
was described by the conspiracy as nothing more than a joke,
the normals went back to the conspiracy way of life
as if nothing had ever happened.
They came so close to getting a second chance in mending their ways,
but they blew it.
They went back to the conspiracy masters,
and for their loyalty,
they were genously rewarded with yet another world war.
There's a strange sense of poetic justice to it, isn't there, friends?
Well,
they haven't seen nothing yet.
Just wait till the real McCoy comes.
It's only a few miles down the road, pink boy.
And like Dr. Al prescribes to his patients,
if you're caught in a nuclear holocaust and your skin begins to melt,
don't panic.
This is perfectly normal.
Yes, friends,
just another normal way to die for the normals doomed to die.
Did I say doomed to die?
I should have said lucky to die,
for bliss that are the dead after X-Day arrives.
The doom,
doomed are the unlucky pink survivors
who must live out their wretched existence under the cruel and merciless exes.
Cruel to them,
but not to us.
Not only will there be no more bowling alleys and golf courses for the pinks,
but there'll be no more subgenies to kick around anymore.
We'll be surfing the celestial stars,
smoking our frock,
unweaving our slack,
and sexing our anti-virgins like there was no tomorrow.
Because in space, friends,
there isn't.
Only back on Earth will it be an Amar,
and then the next day,
and then the next.
It'll be an eternal hell without end.
And we'll be an enjoyin' it all in the heavens on closed-circuit TV,
because we won't want to miss a single revenge-filled minute.
Praise Bob!
Amen.
No!
That's mine.
I'm always finding,
they leave these half-filled syringes layin' around.
We called that 10-30in' where I came from,
because it meant that you left the party at 10-30 and didn't finish your beer.
Half-finished lobotomies.
So I think at halfway through you're nine.
I know, I cleaned up a whole brain yesterday.
I saw that.
This is a reenactment of the way early man appealed to his so-called gods.
Saw spirits in everything that lived.
Trees, birds, and would do homage as best he could with horrible, crude caveman noises.
We're going back to the old ways.
Back when the world was simpler,
there were only two or three social networks.
The old, the new, the old, the old, the old.
The old, the old, the old, the old, the old.
Facebook worked by smoke signals.
And it was actually a lot more entertaining then.
None of this instant gratification shit.
Oh, nice!
A man can never have too many guitars.
Too much is always better than not enough,
as Bob said.
For the rest of this episode, we're back at X-Day.
15 X-Day, rather.
But what we played earlier...
Let's see.
G. Gordon Gordon opened the show.
Then Titles and News by Lee Murr.
But that longer collage with the old man hating,
that was by Slackmaster Sarcastro.
And involved some I-4 Cutler, I am told.
The song Kill for God was, of course,
the Rudy Schwartz Project.
There's a great video of that.
It's from a re-release of the classic album
Don't Get Charred, Get Puffy.
The Rudy Schwartz Project.
You can Google it before it Googles you.
More on that later.
But now, let's go to the sweat-drenched concert at X-Day
by Reverend Trademark Gunderson
and the Evolution Control Committee
as he demonstrates his amazing hand-operated sampler device,
the ThimbleTron.
Ladies and gentlemen, the ThimbleTron is not difficult stuff.
It's just a matter of simple connections.
Just binary, really, which is just kind of yeses.
Yes, yes, yes.
And nos.
No.
Yes.
This is called No Time for Yes.
No.
Yes.
ritt
But then I pause it there from say I'm negative
Negative, negative, positive
Yes!
Yes
No, no, yes
Now I'm going to try a somewhat tricky overhanded maneuver here
I don't recommend trying this on your home thimble-tron by the way
Let's see what you're doing
It's okay to say no
No
Yes
No, no
No, no, yes
Yes
No, no
No
If your test is negative
Because you cannot get into the 리볼비
If you do not get into the rectangle
You cannot get into the rectangle
And becomedimensional
But just please
I don't know how this works
Okay
But you and me
No
You know what I'm saying, give me the whole thing
Yo man, I don't need that
But yo, you know what I'm saying
But you'll know it
Listen
No
but then i'm positive some say i'm negative but then i'm positive some say i'm negative
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes learn how to say no loud and clear
now
you'll know what time it is
a little bit here it must be the uh dripping sweat that is coming from every orifice of
everybody around here for that now well ask uh dr phyla drummond or dr howell a question about
x-day and we will essay to answer you hmm you know the end of the world the subgenius end of
the world just happened yeah ask a question any question we can enlighten you on this and other
topics um after or before one
uh anywhere you want you before after you can before anything you want uh and after oh thank
you that'll be 20 years yeah 20 bucks per question for dr hatton trademark gunderson show here
yeah yes yes well he's so he's not actually i.t that he's the only one who's come out of
that event with some sort of uh what's it called and i will look it up later i guess it must be
called trademark gunderson so did he oh he had thumbelina yeah thumbelina
look and there's a little arrow the arrow tells you what's important excellent well that's good he
went up because he's techno boy i can't imagine living in ohio but i bet it's fun because he was
really unhappy about cost of living and so there everything's five cents but uh but it's 80 it's
still costing only five dollars to live in america yeah there right like it was in 1986. yeah
um in 1986.
86 indeed exactly hopefully you're enjoying this uh this cruise and uh perhaps uh the
well the party uh saucer uh committee would like you to be accommodated in any way you like so
we're going to serve breakfast
biscuit
pancake
waffle
pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake waffle this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick this quick pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake dedicate pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake pancake carrotだから like bedderff thank you
amana story londo covert weekend's taking a live on change thank you
All right, now I promised a lot of you all.
I know you all have been expecting and waiting for a brand new song.
I mean, to get something brand new from Andrew the Impaled,
you've got to pull teeth.
And not mine, the one from the Sarlacc.
But I do have a new song for you,
and I think you'll really enjoy it.
It's called Third Person Blues.
Andrew's got them third person blues.
Okay, thank you.
All right, yeah, see?
Now here's the part where the set list, you know,
would have helped out here.
We're going to play a couple more songs
before the aminos to come on back up here.
But let me say again that I really appreciate being out here
and, you know, how to fuck things up.
I'm going to end up with my fellow Yeti people.
You know, we're all washed in the sweat of Bob.
This keeps on coming in and out.
It's kind of cool, I mean.
All right, now Jane's Addiction for Children.
Jane's Addiction for Children.
She'll be coming down the mountain when she comes.
She'll be one of many children when she comes.
Everybody had their own opinion.
Holding it back, it hurts so bad.
It's jumping out of my flesh, and I said, uh...
Yeah.
That's a way home, or you'll get that on the way home.
This is called Chameleon.
Chameleon.
Yeah.
I gotta make you mine.
My breath, you took it.
I saw you set afire.
I gotta know just what you're into.
Bands that you like most and where you've been to.
One thing I can do, I'm gonna Google you.
I'm gonna Google you.
Time to pay your tab.
You breeze up to the bar.
I see the name on your card.
Photographic.
I type it in and hit go to see where your name is found.
Looks like there's one in this town.
Fantastic.
I got your number.
I know where you buy shoes.
I bet you wonder.
Where do I get my news?
It's all the air, your banking records.
Place that does your hair, your scripts from Eckerd's.
Always something new when I Google you.
When I Google you.
I'm gonna Google you.
I bet you can't resist me.
You'd be surprised to know just what you can find.
About a person if you have enough time.
A little number unlocks a lot and I found it.
Hooray, I found it.
Now that I know just what you want in a man.
I'll go remake myself as best as I can.
I'll be complete.
So when we meet you can't resist me.
Bet you can't resist me.
Change my wardrobe and my music.
Don't let go, tease.
I can lose it.
Learn to play the blues.
If I have time.
I can lose it.
Fill my iPod up with Lenny Kravitz.
Get my hair done up like crap.
It never gonna quit until you're mine.
I'm reading all that I can.
I soak up all that I read.
I'll become all that you need.
Come million.
Why don't you take a chance?
Come on, give me a try.
I'll be your perfect guy.
One in a million.
You got no secrets.
At least none you need to hide from me.
I don't believe it.
Your mother lives right down the street.
I can't wait to get to know you.
Hope you take the bait.
Some things I want to show you.
Up in my computer room.
By the light of the cathode ray tube.
And I bet that you'll be flat-haired too.
And now I go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Whoa.
That was Andrew the Impaled from Pittsburgh,
whose shows also involve fire breathing,
eating light bulbs, walking on glass bobbies,
and actual impalements.
So beautiful.
Before that, the Evolution Control Committee
and the Puzzling Evidence Show talking about them.
Coming up, more jams by several fisted tales of Connie,
the band that exists only at X-Day Drills,
and Sim-G Gordon Gordon.
But first, an unusual wedding gift
presented by my nabar around the coronar,
Mr. Sistar.
A gift for Suds Pasha and Priestess Pisces,
who had been wed earlier at the campground
during the X-Day Drill.
Oh, wait.
It looks like Mr. Sister has something to eat.
Of importance, he's bringing.
I was sent here by Bob
to complete your whole marriage transaction here.
Whoa.
Okay?
Because you got married in July.
There's a factory special.
We don't want your marriage breaking down.
So what we have here is,
for free, Bob's Marriage Repair Kit.
Oh.
Yes.
And I want to read you here that
men always come to Bob with questions
concerning their marriage.
And Bob is never too busy to share with these men
that you are never really a successful man
until your marriage is successful.
Did you know that Bob is an unusual creature
in that he enjoys spending time with people
and giving his autograph to the people he loves?
And Bob's in love with Bob.
But for those who want to meet him
and greet America's most exciting evangelist,
Bob believes that once you get a man on his knees,
you have begun to really make a man
out of a possible mistake.
And this shows up first in marriage.
And then for those times
when your marriage,
let's say, gets a little bit of a flat,
alongside the road, and things ain't going quite right, I have here an album of musical
selectors called Alone Together.
And Joe Lilly presenting his whispering choir and his skyloft with an all-star accompaniment.
Absolutely. So, when it's necessary to be alone, and together, we have the soundtrack for you
as part of our July Special. And this is direct from the dealers.
Do to the mic.
Tro-lo-lo.
La-la-la-la la-la-la-la-da
la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la-la-la la-la-la, la-la-la la...
la-la-la-la-, la-la la-la-la-la-la-la-la la-la,
la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la na-la-la,
K. G.: Key changes.
la-la-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la-la,
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
And that's as much of it as I know.
Hello my baby, hello my darling, hello my ragtime gal
Perfect!
So everybody give it up for Mr. Sister!
What if it's all because they're sitting on their asses?
Slack is self-made
Not give or take
It's something you have to do
Cannot expect it to
be given to you
Nothing is free
But motherfucker don't take my slack from me
Motherfucker don't take my slack from me
I understand you're alone
And slackless
But a thief is still a thief
And you will find no relief
I understand you're alone
If you steal my slack from me
No rest for the slackless
The slackless, slackless masses
But don't steal my slack from me
I will hunt you down
I will make you hurt
I will find a way
For you to regret your birth
Don't steal, don't steal, don't steal
Don't steal, don't steal, don't steal, don't steal
My slack from me
Steal my slack from me
Don't steal my slack from me
This serves a warning
My final warning
I've had enough
I've taken
As much as I can take
And I'm gonna prove to you
I'm pretty tough
Because I'm angry
Angry at you
And I'm frustrated
With what you do
And I'll tell you
There is no choice
Can you hear it
The hate in my voice
Don't steal my slack from me
I'm making it clear as I can
You may think you're the better man
But I'll hunt you down
To the end of your life
Don't steal my slack from me
Don't steal my slack from you
I'll hold your slack
I won't buy the slack still
Or I want avania
I'll fight my deacons
Just that they're best
In my game
And you know
I've never pretty
I've never yet been
Better than they were
now.
The others promise you
hereafter, after
a bad time, we say
have a good time and we promise
you absolutely nothing
after that. You're on your own.
You find a locker,
do dozen things.
Once you get locked into a serious
drug collection, the tendency
is to push you as far as you can.
Downer,
springer, blacker,
bumper. Downer,
bumper.
Downer, springer,
blacker.
bankrupt.
Downer, springer,
generous.
Black, black, oh kill me
Pass me that prop stick, pass me that prop stick
Pass me that prop stick, baby
BEATBOX
It's a great combination, isn't it, Joe?
What's that?
Arm full of narcotics and a loaded gun?
Let her go, Bob.
Boy, did we get high.
Yes, sirree.
We sure got relaxed.
A physician must determine if tendon repairs are needed.
There it is.
But if the chief ever caught me taking these pills, he'd snap my head off.
Here, try one of mine.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, the chief himself's been on these for a week, and he's a change.
Our favorite area for clairvoyance has always been in the field of science and medicine.
What's your trouble, young man?
The Venusian group brought...
Doctor.
Now, see here, young man, my time is valuable.
Doctor, this is a medical emergency.
I hope you like that nonsense.
I try to make the audience a part of the entertainment, and they go along with it all just great.
That chatter with the doctor is no phony bit, really.
It's just the way it happens.
You'll have to make it in one night when you're down Florida way.
All right, nurse, bring the next patient in.
We'll see you there.
Off you go!
ared we go!
We're back to Planet frente in a few moments, you thug.
Let's see what's out here.
I'd like to give you a présent.
I could grab half to a green an8
and
then
disc patterns, you can send us
cow vomit,
tooth broken,
11-gated,
elongated,
creation-oriented,
spear gum,
restaurant,
scars, you can send us
Niki.
Don't look at me that way, Douglas.
You're mad.
Don't be frightened, Douglas.
The emergency, what service do you require?
Give me Dr. Rowe!
Doctor.
Good night, Docs.
Thank you very much.
Make me take off my clothes
and make me go out normal
and I have to go outside and change
before I come here.
Do you love your parents?
Yeah, I love them, but they're...
In culture schools,
the culture of the future
is not taught across the land.
Mere infants are taught all about
contraceptive techniques
and are provided with a plastic phallus
in the classroom
upon which they are trained to fit
rubber contraceptives.
This next one's called Rock and Roll Gestalt
and the San Andreas Fault.
SARAH MAX
Dr. Rowe, I sell a rock gooey
ann ladder for this کا
And change thatcelery
into straight regular lift lift reels
A cloud passed through me and my droogs
As we all did the twist in the frug
So we fell into some kind of fugue
And it sounded like someone was tuning his mood
It was a rock and roll gestalt on a San Andreas boat
And it tasted of the salt of the earth
We were feasting on our own after a bar
We slam danced at the victory tour
Give or take a few bruises or more
When the recorder went past fifty-four
There's a whole lot of shakin' down to the earth's core
Where the world is a mess
Where the sharks and the jets have been switched
Partners with the bloods in the crypts
Tipped the teetering total eclipse
And went tumbling twaddle
On the lips of another rock and roll gestalt
On a San Andreas boat
But it wasn't worth the salt in my beer
Another rock and roll gestalt on a San Andreas boat
And I haven't felt this way in years
And yeah
Another sonic boom
Has shaken up the room
We don't know what to do
We'd better do it soon
Wooo!
This is a rock and roll gestalt on a San Andreas boat
This is a full throttle assault on your brain
Now I just haven't got time for the
Pain
Amoeba Knievel did that
With lead singer Tommy Amoeba
Also from Pittsburgh
And the lucky husband of the amazing Fat Mandy
We really had a great line up of bands
They all busted ass and eardrums
Oh the collage about pills and doctors
Was by St. Byron Werner
We unfortunately did not get a good recording
Of the amino acids from Detroit
Who by the way are hosting another Detroit revival
On the holy date of 1-30-1-3
The day of Bob
Yes January 30, 2013
Can be written out as 1-3-0-1-3
Which of course spells Bob
Try it!
See subgenius.com events
Anyway luckily we did get a good recording
Of the amino acids tribute band
The Slot Rods
Who sound almost exactly like the amino acids
Minus the theremin
And the
The
The The
T
The
Th
Last
guitar solo
Thank you.
You've been listening
to the Subgenius Radio
Ministry Hour
of Slack.
For free information,
write to
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio
or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
There is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish
hark-a-back-flack-a-wharton
Philip Buckaburton
Perkaluma Burton
first night of the war.
Oh, yeah.
Friends, we're glad
you listened to this show
and we're even more glad
that some listeners
have donated enough
to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show,
but subgenius.com
and all the other
archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that
slack back to rebound
to you,
you should go to
subgenius.com
front page
or especially the radio page
or the catalog store page.
And help out financially
as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like
to be on the brink
of total poverty
and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you
still have jobs.
Even five bucks
makes a big difference
even if it's only once a month
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes
an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the way
of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks
and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation
P.O. Box
181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Thanks for anything you can do
to help let there be slack.
We have another video do you know
some там
by the motions
WHAT THIS?
I got to breathe right in.
No we are breathing healthy.
Achievement dollars.
Green pills!
Yes, bloody far!
Kill me!