We understand the value of every single person as a taxpayer.
Now that's the real value of every single human life.
A human life is one that pays taxes.
What do you make of the terrain?
Only thing that would grow up there is a weed.
And that's what marijuana is. A weed.
Now hear this.
All right, men. The smoking lamp is lit.
You mean we gotta sit here and let a hophead get away with murder?
Yes!
Great, Scott!
The Miracle of America.
Uncovered in smelly scales and it's spreading.
All for just $19.99 a month.
And besides, it's fun to have both your eyeballs looking out of the same socket.
There is nothing wrong with your television set.
Do not attempt to adjust the power.
Picture.
We are controlling transmission.
Something must be wrong with the radio, man.
There is nothing wrong with your radio.
Do not attempt to change the station.
We wish to make a stop.
We are controlling the transmission.
We control the volume.
We will control the volume.
We can change the tone to a fuzzy bass.
Or focus it to a tinny treble.
We can roll the air.
We can speed things up so fast you can hardly understand what's being said.
Or we can make things so smooth.
We can change the focus to a soft tone.
We control the content.
We can make it boring.
Food.
Or hilarious.
Food!
We can make it stupid.
Here comes the food.
Or moronic.
It's our show.
We can do anything we want.
Because this is...
The Soul Genius.
Our own show.
Quiet numbskulls, I'm broadcasting.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery...
Which reaches from the inner mind to...
Bob?
Hey! These look kinda homemade.
Why don't you see we light up, buddy?
What do you got?
Light a match.
That smoke smells like marijuana.
Marijuana?
No doubt about it.
Bud?
Yeah.
Man who smokes that stuff could turn killer in a minute.
I heard a lot of hand smokers say that.
I only want to take a few drags.
Later, I said.
Yup!
I got a headline back there all set and gathering dust.
It says...
Kill Bob.
I'd like to...
Kill Bob!
Oh no!
I wish him a long life!
A life filled with a torture I can now inflict on him!
I'm going to start right now!
To thwart him in a blendish manner!
Oh no!
People have been tortured.
No, no, no!
Stop that on me!
No, I'm not stopping you!
Listen to me for a second.
You're members of my religion who engage in brainwashing and brainwashing.
Oh, stop it!
You're so...
No, no, no!
Listen to me!
You were not there at the beginning of this!
You did not hear or record!
Brainwashing.
You are...
You are close!
You cannot discern what you're saying!
What you're saying!
Now, do you listen to me?
Some people say it's a sinister cult.
No, no.
L. Ron Hubbard.
Somebody is shooting.
No, you listen to me.
L. Ron Hubbard.
Isn't a religion.
Definition of religion.
Bigoted.
Is very clear.
He he freely in this country.
Bigoted.
Buddy, you got it.
Right here, right now.
I'm angry.
Real angry.
No, it's your turn to listen to me.
Dead, dead, dead, dead.
Why is Mojo dead?
The aliens should have taken.
I've been staying instead.
I've heard they turned him into some killer barbeque.
So I jumped into my rocket and I had a plate or two.
Something in my water in Texas.
Something that helps us keep our peer.
It's the little thing that makes us slowly go insane.
It's the secret ingredient in our fear.
The little thing is the secret ingredient in our fear.
Dead, dead, dead, dead, why is Ivan dead?
The pink boys finally got him, I heard they kept his head
So now he's on a shelf in the archive of the con
They bagged him while he was trying to mow his freaking lawn
There's something in the water in Texas
Something that helps us keep our fear
It's the little thing that makes us slowly go insane
It's the secret ingredient in our fear
There's something in the water in Texas
Something that helps us keep our fear
It's the little thing that makes us slowly go insane
It's the secret ingredient in our fear
Harbor!
Beer indeed
Secret ingredient
There really is nothing like a short, short, mispronounced
Psycho-psychotic ingredients in his, her beers
I like to make that last consonant very hard, like my forehead
I think that's sick, Sting
I think there's
There's all those people killing you different ways
I think the equipment in this radio station is sick
I can't hear myself on the headphones here
I think your headphones don't work
How about if I put my finger in your ear
At the same time you pompously disconnect the artifacture that we have set up here
We spend so many hours arranging all this stuff
Some of it goes back to the
Do you have any scotch tape or boogers I could use to hold that little wire in that little slot?
I need to keep the pole in the hole
I have some prehensile anal mucus
Which I was using for my surgery
I was teaching a monkey how to do tricks with
I was teaching a monkey how to
Well, you know, I wasn't really
Okay, no, I don't have any mucus or any rubber bands
But here is a rubber band right in front of you
Here's a rubber band
Will that do anything?
Oh, the broken rubber band
Yeah, that's the subgenius style
This looks like one of the new eye wrappings that we use
To try and keep us
Keep our thoughts inward
And our mobility down
And keep us smoking
Free
That is, for smoking
These things work like a charm
And we're not talking about magic
We're talking about actual charming things
Nothing more charming than a diseased rubber band
Around one of your organs
Awaiting the last moment
Oh, boy
So, why were they spurting your name so badly?
Why did they spew so much hate on you?
On me?
Yeah, Sting, Sting
Let's kill Sting
Let's kill him with a shoe
They, uh
Oh, that was by
The Lone Star Tall Boys
Dave
Beer and Texas
That just suddenly appeared in my email
The Lone Star Tall Boys
A song called Small Black Tape
The usual Fernanda Nandi
Lee Murr
Collages were there all through the beginning
Except for the intro
Was a mashup by Phineas Narco
Of now
National Cynical.com
Now, are his sinuses still intact?
I heard after the pre-functory agreement
That he had most of his sinuses removed
Well, he underwent an official subgenius third nostril opening
Right
And I think they had a mistake
A power failure in the middle of the operation or something
Right in the middle, boy
That happens
Praise Bob, you know what I'm saying?
That's the way it always
It has a similar effect on the brain as that coffee
That we drink
Just bought from the machine downstairs
Now, have you considered this?
Since we buy coffee from this same machine
Every time we do the show
Have you considered that perhaps
That machine isn't merely a machine?
What, you mean it's watching us or something?
It could be watching us
An artificial intelligence
Who cares?
They're watching us all the time
I'm saying it's a coffee dispensing camera
In fact, where is the camera in this room, I wonder?
Jerry, what?
Nuts last night
What's his name?
The guy that does the poker show?
Yeah, the guy that does the poker variety show
Trying to find the camera
He freaked out right in the middle of
Who Stole My Kishka?
And started attacking the walls
And pulling things apart
And just like in that old movie
The conversation
He finally found it
It was right where he left it
Right in front of him
I was reading this sci-fi novel
On the toilet the other day
It's one of those toilet sci-fi novels
I know
That your friends write
Most of them are
And in this one
It turned out
When you got
Towards the end
It turned out
That the conspiracy
Had been embedding
Mind control signals
In the television and internet
Everything you saw on your monitor
Was just a carrier signal
For something that was subliminal
And in fact, in this novel
People even got high
Off of certain subliminal light beams
And stuff
Well, I think it's highly likely
And possible in the future
If you could scramble
A few Codicies
You know, a different
Supposedly
It would work
I mean, it's not like
It's unresearched
Or even named like weird
Well, see, quarks have weirdness
And stuff, you know
It's not like some idiot
Just decided to come up
With some names and stuff
No, this is one of those
Sci-fi novels
That probably will find out
It was all true
Unfortunately
Sort of like
A clockwork orange
Which turned out to be
A whole lot more accurate
Than Stanley Kubrick's
Previous movie, 2001
It was
And we did a lot of work
We did a thing in 1999
Spoofing in it
It was 1999, I think
Wasn't that the year
Of clockwork orange?
No
Oh, I don't know
I don't know when that was set
Oh, no, not 99
It was written in the 80s, I think
But there were like
Wilding UK's
No, no, it was written in the 60s
Yeah
Late 60s
Because I saw that
As a teenager
It made me want to dress up
In funny outfits
And go out beating up old people
Me too
And go, man, it's going to be
Really weird in the 1990s
And it was
Yeah
And now I'm
Instead of
Instead of being like
The cool droogs
That beat up the old people
I'm like the old guy
Laying on the pavement
Going blurp, blurp, blurp
In the songs of his father
So
It's a no place
For an old man any longer
A no place for an old man
Speaking of tough guys
That beat you up
But you have to pay, too
I don't like that part
And the suicide booze
That they had in that show
Futurama
Where, you know
It's like a coin-operated suicide
Ha, ha, real funny
We laugh now
Because we do not have
Correct change
Well, you know
I had heard about
About a hundred years ago
I used to hear these hip-hop songs
That DJ A would play
As we'd be driving home
From the other show
And you thought they were
Always talking about your fests
Yeah, because they'd be
Talking about Stang
They were talking about Stang
There was one song about
We gotta do a Stang
And I thought
They're definitely saying my name
I remember that
I asked DJ A
I said, sir
Perhaps you are familiar
With the linguistic peculiarities
Of the quality
Perhaps you could inform me
What the meaning of this slang term
Stang
And he said, oh
That means the sacred scribe
Of the Church of the Subgenius
And it also means
A very manly man
Well, uh
A man who excites the passions
Of every woman he encounters
Or disagrees with
Depending on his pigeon-like mood
That's right
Now, that's a Stanga
See, I looked up
In the UrbanDictionary.com
And it turned out
That Stang had a number of meanings
Yes, you are
New meanings
You are now the Martin Luther
Of the Church of the Infid...
You are ensconced
As some sort of a hero
Of something
Well, I'm not a hero
Well, I don't know about that, Dave
Because here it says
Stang means robbery
As in
That
Biatch
Ridin' clean
On them
Spools
Look like we
Gon' have to make
A stang
That's the example
That they use here
Well, Stang is
So that's like a robbery
My name is synonymous with robbery
Stangbanger
Is a term used to describe
Any
Collar-popping pothead
Who meanders the corridors
At Bishop Stang High School
Well, that would describe you perfectly
Popping your collar
Or a frop of Zulia
That our
Collar's popping
I don't get that
Well, as you know
What's a collar?
A priestly sort of thing, perhaps
A religious sort of thing
Popping your collar
Oh, yeah, yeah
That's true
Well, okay
And fropping your mollusk
And then
Are you with the mollusk
At the end of the hallway?
My high school used to have
Play football games
Against Bishop Lynch High School
Not high school
Not Bishop Stang
So we'd call it a lynchbanger
Mm-hmm
Stang style is to unmercifully go off on someone or something
Or, secondary meaning, to screw up big time
And there's no sexual meaning to Stang style
Just those two
We'll get to that
It says, oh man, I messed that up Stang style
Mm-hmm, I can understand that
Or, girl, you know that man will make me go off Stang style
So that's like screaming and yelling and tearing your hair
Well, there you go
I guess my reputation precedes me
Yeah
A stanga is a word describing a man's
I'm glad they mentioned it as a word
Describing a man's ability to pull the ladies with ease
It is indescribable
The male can be an average joe
But he is just unnatural to pull any lady he wants
Any time he wants without fail
Well, there's the luck playing for you
And there's slack
And that's what Bob promised you
So, you see
So if you make up your own fake name
And make it something like Stang
That later on takes on slang meanings
And they'll markedly parallel the actual Stanguage
That you have evolved in your own
You know what I'm saying?
It's like an observer created reality
Note you're saying
You have created
An observer created reality
And now you live in this world
Where people walk around talking Stang talk
You see what I'm saying?
Only on hip hop records, though
Oh, but no, this is ever-changing
You're everywhere
Don't you remember the letters you've been getting?
The emails you've been getting from Germany lately?
And the amazing Hollanders that send you all these things about the Stangers
I did get a letter from a guy named Andy Stang
Who said, why would you
Why would anybody choose that name?
Because it's my church name
I chose it, you know
I was born Stankovich
Because you could actually see into the distant future
And see your name become an actual form of cultural
Stanged up
Stanged up means messed up or jacked up
There you go
Or cuffed up
That girl is not cool at all
She is straight stanged up
Stangblasted means to cuss out, demean, put down, put in one's place
See, there isn't a meaning on this whole list
It doesn't in some way befit your personality
I know, here's a note
Here's Stang with two Gs
Stanged up
As Melinda Smith would say
It's Stanga
A 13 year old dumbass who acts like he is in college
Two, a rabid fanboy
And three, verb
To Stang
To have a strong desire or urge to rape Tom Brady
I don't know
Who's Tom Brady?
To Stangle
Maybe you'll meet him in the future
And rape him vigorously
Or at least, you know, however he prefers
And you can write about that
Or think about it
Stangle is a sexual technique
Where you are doing your lady friend
And they sneak up on you
And tickles your dangly bells, let's say
Okay
Thus, Stangled
Okay, now once you've been Stangled
Or you are Stangling
Does the lady have to be your friend?
Not if she is herself a Stangle
In a noun case
A Stangle is a girl similar to a skank
She might stank
Maybe wasn't loved enough as a child
So she looks for love in all the wrong places
Troublemaker
Not someone you want to be seen talking to
Uber slutty
Well, not talking to
Tries too hard
Not very pretty
Future stripper
I think these are made by
I think these are written by the users
Some of them are just
They're derogatory towards animals
And towards
And to Stangdoodles
And Bobliogra...
Which a Stangdoodle is a strange tumor grown in unicorns
Which can later be removed and used as ice cubes that never melt
I bet it was said by a subgenius
Because you can only remove them with your teeth
With your teeth
But Stang was not always
I mean it was
It had different meanings in ancient England
English slang
For instance back in the 17 and 1800s
How did our forebears deal with rogues in yesteryear?
There was one method very common in Leith and Ristelrig
Which in many histories is missed out for some reason or another
This was called riding the Stang
The obnoxious person was forcibly placed astride of a rough sapling
And thus being elevated on the shoulders of a couple of large individuals
The popularly convicted was mercilessly jolted over a prescribed distance
And any attempt to get off was prevented by the crowd
Now I still don't understand what happens to the guy though
As he's being uh...stangled?
Is this another use of stangled or stangered?
Ah man all I know is this uh...headphone jack is completely stangled
Well we're gonna have to uh...
It's stanged up
Get new calcium with more calcium than any other calcium
And now there's calcium
Yes calcium contains one third of your daily calcium needs instantly
Ugh
Oh no
It's not even staying in there it may be better or something
Is that the one that was...
It keeps falling out it's just...
It just keeps falling out
Have you ever had that problem man?
Man that's the first time you've referred to me like that
You've referred to me as one of our familiar brothers
You always uh...call me It or YouBags
Which is a very convenient name now YouBags
YouBags
One who uses the YouTube inordinately and incorrectly
A YouBag
Let's see where was my uh...
I don't know I...I'm...
Okay if I were to actually be able to hear now I can hear things again
For all I know when I pushed that button earlier it was playing and I just...
You know it's coming out
And now I found a jack would you like to try to use it?
Uh you found now that...
No no no no no don't use I used that jack before I jacked in
Yeah I jack in friends I'll admit it
We're thinking about having a public confession booth at X Day
But you have to have correct change
We've done that before
Nikki Deathchick used to run the uh...
She would uh...dressed as a hot nun
Hot nun
She would uh...encourage people to come up and confess their sins
And then she would spank them
Oh sister
Which they mightily enjoyed some time before
Oh sister I've been bad
Uh...
I've been a lot worse than bad lately
Just trying to get through everything you were talking about earlier
I don't understand why there's so much hostility towards you
You've tried to enlighten me
You've tried to enlighten people
You've tried to bring them the truth if not the truth of the issue
Well I stank them man
What can I say?
That's what we do
Well what about you be stankin?
Is that wrong?
No that's stinking
That's like a...that's different
You be stanky you be skanky
No
Susie the floozy
Used to be choosy but now she'll use it
Said that the word stanky would refer to a kind of a smell that was
A bit...a kind of a...
Bitter and irritating but not exactly bad
Just...
Stanky
An inconvenient smell an inconvenient odor
Well something that really stuck out poked out at you
Well that's more than inconvenient
If it pokes out of its pants
What else?
Friends there is some news
If you ever look at the internets
On subgenius.com
I'm not selling anything this time by the way
I'm giving some...giving away the artwork
That has been done over the last year by the...
Great subgenius artists
If you look at subgenius.com
There's a new art mine
Art mine tunnel number 23 has started being excavated
And it's got about a thousand new ugly and pretty pictures
But miles and miles of earth removed to get those things up on the wall down there
Yeah I had to drain alt.binaries.slack
The news group of all of its art
And I had to drain an abscess
Yeah
To get some of it back on
That's how what we use to glue the artwork onto the internet
That's the stuff
Is we use the pus from the abscess caused by the bad art
To glue the art onto the screen
The other side not the side that you're on
Looking at obviously
Well and not
That would be impossible
Well and not you've heard of what
But the other side of the screen
Organic reconnections
That's where they're going
So it's all confusing because we're getting ready for X day
The world is going to end
And you know it's funny you always run around trying to clean house
Just before the world is going to end
It's odd the way that works
And you try and pack and you keep on going through your clothes over and over again
You know there's never going to be enough underwear to escape this place completely and finally
I mean you're going to be passing out for Centauri and stuff
And you're going to be looking for a pair of fresh shorts
Briefs
I'm going to be sleeping probably when X
That's my prediction
When I get ruptured
When I get ruptured up as Bob says we all will
All those of us who are subgenius ministers
On X day this July 5th
When I'm ruptured up probably what I'm going to do is go to bed
Well that's what you asked for
You wanted to be sound asleep as you were ruptured
No I want to be awake
Because if you're dreaming about something at the moment of rupture
You'll be locked into a real version of that dream
Yeah
So if you're dreaming you're appearing in your elementary school with no pants on
And everybody's laughing at you
That's going to be it for a while
That's going to be your reality
That was my reality 15 minutes after the first X day
Yeah
7-15 July 5th 1998 I was pantsed and being laughed at by 300 people
That should have told you something right there
That the members of the hierarchy are not exactly square
Well we're not exactly immune to comeuppance from the angry believers
We need more pseudo-religions
We need more comfortable lodgings with lots of comfortable things like saunas and naked Swedish ladies
We have those at Brushwood
Yeah but they're so primitive
I mean it's like well you're imagining
There's the little rascals style sauna
Right right
The little rascals style hot tub
Where sauna the S is backwards you know
Right
But it's
No girls allowed
Yeah
The girl haters club
There was a little rascals where they formed the girl haters club
Oh boy
But then Darla came along and suddenly Alfalfa was singing a whole different tune
And so was Spanky and everyone else they were all singing a different tune
They were singing this song
What is this song?
I don't know but a minute ago it was like a really awful version of Smells Like Teen Spirit
From some
I don't know what this is
I think it's music from Radio Cuba perhaps
Yeah that wasn't what I wanted to play
No they're filtering our funnels
Boys it's too late Reverend Nikki Death Chick is married
Too bad
Last weekend I performed the holy rites of matrimony and married Reverend Nikki Death Chick to Reverend Bob Wilde
That's his real name so she's Reverend Nikki Death Chick Wilde now
And soon she'll be Dr. Wilde because she's studying for her degree in
Torture or something
Yeah but she'll have to grow weird beaver teeth when she becomes Dr. Wilde
To ensure more fright in the smell of children
Oh she can't wait until some kid comes up to her wearing a bob button and being a wise ass
And trying to somehow impress her with his knowledge of the obscure cult
Yeah
When she gets to reveal her real secret identity
If I were one of those prepubescent students I'd probably just say
I'll just go put my head on her teacher chair and wait for her to come and sit down
And they go da da you know
Hey when we went to Dubuque Iowa to
Funny name for a town
Yeah what was it Princess Wee was going to write a song called
Don't Rebuke Dubuque
Beware the Maui Waui in Iowa
Something like that
But Dubuque is very historic
There are giant catfish there on the Mississippi River that have human feathers
And they have a big human festival
Where they all serve
They catch humans and have a big human festival
I missed that we didn't get served
There's nothing like deep fried human with a hush puppy and a bag of snot on the side
Lemonade fresh lemonade it's just like hand squoze
They don't say hand squeeze down there they say hand squoze
I don't know if that has to do with squeezing the actual hand or the lemons involved
But it sure is tasty
Well soon the Iowans and people from other states will be coming to Dubuque Iowa
And they will be converging in Sherman New York
Climber
At Brushwood
Sherman not Climber
For the annual subgenius migration to the western New York breeding grounds
That's another thing we're calling X Day now
I realize it is it's an annual migration
It is like the fennels or whatever they call them the fennukes that go over the cliffs and stuff
Following each other and having sex before and after
Yeah the really really horny ones
The lemmings
Will make the trip
You know the lemmings did not really commit suicide by running off cliffs
That was an idea come up with by a bunch of Disney camera men
Who would throw the lemmings off the cliff to add drama
You know to an otherwise boring documentary about these silly little rodents
It's a good year so we hired plenty of little gaffers to chase them
We didn't have to move
We would sit in our director chair and say lemmings hush begin
And they would all look like they were running over
And that's terrible to think about
I'll stop
Well we're getting ready for the great convention and migration
In fact I've already got a copy here of the welcome to X Day schedule
And the liability waiver
Check this out
Here's the liability
I the undersigned do hereby certify that I must be completely insane to walk into this place
Where I might witness or be induced to perform terrible acts
Which acts will probably be filmed and streamed to the internet
And I likewise recognize that I would be much safer staying outside the 10X Day gates
Signed your name here buddy
And that about says everything
But sister
Now is there a special disclaimer
But but but
Is there a special disclaimer for injuries incurred on the place with you know with the wilding you
That was it
There is they have to sign away their right to sue us
Even even a
And we get filmed
A shrapnel doesn't get you a lawsuit
Getting injured
Yeah
Uh now there is a warning on here
Warning all employees of the US government must prevent present identification to registrar before entering these grounds
All electronic recording devices and weapons must be presented for in-sphinction
In-sphinction
Oh in-sphinction
Prior to entry
Right
US code title 303 section 91998 jy5 dhs regulation 13013x
Well at least you've got the slashes down right
Because they will not do as it says
Unless you've got a
And you know uh Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and the Detardos is not on the schedule
Well you thought I was just not going to I told you a million times I was
The amino acids will be placed
And the
Equal health
Including screening
During bad film
Danger and dirt
Well, no, they're terrible.
They're really, really bad.
That's what I like about them.
Why did you not put my name on there,
at least saying I was going to stop by for a fritter
and a couple bags of snacks?
That's a good question.
I knew that I had screwed.
And there's a band listed which isn't going to play.
However, the band Mike Bison will play.
And Two Beans will have his disco.
You can't call it a rave because raves are illegal.
It's illegal.
Raves are drugs.
But this is a disco.
Discos aren't drugs.
So a process is now a drug?
Yeah, if it has...
There's a law in New York, apparently,
that if you put drugs in your hair,
that you will be able to fly.
Those little neon sticks, those are drugs now.
Anything related to a place where drugs are often used,
like raves, that's all illegal now.
And also, thinking about drugs,
is illegal.
Yeah, that's why you call it a disco instead of a rave
because everybody knows, you know,
people in discos don't do drugs.
It's only raves.
You can't retroactively think about drugs either.
And alcohol's not a drug.
That's another important thing to remember.
It's merely a substance you rub on your body
when you need a shot or a spanking.
Just keep that in mind.
Why do you keep thinking about spankings, Dave?
Nikki.
Uh-huh.
You were thinking about Nikki spanking your butt.
Well, you were talking about her.
Well, I was thinking about spanking her,
but, you know, I...
I wouldn't mind being spanked in it.
Actually, I've seen Nikki did get tied up
and spanked at one of those X-Days herself.
I think.
You think?
Yeah.
You can't remember anything about it.
I know, that's why.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
But, you know, as Mark Twain said,
if you never lie,
you don't have to think about anything.
Um, I don't understand how that...
Well, really, if you will, think about it.
If you don't lie...
Since you're lying,
you're going to have to think about it.
Right, you'll have to go back and...
See...
That's true.
I subscribe to that,
and I haven't paid for it.
But I believe in that.
What a tangled web we weave
when first we practice to deceive.
When you go out and try to stang somebody,
or pull a stang,
you know, then you have to remember
your alibi, your excuse.
You have to think about a lot of stuff.
And you have to think about your stangs.
You've got to think about who you lied,
which told which lie to.
I've got that problem.
So I...
And who are you stanging on?
I used to have that problem.
But now, I...
My curse is that I can only tell
the absolute truth all the time.
I'm the opposite of Bob.
Bob always lies,
but he's always right.
Yeah.
No, no, you've said that before,
and I still draw a big blank
when you say that,
because it's like the two sisters.
One sister always tells the truth,
and the other sister always lies, you know?
So you come to the fork in the road,
and which sister...
You know, it could be a very perilous journey,
so you have to ask the right sister,
which is the way to...
Um, Dobstown?
And so you see,
which is the way to Dobstown.
So what you're supposed to ask is,
you're supposed to say,
any one of them, you say,
what would your sister say
is the quickest road to Dobstown?
You know what I mean?
Wow.
And then she will tell you
what her sister would say,
and if her sister is the liar,
she'd tell you what the liar would do.
If her...
If she's the, uh,
truth teller,
she'll tell the...
You know what I'm saying?
You go the opposite way.
You've heard the story, haven't you?
I wish that our listeners could hear
what I was hearing on my headphones just then,
as the little...
the wire was jiggling back and forth,
and it was cutting in and out.
There's an expensive plug-in
on my computer audio system
that I could use to mimic
the terrible way that I've been hearing this show,
parts of this terrible show.
And you just mute it right now?
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay.
That's just what we did just then.
Now, see, I'm gonna have to go back
and have the effect now.
Forget about that now.
Ay-yi-yi.
Yeah, this, um,
our X-Day schedule and brochure
is a four-page booklet.
It has the nearest liquor store directions on it,
which is really important.
It's in Jamestown.
Not Jamestown, Virginia.
Remember that.
It's in Jamestown, New York,
on the western tier
of...
of, uh, New York,
near the shores of
Great Faken Quaken Lake Erie,
where you can get your fish
every day from 6 to 12.
There's also silence races
carried on in the background
by the bemused members of the church.
Some of them are too fat to roll down the hill,
but we prod them with sticks.
There's also, besides the confessional booth,
attended to by Spanky,
the sister Nikki Spanky.
I've read the saddest thing,
and that newspaper, The Onion,
it said that something like 59% of Americans
are now too obese to commit suicide.
They're so fat, they can't kill themselves.
The Onion never lies, does it?
It made me cry.
Well, are you sure it wasn't
the sliced onion making you cry?
Now, here's an Amsterdam...
This is a Dutch review of X-Day
that we found in an Amsterdam guidebook.
The X-Day house party
and freak show parade
is something even the back-to-gabbers do.
With a pumped-up number of beats per minute,
10 pills down your gob
for 20 hours of chomping your bit.
No ambience,
save for a couple of yellow cube lights,
haven't been able to kill.
I said this is from a Dutch translation.
Also, consider the fact
that bouncing around on bad frop,
probably pills, if nothing worse,
or bad shit,
church air, probably frop, if nothing worse,
is considered a definite no-no,
never mind what you heard.
And then, is it really your idea of fun
to stand around some crossroads
with no clue as to your whereabouts,
with a brushwood map in hand
which has snakes for roads crawling about
because you're hallucinating like an oil slide?
Well then, simply get to know a few people first,
which is not such a hard thing to do at an X-Day,
and all kinds of possibilities will, if need be,
arise by their own accord.
Wow, what a way of looking at it
through those psychedelic...
I'd like to comment more,
but since I guess I'm not going to be there...
Dave, it does say...
The postcard says you're going to be there.
Oh, sure.
The postcard says you...
So you know you're going to be there if the post...
I've mailed out 4,000 of those.
I'd rather be in a brochure because they're fatter.
I like big, fat, juicy brochures
maybe with three or four pages in them.
You know, a postcard.
I want maybe three or four pages devoted entirely to me.
Me, just for no reason other than I want to see it.
Well, once again, your tickler is stanging.
Yeah, everything is all stangy around...
Smells all stangy around here.
And your bells are burning.
Let's talk about hell and what they're not going to miss.
Think of it this way.
The first hour, the first hour they come into that Brushwood camp...
Brushwood, did you say?
I said, Brushwood.
They should call it Breastwood.
Breastwood?
No, no.
Once again, your vortex is spouting you off.
It's not Breastwood.
It's Borstwood.
It's Breastwood.
Flushwood.
And the minute you arrive there, there are all kinds of beautiful, sexy aromas invade your head.
And they plant flags and they put up their own schools.
And you start firing other parts of your brain that don't belong.
And the next thing you know, they own your head.
But it's beautiful.
It's just so beautiful.
And you look out over the horizon there.
And there's like...
Saucers like mirrored against the backdrop.
It's as if they were already here, but they're just on their way and you can see it that way.
And there's so many little kiosks and booths with so many strange things.
And I mean, it's like the evil doctor Lou...
Something, you know, you just walk up to one of these booths and you can have anything in your mind.
If you had one to have one with.
You can order something, perhaps herbs.
My mind is not my mind.
Uh...
Cloth things.
Yeah.
You could wear on your ears and eyes.
But that's not the exciting part.
No, no, no.
Of course not.
That's not the exciting part.
The exciting part is when they start shooting the children up with various chemicals which we use to make things easier.
Of course, you know a lot more about it than I do.
I'm not even sure.
I was just trying to describe what few things I can, you know, try and titillate people into.
Well, we can't titillate them into going to ag state because I stand to make money off of that.
See?
Yeah.
And this is a non-profit broadcast.
Oh!
I hurt myself.
Although if it makes anybody feel any better, usually we just barely break even.
It is a great party though and the lobotomies...
They cause.
Well, they heal up real fast by the time...
I mean, people at work might notice a scar for about a week afterwards.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And you can always just say, oh, well, I bumped my head.
Or I was at an amateur trepanning party or something like that.
They sting.
You don't have to let on that you're in a cult.
You always omit the fact that people have the errant one eyeball pointed left and one pointed right stare after weeks, weeks, weeks after lobotomies.
And, you know, the voluntary trepanations.
Yeah, but most of them do that anyway.
I mean, so nobody can tell the difference.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
But that's nowadays.
Usually what you have is some kind of occipital swelling.
One side gets real huge.
The other one gets real tiny.
And the eyeball looks like a little bead.
It pops in and out and beams neon messages to people or people.
People, yeah, people, sure.
Yeah, people.
That's who we want to...
We don't want anything because it would profit someone.
Right.
Yeah, we don't want anything.
Well, then let's just talk about Bob and what a useless character he is.
Yeah.
Bob.
Yes, Bob.
Himself.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
That's right.
Just thinking of him makes me leak and drain from all my glands while just thinking of Bob's pipe.
All my, I can smell the Bob's pipe.
The, the, my memory of the, the, the smell, the wafting whiff of Bob's pipe.
It just freaks me out, man.
You're a bad sign.
This is my happening.
The Bob's pipe.
And it's freaking me out.
This is my world.
Our grave of a soldier.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
There's a road in West Virginia.
A road where dreams come true.
Named after that Popeye comic who's entertained for you.
And if your life has got you down, there's a place where you can go.
Morgantown, West Virginia.
It's there you'll know.
Dreams do come true on Diamond's Avenue.
They do come true on Diamond's Avenue.
Well, he started out in grade school as a ventriloquist.
And he made so many movies that not one should be missed.
So pour a cup of coffee.
And fill it to the rim.
And watch those classic films that got a road named after him.
Dreams do come true.
Diamond's Avenue.
They do come true.
No time for sergeants.
Wake me when it's over.
Last time I saw Archie.
It's a mad, mad, mad, mad world.
Move over, darling.
The incredible Mr. Lampet.
The ghost Mr. Chicken.
The reluctant astronaut.
Herbie Ghost, Monte Carlo.
Hot lead, cold feet.
The prize fighter, Big Bully.
Then Cannonball Run 2.
Shake this gun in the West.
Pound to frame a fig.
The Apple Dumping Gang.
No deposit, no return.
Dreams do come true.
Diamond's Avenue.
They do come true.
Diamond's is the man.
Shake, bugger, and lean.
Watch one of his movies and he'll know what I mean.
And if your life has got you down,
there's a place where you can go.
A magical road in West Virginia.
Just ask my friend Joe.
Dreams do come true.
Diamond's Avenue.
They do come true.
Dreams do come true.
Diamond's Avenue.
They do come true
Like donuts have a new
Yes, dear friends.
The Chuck Hestens is the name of that band.
And you can reach them at myspace.com
slash thechuckhestens.
They sent a couple of CDs that were quite varied in styles of songs.
But they all mention Hollywood stars, though, right? Or not?
No, this is the only one they mentioned was Don Knotts.
And I played...
There's a lot of subgeniuses that are huge Don Knotts movie fans.
Well, they used to call Charlton Heston Chuck.
Do you remember those days?
When I was working for the National Gun Club.
And as Bob flies his private jet towards Fort Knox
to take over the U.S. economy and set it back...
Yank it up by its own bootstraps and set it back running
for him, the way it should be.
I'll sign that now.
I'll sign that later.
There's a signature for that.
It's something found...
in the wild.
Friend, are you ready to meet Bob?
And you know, we've predicted that the world was going to end
on a yearly basis now.
And...
And the world will end.
And you... And, friend...
The world ends tomorrow.
And you may die.
And, in fact, you will die.
And tomorrow could come any time, you know.
It may come in an hour when ye least expect it.
So are you ready to meet Bob?
Behold...
And or your maker.
Bob is probably not your maker.
They lay not asleep for the hour is of hams.
And it is before them as they sleep before the hour is of tams.
They know not the time of their...
You know, what the time was there that you mentioned.
Yes, the end times.
And they know their own time of they may...
Their own, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Friend, do you own your time?
Or does boss man own your time?
Come on.
Do you have to...
Do you have to urinate in a little jar every now and then
to prove that your mind is still okay?
It's changing colors, for God's sake.
Make that for Tom's sake.
And it'll stay the way you want it.
That's right, friends.
When you become a subgenius,
when they give you that urine test,
you'll break the machine every time.
Because they won't know what to do
when that...
Your blood pressure keeps changing
from yellow to green to purple to red to blue,
cycling,
and sometimes even with paisleys in it and stripes.
When it turns into a moving barber pole of colors,
how's Mr. Boss Man gonna deal with your blood froth content, huh?
When it breaks the machine, my friend.
Yes, friends.
And what are you going to do
when that urine sample begins tock down to the nose?
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
It's the tickest display.
It's the tickest.
Stop.
Jack in.
Jack out.
Track in.
Track back.
Okay, let's take a shot of this guy over here.
His head has just been shaved,
and there's all kinds of weird,
looks like they're henna tattoo markings
on the back of his head saying,
Bob was here.
Here's another one of beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful young ladies.
That's a good tattoo.
I haven't seen that done.
So I'm having Bob was here tattooed
on the back of your head.
Oh, that's as old as Conroy
or whatever his name was,
the Native American guy.
I forget.
I forget its name.
Tompo.
Tompo was here,
and so was Bob so many times.
Bob has been around the block
more than once,
and he offers you a form of slack.
Slack.
If you can handle it.
Most of us can't handle slack.
All the slack.
Slipper.
You could possibly ever want.
It comes and goes of its own free will.
No.
For your own pleasure.
Use it or lose it.
Or just stare at it for a long time.
That's what I prefer to do.
Sometimes I take my little slack box
when the kids aren't watching.
After I've all stuffed them in their mummy boxes
and given Grandpa a tweak on the hard pickle,
sent my old lady to bed where she belongs,
sneak down into the basement,
open up the mahogany chest,
and there it is.
My slack box.
It's got a pipe,
a pipe engraved on the side of it,
given to me by you-know-who,
one and only J.R. himself.
It was a day in Dallas in 1967.
I remember that day as if it was Tuesday,
for Christ's sake.
Look.
Somebody's been messing with my slack box.
Maybe it's one of them damn kids.
Maybe it's that damn woman
checking my slack.
Way more slack.
I'm feeling a little low-key.
Stressed and pressed and lonely.
I need an attack.
I gotta get back to my FX rack.
I'm feeling a little low-key.
Stressed and pressed and lonely.
The car is in.
I'm pursuing my signal.
The car is back.
Can't deal with no flack.
I'm not a flack.
I'm not a goose gack.
This grind I can't hack.
I need.
Way more slack.
I'm feeling the lack.
Getting tired of the mack.
Don't wanna read the fact.
Or crack the manual and shack.
My short stack, I don't even want to whack.
Rosie Palm and her four sisters are losing the deck.
Rosie Palm and her four sisters are losing the neck.
They're losing the deck.
Humbling, mumbling, fully hardest.
I just gotta stack the deck to fuel my frop mecca
I know I need way more slack, way more slack
Let me hear that guitar part sack, take these subgeniuses back
To the beginning of the start of something to give us all
Way more slack, way more slack, way more slack, way more slack
I need a little low-key, best pressed lonely
I need the tech, I gotta get back to my FX rack
I gotta pursue my future, I see the road's finding me
Way more slack, way more slack, way more slack
P.S. if you want to keep your track up, you gotta keep your track up
Way more slack friends from 4L Pr
of 4lprek.com
That's spelled N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F.
That was an actual song.
Norrell Preff?
Oh, that song.
That was a song.
Way more slack.
When you don't play enough and you need to weigh more slack.
How can you weigh slack?
What are you going to put on a scale?
Yeah, really.
What is slack for you?
It would be as if Temis, the ancient goddess of justice,
were holding her scales up high
and there was not enough slack in one half
and too much slack in the other.
Come on, it just doesn't make sense.
It makes about as much sense as the day we both had
putting shoes on the wrong feet,
arguing with other people's children.
And none of us have any right now, do we?
Or was that yesterday?
I'm giving my daughter away this weekend.
And I'm so glad that you're giving her to me, Stang.
No, not to you.
And not to Paul Mavridis either,
who always thought he was going to get that.
Yes, but why not?
I just don't want my daughter marrying a subgenius.
Yes.
That's right.
But what a present for any subgenius.
Stang's beautiful young daughter.
I won't do that anymore.
She's only 39, 48, whatever, 52.
I'm kidding.
She's 17.
There's been a lot of weddings in the subgenius era lately.
But not enough people getting married.
Just a bunch of weddings.
Yeah, and a whole lot of procreating.
That's good.
To create more little...
Sometimes it's good.
Yeah, 10-10.
With the barbed wire and the sandpaper.
Not so good.
Not so good, comrade.
Not over it.
Nah.
Well, you can try it.
Hey, have you ever...
Well, you raised a kid.
Didn't you use barbed wire some of the time?
Once in a while.
Keep them pinned in?
But we were kind of like getting off the barbed wire thing
and the sandpaper.
Weaved from the barbed wire.
Mm-hmm.
We used an electric fence to keep the children in.
One of those cattle fences like Pappy had?
No, more like for dogs and rabbits.
For rabbits.
Cattle fence would kill a child.
I thought maybe you just like cut it back a little bit.
It did actually kill a squirrel one day.
My son and I, when he was real little,
we went out in the backyard and there was a squirrel
standing, clutching the electric fence and not moving.
He had committed suicide, Stank.
And my son, who was about four or so, said,
why is that squirrel not moving, Daddy?
And I said,
that squirrel is dead, son.
That's a dead squirrel.
He touched the electric fence and held on and he died.
What a cruel dad.
And you know what my son said?
Someday I want to be just like that squirrel, Daddy.
Oh, my.
You did not lie to your child and say,
no, that squirrel is merely excremented.
He didn't, yes.
He's having a confused moment right now,
but then he's second hill snapped too.
No, you had to lay it on him at an early age of 35?
Oh, I thought,
we, yeah, we didn't hold anything back from our kids.
We told them all the horrors of the world immediately.
Except for about Santa Claus.
We didn't tell them the horrible fact about Santa Claus.
And boy, when we did, they never forgave us.
Oh, you can't blame them.
Tell them Santa Claus is a Romanian gypsy
with some kind of strange sexual habits.
The other kids mocked them.
The other kids usually get BB guns and converge on your house.
And they'll all, you know,
besides swearing to put out your eye,
they'll tell you the real political meaning of Santa Claus.
Santa Claus, they call him sometimes.
I just want to make sure them kids stay off my lawn.
Hey, it's one minute till showtime end.
And I'd like the listeners to know
that they're listening to Hour of Slack number 1106.
1106.
And if you want more information about what,
is going on here,
you can look at a website that never ends
called subgenius.com.
Subgenius, by the way, does not have an O in it,
although dot com has at least one.
At least part of the time.
And this music in the background is the swinging love corpses.
Before that, we heard some background music by
Javier Cugat,
Lombada,
and the Moog cookbook.
Oh, and Ed Fred.
Oh, and you forgot to mention,
you played some of my music too.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's detective music
was used at the opening of the show.
Yes.
And in the background credits of other shows
that Dave doesn't get to hear.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Heh, eh.
Okay, now let's see if I can...
I just noticed that pause button is actually,
the disconnected pause of the squirrel at your ranch.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Bah, bah, bah, bah, down on your knees.
The job is easy.
Fresh beauty.
Save yourself.
Take life easier.
I can even give it to you backwards.
Wow, how disgusting.
Lady, it was nobody else's butt.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
So dirty, you know.
I vibrate.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Mm.
Heh, heh, heh.
Hedge.
Pretty good, Johnny.
But that ain't the way I heard it.
Give me that monkey.
Heh, heh, heh.
That's what they all say.
Send over your...
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'd like to make a suggestion that I know will be very helpful to many of you.
Play with it.
Clap with it.
I finally got the darn dirty ahead to eat it.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
here is a vital message on our nation's internal security
from J. Edgar Hoover,
Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation.
Mr. Hoover's message is, and I quote,
For wartime security,
American industry has had to maintain secrecy
about many of its most amazing projects.
For instance,
The Sogenius Powerhouse.
Everything's flowing smoothly
until they start their undercurrent of bitterness.
They spread rumors round and round
and suck a lot of foolish people into the trouble
that they stir up.
It gets harder and harder to see clearly.
It becomes impossible to keep your head
above water.
You just go thrashing about,
striking out at everything in sight
and never making any headway at all.
Now, you can avoid getting into such troubled gang
just by sticking to the mainstream of friendship.
No purchase required.
No obligation.
Free while his supply lasts.