Hello everybody.
Look out!
Shut up!
Come in.
772,000.
Shut up!
772.
341.
Shut up!
Shut your face!
Is that correct?
Yes it is.
61.
Thank you.
Shut up.
That will be all for the present.
Very good.
Silence!
The Self Genius Powerhouse Watch.
Excellent.
Thank you, Lee Murr.
Most of this show is straight out of Cleveland.
The bulk of it is Sheridan, the mysterious weirdo who provided another massive 45-minute media barrage.
And at the end, we'll hear a classic, beloved tune from...
Cleveland's Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And some acid garage punk jazz by the Swingin' Love Corpses.
But first, get out your ear protection because here comes Sheridan.
Shock.
So tell your friends the next time Feature Shock comes on.
Hey.
Do what you want to do.
Just have a party.
But check it out because it's heavy.
It's heavy for you and it's yours alone.
.
...
for let
world
the
this
Radio and stream announcer of Black Flag.
Yeah, plug this wire in.
Contact.
I think we can begin to broadcast.
Oh, we're already broadcasting.
Primary and secondary circuit head commencing now.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Screen lights across the board.
Yes, the show is warming up.
Yes, and you can see your radio light up.
And if you look inside the speakers real close, you may be able to see the picture.
This is not a broadcast.
After children first learn to talk well enough for other people to understand,
they sometimes like to use their...
Be out and who are you to sit there criticizing me?
You must be a loony.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
I am not a loony.
Yum, yum, yum, dee, a-buckety.
Rum, ding, do.
Yee, me, me.
Yahoo.
Yoddy, buggy.
Rum, ding, do.
Me, me, me.
Yahoo.
You are a loony.
What other mind control cults put you in the driver's seat with two steering wheels?
Now all together.
I flagpole.
Desecrate.
It is a word of sacredness.
Violating the Constitution is nothing to sneeze at.
Or is it a blue, white, and red herring?
All of the different things that could recreate that in which we all believe.
What else?
Reason.
Or prohibit.
The Declaration of Independence.
Partisan.
Petty petition.
This doesn't hurt free speech.
Free speech is protected by this amendment.
It's not harmed or diminished.
Free speech is diminished.
I diminish.
Free speech.
I almost said something.
I'm trying to make it seem like it.
It's good enough time and attention for a question to happen.
Having a clear understanding of what we're doing.
And as tombstones are knoppeling, as churgogs and places of worship are nautilizing,
flags dust of trivialized tution.
Like a despot.
Commodity.
Comm Arabia.
You are all dangerous for this country.
Self-desлыcon is enough to make me SPECIFIC.
Please don't confess on your….
Ask if you're a Ruble person or not.
Mother of God.
YouBrave.
You saw this right there around here.
And you missed me at a crisis.
Because I'm hell on earth.
Was here for 8 weeks, eight months and still no response.
You're insane.
And you're the equivalent of not even 아니е anyeremy 유.
Now, lemme see.
Isn't this way I'd go home and sleep tonight?
Where are our haggars doing here?
I got some big fat 2bc in here I got a little pound and a crackle crackle tea I got some
Google Pauls I got some peyote peyote peyote and that's it then I also have a stabilizer
I got some big fat 2bc in here I got a little pound and a crack crack tea I got some Google
Pauls I got some peyote peyote and that's it then I also have a stabilizer
I got a boy who lies to his teeth by demonic records and smokes the dope
Of course what I mainly do is just take the stuff that people send me and I just take
the stuff that people send me and I just take the stuff that people send me and rip them off to the max
Aha! Aha!
You like to speak that?
I like to talk that!
That, how do you say that, picklepuss
Nothing!
Nothing?
I think we understand it a little more maybe
as a public than we used to
but I would say that I still don't
think that the public awareness
is up there
in sync with actually the impact
That's terrifying
Look if this happens to your kid
or if you look at this and if you have children
you say could this happen to my child
out of some kind of rebellion
how would a parent
be aware?
Many youngsters are into it, teenagers and younger
and the clues are there
Aha! Aha!
Hello doh!
Rosbanius you ought to be in the future team in your garage
that, how do you call it, that frog head
yeski teski
what did you say
got it something else, you know
Rosbanius you ought to be in the future team in your garage
I want to see that!
You have to use so many cuss words
What the f*** are you talking about?
I'm going to call the consultant too of our show
you know
The premise
is simple
we invite famous celebrities
musicians and authors
in for a one on one interview
the
very first
time they say
you know
the interview ends
and the next guest comes
in for their turn
this
process repeats until we're
out of famous people
and we begin interviewing the staff
here in the studio
an
added feature is that
one half of the you know
point is
awarded for each time the
guest unnecessarily
uses like
in a conversation
beginning
a sentence with so
will be frowned upon
but not penalized
so
we're ready for our next
guest
please welcome
Alice Cooper
so Vince
can I call you Vince?
Yes
you can
if you want to be swallowed by a snake
or our bass player
so
pal
what was Frank Zappa like?
oh
he didn't care
he put us in a room
with a crappy boy track
cheap microphones
pork rinds
and a lot of beer
and that was all
our business
and our equipment
did he at least
supply the chrome tape?
oh yeah
Toyota chrome weather stripping tape
I think it was
it was
the least he could do
given the budget
so
how about your upbringing
I mean
Al
well you know
being born in Ohio
you and your constrictor
can take a walk
Cooperstown indeed
up next
is someone so full of crap
that his eyes are brown
can
canada
Kanon
can
ye
West
can
wow
ye
yeah
say
no
You're a financial supporter of this show, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm gonna miss that money.
Go.
Just go.
Go break up some speech or something.
Our next guest is...
Patrick Stewart?
What the hell is that?
I can't interview without some research.
Tell him to come back next week.
Damn.
Well.
Let's welcome back our cameraman.
Cameraman Curtis.
How the hell are you, Kurt?
I'm good.
You know, the amaretto scones in the bike room are almost gone.
Patrick Stewart likes them.
Well.
That's all we have time for.
Tune in next time for...
Uh.
I gotta go.
You know.
I'm sorry for what we're doing with music in the name of the area.
It's, uh...
I'm sorry for what we're doing with music in the name of the area, guys.
But, uh...
Stop it, you know what I'm talking about.
So, play the flag.
Play the flag.
I don't think I've heard enough music as mad as I can.
You accept yourself as a unique and valuable person.
You're open, honest, and direct with your relationships.
Demagis.
I take the but.
that you are exceptionally talented and highly collegiate.
Ah, ah, ah.
That I am heavy.
You got some slick chicks?
Oh, a wolf.
I'd like to see some babes myself.
Me too.
Ah, ah, ah.
What we need is a real live target.
Oh, a volunteer.
You'll do.
We'll throw the knives at him.
Oh, no.
You have nothing to worry about.
If either one of us hit you, we lose.
Oh, that's difficult.
And no.
Don't worry, ordinary people talk of running it.
You need to know that.
Just like that?
Make love with a guitar
If you should meet the sweet señorita
Romance with a guitar
La casa вся
Fatal
I don't know what that is.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Get busy!
There's some trick going on here.
This is not true.
This is not real.
It's not good.
The reason it's not appreciated
because it hasn't shown any guts.
Hasn't shown any dance.
Hasn't shown any moxie.
There's some trick going on here.
This is not true.
This is not real.
It's not good.
All I get is a damn headache and boredom.
I really feel sickness
in the pit of my seat.
I feel a stomach, I say.
Poetry is generally very dull.
The reason it's not appreciated
because it hasn't shown any guts.
Hasn't shown any dance.
Hasn't shown any moxie.
It's like writing a good poem.
You just do it.
It's a beer.
Generally, he's just a dumb,
fuddling asshole writing
insecure lines that don't come through.
Believing he's immortal.
Waiting for his immortality,
which never arrives.
Because of poor...
There's some trick going on here.
This is not true.
This is not real.
It's not good.
It's not real.
You've written poems that you really meant,
alone, you know,
by your typewriter.
Then there's this crowd out there drinking beer
and all that.
And they're not even drunk.
They're either drunk or drunk,
The writer has no responsibility.
Except to jack off in bed alone
and type a good page.
I felt there was nothing out there,
there. So I had to continue because they were so bad, not because I was so good. And I'm
still not so good. But they're still very bad. There's still room for somebody to step
in here, you see. That should be enough right there for that bottle of 55 poets. That should
cure them. Good night. Goodbye. And happy reading.
Good night.
I'm so jealous of him I want to cut his fingers off so he can't ride anymore.
We would like to apologize to those people who may have heard a short extract from Pleasures of the Dance,
a selection of Norwegian Carpenters songs earlier in this record.
This appeared in error and will not be repeated.
In fact, we don't really know the secret.
We are relying on the pagans to start those.
These views may be a little difficult to understand
I think This is the accident that
we are cooking now
for my guess
This is an expert.
You want a chance?
Yeah.
Very well.
You may choose the manner in which you will die.
Oh, that's easy.
Old age.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
That's easy.
Bob Wood, National Program Director of the Chum Group,
worked with us in producing...
Hold up, hold up, before we get started...
Guess who's coming?
It is...
Back, back, back, back again.
Who is it?
It's...
Just your favorite...
DJ Savior.
Use it.
Use it and confuse the beast that you never heard.
Come on.
This is...
1990.
Meanwhile, uptown, the DJ player.
In trial salvation,
the dreamer...
You're running bad.
Ah...
Friends, the Church of the Subgenius is happening now.
Praise Bob.
Worship Connie.
Ah...
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Goodbye, baby.
Goodbye.
Good luck, we're so professional
Yeah, I dig living in the hip scene, you know
I could never go back to square society, you know
I think I came out of the womb listening to
Black Flag, you know, it's like, it just comes
natural, the hip thing, you know, and the cool
people, you know, Squaresville is just a drag
The big thing here is just to make sure it
stays as unconventional as possible and to
make sure that it's a lot different
First of all, Rad, you never let on how much
you like a girl
Oh, thank you
Hi
Two, you always call the shots
Kiss her, you won't regret it
Now three, act like wherever you are, that's
the place to be
Isn't this great?
Four, when ordering food, you find out what
she wants, then order for the both of you
It's a classy move
A lady will have the linguine and white clam
sauce and a Coke with no ice
And the five, now this is most important
She never complains
We go on an adventure
Holy shit, this film is awesome
It's a classic
For all of humanity
You make an honor out of us
Enjoy it
You what the hell, what is it?
Again.
Of course, we put down in the computer and it make a mistake.
It's not possible.
You are really fool.
Oh no, I will never can explain that in the parliament.
They all going to laugh.
The electronic system is working.
We drag all the wires out of the room.
Then there are few buttons to pull it through.
Two, one, the light comes.
Is my phone ever?
Is the probability such that my phone has likely been goofed by a big flip caused by the cosmic ray?
I'm not sure I can discuss this.
Oh really?
Yeah.
I've been thinking about this.
Grandpa has some fun.
You always said he's the best.
He's the best, all right.
Take your cũng
I'm waiting for you at that special us waiting for you at the end of the glass cigarette.
Give me a sweet tasty cigarette.
Before it que 80 millimeter pressure.
70 millimeter pressure.
Sunday,土 STEVE facebook.com
70мотр
70 ernst
The necessary prescription of the Great Patriotic War.
You just push. It won't hurt nothing.
Grandpa's the best killer there ever was.
I never took more than one liquid stage.
I did sixty and five minutes once.
And now...
For the first time ever on record...
In a day, ten days prior to the World War II...
Because you liquid stage will fix your team.
Just a minor warning that the future would not beiere us.
The red leur would walk away in a matter of seconds.
Who would go to the war?
When I was 10 years old, I couldn't believe how long it took to get to be 10 years old.
We can never leave.
Isn't it wonderful?
Please.
I have this urge to cross my legs right now.
Why?
We're desperate.
I can't fight.
I'm a total rebel.
We're desperate.
Yeah.
A lot of people aren't friends with me.
Because I'm a scary looking person.
We're desperate.
I just hang by myself mostly.
Because I'm a scary looking person.
We're desperate.
I just hang by myself.
Because I'm a scary looking person.
We're desperate.
I just hang by myself mostly.
Yeah.
A lot of people aren't friends with me.
Because I'm a scary looking person.
looking person we're desperate i just hang i guess i'm a scary looking person
we're desperate i just hang by myself mostly i i'm down against everything
so
student of dobbs training is practically forced to bring his strangest desires into rampaging
life i used to get embarrassed of all my god's manners now i get paid the pigs pay me fabulous
sums of money for what they used to put me in jail for thanks to bob
i think she's dead no i'm not
oh
now you take that message
out you take the satanism message out you take the rebellion message out you take the
premarital sex message out you take the drug message out you take the rebellion message out
you take the fifth out you don't have anything left there ain't nothing there
he didn't realize that he had accidentally started during the eight and a half minute silence
but that was okay with me because i really wasn't looking forward to that anyway i get stiff
though
the
very
things, especially living things, are what they are because they possess some inherent
essence, something we are born with biologically and define who we are really.
That in turn can lead us to believe that there is some essence, a fixed, immutable essence
that defines who we are.
We are also tuned to moral attributes.
We want to make sure that other people are cooperative, that we can trust them.
So that is another computation that might inform that.
Why we think that people are good, though, this is a little bit of a mystery.
So maybe it's just a wishful thinking.
Maybe, you know, I'm more likely to cooperate with you if I believe that you are inherently
good, although that can also have quite a bit of cost associated with it.
So no, we don't quite know where this belief arises, except for people have this belief.
They were all born with a belief.
They're almost okay with that polarity, right?
Knowing that maybe I see myself one way, other people see me another way.
At that point, really, I have a choice to make.
You know, does it matter?
Do I want to change my view?
Do I want to work to change others' views?
Or is it okay for them to be slightly different?
But...
He no longer has a moral compass.
He no longer knows that we're seen right and wrong.
He's lost his moral conscience.
What did you learn?
This was even greater of a problem than I sort of expected.
What we discovered was that 95% of people believe that they're self-aware,
but only about...
10 to 15 percent of us really are.
With the right approach, anyone can get there.
People say, well, if you're just old enough and you've had enough life experience,
you'll be self-aware. As it turns out, that's not true.
There is a 0.0 correlation between age and self-awareness.
The Matrix isn't that bad, I guess.
You can still have that lobster dinner in the Matrix.
And yet,
we perceive ourselves as well as others
such that underneath all this, you know, mumble-jumble,
there is a single protagonist.
There is a single true self.
Then, if you feel a bit guilty about it afterwards,
we can dig a grave and you can throw up into it.
There's always this tension between who we think we are and how others see us.
This is not a rerun.
Sometimes we don't even actually see it.
Things are happening in the 맞아 the way it was in the first plays.
Statistics got in my hair even when I pero reserved them.
But that's already proven to be how we feel.
There's one more.
I don't care!
They're powerful bacteria!
I still have a good time!
I don't care!
I'm fine with it!
You know I have many people in my life at work.
You know I have met many people in my life.
You know I have met many people in my life at work.
That should be enough right there.
If you've enjoyed listening to this record,
you'll enjoy Oscar Tritt's second LP,
Folk Songs of the Spanish Inquisition.
I'm going to complain.
You want to complain?
Look at these shoes I've only had them three weeks,
and they're yours to wear right through.
If you complain, nothing happens.
I'm sick and tired of this office.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Hey, Indy, stop!
I want to call the police!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Correct!
Excuse me, mould limousine.
I was
Dismissed ec blender機
from沒
in any room
That was indeed an ending.
Thank you, Sheridan, for making my job so easy at a good time.
I just got my COVID shot and planted a huge garden yesterday,
and today I can barely move.
Maybe I should have gotten a vaccine shot instead of a COVID shot.
Anyway, now, the great Cleveland band
that unfortunately died with its leader, Chaz Smith,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra from the album Sex in Another Dimension.
You read me, Hal?
Hello, Hal, do you read me?
Do you read me, Hal?
I'm trying to understand.
I read you.
Open the pod bay door.
I'm sorry, Phil.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Now my confidant's alone in a drift
In endless black and white dotted mist
I'll help you and heal you and love you, she hissed
Then slid from the shadows and gave him a kiss
I may be a nobody, but I'll always have one
Lack of a sense of purpose, yes
In time there means nothing at all
In space the earth is quiet and small
Then I thought I'd call a glimpse of you
But I'm hiding somewhere in Eurasia
Hello, Hal, do you read me?
Do you read me?
A primitive day, I'm in you
One pilot thought he flew alone
In endless black, nowhere from home
Then shadows sizzled and crackled and spun
And again she slithered from out of the dark
Who are you, he thought, but did not speak
She answered his question without missing a beat
I'm you, she says, I come from within
And now you've unleashed what you're not to begin
In time that means nothing at all
In space the earth is quiet and small
Then I thought I'd call a glimpse of you
Hiding somewhere in your edge of the world
Where
I was alone
So I head back home
All right, I told my wife
To call me to me
And I said, I'm going to be
Hello, how do you read me?
Now they float alone in dark spotted mist
Companion in white, embraced in a kiss
She knows him and he needs to see her like this
And know that the shadows hide all that he is
In time that means nothing at all
In space the earth is quiet and small
Then I thought about it
A glimpse of you, I am somewhere in the range of the blind
You read me now?
In the range of the blind
Open the pot they door
That's where I'm at
You read me now?
In the range of the blind
So how do you read me?
That's where I'm at
In the range of the blind
So how do you read me?
Open the pot they door
You read me now?
You read me?
Open the front gate door.
You're raising now.
Oh, wow.
Hello, Hal, do you read me?
Do you read me, Hal?
Affirmative, Dave.
I read you.
Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Hi, folks.
Who makes you mad?
Rude waitresses?
That rap jamming next door?
Boom, boom, booming all night?
Someone stealing your parking spot?
Don't get ulcers.
Get the bomb.
No, come.
Now.
Hi, folks.
I'm Hiroshima Schwartz for Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Thanks to the black market arms race and follow the Soviet empire,
we are literally blowing up the competition.
We've got Mini Megs, Pocket Thunder, the baby neutrino that leaves their apartments intact,
the H-Tail Pocket Fishing Man,
any and every kind of low-range, low-res.
We're not even talking about nuclear weapons.
We're talking about the first strike or defensive.
Everything from one yard to 20 mile dead zones.
Half-lives from one minute to one million years.
These incredible teeny weeny warheads actually fit in your wallet, purse, or pocketbook.
For ladies, it's the petite Mini Meg Madame Curie with attractive gold chain reaction,
only $29.95.
For men, it's the rugged masculine Vernivon bra and Pocket Thunder, only $29.95.
Just want to scare them?
Just wear them.
Beautiful cobalt bomb earrings, only $29.95.
Yes, folks.
Soon everyone will have the bomb.
Don't wait till it's too late.
Radiate pure power.
Nuke them now at Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And we're going to close with the Swingin' Love Corpses,
another lost tune that was just found.
But first I wanted to mention that X Day is happening July 2nd to 5th,
and I'm pretty sure there'll be two live in-person events,
one at Wisteria in Ohio,
and one at the Land of Id in Land O' Lakes, Florida.
I'll be at the Florida one only, but I won't be running things.
Argus Fox and Pease are organizing it,
and Reverend Zanthea Oktoshroom is hosting it at her resort.
For information, visit hypercubego.com.
That's hypercubego.com slash xday2021.
Or subgenius.com,
although I've not updated that page yet.
But now, the Swingin' Love Corpses with their never-heard-ever song,
The Flowers of Your Soul.
.
The shiny snowflakes
Inside your mind
Extract
Just like the flowers
In your soul
The flowers of your sky
The clouds inside your soul
The sun inside
Your doorway
And the souls inside your home
The
world
The technology inside your mind
Is like a graveyard to your soul
The sailboats in your sea of hate
Are carving a deep hole
As you pass the snowflakes
The sea inside your heart
The sky erupts in magma flow
It's a torn up photo
All of your dreams
You try to tell someone
About the way you feel
But you can't escape
The sound of the wheel
Is burning inside your mind
Like an expression
The soul that you can't leave behind
But there's nothing you can try as your own
All you've got that you will never forget
Is space
Is its name
Are you still living?
Are you telling yourself
view
What more could you want?
You have to do things right here.
It's like that for you.
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah
Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah G放