Do you want more from life?
Are you struggling to find your place in the world?
Maybe your place isn't in the world at all.
Long ago, people thought the stars determined our fates.
What if you could choose your star?
A faraway sun.
And orbiting that sun, a new world.
And on that world, a new life.
A fresh start.
Room to grow.
We are the Homestead Company.
And your future is our business.
Say yes now.
To book passage.
And to be a part of science.
Someone on our home planet?
Your future back.
One to perfect.
This universe.
One to finish.
Year 2 dispersed Shaftesbury fingers!
We don't have no time for that
All we want is an hour of slack
Do you know where it's at?
All you need is an hour of slack
Everyone needs a straight jacket
Hold it tight, let's all slack it
Hold on tight, let's all slack it
We're collecting, typing it in
We're selecting, we're tapped in
We brainstorm, we uplink
We're on the platform, we're in sync
We're doing what we're told
We're on system overload
We're online, we've got the stats
We're on time, we're fixing facts
Feel the drive, we do what it takes
We're saving lives, deleting mistakes
We're doing what we're told
We're on system overload
We're feeding the crowd
We work for you
It's what we do
We're on system overload
We analyze this, we analyze that
Compliance matters, data dispatch
Behind the curtain, you are not needed
When we are certain, you are deleted
We're doing what we're told
We're on system overload
The distance between the stars is beyond imagination.
A space too vast to cross.
Until now.
Today's starships, powered by ion drives to half the speed of light, make the journey
possible.
The new barrier is the space.
The future is not space, but time.
How do you reach the stars when the voyage is longer than a lifetime?
The answer is sleep.
The HSI-709 is the state of the art in hibernation.
No chemical bath, no traumatic freezing process.
Just complete metabolic suspension.
Our proprietary technology doesn't just pause your life processes, it arrests all biological
activity down to the microbial system.
Another آپous introspection lies beyond the beat.
You are
I teach
Fresh
Master the
Arrange
No chemical bathroom
No natural disturbance
Heaven
One minute
cuál
Western
between heaven and earth and hell
You live in great vanity
of the love that you need to feel
J.R. the Bats
was killed so many times
But by the love he had
the life that he now cannot die
J.R. the Bats
Bob speaks about conspiracy
and the false that they sell us
To join a false society
The church of some genius
J.R. the Bats
Whether he was pounding his way through a Girl Scout cookie eating contest or meandering
through the back roads in search of a pancake breakfast, we'll always remember Doug Smith
as an original, the one and only cheap gourmet and the fun ranger who with his wife Polly
showed us the lighter, luscious and less costly side of living in western New York back in
the 80s.
Doug Smith, St. Joseph's Festival is a happy occasion to be sure, although maybe it's just
a little bit more solemn than what we perceive as the tip of the iceberg of the St. Patrick's
Day Festival.
Doug was a former Courier Express newsman from the old school, the go-to guy in the
newsroom when we had a question about grammar or style.
He was a gifted writer who often used his considerable talents to write about baseball,
the game he loved.
And he was doing that right up until his last.
A year ago, Doug and Polly invited many of us to share a farewell hot dog.
That's where Doug passed away surrounded by loved ones and leaving all of us with fond,
lasting hot dog memories.
On the Starship Avalon, we believe your voyage should be as extraordinary as your destination.
That's why we're offering our elite passengers a special gift.
A new level of luxury.
1,200 thread count sheets of the finest hydroponic cotton.
300 cubic meters of personal space.
An unlimited water allowance.
Speakerless surround sound.
A library of over a million movies, series and self-casts.
If you can take your eyes off the best view in the universe.
The best view in the universe.
Elite Suites.
Only on the Starship Avalon.
.
Tango Lessons in a Fascist Whorehouse.
A beautiful thing.
Before that little news report.
Oh, the song about J.R. Bob Dobbs was by Reverend Burn Bridges.
And I can't really hear the lyrics to that.
So I hope they weren't too offensive.
It seems like a catchy little tune.
And System Overload there at the very beginning, as well as the Slack It titles.
Are by Exposed Four Heads from their new album Push Me.
And of course, some commercials from our sponsor.
Now, we're going to be calling Lonesome Cowboy Dave tonight.
And we'll also be reading from Lonesome Cowboy Dave's novel Neighbor World, which we're proofreading.
But first I wanted to read from...
Dr. Onan Kanabite's book, OVO 21.
Actually, it looks like a book, but it's an issue of his zine that he's been doing for about 40 years now.
This one is called OVO 21 Terminalia, and it's a collection of rants that he publishes these.
He is a publisher, just as we have become publishers.
Using the print-on-demand and e-book way of doing it, where you don't have to spend any money, but you can publish books.
He led the way. He showed me the way, personally.
He wrote me a very clear, concise letter that said, here's how you publish books.
And he announced to me that he has actually paid his rent sometimes, using the income from these books.
But in this particular...
rant...
called Sophistication.
Oh, it's got a great quote at the beginning.
From a friend of ours, Odorous Orungus of Gwar.
The late Odorous Orungus, who said,
Virtual reality satisfies man's need to stick his head in a box.
I'm not going to read the whole rant here, but it's great.
There's just a little section.
The sophisticated world of today is taking away ever more of our ability to discern what is true.
The mob courts of public opinion are weaponized with social media.
Video and still image documents can be manipulated beyond anyone's ability to identify.
Graduation rates from public education have never been higher, and the quality of public education has never been lower.
College degrees are easier to get and worth less.
Our leaders can make the most self-evidently false statements, and yet our nations lap it up as divine ordinance.
The United States has never been dumber.
How are things in your country?
In the sophisticated world of today, good guys and bad guys are not recognized by what they do, but by what others do.
What others say of them.
Plagiarism and publishing fiction as fact is what bad guys do, but when a good guy does it, say Alex Haley's book, Roots, all is forgiven and quickly forgotten.
Quoting from the white nationalist website American Resistance is what bad guys do, but when Slavoj Zizek does it, the incident is not to be a concern.
Pardon me if I pronounced that wrong.
And when the marching morons get it stuck in their melons that some guy is a bad guy, they're a bad guy and there's no redemption.
It's clear that Saudi Arabia had a hand in 9-11 and so the United States attacked Iraq, because by gum they're the bad guys.
It's true that the United Kingdom has a problem with Muslims doing what Muslims do, and so the United Kingdom banned the most peaceable and articulate critics of Islam from entering the country.
Robert Spencer and Pamela Geller.
Because by gum they're the bad guys.
Women around the world are being subjected to genital mutilation, forced marriage, honor killings, stonings, being set on fire, acid attacks, second class citizen status and more by Muslims.
So feminists are criticizing video game authors because by gum they're the bad guys.
The Islamic State is abducting children who are then sold as sex slaves or criminals.
Or crucified or beheaded or buried alive.
And so the White House is hosting conferences about those who lack courtesy online because by gum they're the bad guys.
When the masses of asses, the democratic will of the people that is, get together with their torches and pitchforks, there's no stopping them with trivial evidence and objective fact.
Some men are crowned with halos, some with devil horns, and the world gets slightly more sophisticated.
For example, the American people are crowned with the mainstay of the human race, the blue-collar people.
It's not the American people who are the most sophisticated.
Well, that was a short excerpt from a longer rant by Dr. Onan Kanabight who actually, he writes under the name Trevor Blake sometimes.
Trevor Blake of Portland, Oregon.
And you can find him at Box 2321 Portland, Oregon 97221.
Or just Google around for Trevor Blake, Onan, Canabite.
OVO127.com
It is.
And that brings us to another wonderful book, a novel this time, not rants.
The novel Neighbor World by someone called Dave DeLuca,
who also goes by the name of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And before I call Dave and put him on the air, I'm going to read from his book a little bit.
The main character, Standard Mazuk, that's his name, has just gotten into his car,
which they call an EMAG. It's not exactly a car.
The MAG's voice intoned,
13 minutes to...
destination.
Then the sound of music swelled through the MAG, a song called El Chimpy,
with surfy psychedelic guitars, a Latin edge, and screeching chimpanzees.
The MAG accelerated and leveled at 50 kilometers an hour.
When I was a kid, cars could go a hundred miles an hour.
You could go anywhere.
I'd rented cars in Car Town,
but the speed limit was 30 miles an hour.
I'd driven 25 miles per hour down there.
An EMAG was a servo, a computer car, riding the neural circuitry of an immense transport grid.
It could be driven manually, steered to the left or right of the path, slowed down and stopped,
but it was still part of a closed system, totally next in, like everything else, Neighbor World.
Rows of HABs fast-forwarded by, filled with neighbors who had never seen their neighbors.
They were in their homes from the outside.
Wet leaves were smeared all over the HAB windows, but that was okay.
No bored kids or horny teenagers ever peered out of them.
The neighbors' world was in the screen.
Images and sensations passed through neighbors at light speed,
and they traveled anywhere on light.
They didn't need to go outside.
The global neighborhood was their living room.
They were all dreaming in unison.
To me, though, gliding in a red, gold, and silver EMAG was nice.
It was like being in a big local where neighbors went outside sometimes,
to live spots, to plays, to full-saturation enviro-parks.
In big locals, they knew how to live, not like 838's Zoombies.
Wow.
Well, friends, yes, this novel is a little bit different.
This novel does take place in the future.
In fact, here's a clue in this paragraph.
What year was it, anyway? 2037?
But years weren't numbered in 2037.
It was just last season, or this season, or next season, or three seasons from now.
No numbers.
Seasons and years were merely green access markers that turned amber after you passed them.
Time was relative, wasn't it?
The past and future were one.
There was no common era.
Only then, now, and shaping up.
A nice quote there from Neighbor World by Dave DeLuca, soon to be published by the Subgenius Foundation.
In fact, I'm reading from an actual book that we're looking for technical mistakes in.
So, let's dare to call the Dave and see what happens.
Princess Wee has joined me for the important phone call.
It's calling somebody, but I don't know who.
That's not right.
It's not funny. You're laughing.
It's not funny.
I'm going to call his work phone, which is really his home phone.
But it is funny.
Do we hear it?
Yeah, we hear it.
And hopefully he can hear us if we yell into that and these.
Hello? I must adjust something. Wait a minute.
Oh, he's going to adjust something.
I think I know what that something is.
He must have to adjust something.
Something big and heavy and sweaty.
And he's been sitting on it all day.
It needs to be pulled around to the front so it can air out.
That's what I believe.
I believe what I need to believe.
That is what Pappy said.
And that's the human condition, folks.
We believe what we need to believe.
And I need to believe that this book, Neighbor World, will...
be a classic.
That will be taught in high schools.
Yes.
Junior high.
Heck, elementary school.
Oh, yes.
You know, and the kids will be zooming the loom while they...
Well, they won't read the book because it will just be injected into their brain.
Right.
Directly into their brains.
It's like taking the red pill and the blue pill at the same time.
Why not both?
Hello?
Daveman.
Dave?
I'm coming.
I'm here.
Oh, good.
We're so glad you're there.
Well, I'm only, you know, I'm hanging in here.
He's there for us.
We need you to be there.
We need you to be there?
Why do you need me to be there?
Jase.
Because otherwise life is just grim and dim without any lonesome cowboy Dave.
Well, that's the most...
That's wonderful.
That's the biggest lie anyone's ever told me.
It's all true.
It's all pure, pure true.
Exactly.
That's what I mean.
It's not exactly true, but it's very...made me feel very warm inside and cool outside.
It's princess truth.
It's all true.
True through and through.
It's altruistic.
Well, what's going on in the line of bellybuttons and beans down there in southern...Yabioca?
We're in northern.
Northern Texas still, but we'll be back in Cleveland in about two and a half weeks.
Will you be wearing the Nordic American Bund uniform and have a mango haircut?
Oh, we have to just to get into Ohio to get through the, you know, the customs border
and the gates.
Don't blame it on us.
You know, between Kentucky and Ohio, they search your car, they search your pants, they
search your face.
They search your mind.
They do a pencil tucky too.
They like to look like a...what do we call those people with squirrels that wear squirrels
on their shoulders?
So one of the guy was trying to pass off one of these pet squirrels he had on his shoulder
as a parrot.
Dave Billies they call it.
Yeah.
The Dave Billies.
They're people from the, you know, way, way out in the really small locals.
Like nearby the border.
And they have a border here.
They call it pencil tucky.
Isn't that insulting?
Well, between Tennessee and Kentucky, you have to go through another border control
wall.
And then between Arkansas and Tennessee, there's a huge wall lined with border guards
and machine guns and trenches, draw bridges.
Yeah, but most of the part of...
Alligators.
Yeah.
But most of it's old shoes, which is, you know, they're kind of easy to get over there,
especially if you've got a 22 foot ladder.
Yeah.
But a lot of people just plow their way through those shoes and say, hey, screw you, ICE,
which stands for International Customs and...
Just hold your nose and just charge on through that gauntlet of old shoes.
I heard that...
Who needs a green card?
...old Presidente was going to try and put up a big barrier somewhere south of San Jacinto
of human underwear and rodent fur.
Now, who's going to do that?
The artist Christo?
Or the artist Trump?
I guess Trump was going to commission Christo to take his fag bag balloon or whatever it's
called in Norwegian, some strange name, just like he did in the hills of Northern California,
you know, and just create these walls, luminous like dingleberries that shine in the night
that keep on keeping on, you know?
That'll make America goat again.
Yeah.
And gulp.
Yeah, gulp.
That'll make America gulp again.
It sure will.
I felt sad just hearing about it the first time when I realized I talked to it.
It was a doctor from San Jacinto that said that they're closing up the plasma schools
and all the other important parts of the village were being destroyed.
Yeah, they're going to shut down everything that doesn't pay directly into the...
The private prison store, Trump's stock.
And we'll all have to have new salivary glands installed and stuff like that too so they
can...
Makes my mouth not water just thinking about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can't wait to get my salivary glands removed and replaced with those new chemical
processors.
Well, mine's been on order for three weeks now.
Yeah.
And I thought they were still going to deliver it through the hydro pack.
Well, no, I guess some people can get that injected with the hydro pack, but it kind
of depends on which state you're in.
You'd have to cross the wall into Indiana to be able to just sit on it and have it soak
in like that.
Yeah.
But wherever you go, you're going to have to be able to bring it in.
And you're going to have to drive some corrupt official or some kind of...
Right.
Using some member of the clergy.
The clergy.
Yeah, those are the police now.
Well...
But one...
Yep.
Same difference.
You know...
Yep.
Now that every officer is an ordained Christian minister, they can do anything they want.
My salivary glands are quivering in fear.
Well, you just take your salivary glands...
Is that what just sprayed me?
Yes.
Put some beans in the next tater from the side.
It's going to wipe in my face.
It's got spritzed.
It's their fault, dear.
It's not mine.
Those huge salivary glands.
Speaking of salivary glands, we ought to milk the dog.
If there was a way to sell dog drool, we'd be rich.
Oh, we sure would.
There's got to be some new age thing we can stick on, you know, homeopathic holographic
dog infusion.
And it'll be real.
We wouldn't trick them.
It wouldn't just be thickened water.
It would be real drool.
We wouldn't need to fake it.
There's plenty.
Yes.
On a hot day, we could gather buckets of dog drool and sell it...
Well, you know...
...to new age suckers and survivalists and just like gold and silver.
Dog slobber.
You know, they're marketing that gelled alcohol that you buy in a pump bottle.
What's the point?
with a label on it that says dog drool because it's like a gag gift are they really yes i didn't
know it's not like the celebrity snot hairs that they're they're marketing now today right yeah
sheriff's not really old celebrities well the drool is easier to collect from the really old
celebrities yeah share barbara streisand those are real big uh clint eastwood robert redford
they're drooling a breaking wind expensive but not hard to find
break wind break and crack cheeks crack hey get this dave our comrade reverend bleepo abernathy
who is the guy who actually says the hour of slack almost every week not this week but most weeks
bleepo just
worked with the what's left of the fire sign theater yeah yeah in los angeles um there was
a thing called something along the lines of looking for the fire sign theater or something
like him or them or something and phil proctor was in it um i i guess phil proctor may have been
the only one i didn't recognize i didn't see david osman pictures the other two are dead
i thought osman was still uh breathing he is
he he is but i don't think he was in the show this was proctor and uh and fire sign fans
such as reverend bleepo and you and me only we weren't you know there to do it oh we weren't
invited no well it was sure if we wanted to pay buy tickets we were invited listeners
uh many of you under the age of 180 wouldn't recognize the name
the fire sign theater but for everyone who does an old-timey subgenius show that's us and dave and
puzzling evidence philo hal suzy the floozy and ministry of slack well maybe not them and maybe
not thorazine you're in podcrest but but us old-timers to us the fire sign theater were like
the trance spouting comedy gods absolutely
although they actually wrote these elaborate scripts that were see that was quite an enlargement
for me to hear because i'd heard of the pacific radio tapes and stuff like that i thought
these guys just know they were jamming and then they would take the jams and they would turn them
into scripts i thought everything was fun when you listen to their old shows it's as if they
were recorded yesterday they might refer to nixon but it's still the same
name there is and they didn't do like us they tried to stay away from extremely dating uh current
events because they were looking for eternal events they were looking for the the truth in
the eternal recurrence of richard nixon over and over and over you got it bro
but they didn't have to say nixon's name it could be any president yes they were so great
we owe our lives to the fire sign theater our younger listeners out there to perhaps go and
find the cd or some you know find it on the net somewhere and just download as many
uh as you can the fire sign theater in turn were inspired by the the goon show
of
british radio the goon show with spike milligan and peter sellers and another what was the other
guy another genius yeah right and their stuff sounds it has that way about it and many say
this is what was the beginning of both not only fire sign theater in america but monty python in
oh absolutely first there was goon show then fire sign theater then monty
python and of course a million other things came after yeah but there's nothing like a fire sign
theater album the first dave the first time i heard one of those i was 15 or 16 and i had
started hanging around with the theater kids in school because i was at a boys school and the
theater department ballet slippers had girls football helmet no this was it was i was hanging
out with the kids and i was hanging out with the kids and i was hanging out with the kids and i was
hanging out with the theater sissies because that was where the girls were in a private boy
school yeah so uh some older kid who was really hip or maybe an older brother had turned somebody
on to this fire sign theater thing and i remember laying in a dark room with a bunch of other
intellectual wimpy kids listening to this stuff in the dark and we weren't high on drugs because
we were only 50
teen and i remember thinking very specifically this must be what it's like to be stoned as i was
listening to the fire sign theater and i was quite right you were yeah this must be what it's like to
be stoned some people go through life without ever shutting their brain off like that i can't
some of them need to have their brain shut off they need the master calculator to
into the room and pick the off which oh i need the big rubber mallet every five minutes
well it's a big phallic dildo as far as most of us are concerned and you keep on arguing
no it's just a big rubber mallet that knocks you out why do you have to turn everything into sex
dr freud that's outdated thinking that's old school thinking it's very old school
old school hey now dave here's the part you don't know i read
you don't know i read you don't know i read you don't know i read you don't know i read you don't
know i read you don't know i read you don't know i read you don't know i read you don't know i read you
some of your book before we called you
out loud like like a story for the kids a bedtime story well that's that's wonderful
that's absolutely ridiculous i'm i'm so proud of yourself hey you want to hear some more of me
what did you what did you talk about um
how the well i found the part where it said the year was 2037
Oh, that's only 20 years from now.
I know.
And it was only one paragraph, but it's a great paragraph.
And I read the thing about neighbors who have never seen their own house from the outside.
It was wonderful.
That was wonderful.
And what I would like to read now, this is a description of Standard's job rival, Nogo.
Nogo is a gen-alt.
That means he's been genetically altered and stuff, so he's, you know, slicker.
And Standard is kind of like, well, the rest of us.
Yeah.
Standard.
A normal person.
Kind of a slob, kind of a mess, a little disorganized.
Nogo is Mr. Perfect, though.
Now, I'm going to read this.
Nogo was a good chef, sure, and a good artist, composer, director, whatever.
Everything he laid.
He laid his splice baby new lizard hands on, cued cred.
Naturally, or unnaturally.
He was genetically altered for art, for right brain dominance.
But a goofy glitch whispered in the opposite.
Imbalance and unexplainable left brain dominance flawed his work.
The past and future are one, Advo, Nogo said with a smile.
There's only then and now.
Shaping up.
Seize the moment.
And ride the Zoom.
It was like God superimposed a slapstick reminder on the artificial prodigy.
A memo from the executive producer to disregard all this gen-alt crap.
Meaningless patterns blasted through his all-systemic visual art, searching for significance.
He couldn't cook without pre-pros and measurements,
compose without tone and pulse standards,
or make art without matrices and interfaces.
That describes me.
I doubt that.
I have to have matrices and interfaces.
Well, we all do it.
It's just one of those things.
He's a slave to it, or something like that.
This Nogo guy, he's...
He's been genetically altered for art.
I mean, you know, to be a showbiz...
You know, Mel...
Melting, melted media guy.
You know, like when social media and the internet and television,
cable television or whatever,
all meld into one massive autocratic,
slain, haunted, pathetic,
scryed-ass, legend...
And he's made for that.
Well, he was...
We gotta change that.
Great.
Great Nogo...
30 years in the future.
Maybe.
Great.
Nogo snarled sarcastically.
That would give them something to remember.
But they can't remember anything.
Remember?
Nogo liked...
Nogo liked to make folks ooze sedition,
Malko, and InfoCrit.
And then, entrap them.
He was a provocateur who catalyzed trouble,
like someone who started a fire and then anonymously reported it.
You had to be careful what you said.
The only way to handle Nogo was to confront him directly,
like when dealing with our boss.
I looked right into his eyes, and he looked back for a second, then away.
He flinched.
Nogo was hiding something, and I saw it.
That made me alpha now.
Mm-hmm.
The plot...
So, see, friends, it's written in another language.
It's a Dave language.
But if you're listening to this show,
you must have kind of liked the Dave language to begin with.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, if you're still...
Well, if this isn't the first time you ever listen to this show...
Right.
We don't want to...
Because so many are like the fierce pigs of Norway.
Remember when the Tuskegons first barbecued the whole universe?
Starting with the...
I guess it was the Tompkins sisters, and...
They were the masters.
In those days, we were the bacon.
Yeah, that's it.
Like the Manhattan Project.
That was part of it, too, and Montauk,
and Harry Naval Week, and all that.
Stuff like that.
Yeah.
They drank too much.
Wait, you can drink too much?
Oh, no.
Well, you can...
Yeah.
Oh, man, that's bad news to me.
Well, I love proofreading Neighbor World
because I've had to pay real close attention
to every single letter
to make sure there's nothing misspelled.
And here's a word...
I didn't even know existed.
Amoebi.
I guess that's a plural of amoeba?
Yeah.
This is no-go talking again.
The point is that all those folks are just amoebi.
They're like some single-cell creature
feeding off some more complex creature,
never knowing what they're doing or why.
Most of them can't even remember their own names,
for Christ's sakes.
How can they retain all the info drizzle
they connect into daily?
It's meaningless to them.
It's like...
Psychic fiber.
It passes right through them, man.
Right through them.
Now, I'm probably using exactly the wrong voice for no-go, but...
Yeah, you may sound like he was a hairdresser
or a police pederast.
Well, I was thinking he was like a...
A provocateur.
A media art guy and a hipster.
They're incapable of assimilating new info, Stan,
he said as if announcing some important secret truth.
Neighbor World has fabricated a comfortable transition
century for a bunch of amoebi.
Our celebrated Nova century is nothing more than
a regurgitation of the past, attractively packaged
to keep a dead race thinking it's alive.
They're not asleep, Stan.
They're dead.
His eyes got really wide when he said dead.
Wow.
That's a pretty weird book, man.
And it's about the weirds.
It's about the search for the weirds
who are weirding out the system.
Which we'd all love to do if we all had the right haircuts
and everything.
Some of us are like...
We'd have to have hair to begin with to have the right haircuts.
Yeah, well, if we could muster a few snaggly-cragly two hairs...
Oh, I've got enough to wrap all around my body,
but they're just hanging from the back of my neck.
There's nothing else left.
The ones that are there are five feet long,
but there's only seven of them.
They'll look lice and chiggers, too.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, God.
The chiggers are worse now than they were last week.
Oh, they are.
Actually, they're not.
I think they're dying off, or they're growing up.
The chiggers are maturing.
They no longer need our blood.
They're not so insecure anymore.
Yeah, they're learning to drive.
Like our president.
They're learning.
Except that they can learn.
Chiggers can learn.
I don't know if we're...
Are we nuts?
Are we supposed to criticize?
Because I think old Mango Mussolini,
as some people like to call him and stuff,
has gone to new...
Did you see some of the...
Probably fake news on the Internet, of course,
but some of the pictures of those places
where he was speaking to standing-room-only crowds?
Yeah, they weren't standing-room-only.
There was a lot of empty seats.
Yeah, he's not selling out the crowds now.
He got a little bit, and there was a lot of empty space.
he's crazy.
Yeah, he's crazy.
Yeti's our president.
Way crazy.
President is a Yeti.
Yeti's our president.
That's an old Dr. Howell line
from another president
long, long ago.
I think it was Reagan.
Was Reagan a Yeti too?
Reagan was in a band
with Bob Dobbs and Philo Drummond.
He was in Doctors for Wotan
for a while.
They used to jam on the weekends.
He had to get away from Nancy,
you know, and he'd frop
and they'd jam and everything.
Actually, Reagan was nothing like...
And they'd have to rush her
to the hospital.
And that would be another party blown
because the Reagans came by
and had their weird drug paraphernalia.
Well, they were into downers.
Like the hat and the wombats
and all that stuff.
The Reagans were real into
barbiturate.
Then when Quaaludes came along
they were into that, of course.
Yeah, she was a soggy froggy
from the get-go.
And astrology.
Yeah.
Right, right.
The stars will...
Some people feel that the stars
guide our fate.
Come along with us, Dave,
on the starship Avalon
as we travel
to a better world.
Avalon.
All stars.
Not a reason not to include.
Well, I don't know.
I doubt if it's really going to ever
be a better world
even than Avalon and Caldonia
or Overtureland.
Oh, sure.
10,000 years from now
when the squibbons evolve
into tool-using creatures,
they'll create the utopia
that humans were never able to pull off
due to their glands.
What about the angry squid
you preach upon?
Every day of your sacred,
holy, miserable life.
When the squid evolves
into the tree squid,
when they leave the water
and evolve after people
into tree squids
or squibbin',
they will eventually start using tools
and evolve into,
well, not men,
but squim and squimmin'.
Land squids with hands.
You don't have to have feet.
Well, cephalopod,
that kind of means head foot.
Pods are feet, aren't they?
They're head foot.
Oh, yeah.
Cerebropods.
Cephalopods.
I think that's what they're...
That's what squids and octopi are.
Mollusks.
They're a type of mollusk.
Mollusks in general are just...
They're kind of blobby.
They're...
Mouth and butt
and stomach and brain
and eyeball
are all usually
just one big mass organ.
And they taste so good.
Boiled, smoked, raw, pickled.
Mmm.
Up here on Lake Erie,
you know what I'm hearing now?
One of the first things
that the industries
that they polluted
was back in the 1890s,
there was all these
Lake Erie quahogs
and these other mollusks
that people used to eat
just like a clam shot.
Yeah.
I've heard of those.
But you don't...
People don't eat a whole lot
from Lake Erie anymore, do they?
No.
I mean, you can.
Somehow...
Somehow Ontario is allowed
to have fishing fleets
and, you know,
you get your Lake Erie
perch sandwich
here on the shores of Lake Erie
and everybody thinks
it's from Ohio.
They don't know the difference
because we're not allowed
to fish anymore,
but they are
because somehow
the fish actually...
They actually know
where the boundary
between the United States
and Canada is.
Right, yeah.
Well, there's a line down there
under the lake.
Yeah.
Oh, big...
It looks small on a map,
but under the lake
in real life,
it's like, God,
100 yards wide.
It's huge.
Yeah.
Easy for fish to see.
The Philistines,
I guess the major one,
of course,
being the mango
Mussolini himself,
Comrade Trump,
have vowed
that they were going
to fix all the fissures
in the wall
between Canada
and the United States
and Lake Erie.
Right on.
That'll keep out
them people from Canada.
Yeah.
They talk English,
but not real good.
They don't talk good.
They don't write good.
They take strange
bowel movements, eh?
I'm quoting...
Bowel movements,
get it?
Like, you know...
I was quoting the Cheeto,
actually.
You stand on guard
for the Eden,
you know,
and, you know...
He can do that,
a lot better than I can.
Well, because I used
to hear them sing it
every night before
they used to have,
you know,
when I would fall asleep
before they had
the other forms
of television.
And the Canadian radio
or the TV
would be blasting away
the Canadian National Anthem.
And you'd be the only kid
in school
that knew the Canadian
National Anthem
because you'd fall asleep
with your head
right by that TV speaker.
Reverend Angry Larry
has talked about that.
He grew up in Detroit,
which is right across
from Canada.
Right.
And they got all that
propaganda broadcast
into their heads
from the evil
Canadian socialist government
and stuff.
Well, at least
they can cook sugar pie
and they know how to make
a damn bleamy sandwich
there in Windsor
on the lake.
Whatever.
I went to Toronto once
to be on a lame
morning TV show.
It was ill-advised.
It was ill-conceived notion.
And the main thing
I remember is that
Marlborough's cost
an extra 75 cents there.
Yeah, smokes are
very expensive in Canada.
That was a long, long,
long, long, long, long,
long, long time ago.
Now you've got me
yearning for bleamy.
Well, everyone loves it.
What is this bleamy?
Put the little
blue black bar
on the bleamy.
Or if you want to have
a more savory style
with a piece of
Romanian egg spark.
Ah.
Which I just crazed
in my mind.
Well, I'm looking
at the recording timer
and I know that we've
gone over
what will be an hour.
Seriously?
Yeah, we've
rambled on.
Well, because I played
some songs and stuff
at first.
It's like a regular
hour slack where there's
some music
and some blabbering.
Yes.
We used to go back
and forth,
blabbering music,
but now it's like
music, music, music,
then blabber, blabber,
blabber, blabber.
Yes.
Because it's easy.
My silly songs should
be ready in a couple
days to email these
to you.
Yeah, Dave is working
on new Dave songs.
It only has two verses,
so I don't know
if I should let it go.
It sounds pretty
unprofessional,
but kind of Spike
Jones silly.
Or if I should try
and sharpen it up
so it sounds like
Spike Jones on purpose.
Why not both?
We'd do the cheap
one first and then
the expensive one later.
You might not ever
get to the expensive one.
Right.
Yeah.
Take one out, man.
Well, that's what
the guy said last night
who's doing most
of the recording.
He's also going to
send you some
silly loops.
He has some silly
loops that you can
use in the background
of the show.
Sure, man.
Silly loops.
Well, we'll be back
at WCSB and we'll
be able to use
the equipment,
the good equipment.
I have to set
these microphones
on potholders
and pillows
in order to keep
the vibration
from the CD player
from coming
through the mic stand.
Okay.
That's the kind
of setup we've got
here.
Tarzan's radio station,
Ducks Dot Mountain,
Fossil House,
Stang Ranch,
Stang County, Texas.
Oh, Stang'sville.
Stang'sville,
not Stang County.
Stang'sville in Stang...
Well, it's in
Stang County.
What an ego.
Sure, it's in
Stang County,
but you're not
supposed to remind
everyone, like,
rub your nose.
My family's been
here for centuries.
They're a bunch
of Confederate
ludicroids.
No, they were here
before the Spaniards.
They were here
in the 1300s.
They were a bunch
of first Neanderthal
colonists of Texas.
Oh, and Dave,
if you could be here.
Well, that's where
they did discover
those people
that were like,
there's many, many,
many more thousands
of years.
Yeah, no kidding.
That blew my mind.
They found evidence
that there were
hunters slaying mammoths
in California
130,000 years ago.
That no one
had ever placed
humans in the new world
before about
10,000 years ago.
11,000 years ago.
This is a major thing.
Old world, yeah.
And maybe things
are true,
what the Indians,
what the Native Americans
would say,
is true that they
were the first
modern humans.
Right.
There may have been
prehistoric humans
here first.
How did they get here?
Only alien transfer
can explain it.
Eric Von Donaghan's
Chariots of the Gods
on sale now.
Chairman of the Geese.
The Geese?
Is that what his name was,
Von Donaghan?
Chairman of the Geese?
Of spark plugs of the gods
is what I call it.
Spark plugs of the gods.
These ancient spark plugs
were found in 80 billion
year old rock.
Proving that man
could not have built
the pyramids himself
because brown people
are too dumb
to build giant monuments.
Only aliens can help them
and that explains everything.
That was what I hated
about the whole blitz.
You know,
it's totally baloney too.
Yeah.
They know how the pyramids
and Stonehenge were built
with a lot of clever,
clever thought put into it.
And actually,
I think the people
who built the pyramids
were paid.
Uh-huh.
It wasn't even slated.
They were paid pretty well
and they were given
family stipends too.
So apparently there were
a lot of people camping by.
Their families were camping by
near these monuments
that they build them.
There's many,
you know,
places where they would
build an edifice like this
in the current age and stuff.
And they showed like
what they were feeding
these people along
with their regular stipend
of whatever was
the equivalent of money.
They had a lot of food
Salt.
One day.
Probably salt, yeah.
I am civilized, man.
By harnessing the power
of the weak,
I built the pyramids.
That's a Fireside Theater quote.
Yes.
From I think we're all bozos
on this one.
I think that was
their fourth album.
Man, that was such a classic.
Uh huh.
Okay, Dave,
we have to go now.
It's the Hour of Slack.
That's the show this is.
We're all bozos
on this bus.
Huh, huh.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
has been here with us.
We're about to publish
his book Neighbor World
in a matter of weeks,
I hope.
I'm going to try to do
the next 50 minutes
of 50 pages tomorrow.
You gotta make sure you do it
when I'm still around,
sonny boy,
you never can tell.
What are you,
that's the,
yeah, that's,
why do you think I'm doing
this e-publishing thing, man?
I know, I know, I know.
We don't have that much longer.
Don't let it in already.
We can't wait for somebody
else to do it.
We tried that.
Well, I'm just going to have
to keep stinking up a storm
wherever I go.
Yeah, man,
write another book.
We'll print another one.
It doesn't cost anything.
It's easy.
Yeah, Dave,
please write another book.
I'd love it if you wrote another one.
Okay, Dave,
I don't know,
this one is even sillier
than that one,
or less.
Okay, man,
it'll all be there
at subgenius.com
when the time comes.
Praise Bob.
When the time comes.
Hail Connie.
Praise Bob.
Leaving Earth
for a colony world
is more than a life change.
It's a leap of faith
between the stars.
Don't you want to travel
in style?
I'm not going to.
Take flight
on the starship Avalon,
the Homestead Company's
finest colonial starliner.
Our state-of-the-art
hibernation bay
has room
for 5,000
sleeping passengers.
You'll wake up
in orbit
around your colony world
and meet your fellow passengers
on a four-month
orientation cruise.
Dulge your senses
at a dozen
gourmet restaurants.
Relax at the
Concourse Bar,
where the best bartender
in the galaxy
is always on duty.
And if you're
at your service,
see the stars in style
on the starship Avalon,
a Homestead Company starship.
All passengers enter
a lifetime contract
with the Homestead Company.
The Homestead Company
is not liable
for financial
or personal losses
incurred by passengers.
Make yours
a flight to remember.
Dave actually did hang up.
I'm sorry.
I didn't fade him out
or anything.
Well, friends,
that's my cue
to tell you.
Now, I know
there's still some holdouts
who don't think
that joining
the Church of the Subgenius
is the cool thing to do
because they're not joiners.
Well, you're right
and you're wrong
because you're buying
a really cool kit
for your 35 bucks.
A kit with 35 bucks
and 30 different pieces
of stuff in there,
most of it printing matter,
that will take you
a month to really soak up.
Just the two pamphlets
take like a week to read
and a magnifying glass.
So, friends, think about it.
Subgenius.com, 35 bucks.
You become a minister.
You get to meet
the other subgeniuses.
You may not want to do that.
Can't say it's a good thing.
I guess I blame you
in some cases,
but you also don't know
what kind of hot stuff
you might be missing out on.
And mainly it is not slack.
You have to make your own slack,
but it is an ever-present
encouragement to do so.
Don't just accept
the false slack of the conspiracy.
Get off the stick
and get on the stick
and get some slack for yourself
with a little boost,
a little bootstrap up
from subgenius.com
and that great big thing
we call the membership pack.
I'll be writing your name
and address on the outside
of the pack myself.
That's how it works.
It's very personalized still
because, let's face it,
we're not Scientology.
And you can thank me for that.
Praise Bob.