🎵
Genuinely beautiful.
Giant.
Perfect.
Cool.
Special.
Cheered.
Elaborate.
Easy.
Ultimate.
Best.
Natural.
Growing.
Special.
Nice.
Quicker.
And much more.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not
going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it all into just this one intensive total rerun show, except
that actually it's not.
The whole first half will be largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for the holidays
and holy days and the hole-in-head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of salad.
Selling.
Yes.
Oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus and Guitar Axmus.
It's cool, man.
Cool.
And praise Bob and the whole world.
Oh.
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt up on this Christmas tree.
I'm not sure I can stop that.
Yeah.
And left me stranded on this Christmas tree
When this angel heard
A dreadful fear went right into my heart
Those pine tree needles sting me
Ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-ding-dong
You'll never know how much that smarts
So who put the stump in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong
Who stood the wood where I boop-sheep-boop-sheep-boop
Who put the stick up my hip-a-dip-a-dip
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush
He made this angel beg for mercy, please
Too tight, too tight
And I'm gonna say to you
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid him
Don't go walking down to the bar
Cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard
I mean, I'm gonna park my store and look at the credits
And in the right
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw, yeah
And I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
Till I get to bed
I have chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday
Now you boys be good and I'll give you some of this here
Apple mango pie
You ain't no good of a child
That dog's running off with them brain cells
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right
No!
I thought
Kidding!
It's possible
I could've wiped it all off
Yeah..
It's simple
It's easy
At least I'm not Nozomi
The biggest thing is
Totally
No, no, I'm not
It's not
No, no, no
I did buy her that
I'll never buy you anything
Anything that's worth it
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pills.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied...
I'm shocked by the...
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels we have heard on high
Singing about mountains high
And those mountains in reply
Saying we wish we had some too
War in excelsis Deo
Barbie Dolls
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower the students.
Yes, sir.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the power.
It will be called Bobber for Kids.
But how?
How will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has a lot of muscle.
Good.
Good!
The primitive Earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have great physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires,
latent,
and children brought out through the vehicle of this so-called Farmer-Columbia-Split Church.
Batteries not included.
She's new from Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys!
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme recorded there at Dockstock.
Floppy,
clicks,
So sick.
You can't sell this shit salvationist.
Are you mad?
But you sell stuff, submuş noses,
As avait vous dit en l'ar argente de l'agande a buchette de chiffonette bagesse Suisse,
Seems to be true, isn't it?
Ah, yes, and next up, The Real Story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted tens and twenties, tens and twenties.
And he...
He got McDonald's gift certificates and he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Take the halls and the miles of holly
Tears of the season to be jolly
Don't we know I'll get a barrel
Roll the engine and take care
La la la la la la la la la la
So separate, so separate, so separate
You from Tolga
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob.
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal.
Shut up, pink boy!
No way, I'll never sell out to the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien fool!
Bob Dobbs!
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher, jayner device, oligarchatism, fighting Jesus and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required, batteries not included. This toy falls apart in three days.
He-Bob!
...and wrestling.
...and the bastards of the universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
...and Queen Barbara Dolls.
...and I can doze whole separately.
Gorgeous!
...seagulls can blow from head to toe.
...and everything you see here.
...can doze whole separately.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
Santa Claus!
...and the aliens will soon be back.
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing on his mind, even to the table where it was going to set it up.
I'm going to picture the whole thing.
He would dream so hard that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy looking train set with locomotives and freight cars.
And a station and a gateman.
The mortar tower and all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So grand that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
So come and get it everyone and just buy our products.
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we?
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now.
And sell everything to the pigs.
Oh yes, once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
Before it was, after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season.
It was something.
There was something else, but I think they started to war over it.
Yea...
At that Jesusién tomb Justice All
Oh, oh, oh, Gloria
Hosanna in excelsis
You better not, you better not, you better not tell anyone.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Material plants, biological agents who only take 15%?
Oh, it's a great day, all right.
A salute to Mr. and Mrs. America.
Shop as usual.
And avoid panic buying.
Beast
Santa Claus is real.
Santa Claus.
We are the cause for the child.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man.
He was so real.
How come he didn't get scared?
He got caught last year.
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan.
On July 4th.
And now you can have it all.
All pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan.
As told by various authors and eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
An announcement.
Of the blessed anointment and birthday of our Lord.
Zin.
Praise.
For.
One.
Bright Christmas morning.
Zin.
Was born.
In a cradle.
To a rich man's family.
The rave Jesus.
Oh, I know the rave Jesus.
I'm part with the rave Jesus.
I'm part with the rave.
On my wedding day.
At the church.
I was in the room.
Are you the same
También soy yo mismo
I was so sad.
That I thought.
From the dream enjoy brought estar.
Sorry I أحετε жrzyк once
Have yourself a very little bit of salt.
From now on we're miles away.
Once a day as in olden days.
Happy golden be miles of us.
Let your heart be out of sight.
From mutated Christmas friends,
have yourself a merry little Christmas by
No
dash
L.
No
Before that some year old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas from
the Tarkin Records All Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now the Jethro's.
Here we go.
Tarkin Records
The Weirbobs and Ima, those who have the psychosis that convinces them that they are the Santa Bob.
Or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow on their nameless, hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stop using the locks of their doors and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
And, you know, just going to church ain't enough.
You gotta send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me told their kids that Santa Claus,
Santa Claus bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
The kids were asking if their parents, maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he totes the note.
Let's be friends.
Oh, boy.
And amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on Corporal Blossom and the mutated Christmas.
is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
And now, more Jethro's.
Jethro's Art
Jethro's Voice
First Christmas Witch
he used to put a stocking cap on his head and put a knot right in front of it.
Daddy wake up with that stomping headache.
And he said, the kids are saying, my head's hurting so bad.
I said, I don't know what Santa's going to get y'all for Christmas,
but he's going to bring you something.
So Daddy took that old rifle and went outside and shot up in the air
and come back inside and told us the biggest lie ever heard.
Said, kid, Santa just committed suicide.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle but Satan Claus?
Whose father, Paul Bunyan, and whose mother, Big Sister, created the conspiracy?
Before there were malls, there was no such thing as Christmas.
Yes, there was a down-home Norman rock.
It's a wonderful life type of Christmas.
It was a kite-flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas,
not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
Now, it was a...
When your little brother fell through a hole in the ice sled,
and you went and saved him, you didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful...
It was a wonderful life back then.
...and we pulled some eggs, little jokes about him waking up,
and then we'd put candles, like most people have for Christmas.
He would have that smile on his face and a big red nose.
But today, Christmas is lost its meaning.
He'd have beaten the crap out of Santa Claus.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected me.
And to your eternal soul,
you have found that I only...
Could you afford to give to God that which was his?
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
In the outer darkness, where there is wailing and gnashing of teeth...
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir!
I don't want to go to hell, sir!
Sir, no!
No!
Thank God I don't want to go to hell!
Noooo!!
....as brave as he could be!
And the children's Saber can laugh and play just the same!
Arise you and me,
the tail bearer will be at the judgment!
Imagine any dark, moonlit night and Rambo,
is the same as that night decided tomorrow,
Soumber a sé horror!!
all over the world. The wife of a carpenter experiences virgin birth and a baby is born
with a head that glows like a fluorescent lamp. Dare I ask it? Yes. Was the infant Jesus neither
man nor God, but merely one of the countless aliens that visit the earth each and every day?
The answer? Yes, definitely. Take that and shove it up the tube, mark certainty,
in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Pieces of Cupid and Comet, and he tied up his helpers, and he held the elves hostage,
and he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage. He got dancer and prancer with an old
German luger, and he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger, and he picked up a flamethrower
and a barbecue blitzer, and he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken.
The Night Santa went
crazy, and he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken.
The Night Santa went crazy, the night is cringy when the Santa can hardly walk around the North Pole
without stepping in reindeer guts. There's a National Guard and the FBI.
There's a van from the Iowa News and helicopters circling around in the sky,
and the bullets are flying.
And the bodyguards rising, and everyone's dying to know who Santa was.
My, my, my, my, my, my, you used to be such a jolly guy.
He knows when you're asleep. He knows when you're awake.
He knows when you're bound for good.
So be good for goodness sake.
You better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not pout.
I'm telling you why.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing called Santa is Coming by F. Gillespie and F. J. Coote.
ElectricElf at Loop.com can tell you more about that.
But now...
Who gave the Lord the claptrap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind?
Yeah, we're now officially in the Jesus season.
The time of the Lord, of the fact that...
How many before you reach your limit?
How many do you get?
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many Messiahs can you bag?
Jesuses.
If you're doing it in season...
If you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit.
Oh, you never do that.
And you can only take one.
You never bag the Lord in C.
You bag the Lord in B-flat so you get that kind of rough sound.
But when they're in season, it's every God for himself.
This is the season for the...
For the fighting Jesus.
Obviously.
We are between a rock and a hard place.
Did you know the Lord walked through Chaldea in the old age
and he got a very, very hard foot?
And he got elephantages of the rectum.
You know, it's not something well known by many Christian scholars.
That can be messy, messy, messy disease.
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was...
Well, I like the story.
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies
and then comes here to America and settles, you know,
tames the West.
I like when he moves into a trailer park and...
I like the cowboy's dog.
Jesus fought for the Confederate army.
The ranger.
I like the...
The Texas ranger.
Jesus, Texas ranger.
Johnny Ripple was a Jesus.
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police,
for maybe the Hopi police force.
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus.
Man.
The white brother who came to instruct the Indians how to be liberal.
Well, what about old peacemaker?
The Jesus of the...
The Iroquois who was actually Huron.
A Huron.
You didn't know that, did you?
I got you.
Thin Ron.
Jesus.
El Ron.
I got a Jesus like no other Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus.
A different Jesus.
It tastes like...
A future Jesus.
A future pie children.
A pipe-smoking Jesus.
Hey.
Dave, you know where it is.
Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it.
I'll kick it again, though.
Kick it good this time.
We don't...
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We hope that...
We thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving.
Clapping.
We appreciate all that.
And we're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemy stuff.
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob and Jesus.
Next topic.
Terrorist insurance.
And the atheists.
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science.
Well, that's the life of Brian, isn't it?
That was...
And Greek mythology and Norse mythology.
Listen to the sounds of hell.
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked.
Wrapped in wrapping paper.
We're gonna break.
We're gonna break our necks.
Got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The elves are full of cheer.
The kids are tucked in bed.
What?
Santa ain't coming.
We're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Their dreams are filled with toys.
But they're out of luck.
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to...
Sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh ride to...
To...
Heck.
The greatest scary Christmas song ever, friends, from his new album, Don't Trust Whitey,
James Kozalka, Superstar.
You know, see, a subgenius has so much faith
that he not only can accept somebody making fun of Bob,
stomping on a picture,
Bob, he'll do it himself. He has so much trust and faith in Bob. Bob is such a good friend that
he can insult Bob. Now, we subgeni, I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of
entertaining tapes, but we subgeni may be bad, but our way of bad is holy, is holy compared to the
evil of so, not all, by any means, but so many American fundamentalists, charismatics, evangelicals,
et cetera, in general, of course, they and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya, South
Africa, et cetera, if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve. Wolves in sheep's
clothing, friends, just like Jesus warned about. Jesus and Bob, like we say, our old drinking
buddies, got nothing against Jesus. It's just his fan club. And now, we aren't saying that Bob is
the ace up God's sleeve. He's more like the smear.
They're on God's handkerchief, just like you or me. But the uptight rival cults, they don't think
God has a handkerchief. Uh-uh, no, because God's perfect. He doesn't even sneeze. We're made in
his image, except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us, and we have to go in the
secret room, the bathroom, to do awful things. But God, oh, he's clean and pure, according to them.
Oh, and he's male, but he doesn't excrete juices and sweat.
And smelly stuff out of him like we do, because we sin. Oh, yeah, we all sin. We're bad. We're worthless.
We're no good to God, unless we sign a contract with his agent.
We interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement.
We turn.
E-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
Santa Claus is coming.
We'll have to wait until They Pet the
Poke episode, with Michael Dean and the tent technological
Speaking of assholes—
Oh, what a fainting dark strand
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the trees are small
And the children are safe
And I'm dancing in the snow
I'm dreaming about the page you just sent me
And everyone can come back, right?
May your days be rich
And short
And may all your dogs
Spend new lives
Oh, holy night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our gist and youth's birth
Long lay, long lay the world
In sin's pure and right finding
The pit and the stone found its rest
A thrill of hope
The weary world rejoices
Beyond our grace
A new and glorious morn
Fall on your knees
Oh, hear the angel voices
Oh, night divine
Oh, night when Christ was born
Oh, night
Oh, night divine
Have yourselves
A new day of life
Anal baby
Fading with the wind
Of love lives
Through the holy,icoly
Wander round the blue
Of grace
The gloomys
And the baby
behavior
Of grass
Slice the apple
Of great light
Eطha
Chocolate, Space Cadet, life support system down to zero, Coco.
Feeling space-free.
Have some of my new Coco Pimples.
Now so trumpety.
Smells coconut-ish.
This Coco Pimples.
Blue.
Hello, friends.
What do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob?
The Santai Bob, as he's been referred to in some early prescriptures.
The Jethro's, friends.
You need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at, they did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth, N-H-O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net.
Illegal art.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob.
There's a bright green bob in the window.
Is there a light out there?
And Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA?
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
This side is always so ready to let him be.
What?
For so long.
Hey, Bob and Mary X-Men!
Come on.
Oh my goodness.
Lone cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Don't despair, just because it's Christmas
Children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street
Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas!
What a night!
Before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse
The stockings were hung by the tree
Merry fucking Christmas
To you!
Thank you.