You are on the theological hotline. How can I make you hot?
Ah, yes, dear friends, welcome to the Hour of Slack, number 1,370-something.
And may this Hour of Slack be the most slackful of all the hours heretofore and forthwith.
Your time of listening is now your time of deep, relaxing slack.
Slack is the soft voice, slack the luminous cloud.
We in our slack rejoice.
And thence comes all the charms or ear or sight, all melodies the echo of that voice,
all colors a suffusion of that voice.
And though the exists once more withheld the lights of their countenance
from the helpful, hopeful, upturned faces of the ex-day postulants,
we have not even been challenged.
Nay, rather than that, our faith has been reinforced even more
so that we are truly the children,
the warriors of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise God!
But not the worriers, sir, we're not the worriers of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We're not worried because we have faith in the ultimate success of our mission,
the Nameless Mission, a small part of which is to bring you broadcasting opportunities
such as this one where you and we can participate together victoriously in what we call,
the Hour of Slack.
Rar! Rar! Rar! Rar!
That actually hurt my Adam's apple.
I have done that so many times in the last few days.
I've developed a bruise on my throat.
In Adam's fall, we sinned all.
And the bruise on the throat, which the Bobcaster feels,
is only cognate to the bruise on the heel given by that old serpent, Satan.
Yes, the adversary, the evil one, was nipping at the heels of the faithful at Exde.
But even old Sequa, most monstrous denizen of the watery depths,
took only four minor victims.
When we expected a holocaust of many, including even the most faithful.
Perhaps the locals had fed him the sacrifices,
which, oh, I'm sorry,
according to Native American tradition, are his due.
But perhaps he, like the holiday itself,
decided, for no reason that could be named,
to be kind and forbearing,
and to have the faith, the faith in Bob.
But there is a great support for the Lord.
To atone everything for sin?
To back one more victor.
Blav clav.
And to make a promise of running in heaven.
We. We.
She's got big bobs, daddy.
Shazam.
The corporations themselves receive corporate welfare, corporate television, corporate money.
They're corporate fascists. It's all true.
Can I get a free spa?
Brain and brain. What is brain?
My mind is not my mind.
Yes, dear friends.
Welcome to hour of slack number 1515.
One thousand five hundred and fifteen.
That's how many shows.
That's too many.
But we're going to do it. We're going to do another one anyway.
And I do have something unusual in front of me tonight.
It is a book, a great big, thick black book.
The hardcover.
It came to the sacred post office box of the church.
I sort of was expecting it, but I couldn't believe it when I saw it.
It is the title of this book.
This book is rhetorical ripples.
The Church of the subgenius, Kenneth Burke and comic symbolic tinkering by.
Well, for our slack purposes, we'll call him Reverend Lee Cipher, Ph.D.
And this giant book is this guy's dissertation in partial fulfillment.
Of a Ph.D. requirement in media art and text.
And I won't embarrass the huge university.
And the guy did get his Ph.D. or his doctorate or whatever he was getting this this bruise of his work.
There have not been many academic studies of the Church of the subgenius, although he does mention them.
And they're kind of interesting because one of them really didn't like it.
I thought.
You were deliberately stupid and we are, but that's not all we are.
Anyway, I'm going to read some of this because I couldn't believe it.
I couldn't believe how seriously somebody was taking our spazz church of macho irony.
But as it says here.
Humor has long been an effective way to engage difficult socio political topics in a way that avoids.
Polemical confrontation and provides opportunity for pleasure, catharsis and self knowledge.
In the context of today's polarized politics and protest, creative satirical performance that deploys symbolic tinkering can provide a comic frame of reference that, according to Kenneth Burke, more effectively conveys its message.
While providing.
Reflexive insight.
The.
Now, I don't understand this word satirical.
I'll have to look that up.
This satirical church of the subgenius naturally practices this rhetorical frame in their multimedia creations.
Using the lens of Burke's attitudes toward history.
This essay is an analysis of subgenius rhetoric with a focus on their hour of slack live radio.
Program and the book Revelation X to provide an informative example of Burke's comic frame applied and clarify the nature of its utility by exploring the rhetorical impact of the church of the subgenius and the relevance of its quote comic corrective.
Unquote.
Politically cynical subgeni are actually that should be pronounced subgenie.
Subgenie.
Politically cynical subgenie are none.
Nevertheless, keen cultural critics who sophisticated use of a complex comic rhetoric warrants more serious attention.
And then he quotes quite a bit of art graphics and slogans from our material, such as J.
R.
Bob Dobbs.
Great statement.
You'll pay to know what you really think.
Or as it says in subgenius pamphlet number one, our creed orthodoxy is the only heresy.
And as Ruckert said in encounters with Kenneth Burke, the most serious truths can be coached into jokes.
Now, don't worry, I'm not going to read this entire book.
I should hope not.
It's quite thick.
Yeah, it's a great book.
A great.
It is a great book.
Great in size.
But it is very impressive looking.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And for the most part, although it's hard for me to understand the big words, I kind of agree with them.
Although I don't know what I really don't know what he means by rhetoric at all.
Anyway, here's some more of it.
Burke's initial connection written in 1937.
Kenneth Burke's observation above.
About the utility of the comic frame to promote maximum consciousness is even more relevant and necessary in 2014.
As our world is rapidly connecting and transforming via new protein communication technologies, most notably the web, smartphones and social media.
While these astonishing new tools have sparked revolutions and helped to hold power accountable, we have yet to transcend our foibles.
The world remains at the mercy.
The world remains at the mercy of unaccountable power, deadly conflict, environmental degradation and increasing socioeconomic disparity.
Burke addresses these issues directly in his writing.
And they are also central targets of the subgenius satire.
I'll have to look that up.
Which, in spite of its non-activist nature, has nevertheless had a subtle but surprising impact on popular culture and civic discourse.
The Church of the Subgenius is worth our attention for its evolving protean narrative.
Its unschooled use of Burke's sophisticated rhetoric.
You got the unschooled part right.
Its keenly targeted cultural critiques.
I'll have to look for those in our material.
And perhaps most importantly for its insistent valorization of sufficient leisure for unfettered creativity.
And its modeling of the world.
Its
I hope the powerful utility of the comic frame and the crucial necessity of free creative exercise will become clear in the following pages.
Wrestling power to account with humor.
And personal development of strong creative skills.
Maybe two of the most valuable and hopeful survival tools.
We can deploy in our rapidly changing 21st century.
Wow.
And, uh, yes, that's just page one and two.
There's a lot of stuff in this big book.
There's a lot of quotes from me.
I guess he interviewed me a couple of times.
I vaguely remember that.
He actually came to Wisteria during a Starwood and interviewed me.
I would call that a tome.
Yeah.
And he did a survey of Hour of Slack listeners.
Well, here's a picture of Philo and me at Burning Man in the year 2000.
Isn't that pretty?
Very pretty.
It's in color.
Here's a reprint of Buck, former pastor Buck Naked's little newsletter, which he called Hour of Slack.
And, um, in the fall of 1984.
We got the radio show in 85.
But, uh, yeah, you can't see this.
And so I'm not going to show you the pictures.
Although it is really a strange thing for, oh my God, there's my ex-wife belly dancing at X day.
Strange, strange, strange.
Uh, well, him.
Aha.
Oh.
And I thought my church was bad.
Praise Reverend Cipher.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, it's, it's funny.
I was reading all these highfalutin things about how wonderful we are and, and how strange and weird that man is who is called Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
If you can hear me, can you hear me?
Yes.
I can.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Cause I was going to ask we, if you do me a favor.
I'd even do you a flavor.
What is it?
Um, sometimes.
You could say, hello, you're on the theological hotline.
How can I make you hot?
Only do it real sexy, right?
So it sounds like.
I'll write that down.
You're, you're on the theological hotline.
Hello.
You're on the theological hotline.
How can I help you?
Can I do something hot?
No, no.
It's how can I make you hot?
How can I make you hot?
Type two.
Take three.
No, no.
I can do it.
Take three.
They're small.
Can I do that again?
Just one more time.
I know I'm done really, but I can do one better.
Just one better.
No, she was one who's going to do it.
Here, I wrote her a script.
He's written my script for me now.
I have the power, the power of pen and paper.
That's because you're her suit, young man.
Okay, stand by.
We're going to do, we're going to do.
Here, stand by.
I'm pulling music now.
We'll do take one.
You're on the theological hotline.
How can I make you hot?
Only do it real sexy, right?
Do that one more time.
A little bit slower.
A little bit more slowly.
Yeah, a little breathier.
Yeah, it's a lot.
She's a little bit juicy and stuff.
You are on the theological hotline.
How can I make you hot?
Okay.
That's a wrap.
Yeah, I'll have a chicken wrap and a pork wrap.
Yeah, that's good.
And wrap some bacon around it.
I was thinking about clear foil.
I'm sorry.
Speak.
That's a wrap song.
A wrap sandwich song.
Yeah.
You could sample that and put sandwiches on it and just describe everything that's going
on in the world because none of it makes any sense to begin with.
You could just perfectly just describe any, I'm sorry.
I read that phrase, nothing makes any sense.
Anyway, earlier in this book I was reading, it was a book about the Church of the Subgenius,
Dave.
I just got it in the mail.
There's only two copies that I know of in existence, but this guy, Reverend Lee Cipher
in Virginia, wrote his PhD dissertation book about the Church of the Subgenius, and he
sent me a hardbound copy of it.
It's not terrible.
It's actually pretty cool.
No, it's really pretty cool.
I couldn't understand it.
It's not hiding her hair of the fancy wordage, but it has lots of good pictures.
Well, look here, Dave.
Here's a letter from R. Crumb down at the bottom.
God, it's so lame.
Well, keep on Bobbin', and an R. Crumb drawing of Bob Dobbs saying, Hup Ho, in his keep on
trucking thing.
It's in the book?
Yeah, it's in the book.
Yes.
He's reprinted a letter.
You don't know about all these?
Well, I don't know.
I saved our famous people letters after they became famous before I threw them away.
Well, here's one from Ken Kesey.
Ken Kesey said in July of 1982, Attention all you subgeni who claim to represent Bob.
You are taking yourselves and your religion entirely too seriously.
I used to love reading the stark fist, but with your new issue, more than 50 pages, you
have invaded the realm of wretched excess.
It now takes up all of my slack time to stagger through this voluminous rag.
Slack off.
Dobbs would understand my dilemma.
Surely, a few pages would suffice.
Wishing you luck, the Reverend Hardly Visible.
P.S. I'm enclosing money.
And he scotch taped four pennies.
And that was the late Ken Kesey.
No.
These relics of antiquity need to go in the sacrosanct areas of the Turks' compounds deep
in South America, where the monkeys hide and the children play in the trees and argue with
each other voluminously.
Well, all of this historical stuff.
Questions of?
Yes, yes?
Questions of theology.
I'm sorry.
Theological.
You're on the theological hotline.
How can I make you hot?
Why?
I don't want to.
Here's a postcard from Mark Mothersbaugh of Devo.
Wow.
Yeah, it's a, yeah, the back when we were famous and famous people paid attention to
us, that was cool back in those days.
But I could see your house though with luminarias and stuff like that all over the place and
little votive candles.
And here's, here's a framed autograph from so-and-so, so-and-so.
He said, keep, keep.
You know who I do have a framed autograph of?
Ray Harryhausen.
Ray Harryhausen, the great stop motion animator.
Yes, we do.
It's framed.
That is some Vinars right there, buddy.
Well, notice I didn't, I didn't frame the letters from R. Crumb or Ken Kesey or Mothersbaugh
or David Byrne.
I framed the, we framed the Jack Chick comic postcard.
Oh, I see.
The Jack Chick comic posters and the Susie the Flusie artwork.
And I framed the Oingo Boingo fellows.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, Danny Elfman.
Elfman's autographed photo.
I, I framed that.
And I framed it.
It's a frame.
It's a frame up.
You framed Elfman.
Yep.
He didn't really write any of that repetitive music.
Frame up.
Starring Wins Hardwick.
Yeah, and Jim Slanny.
Jim Slanny.
And back in them days, back when Bob was famous, we was riding high.
And I do mean high.
This was the 80s, remember?
Everything goes back in the 80s.
Everything did go.
It went away.
All our money, our fame, my voice.
Now I talk like Bill Clinton.
Just a poor old washed up, old adulterer.
Well, I think we'll everybody.
What everybody wants to know and what the listening audience wants to hear is why you
sound like Bill Clinton and why you've chosen that as some sort of icon to live out your
macrimony.
And one other thing, you refer to yourself in the very beginning as shot and spent back
in the 1980s when everybody knows you just have not capitalized on your fame very well.
Linda?
You mean that?
Well, you know.
You mean the fact that I don't answer letters from famous people and hide from the telephone
and never go to parties.
But I'm not Bob.
Bob does all of that stuff.
I'm just a scribe.
I'm supposed to sit in the office with a hunchback in a garret assembling ministerial packets
to mail out to subgeniuses, which reminds me I have to do that very thing starting tomorrow.
And carefully documenting everything that happens.
Now, we need.
What we need, Dave, is a chimpanzee.
To do most of the work that I do.
Oh, I thought you meant to do a chimpanzee voice and I haven't been able to do chimp voices
anymore.
Oh, wow.
I learned that from Cheetah.
Was that you or we?
No, that was me.
No, that was him.
Well, it was Cheetah.
I was channeling the great spirit of Cheetah.
The inimitable imitator.
The army of Cheetah.
The great stripper author of Ritalin for Brother.
Wow.
In Lobotown, USA.
Yeah, I can channel these different dead things.
These different artifacts you can reconstruct in your mind.
I'm a spirit medium.
Yeah, I'm not just making this stuff up, you see.
These are the spirits are speaking through me.
They're thousands of years old.
The elder brothers and sisters of mine.
The elders of the goddesshood of the hidden mountain are speaking through me and I'm
channeling their homeopathic wisdom.
Well, I don't know...
Water has a memory.
Did you know that?
Water has memory?
Yeah, water has a memory.
Well, that's the premise for storing information.
Water, like in Rollerball.
I'm a new age homeopath.
Water has a memory.
See, if you put one molecule in a bottle, it's like water.
If you put one molecule of medicine in it, why, then you can sell tiny, tiny jars of
it for thousands of dollars because it has medicine in it.
Because water remembers.
I saw that in a movie called What the Bleak Do We Know?
And that movie proved what the makers of the movie know, which was a bunch of hogwash.
You see, I'm adherent of the forbidden sciences.
Oh, yeah?
Not the allowed sciences or the quiet sciences, but the...
What?
The arcane truths.
What are they?
Can you explain in detail if you have them?
If you have five, think of your Oriflex...
Dave, explain it in detail.
Isn't that what we've been doing for the last 35 years for an hour a week?
Explaining or at least teasing, hinting at the arcane secrets.
That's what I thought.
Or going so deep that perhaps fracking is not a solution or reverse or whatever you
call it.
Injection.
And injection into another planetary sphere would be nice too, but you hear everybody
speak about lately.
You hear all the big humdrums and the fatwigs on various radio shows using your expressions
freely.
The pundits and punsters.
And what they don't pull over us is the fact that we're not going to be able to do anything.
They're just going to be on their own memories, can't be given anywhere else.
There's no sukkur or balm of Gilead coming from those breasts.
They're just feeding us a bunch of...
It's bad to say it.
Lone cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Of course I remember that.
I think it was 1974 in the backyard of my grandmother's house.
No, it was in the backseat of your grandmother's car with Reverend Televangelo.
Oh boy.
Remember Reverend Televangelo?
Yes.
She was very pretty.
The car is not in the yard though, because it certainly is.
For all intents and purposes, you know, you live in the car in the back of the house.
We'll all live in the car in the back of the house soon, Dave.
Behind the rich man's house.
We live in the abandoned car behind the rich man's house.
That's the fate of what was once the most...
Middle class.
We'll live in a bog among the reeds, Paul.
That'll be about it.
Just a little sphincter movement to the right, a little sphincter movement to the left.
Everything's fine and settled back into the grit of post-urban society.
Whatever this is, this transhumanistic...
Hey, did you ever read Bill McKibben?
No.
He makes you cry.
Well, I'll drop that right there.
He'll make you cry?
This one.
The first one.
Those who can do, those who can't teach, those who can't teach become cultural critics.
There, how's that?
Well, that's perfect, but it still doesn't make sense in the way that we...
The reason I mentioned that...
...in the way that we...
In this book about the church of the sub-genius, the guy said that there hadn't been a lot
of academic coverage of the church but some of it was negative okay here this
is good you'll like this chapter 3 academic responses a brief survey of the
literature in contrast to the occasionally alarmed attention of law
enforcement to the Church of the subgenius academia has hardly bothered
to take a second look at Bob until the 2010 publication of Carol Cusack's
invented religions imagination fiction and faith there had been very little
serious examination of the Church of the subgenius as Cusack notes in her work
quote most critics are hostile in the sense that they are certain that the
Church of the subgenius is a childish prank and nothing more unquote a few
references that can be found
you can see the reference to the book of the church of the subgenius in the
book of the church of the subgenius in the
few references that can be found are usually brief and dismissive for
example Paul Mann's May 1995 postmodern culture essay stupid undergrounds
describes the Church of the subgenius as quote worthless expansive and
aggressively sophomoric in his criticism of various underground challenges to
traditional rationality Cusack also
notes Mann's scathing assessment of the Church of subgenius writing that he has
quote foamed at the mouth over JR Bob Dobbs and dismisses the impact of their
satire now here's the funny part I've looked up this guy Paul Mann in
Wikipedia
and he's not in there!
he wasn't considered notable enough to be in Wikipedia but guess who is Reverend Ivan Stang how about that
uh-huh
And dr. Renfield Fuckhunter aka Dr Firely Drummond
Dr. Well I'm already dead so let's give it a try
I mean, why not live each day as if you died a couple
weeks ago and smell the same way my theory about the whole thing you're not
really the populating you're on your undulating to a different rhythm you
don't know yeah like you're not depopulating your undulating to a different rhythm uh-huh
rhythm. It's all by virtue. That's a household knowledge. That's more than a
noticeable too. It's about, it goes far far into space, you know, the vibrations and
waves go on forever. Every stupid vibration is made because everything's
constantly making stupid vibrations goes on forever. What a blight on the universe.
Maybe. Well anyway, I just thought it was funny that that cultural critic of
postmodernism never did anything worth listing in Wikipedia or anywhere else. I
typed his name in and there were about ten notable Paul Manns, but they weren't
him. Though Mann's complaint seems to miss the complexity of subgenius parody,
he also seems offended by the energy of the subgenius' voluntary creative
participation in collective critique. Quote, oh this is good,
the cult of Dobbs Christensen
analyse a rabid over-participation in the stupid spectacle
of the Real that goes far beyond any blank parody or post modern pastiche.
In an... Then our on a friend goes on. In an age, that has been noted for
increasing isolation and disengagement, participation seems an odd thing to
condemn, as subgenious history reveals the rhetorical performance of the church
can sometimes evoke passion. But ifacjiah is guilty of sounds of holes, vision of
guided responses, like when that guy killed that person that one time.
And they have not been limited to mere academic polemics.
And then he goes to some other bookie person who said,
oh, the Haverford Journal essay, quote,
the new traditionalists, Baudrillard, Devoe,
and the postmodern de-evolution of the simulation.
Listen, he focuses on rhetoric to describe subgenius impact on Devoe.
The pseudo-religious organization's rhetoric forms yet another pillar
of Devoe's de-evolutionary philosophy.
The church is an artificial postmodern religion that ordains priests,
such as founding Devoe member Mark Mothersma at the low, low price of $29.95.
We never did that.
We never sold membership.
We never sold membership for $29.95.
No.
It's always been $29.96.
Yeah.
No.
So it's been round.
No, we actually, we round them off because it's hard for us to do the math.
Well, are you supposed to be doubting the credibility of somebody who did a thesis about you?
Yeah.
I mean, is this Paul?
Is this Paul Mann existing, or is he like, are you going to have to go?
I'm sure he's.
And search through literary journals, because there's a lot of people named Paul Mann.
You wouldn't expect him to appear in Wikipedia.
But he might appear in the line.
Yeah.
I mean, I've read a Harvard College review of photojournalistic essays on pubic hairs and formations in the nearby rock structures or something.
And, you know, they got all that stuff like they talk about, you know, like you were just saying.
Well, I got one thing to say.
You've got to search through literary journals.
Fight the man.
Fight Paul Mann.
Actually, I'm sure he's dead by now.
No, he might be on his.
He might be sailing his.
Someplace where the luminaries don't shine, you know, just to hang in his head in shame and then going around hoping for tenure, which is more than five year.
Well, apparently we have been mentioned in a whole bunch more books.
We were mentioned in Magic, Rhetoric and Literacy by William A. Covino.
You Google that one successfully?
No, I haven't bothered with most of these other ones because they like us.
They thought.
We were funny.
A world of fantasy gone wild.
And they spell fantasy with a P-H.
A protean sophistry.
Which, okay.
You don't need to say that in a scientific journal.
So, man, those guys are rough on each other.
Princess, you'll like this one.
Listen to this line.
In a unique observation, Covino demonstrates some interesting rhetorical parallels between the description of.
Bob from the book of the subgenius and a contemporary description of the goddess by author activist Starhawk.
Oh, my.
Yeah.
So this guy compares us to Starhawk.
Goodness.
We compared Bob's description to Starhawk's.
Interesting statements about some fictitious goddess.
I see.
It's very, very interesting.
And there's a parallel with Marcuse.
His great refusal countering the commodification of culture.
A riotous acknowledgement.
The part about when he fought in the Spanish Civil War.
I remember that.
The part where Stan was a hero in the Spanish Civil War.
Where he saved a bunch of American volunteers by washing tampons and putting strange articles in his eye, ears, and nose.
Here's a good one.
This is a real good one.
It seems Covino's final analysis of the church is tainted by the hyperbolic observation.
Of former subgenius J.
Kinney.
As recorded in the fall 86 issue of Whole Earth Review.
Kinney fears that.
Now get this.
Quote.
The church's widespread cynicism is a license for widespread hatred.
And that quote.
The church's absolute cynicism is tantamount to fascism.
Now the funny thing is.
I know J.
Kinney.
He's a little friend of ours.
He was the guy who first put us in touch with.
For crime.
Yes.
And Paul Maverick.
J.
Kinney was kidding.
Funny letters.
This.
The statement about the church.
That these academics have been quoting for 25 years.
Was written like the church itself.
In jest.
J.
Kinney was kidding.
And these academics have.
It's.
They're academics.
Yeah.
Right.
What can you say?
What.
You know.
They're half and half.
Just like everything else.
Like the authorities.
And the anti-authorities.
Half of them are into it.
To be.
Do good things.
And get stuff out there.
And the other half are just.
Well.
They have to get.
They learned how to speak this way.
And just like.
They still had to do a lot of work.
And it was probably fun for them.
And they're a real jerk off.
No.
Never mind.
I.
Went too far off one range.
Among academic responses.
Carol Cusack's invented religions.
Represents.
The first thorough and thoughtful analysis.
Of the church of the subgenius.
Making it a central text.
In my brief review of the literature.
No.
Nevertheless.
Cusack argues.
That.
In the context of 17th century.
English ranters.
The church has a quote.
Legitimate pedigree.
In the history of western religion.
One that stresses anarchic protest.
Sensual indulgence.
And innate divinity.
I think they.
What they meant was.
Divine.
Innainity.
I thought.
We were.
Diddling.
Innainity.
I think.
So there was a misprint in here.
Oh.
I thought you were.
Offering sexual amenities.
That's not.
How bad my hearing is going.
Right.
Lately.
I think it's from putting.
Tabasco.
Stars.
On.
Right in there.
You know.
Where it isn't.
Really.
You stuck it in your ear.
Didn't you.
Dave.
They told you not to.
Well.
They said.
If you.
Put those nails.
They said.
Dave.
If you put those nails in your ear.
We're not going to let you watch TV.
In the group room anymore.
Have you ever watched the plasma.
Grow in the group room.
Have you ever.
Ever seen the plants.
Wave to you.
And then start to bark.
Softly in the wind.
No.
I was never locked up.
In a mental institution.
Like you were.
Dave.
I was not locked up there.
I was there.
Of my own free will.
And I could come and go.
As I please.
And I just chose.
To not be held.
And dragged down to the ground.
And beaten up.
By people with street jackets.
As the great man once said.
Stop abusing that substance abuser.
Now.
Baby.
Oh.
That is one of my favorite songs.
Especially in Quebec nowadays.
Where everybody.
You know.
Get silly on the church.
Of the subgenius.
And everything.
The guy like.
Got there.
You know.
I think God.
God got mad at Tibet.
No.
It was Nepal.
God.
Oh.
Man.
He put the hammer down.
The hell out there.
You know.
Those people must have done something.
They must have legalized.
Gay marriage.
Or something.
In Nepal.
Because they.
Did you hear about that Princess?
Were you about the terrible earthquake?
Yes.
It shook Mount Everest.
I did.
Yes.
It shook Mount Everest.
And a bunch of rich people got killed.
They were climbing Mount Everest.
Yeah.
Two Americans.
Who probably would still be alive.
If they'd never been rich.
And successful enough.
To live their lifelong dream.
Of.
Climbing Mount Everest.
Yeah.
Which of course.
Ended their life.
Because.
Happened to climb it.
On the day.
When the big earthquake happened.
And there was an avalanche.
Well they turned it into a tourist event.
Where like.
You know.
Your helicopter.
About three quarters of the way up there.
So you're just taking a walk.
In a place real close to the crest.
And then.
You know.
If you're one of the.
A climber.
Who has a.
A Sherpa with him.
Then you can go all the way up.
And put your.
You know.
Your rings.
And your goblets.
And all your different.
I have.
You carried from the church.
Church.
On the top of the suitcase.
Whisk it back.
It's a tourist event now.
The helicopters aren't even real anymore.
They.
I read that.
On Mount Everest.
At the various.
Camp.
Base camps.
That you stop along the way.
There's.
There's so much.
Human excrement.
That it's piled up.
In.
Like.
Huge walls.
Because.
What do you do with it?
It's frozen.
It's frozen solid.
There's no air or heat.
To decompose.
The poo-poos.
It doesn't decompose.
It just freezes.
And they pile it up.
In huge piles.
So there's giant piles.
Of frozen.
Poo-poo.
Of people.
Not yet.
He's.
You can't grow.
Frop on this stuff.
Or you can.
You probably grow.
Some kind of.
No account.
Dirt weed.
Marijuana or something.
But you can't grow.
Frop.
Unholy.
Not on human.
Not on frozen human.
And so.
So.
You know.
It's sad.
How people just have wasted.
And you know.
They're talking about.
Putting a tram.
Into the Grand Canyon.
Did you hear about that?
It's the lag tights.
You mean.
The micro.
I mean.
The Mennonites.
No.
In fact.
The Navajo.
And.
Or.
Whichever Indians are.
In control of that section.
Of the Grand Canyon.
Where they have that big.
Glass.
Shelf.
That you can walk on.
For fifty dollars.
And look down.
They are.
Seriously.
Considering.
Putting a tram.
So that anybody.
Can go down.
To the bottom.
Of the Grand Canyon.
Just get right on.
And you know.
What that's going to mean?
Trash.
And noise.
And big.
Fat.
Waddling.
Americans.
And Asian tourists.
Everywhere.
The animals.
Will all.
Go away.
And someday.
The Grand Canyon.
Will just be filled with.
Big gulp.
Cartons.
And.
Burger wrappers.
Blowing.
Through the wind.
As it is.
The Grand Canyon.
Is so.
Grand.
That I know.
That I'll never be able.
To walk down.
In there.
Because then.
I'd have to walk back out.
And I've stood on the.
I've sat.
Halfway.
A little ways.
Down the trail.
And watched.
Strapping young people.
Walking out of the Grand Canyon.
And the pain.
On their faces.
Is how I knew.
That I would never.
Do that.
But now.
They're talking about.
Putting.
For money.
A tram.
Or you know.
A subway.
Whatchamacallit.
A conveyance.
A train.
That goes down.
From the top.
To the bottom.
Of the Grand Canyon.
So that the waddling.
Obese Americans.
And other.
Tourists.
Can suck their thumbs.
While they.
Shuffle along.
Going.
It's hot down here.
Why should air condition.
This place?
Because people.
Are spoiled.
Foul.
Ugly.
Things.
Whose.
Lives.
Are not.
But.
An endless.
Succession.
Of vile.
Tasks.
I must say.
As a personal reflection.
I visited.
Chaco Canyon.
One time.
And the thousand.
A couple.
How many thousand.
Year old trail.
Which is very straight.
But very narrow.
Was damaged.
While I was there.
By a bus full of stupid.
German tourists.
Oh my.
That thing is named.
Deutschland.
But it's like.
Let's go.
Okay.
You know.
And like.
No man.
It's hard for one car.
To go on this trail.
And everybody suggests.
You use the regular.
You know.
20th century.
Asphalt.
Trail.
That extends.
All the way around.
But isn't the old one.
But they let you go on it.
And the tribal elders.
Of which.
There aren't any.
It's the.
Park system.
Told the police.
That they had no.
Right.
Or left.
Or shoe.
Well.
You know.
Dave.
You're right about.
The.
The tribal elders.
Have pretty much.
Been replaced.
By tribal.
Politicians.
Who run.
For the office.
Of.
President.
Or chief.
Of the tribe.
And they're just like.
Every other.
Kind of politician.
And the corruption.
Within.
Tribal.
Organizations.
Is one of the biggest.
Problems.
That our Native American.
Brothers and sisters.
Have.
It's not just.
Problems from.
Outside.
From the pink man.
But the.
But the fellow.
Red man.
Sometimes.
Is.
Spitting.
A bunch of.
Red man.
All over.
The place.
So to speak.
Isn't that a kind of.
Chaw.
Tobacco.
I think so.
Red man.
Yeah.
You know.
Everything gets.
In our land.
The conspiracy.
Lives inside.
Even.
The most devout.
And pure.
Subgenius.
It's kind of a.
Contradiction.
In terms.
There.
You know.
But I mean.
We.
We run into the same.
Silly.
Stupid.
Office.
Politics.
Even within our.
Nice little.
Harmless cult.
Harmless.
Until next day.
That is.
When our brothers.
From the stars.
Shall come.
And give us the weapons.
We have long.
Awaited.
That we may.
Meet.
Out.
Vengeance.
On the.
Incensei.
Meat.
Puppets.
We call.
Humans.
E.
My throat hurts again.
Yeah.
I had just a.
Short while.
You will be.
Fine as wine.
In.
Supper time.
And just to relax.
And.
Tell us more.
About the.
Antiquities.
And about your.
Your own life.
At home.
Were you a.
Coddled child.
Or were you.
A reasonably.
Good boy.
I was a.
Cobbled child.
They.
Shoot me.
Like.
A horse.
And they built.
The shoes.
They nailed.
Around my feet.
And said.
Now go and walk.
My son.
Actually.
We were talking to.
Pappy today.
That's my father.
About.
Your feet.
Eighty six.
And he said.
I.
He said.
What did he say.
He basically.
Was explaining.
Why.
I was stupid.
Because.
He.
Had imparted.
To me.
Certain.
Arcane.
And.
Occult.
Secrets.
That.
He says.
Essentially.
Made me.
Rather than.
The sharpest.
Sharpest.
Hunting knife.
Instead.
Into a wooden.
Stirring spoon.
Dull.
And.
Soft.
My father.
Doesn't.
Give me.
All that much.
Respect.
It's funny.
Well.
I would say.
Such high winded.
Or long.
You know.
When it comes to.
Breaking wind.
Your father.
Yeah.
Probably one of the most.
Supreme aristocrats.
In the entire universe.
Well.
You might say.
The apple.
Don't fall.
Far from the tree.
Well.
Apples.
Are good.
For feeding.
Horses.
And making them.
Do you know.
What.
And that's what.
We're doing.
Right now.
But I was talking.
Specifically.
About where.
To get such.
High minded.
Occult.
Ideas.
I mean.
There's just.
Some sort of.
Do you have to wear.
One of them.
Conical hats.
No.
My father.
Was saying.
The opposite.
That.
Because.
He had.
Inculcated.
Me.
As a child.
With certain.
Arcane.
And.
Occult.
Garbage.
That.
That was why.
I was so dumb.
He loves to.
He.
He cannot.
He just cannot.
You know.
Grant me.
Any.
Slack.
In terms of.
Well.
You know.
We ought to show him.
This book.
A good luck.
Pappy.
This.
A learned.
A scholar.
In a dang.
University.
Somewhere.
And wrote up.
A fancy book.
About how smart.
We is.
Yes.
You should show that.
To him.
Well.
You know.
What he'll do.
He'll skim through it.
And go.
Well.
How come.
There's not.
Not more.
Color pictures.
They didn't spend.
Much money on this.
Now.
Did they?
You know.
That's.
He just.
I do know.
I love my father.
And I think.
That he truly.
Loves me.
Despite.
My.
What he considers.
To be.
Idiocy.
Because he keeps saying.
He kept saying.
Now.
Ivan.
You need to.
Learn from that.
Billy Graham.
And.
Jim Baker.
And Jim Jones.
And some of these.
Other successful.
Televangelists.
And make your.
Churches.
Subgenius.
Fancier.
So you can get more money.
More money.
And I was going.
Well.
But.
But Pappy.
Well.
That was what Dr.
Axe.
Originally.
Wanted us to do.
Was to rip off.
Stupid people.
Like all the other religions.
Did.
And I.
I was going.
No.
We want to rip off.
The nice people.
Not the stupid people.
So.
And he never understood that.
No.
He never got the part.
Where you can't keep a straight face.
I can't believe.
A lawyer.
Would not understand.
Oh.
He does.
He.
He understood it.
It's just that.
Because.
It was his son.
That did it.
He always has to do.
The one upmanship.
You see.
I think that's really odd.
But.
I'm kind of stuck in between.
My son.
And my dad.
Who both.
Are constantly proving to me.
How much better they are.
At everything.
No.
Seriously.
I know.
Well.
I have to laugh.
It's just bizarre.
I used.
I used to cook.
For the family.
You know.
Pusket.
And chili.
And stuff.
Well.
My son.
Decided to become.
A gourmet cook.
He makes sushi.
And things.
Like that.
Really.
Really fancy stuff.
He makes amazing things.
It's just.
It's just to prove.
That his dad.
Doesn't know how to cook.
I used to make movies.
Remember.
I was like a filmmaker.
Well.
He's a.
I was a film editor.
He's in the director's guild.
Mm-hmm.
He lives in Los Angeles.
Hollywood.
Mm-hmm.
So.
They.
They're motivated.
My whole family's motivated.
By how to make.
Poor old.
Grandpa.
Stang.
Feel.
Inadequate.
But.
I won't listen to him.
Because I'm a sub-genius.
We're not as smart as geniuses.
We're sub-geniuses.
We're not.
We're.
We're better.
Just because.
Not because we're smarter.
Or better looking.
Because we ain't.
Amenical case.
Just because.
That's all.
Because why?
That's why.
Because.
Hey, did our music finally end?
No, that was.
I think.
It's a sort of.
Gently faded away.
I use this CD because it is 40 minutes of non-stop music.
By people who slayed Pink's for Charlie Manson.
It's from the soundtrack album of the film Lucifer Rising.
Kenneth Anger.
Oh, man.
This unbelievably boring art movie.
Oh, it is.
It's so.
God.
He saw me walk out of the theater.
I'm so bored.
He gave me that autographed poster.
That's another autograph we have.
Yes.
Kenneth Anger.
He gave me a poster.
And he gave me the record album of this.
And then I went into the theater and watched several of his famous underground movies.
And they were so dull.
And then when it came.
Pretentious and artsy-fartsy and pompous.
And then.
Then.
Then Lucifer Rising starts up.
And it's like.
And I thought, I need to sneak out of here.
But I hope the famous director, Kenneth Anger, doesn't see me.
But he did.
And then when I ran into him again 10 years later, I said, hey, could we use your music on the Hour of Slack?
And he said, no.
It's sacred music recorded in a prison by Bobby Boosalil.
The Charles Manson's minion.
And you can't use it for any subgenius stuff.
So.
So the anger in Kenneth Anger.
Came out.
It's going to be even angrier now.
Because I just played that home record in the background on a stupid subgenius show.
Hello?
What?
What's happening?
Is this the theological hotline?
How can we make you hot?
Well, it's just a question.
It's a question of controversy over the last few millennia.
I've always wondered if Dobbs, perhaps, doesn't recreate himself over every generation for the last few.
If he doesn't just become a new thing for time.
And then becomes an old thing.
And becomes a new thing.
And self-renewal.
Like Oslapis.
Or Mamamoo.
Mamamoo.
I don't know what the heck that boy's going on about.
I don't know.
And I don't know where that alien voice came from either.
I think that was Dave's tape recorder, wasn't it?
Was it?
Was ist?
Was ist los?
The hunt is los.
No, no, no.
Hey, I have, it's getting near to the end of show.
And we haven't played much music.
But I have some new music from Reverend Byrne.
His last name is Bridges.
Reverend Byrne Bridges.
And I think he's an American, but he's in Germany.
Reverend Byrne Bridges?
What do you think of that, Princess Leigh?
I think he's in Berlin.
And his name is Byrne?
Byrne Bridges.
I like it.
It's a good name.
And he sent three pieces of anti-music for Bob,
of which I'm going to play one for three minutes,
starting in two minutes.
And that'll be the end of the show.
The end of our show.
So there, I've done that.
Yeah, two minutes from now, I will play this.
And it's very, it's quite different.
It's new.
It's brand new.
I might want to listen to some of that,
even though I'm not participating.
But I might want to linger to.
I'll leave you on, but potted down.
Like a potted plant.
Ah, if only someone would pot my plant.
Someone would plant it deep in the earth when it needs to be.
The sun can shine and the moon can whisper soft things in my head.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one evening,
I think it was at the end of April, sometime like this.
No, no, I'm sorry.
I didn't know that the sun could shine
when your roots were way down there.
Well, when they plant you, Dave, rest assured,
I will come and water you.
Wow, that's so sweet.
You will even,
you will even leave droppings, I suppose.
Yeah, yeah, because, you know,
froth grows on the graves of dead holy men and yeti's.
And yeti droppings.
And between your holiness planted in the ground
and my droppings,
maybe we can grow some decent frappe on that thing,
on your Skellington, the Dave skull.
But what will it avail, Stan?
It won't avail the universe, or the world, anything.
It will not avail it.
Right.
It will all come to no avail?
Yeah, but at least it'll save me an extra trip to the bathroom.
Let's put it that way.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry,
Hour of Slack, from the Church of the Subgenius.
You can write for more information,
those of you in prison, from Subgenius.
That's post office box 181417, Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob.
Hey, that Monster Hunter music went really good.
Yeah.
That worked.
Yeah, it was perfect.
Thank you, thank you.
Yes, it was an excellent cue.
That's some orchestra in Japan doing the Monster Hunter
video game theme.
Yes, yes, I know.
I think that was the fifth anniversary album.
There should be a new anniversary album.
Coming up, it's a big deal in Japan.
I'm a Monster Hunter.
We'll play that song.
OK, OK, we have a song we have to play.
OK, Dave, I'm going to start fading you out.
I'm going to fade down that music.
I've been feeling faded for most of the evening.
I think it was those giant things you gave me, the water.
And coming up, burn bridges.
Oh, don't feel faded, Dave.
You've got to live your life in excess to the arrival of the excess with the rule over
your life.
You don't need a God's approval, just the starkness of removal and they are bobbed up.
You've got to live your life in excess to the arrival of the excess with the rule over
your life.
The teeth standing, suck of the ecchi.
Wash the pinks, turn into confetti on the morning of X day.
You can make the water wetter, but there's a deity that's better.
It's J.R. Bob Jobs.
The true job was some genius.
Oh, yes, flak and kernel foundation.
And lots of sex.
Until it hurts.
I just killed you.
It's a faith founded in common.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
And flak for the ordain.
And the lads say the butterfly coppers had a baby struck Emily.
And the blanched hour under itself leaves the smusk in the hands of a true believer.
And it shall cause empathy upon the fat of thy own lambs.
And it shall wait upon the neck and stump to thy very end days.
And the demons shall yet accompany thee upon the holy quest for the blood of Moab and the lamb.
On of the eighty billion tribes of Moab.
And sickness and blight and malady and beast shall be upon thy own lambs.
And enemies in the tempest.
And it shall be good.
And it shall come to pass in the end times.
And it shall reek upon the trembling masses at which they shall soon forget.
Yea, early I say unto thee.
Yea, yea, by the smiling pink false prophets.
And launch and yet launch again.
And E!
ANURA!
AMRE!
SHEEPY MAD distinction b
nazdie
altered
death