But now at the beginning of the 1980s, I want to make another personal prediction.
The 1980s will be the most catastrophic decade in the history of man.
And yet no one who will accept what God has to say has to be afraid.
As a matter of fact, you can be so excited that every day can be a day where you are not only optimistic,
but saying, this might be the day. This may be it.
And in the meanwhile, God has promised that as we claim his promises,
he will sustain us even in the day.
This is one of the darkest hours of history.
And give us a way out.
Time for show. Live show for you now.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of Slap.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The past year resembles nothing so much as the bad alternate timeline
that the hero of a cheap science fiction book has to go back and fix.
And you, the listener, are that time traveler.
If only your memory could be restored to you.
You are the listener.
You are the humble time traveler.
I know what you mean, though.
It does...
Yeah, that would explain a lot.
It would explain the wooden-headed people coming up to us
while we're taking our sulfur baths.
It would certainly explain all the money that's now going to be flowing into arms.
And legs.
And think of how fully well laundered that money is.
It must be very squeaky clean by now.
Just think about George, the bushy-haired one himself,
and counting that money back in some room.
He's got to replace those behind the oval orifice.
That's not what this is all about.
No.
It's all about revenge.
That's it.
Taking over Mars.
Yes.
Eventually, to take over...
To take back Mars.
Yeah.
Take over Mars.
To take Mars back.
Our rightful home.
That we, the true Martians, were expelled from.
So that they, the oil sheiks, and the oil billionaires,
and all the oily characters,
would have some...
They did...
So we're living in the Martian time slip?
Oh, I can grok to that.
In this time continuum.
I can grok to that, my water brother,
but by the same token, when do we...
We were enslaved.
We've got to go back in time and kill Bob's mom.
The psychic shackles...
They came and took us off our home.
After Bob was born.
Exslaid thousands and millions and bazillions of years ago.
Does this mean that there's a big deal with all the money we want
here at the front of our house,
and we can pick it up and just...
It doesn't mean anything like that.
No, man.
It just means that we were kidnapped,
and we're going to be kidnapped.
We're going to be kidnapped from our home world,
and we're stuck here with you twerps.
Yeah, you guys.
You just...
You guys.
Go ahead.
Make my...
Bob?
Right.
Now.
Ha ha.
I am an antichrist.
I am an anarchist.
Don't know what I want,
but I know how to get it.
I want to destroy the passerby.
Cause I want to be anarchy.
I want to be an anarchist.
No.
Dog's body.
Anarchy.
For the UK.
It's coming sometime.
Maybe.
I give a wrong time.
Stop a traffic line.
Your future dream is a shopping scheme.
Cause I want to be anarchy.
In.
The.
City.
How many ways to get what you want.
I use a ashtray.
The best I use the rest I use the enemy I use anarchy cause I wanna be anarchy
The only way to be
Is this the MPLA?
Or is this the UD?
UD?
A
Or is this the IRA?
I thought it was the UK
Or just
Another
Country
Council
Tenancy
I
Wanna be
Anarchy
It's time to rule!
Mistdrop
التعامل
Anarchy
which is where we subgeniuses sometimes throw all of our weird new audio discoveries or creations into the mix
and then suck them right off for each other's and for use here on the Hour of Slack.
Now, that song Anarchy in the UK, that computerized cover version was by someone named Jima or J-I-M-A.
But what's interesting is where it came from.
It's a website called dictionaryoke.org.
Online dictionaries that sing the hits of yesterday.
You can basically program in songs, pick songs, and if it can find the tune, I guess you feed it the lyrics or something.
Yes, that's www.dictionaryoke.org.
Some of the other weird little sounds and burblings that pop up here and there on the show.
It came from Johnny Wishbone and I am BJR and Fernando Nende Lemore and from Artemia Salina, all the regulars,
and Dr. Noumonet, the regulars, so to speak, on all.binary slack.
And now I guess Hour of Slack.
And of course, friends, we always hear lots of ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland,
which is on every Thursday night.
And anybody can call.
Call in.
It's like about midnight Eastern time at WCSB Cleveland, wcsb.org.
Friends, that's Professor Chaz Smith as the host.
And our caller there that time was Reverend Turin.
And, of course, Lone Cow Dave.
Lone Cow Dave is always there, even at Christmas.
And see where I am right now, friends.
It is still Xmas, or about to be, something like that.
See, I never know exactly when each station is going to play any given particular Hour of Slack show.
I mail them out and I generally assume that they play roughly two weeks after I do them.
And so this show may be playing after Christmas or Christmas Day or sometime around these holidays and so forth.
And that's why it's not all Christmas stuff.
But we have yet nonetheless more to come.
From the great obtuse, from the gabofam,
even weasel teats, and Brother Clay, friends.
A lot of old and new Xmas Hour of Slack.
Old Hours of Slack and old me young.
So separate, so separate, so separate.
You from Telco.
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob.
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal.
Shut up, pink boy.
No way, I'll never sell out to the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien tool.
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher, jayner device, all you got to do is fight Jesus and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required, batteries not included.
This toy falls apart in three days.
He-Bob.
As the bastards of the universe, too much is always better than not enough.
From Bob Dobbs.
I came down so separately.
Gorgeous.
We can blow from head to toe.
Joy.
My God.
Everything you see here, can't also separate me.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
Santa Claus.
Yeah!
Ah!
insecurity
bakın
conseguir
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted.
for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table Jay did prepare.
for it was going to set it up.
So, I paid him a commercial for an electric train.
So, I need a car a regular ride.
He would dream so hard that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy-looking train set with locomotives and freight cars.
The station and the gateman.
The water tower and all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So grand that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
I didn't do it. Can I still have my dog?
No!
Boys and girls, everyone wants a Slinky.
You ought to get one.
Get a Slinky. Get your Slinky now.
You know what else let me down?
You're sloppy.
They had those big magnet things.
You're stinky.
And then they showed on TV somebody pulling a Volkswagen with the magnet that looked red.
It was red and it looked like a Mighty Man thing.
Oh, wow.
And it was a big magnet.
There was another good one, too.
You had a big red magnetic thing?
It was a finger that would shoot.
There was a lot of spy toys.
There was a lot of spy toys around.
Yes, exactly.
And there was a finger.
I can almost remember the song.
Double Agent Man.
How did I ever get along with five?
Secret Agency Woman.
Yeah, the fingers you could get.
All different kinds of fingers.
Some of them would shoot little darts, poison darts.
Some of them would...
So there were the mind control, remember the little mind control devices?
Some of them would launch little tiny nuclear headed...
Nuclear headed boys and girls.
See, that was the main problem.
The secret Sam brainwashing kit.
Sexual devices or something like that.
Those were the best.
Those were the best for me and my mom and at least dad.
I sometimes, when I come home, I was sober enough to walk.
Or is that called marital aids?
Well, that wasn't too obvious.
What, marital aids?
I had a...
No, you don't want to talk about that.
A secret Sam brainwasher kit where one kid would play the red Chinese interrogator.
Yeah, those were great.
And the other guy would play the American prisoner in the Korean War.
Did you ever play double Manchurian on that?
I'm glad to see battleship is still out there.
Actually, I ended up attacking a school teacher.
You did?
Say what?
Like three weeks after playing that because...
The light went off.
...a kid deprogrammed me to.
It was called Six Finger.
That is a beautiful story for Thanksgiving.
Don't!
You're wasting my time!
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap's just bull.
Santa Claus.
Santa Claus is real.
Santa Claw is a fool child.
Santa Claus.
Santa Claus is real.
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man.
He was so real, how come we didn't get squat last year?
But if you'll notice from time to time, especially on this most joyous birth of our baby dog,
that the things that you're wearing, never mind what I'm wearing, come on, get out of here.
Hey, stop.
Get your hand.
Hey.
Come on, put your hand.
Well, I had no idea.
It's no big deal.
I don't, you know.
Joel, right, man.
I understand Ed Wood was into that.
Ed Wood took the beach at Normandy in his frilly pink panties.
And his, you know, and his entrenching tool.
And that's the important part.
I want everybody from Sea Company over here.
The baby Jesus, the Mother Mary, and Bob.
Let's take them.
Christmas Day, June 1944.
We kick some Nazi butt.
The Babylonian hussars entrenched deeply on the beach,
dressed in their crab suits and their funny long underwear.
The cause of consternation isn't having anything to do with their cyclical cults.
It has more particularly to do with their religious doctrine.
And the Christmas Nazi devils fought the Christmas army men.
They stood together.
And God won.
Hand in hand until God won.
And the devil cried his devilish tears.
They were salty.
They were vinegary.
They were very bitter tears.
And as we collected them like tiny raindrops in a toxic pool,
we sat together and shaved.
And thanked our monkey we were born again in the incandescent light.
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan.
On July 4th.
And now you can have it all.
All pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby.
The baby Satan as told by various authors and eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
An announcement of the blessed anointment and birthday of our Lord.
See you.
Pray.
For one bright Christmas morning.
See you.
was born.
a cradle…
the rave Jesus at sorts.
To a rich man's family.
Batons
the river.
yss
Oh, I did that, my friends.
Well, rather, I pushed that button, I guess you could say.
And this music in the background is actually the Bishop from New York.
We've heard other burblings and sounds from Johnny Wishbone and, of course, ESO Swamp Radio.
And before that, Obtuse did all that Santa crap and Slinky crap and the beautifully mixed holiday buying crap.
And you can get it.
You can get it.
You can get his free album on buying.
But it's free.
Check their website, obtuse.iuma.com.
Yeah, and email them from there or something.
It's obtuse.iuma.com.
Great stuff.
But now, friends, now a premiere, a world premiere, truly, of the latest, greatest new hit from...
Gary Gaprogfran of the band that dare not speak its name, and he still dare not...
Putty Butt.
My baby just sits right there
Dressed up in her underwear
Jerry Springer is on the air
She's a putty bug
My baby ain't got much fat
Overeating's not where she's at
Not moving from where she's sat
She's a putty bug
I'm sitting like Barry White
Trying to get her to move at night
Guess I'm right
She's a putty bug
My baby ain't going nowhere
Once a week she moves from there
So I can pat you under her chair
She's a putty bug
Putty bug
By Gary
Gabofam
Wow, Stimpy.
We sure walked a long way.
I'm pumped.
Look, Ren.
It's St. Wizzleteat's house.
This must be the West Pole.
Hey, why don't we sing for him?
Yeah.
Then we can get our socks filled with sausages.
Well, hello, Mrs. Wizzleteat's.
Is Stinky home?
Stinky?
There's some filthy little street urchins to see you.
Huh?
Urchins?
What are urchins?
Some kind of newfangled dog?
Is that what you are?
Some kind of dog?
Well, then, you better bark like a dog.
If you're gonna act like a dog, then you better cry like a dog.
Honey, go get me my dog walloping two by four from the shed.
No, no, no.
We're here to sing you a yaksmas carol, Mr. Deet, sir.
Singing?
Well, that's different.
Honey, go get me my dog walloping guitar.
But let me sing you a song.
A little song I wrote to go somewhere.
Something like this.
Oh, the big wooden chicken lived in the bush.
A big fat bush full of worms.
Hey, man.
I think it's time to get out of here.
They ate the chicken and they all died the next day.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
Oh, yeah.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
I know.
Yeah.
Are we?
Is Chris?
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
But before it was after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season.
It was something else.
But I think they started the war over it.
Yeah.
If you haven't heard of me, I wouldn't be surprised.
I bet you know my relatives.
Their names will never die.
My mother is a saint and my brother is a God.
But all I am is Jesus Brother Bob.
Jesus Brother Bob.
Nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the brother of God, Junior.
Ah!
I have to pay the ferry to cross the Galilee.
But not my brother.
No, not him.
He walks across for free.
I finally get to work about a quarter after nine.
Already he's turning water into wine.
Jesus Brother Bob.
Nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born.
Just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the brother of God, Junior.
One day when I was home, I heard a mighty roar.
There were a thousand people right outside the door.
Help us Jesus, help us.
Came the cheering from the mountains.
There were a thousand people riding a ride.
But-
Then they got a look at me,
I'm not its only Bob.
Jesus Brother Bob.
Nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born.
Just a little sooner.
I'd be more than the brother of God, Junior
He, he died up on the cross
I thought that I was free
Finally, people would get to know me
For me
Hi, Bob
Hey, Judas
Hey
This was my big chance
To finally get ahead
The next thing you know, he's rising from the dead
Jesus, Brother Bob
I know, buddy, Brother Jim
I'm the son of God
If only I'd been born just a little sooner
I'd be more than the brother of God, Junior
Jesus, Brother Bob
I know, buddy, Brother Jim
I'm the son of God
If only I'd been born just a little sooner
I'd be more than the brother of God, Junior
Bob
Now you're back.
You're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
Except I sort of understand, because...
I've understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus,
no flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to,
it's that they won't let you.
No, there's just a crime in wilderness.
They're ashamed.
In the hot pursuit of wolves,
everywhere in the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
Oh, it's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind.
I can't get my finger off the paper.
I can't get my little knife in the pan, Jan.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man, I was trying to hear it against your tree,
and it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's your Christmas witch coming.
It's true.
A Christmas witch.
I'll be whole.
Oh, my God, yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more...
Her breasts are so cold.
Witchy than angelic.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that
if that's what she's packing out of you for real.
She's surrounded by hovering Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas witch.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I swear she had a much higher voice before when she called.
But...
Are you the 29-year-old girl I've dreamed of for the last 25 minutes?
Yo.
Are you the 29-year-old woman I've dreamed of for the last 25 minutes?
No, but, um...
Can you...
Hello?
Yes.
I figure that, um, on an occasional guest that,
quite frankly, that people want to listen to.
That I could quite entertain them.
You?
You could entertain them?
Oh, sure.
Quite frankly.
Uh, what do you mean by quite frankly?
And here's Frank!
I'm a sexy black male.
That's what we got Frank here.
He's a sexy black male.
He says he works in the computer industry.
He's 35 years old.
Oh, no.
Skiing, fishing, and...
That's a complete lie.
Pardon?
But what's behind door number three?
That's right.
It's the monster woman of your dreams.
No, you're not going to be the babe of your life.
Behind door number three.
The queen.
Who is the king?
The money machine, says the queen.
Bing, bing, bing.
Bye, bye, bye.
My credit card makes me high.
My, oh, my, until I die, die, die.
Swing, swing, swing.
Who wants the diamond ring?
Bye, bye, bye.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay.
Hail Mother Mary,
Our blessed lady.
I fell in love with your son.
Hail Mother Mary,
Turn me on and on and on.
Thank God for you and your son.
Ho, ho, ho.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, commercial America.
Speed胸
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, commercial diret.
He-he-hey, king Kong, let's dance.
Are you there taste a 쓰는αν .
Malenya.
Omise surfing in Holland?
If yes, then ho ho ho ho ho ho.
Oh, blessed lady, Hail Mother Mary
I fell in love with your son
Hail Mother Mary, turn me on and on and on
Hail Mother Mary, thank God for you and your son
Merry Christmas
King, king, king, who is the king?
The money machine, says the queen
Bing, bing, bing, bye, bye, bye
My credit card makes me high
My, oh my, until I die, die, die
Swing, swing, swing, who wants the diamond ring?
Bye, bye, bye, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay
Merry Christmas
Commercial America
Commercial Germania
Merry Christmas
Commercial Babylonia
Cold as ice, Papa was not nice
He doesn't even care that the roof is true
He's a loser in despair
Christmas is near
Let go of your fear
Forgiven, let live now and here
Children are pure
Santa is on tour
He pays him visit to every digit, that's for sure
Yeah, if you've been nice
If you've been nice
There's not enough
Hey, Mother Mary, oh blessed lady
Hey, Mother Mary, I fell in love with your son
Hey, Mother Mary, turn me on and on and on
Hey, Mother Mary, thank God for you and your son
Hey, Mother Mary, oh blessed lady
Hey, Mother Mary, I fell in love with your son
Oh, oh, oh, Nina Hagen, Nina Hagen, mmm, mmm, mmm
What a doll, friends!
A devil doll!
And before that, a Christmas witch on ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland
And that song, Jesus' Brother Bob, is by the Arrogant Worms
A band called the Arrogant Worms, posted by Dr. Lake Hume
And friends, now we find ourselves pushing our way into a new century
Oh, wait, we already did that
Well, anyway, we still are pushing our way into a new century
And the changes are not always up to us
But sometimes they are, friends
And we need to think of what we're going to do next
Well, actually, we don't have to worry about it
Because July 5th through 7th, 2002, the Exodus will arrive at Brushwood Campground in New York City
And we'll probably meet you there
But if not, we sort of need to make plans
And I don't know, my friends, exactly what we need to do
Maybe, maybe we need to do a winter revival to get kind of pumped up for, uh, for, uh, Quad X Day
To get ready for Santa's Big Red Sack!
Santa's coming with his big red sack!
Singing and dancing to their pagan deities
You got Santa's big red sack!
Sun rising in the distance
Well, uh, thank you so much!
I'll be in love!
Daddy, when's Santa be showing with his big red sack?
Music
Way up north where the cold wind blows
There's a little old man that you all know
He's been busting his nuts the whole damn year
Stampin' on tools, ridin' his deer
Come prance up, oh, blitzin'
Oh, what a great book!
It's that time of year, guess I've got all the luck
And you, Mrs. Claus, are you ready at last?
Our North Pole is ready
I'm pumped up with gas
Christmas time is my time of year
It's your sweet boy's cooking, let's get into gear
Santa's red sack is packed and he's ready to roll
You'll love them women from their heads to their toes
Time to pack up the sled!
Make that be a trick!
No time to complain, don't you give me no less
There's a countin' on me!
It's Christmas time!
Deliver my loan if I don't, it's a crime!
Through the cold north sky I fly in my sled
Don't need no radar, I'm usin' my head
To direct my nose to your good fun
I tickle your fancy till the morning comes
I'm ready to go
Christmas time is my time of year
It's your sweet boy's cooking, let's get into gear
Santa's red sack is packed and he's ready to roll
You'll love them women from their heads to their toes
Well, I come down to you just once a year
With my big red sack and belly full of beer
I'm gonna bring all the women lots of Christmas cheer
Load it in, ready, Saint Nicholas is here!
This is the story of old Saint Nick
With his big red sack and his candy stick
Flying back home with his beer so ice
He's lickin' that prune tang all Christmas night
Christmas time is my time of year
It's your sweet boy's cooking, let's get into gear
Santa's red sack is packed and he's ready to roll
You'll love them women from their heads to their toes
Christmas time is my time of year
It's your sweet boy's cooking, let's get into gear
Santa's red sack is packed and he's ready to roll
You'll love them women from their heads to their toes
holiday Christmasさん
Christmasさん
And Jesus also sequenced,
said there would be the birth pang of strange phenomena in the atmosphere. I believe that the
unidentified flying objects are part of what Jesus could have meant by these strange signs
in the atmosphere. But we will really see some pyrotechnics when the Jupiter effect takes place.
Well, we're live here at the plasma drift, and it looks like Santa Claus is never going to make it.
He's going to not make it. He's going to create it out of the back of his mind. Santa Claus has been
cloned, and he's in this small PC jar here. As you notice, the fluid is checked perfectly clean
and clear, and also at a temperature of 79 degrees. We're going to have to go up or down,
as so many of us do after the holidays. Some of us just want to take a long drive in the
opposite lane of the freeway. Merry Christmas, you bastard, you're mine.
Merry Christmas, you bastard, you're mine.
Quit your job. Slack off. Quit your job. Slack off. Quit your job. Slack off.
We're going to have to go up or down, as so many of us do after the holidays.
Attack!
Well friends, we've got, um,
our own special Christmas carol
that we're gonna play that's, that we're
inventing as we go right now.
X-mas.
Snap!
Sound system!
Ho ho ho!
Come one, come all!
It's He-Bomb! Hey kids, you can help the mighty Satina's rights
overthrow the evil normals
with new Bob-Dobs, actually bigger with
Rock and Pie. What I wouldn't do from Bob-Dob.
Get new more chocolatey pebbles from
you know who? I'm a chocolate
space cadet. Life support system
down to zero cocoa.
Feeling space-free? Have some of my new
cocoa pebbles, now so
thrombody!
Smells coconut-ish.
Nice cocoa
lickable.
Whoa!
Well friends, what do you, what do you think?
Is, is it the nativity of Santa
Claus that we're trying to
celebrate here, or is it
the horrible death of
the Santa Bob, the Santai
Bob, as he's been referred
to in some early pre-scriptures?
It's so separate, it's so separate.
professionally.
How demёт
Trust the
Bull discharged
the
tipos
in success this year
Yeah, here I is again, that's me, and there's you
And I dig all you cats out there whippin' and wailin'
And jumpin' up and down and suckin' up that fine juice
And pattin' each other on the back and tellin' each other
Who the greatest cat in the world is
Mr. Malenkov, Mr. Dallenkov, Mr. Eisenhorn
Woosin' Weasin', Meissenwooser, and Mr. Woodhiller
Mr. Beechiller, Mr. Churchill, and all them hills
They gonna get it straight
If they can't straighten it, they know a cat that knows a cat
That's gonna get it straight
Well, I'm gonna put a cat on you
Was the sweetest, gonest, wailin'est cat
That ever stomped on the sweet-swingin' sphere
And they called this your cat
The Nair
That was the cat's name
He was a carp in the kitty
Now the Nair was the kind of a cat that come on so wild
And so sweet
And so strong
And so witted
That when he laid it
Wham, it stayed there
Now see all the rest of the cat look to see what he puttin' down
He said, man, look at that cat blow
Let the cat go, man, look at it
Get out the way, let the cat go
Man, don't bug me, get off my back
I'm tryin' to dig what the cat's sayin'
They pushin' the Nair
Cause the one that's got the Nair
Want to dig his lick, you see
Dig his miracle lick
So the Nair say
Wait a minute, babies
Tell you what I'm gonna do
I ain't gonna take two, four, six, eight of you cats
But I'm gonna take twelve of you studs
And straighten you all at the same time
Heh, heh
Heh, heh, heh
Look like you pretty boys
You buddy with me
So the Nair and his buddies was goofin' off down the boulevard one day
And they run into a little cat
With a bent frame
So the Nair's
Look at this little cat with a bent frame
And he say
What's the matter with you, baby?
And the little cat with the bent frame
He say, well, my frame is bent, Nair
It's been bent for me in front
So the Nair's
Look at the little cat with the bent frame
And he put the golden eyes of love on this here little kitty
And he look right down into the windows of his soul
And he say to the little cat
He say, straighten it
Boop, boop
The cat went up straight in a Nair
And everybody jumping up and down say
Look what the Nair's put on that boy
You dug him before
Dig him now
Yes, I can feel it
Now you see the Nair's a-comin' on so strong
And so fine and so great
Talkin' about when's he gonna appear next
What did he do there?
He put it down once for the cat
The cat dug it, didn't dig it
Put it down twice, dug it, didn't dig it
Put it down the third time, the cat dug it
Wham! Walked away with his eyes buggin' out
Head in the air, bumpin' in there, everybody
Nair's a-comin' on so fine and so strong
They put it on his coattail
They want him to sign the autograph
They want him to do this gig here
They want him to do that gig there
They want him to make it to the radio to video
And they're all that jazz
He can't make all that jazz
Like a splendid cat of carbon
The kitty's got his own nick
But when he know he should show
To blow and cannot go
Because he got some strain on him
He sends a couple of these cats
That he's straightenin'
So came a little old 50-cent gig one day
And the Nair's couldn't make it
So he put it on two of these cats
He said, boys, go straighten that little riff over there
Boys, he said, take it off the ground and put it on the floor
off your mind, Naz. We got it covered.
So on the way over, the boys
run into a little old
20-cent pool of water,
and it gets right in the
middle of the boat, and all of a
sudden, laugh!
The thunder stormed, lightning flashing,
and the thunder roared,
and the boat rolled up and down, and the poor
cats figured every minute gonna be the last,
and one cat looked up,
and
here come the
Naz.
Cool
as anyone you ever
see. Right
across the water,
walking,
and Naz is a little
boy on board. I think his name was Jude on
board the boat. He said, Hey, Naz,
can I make it out there with you?
Naz said, Make it,
Jude. And old Jude went
stomping off that boat, took about
four steps, dropped his whole cart,
and Naz had to stash him
back on board again.
So the Naz
looked at these kiddies, and he said,
What's the matter to you babies now?
He said, What's going on here, boys? He said, What's taking place?
He said, What's all
this fuss about here? What's going on?
He said, Man, what's going on? He said, Can't you see
the storm storming, and the lightning
flashing, and the thunder roared?
And the Naz said,
I told you
to stay cool,
didn't I, babies?
Now the fame
of the Naz is jumping!
The grapevine is shooting
out sparks 40 feet long, and they're
talking about what he said, and how he stood up
to all these big bad cats, and
dug all that bad jazz,
and put them all down.
And what he said he's going to do, and where he's going to be,
and how he's going to be it, till the grapevine is jumping
so bad, there is now
16,000
of these studs and kiddies
in the Naz's
little hometown where the cat lived,
looking
to get straight.
Well, the Naz
know he can't straighten them all. There's two smaller
places to want to hang everybody up.
Nobody can make it.
So the Naz look out at these 16,000
studs and kiddies,
and they say to them,
Come on,
babies.
Just get on out down
the road.
And there went the Naz, swinging
away ahead of all these studs and kiddies and 16,000,
stomping up a big,
big swinging beat behind them.
And their great necklace of love
is supercharging
and charging to them.
Oh, it's brothers and brothers and sister to sister.
And the Naz is stomping
on a sweet swinging beat,
going down the road. Naz talking about
how pretty the flowers, how pretty the hours, how pretty me,
how pretty you, how pretty he,
how pretty she. Naz
had them pretty eyes.
He wanted everybody to see through his eyes so they could
see how pretty it was. And the
havers are too wailing gorgeous.
And the mother got time that before
you know it, it was
scarf in time. And these poor cats is
42 mile out of town. Ain't nobody
got the first biscuit.
Well, the Naz
look at these cats
and they say they're kicking
the sand out there. The Naz say,
You hungry?
Ain't you, babies?
They say, yeah,
Naz. We digging you
so hard what you putting down that
we didn't
be fair, Naz. We goofed.
Yes, that's what you call it.
So the Naz say,
Well,
we gots to take it easier.
We wouldn't
want to go ahead and order up something you might
not like, would
we?
And they say, No, Naz.
You put it down
and we'll pick it up.
So the Naz step back a few
paces and he say,
Oh, great
swinging
flowers
of the fields.
And they said, Oh, great
nonstop signal of sound and beauty.
And the Naz
say, Stamp
upon the terror.
And they hit it.
And the Naz say,
Straighten your miracle of body.
The body went up.
And he says, Straighten your arms.
The arms went up. And he said, Higher.
And the arms went higher.
And the Naz say,
Dig in
further.
And they dug it.
And when they did,
Wham!
The thunder went to.
And they look in their left hand.
It's a great big sweet
stuffed
smoked
fish.
And in the other,
a big thick loaf
of that gone
crazy honey tasting
nonstop sweet
swinging southern
red.
Why, these
polecats flipped.
Naz never did nothing simple.
When he laid it,
he laid it.
Say, when the saints
marching in,
when the saints
go marching in,
Hallelujah!
All wants to be
in that number,
the saints go marching in.
Say, when the saints
marching in,
go marching in,
when the saints go marching over me,
Hallelujah!
All wants to be
in that number,
the saints go marching,
and rob all the judges of
ruin.
Oh, holy night,
the stars are brightly shining.
It is the night of our
gisting and birth.
Long lay, long lay the world
in terror and the fighting.
The pit and the stone
found its rest.
A thrill of hope,
the wheel of hope,
the weary world rejoices.
Beyond the grace,
a new and glorious morn.
Fall on your knees.
Oh, hear the angel voices.
Oh, night,
when Christ was born.
Yes, yes, yes,
Lord Buckley.
The great,
the old New Orleans beatnik.
Lord Buckley with that amazing rant
on the naz
and the fishes and loaves.
Oh, and friends that bobbled up
jingle bells that we heard much earlier
was from our own Rev. Uconn Jack.
Praise Uconn Jack,
Back and praise WICA, which plays this show.
And praise all the stations that plays this horrible show.
And we love you.
And, I mean, seriously, we appreciate every listener out there,
no matter how much they might hate this show.
And we actually love the holidays, too,
because despite all that Santa crap, there's still a lot of slack.
We'll see you next time.
At P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Or visit the SoGenius website at SoGenius.com.
Thank you for listening.
And praise Bob.
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window.
And Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA? Is a DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for a DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present.
Under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in sight news, isn't it?
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise.
Gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
Besides, it's so ready to let him be.
What?
Praise Bob and Merry Xmas!
The preceding brought to you by your station in observance of the 450th anniversary of the Reformation.
Get.
Piff.
Destroy.
Long call, Dave.
Don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Yes.