Ah, yes. Thank you, Robert.
I get the little swivel chair myself.
The Tower of Power.
10,000 mighty watts.
In the service of Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius.
Now, friends, if we can just figure out what the technical situation is on tonight's show.
It's always different, see, in this studio.
It's like an obstacle course when you get in here.
And that makes it exciting.
And if I push this.
Aha! Nothing.
How about this?
No, nothing there either.
See, friends, I've decided this time I'm going to stay on the air and fight this conspiracy of...
Let's just think.
That's ridiculous.
I need at least five tape decks to do this show properly.
And I've...
I've got mine working.
They all run at different speeds, too.
That's another problem with this stuff.
All the tapes are at different speeds.
All the subgeniuses out there hear everything at different speeds.
They all live at a completely different rate.
Weird.
Yeah, different time zones.
Okay.
There we go.
Praise Bob.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have a bucket!
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates.
And remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part.
Part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Spirit.
Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megaphyst Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius.
With Pastor Buck Naked of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs, living avatar of Slack, and saint of sales.
On planet.
The
people try to listen to this show.
And we do not recommend using central nervous system depressants such as Downers, Valiums, Best Sellers, School, Work, or MTV.
These are all forbidden for use with this show.
The incredible complexity of the recordings played here will be incomprehensible if even the most Dobbsly minds are featured in this way, friends.
And so, those sleepers and stumblers may be fine for listening to the radio.
But, it is a deadly mix with the media barrage cassettes that we are going to be playing here tonight.
Oh, yes.
Stimulants are also self-defeating with this show.
Your brain will attempt to somehow keep up with the show.
But, you will really just be hearing blistered echoes of your own subconscious wallowing in the egotistical delusion which these products induce.
There is also some danger of synaptic backfire in the brain pan caused by over-exercising.
And, this dense packing of brain cells without proper organic coolants, such as FROP, accelerated to near fission point has been blamed for three recent cases of spontaneous human combustion.
So, do not play games with this show, friends.
You are playing with fire.
Okay.
Let's get that insipid cosmic sweetness and light music off of there.
We have some...
guests here in the show.
One of the fabulous Smith's zombies that we had.
There, he's back there.
Look at him.
Pulling at those little electrodes on his neck.
It still itches a bit where the sutures are...
are loose or something.
We have to prepare these zombies just exactly right for use on any subgenius show.
I don't know if...
Oh, look.
We've got a new microphone in here.
A new microphone?
Yeah. How's that? Stereo?
Is that stereo, I wonder?
Can you shut that door?
I don't know.
Oh, this is falling off.
Friends, everyone's falling off the edge.
Just waiting to see what exciting things will be on the subgenius show next.
And, well, our new guests...
Well, so much for the zombies for Bob.
They snapped.
They all snap sooner or later.
You put them to work for the church and...
Sooner or later, they really see Bob.
They actually do.
So, let's see here.
I think...
Yeah, our new guest, Reverend Timothy Leary, I believe.
And he's on the...
He's on...
He's over in...
You can be anyone this time around.
You can be anything this time around.
You can do anything this time around.
You can be anyone this time around.
You're the first generation in human history to know how to control your own nervous system.
Change your own reality.
Blow your own mind.
Make up your own mind.
You can be anything this time around.
You can be God this time around.
You've got to be God this time around.
You can be anything this time around.
You can be anyone this time around.
You can be Krishna.
You remember him?
Body paint, barefoot, flute.
Yeah, you could be Bob.
You remember him?
Pipe smoking, idiot, crazy, made a lot of money, millions of bucks.
You can be Porfo the dead worm this time around, folks.
Yeah.
Oh, duh.
Boy, you know, Tim, Tim, Larry, I don't know.
Yeah, you can be anything this time around if you're rich.
Not you, Doug.
You can be anything this time around if you've got a paid-up visa card.
Right, you can be anything this time around.
Not you, Stuart.
Not this to you, Stuart.
You can have any date this time around.
Not you, Janer.
No.
You can, oh, that's sweetness.
And actually, actually, good old Tim.
I mean, what he's saying is right.
It's true.
You can be anything this time around if you want to pretend a whole bunch.
It's sickening.
I can't even say the title of the tape that came off of.
Mine.
Oh, let's lick it one time.
Lick it.
Oh, let's smell it one time.
Smell it.
Oh, let's chew it one time.
Chew it.
Ch 봐r Empire
Let's bite one time
Bite, bite, bite
Let's eat one time
Let's suck it one time
Suck it
Suck the hella
Don't suck lemons, suck sex
Praise Bob
Now see, that's
a
That's a different
That's the
Scalpel
It's a need to squirt in the universe, friends
It is
It is squirt in the universe, friends
I really appreciate you taking time off
All right, there we go
That's the
That was the fabulous Billy Goons
And that was Dr. I know that band
I've had
I've been on stage having beer bottles thrown at me with that band as a matter of fact
The Reverend Cleve Duncan was
Is the
One of the main guys in the fabulous Billy Goons and now he's
The keyboard is for the Del Fuegos
The proof that the luck of Bob can work out for subgeniuses
That guy slaved away for the conspiracy on working in a bookstore for years
Doing this so-called novelty music of which I'm about to play a little bit more than he did for the church
Can't play much of it because it's nasty, nasty, nasty
Friends, this could be if it weren't for the FCC
If the FCC would let us speak the truth
The king's nasty English the way people talk
I wouldn't have to edit the subgenius tapes before we played them
90% of our stuff is
Really, really dirty and good
Yeah, it's illegal
It's illegally wonderful
So, but anyway
Oh, someone just called
We just got a call from a listener
And I'm gonna
He was asking where
How he could send us a tape
I'm gonna try talking to another listener here on the air
Let's see how this works
This is K-N-O-N
Hold on, let me put you on hold for a second
Would you guys talk to this guy?
Well, friends, it turns out
See, they have a button in here that says
If you push it, you're supposed to be able to get the phone on the air
And it
Wait a minute, let's try it this way
How's that?
Hear anything?
Say hello
Hello
No
Friends, see, now once again
That's some subgenius technical difficulties
I'll just get
Let's get back to Reverend Cleve
Oh, dear
See, I tried to do call-ins, friends
But as I was saying
If you want to send a tape to this show
We play a lot of cassettes
And you can send that to the church of the subgenius
I'm gonna read that P.O. box
And I'm gonna give the P.O. box again at the end of the broadcast
For right now, just right now
Right to Bob
At one fo-
Post Office Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214
That's Box 140306
Zip code 75214
Anyway, welcome to the end times, folks
Welcome to the end times, boys and girls
We're gonna shock shock the house
Put your brain in a whirl
Bob is getting down with you here tonight
Bob is getting down to help your plight
Bob is coming here to ease your strife
Come on, suckers, let Bob into your life
When I'm MC Cleve, I'm a master of rap
Well, see, friends, I can't play
I can't play the rest of that song
Sad, sad, sad
I'm gonna have to find something else here
Bastard
Oh, yes
Right now, with the
With the
We have these tiny mustaches
And I'm glad to have those
Oh, there goes a few more of those dissenters
We have some disbelievers out there
And we're glad you callers'll call up and support us
Because as you can see in the background on camera six here
We've had to eliminate a few of the dissenters
Small political problem
It's only after a phone call
That not pertinent to the relevance
Or convenience
Got no real reason to sentence the senior
Working for the Nazis
In 1985
How did those nasty Nazis ever stay alive?
Well, the government hired them and they brought them to the states.
They dressed them up in brand new suits and made them look pretty great.
Oh, yes, friends.
This is the least prepared hour of slack show in the world, I must say.
It's chaos, but feel that chaos hit, friends.
This show has got waves of chaos washing over it.
Swimming in chaos.
Friends, you're swimming in a sea of pills and you just can't see them.
Oh, get a good whiff of that church air while you got some purdy music here.
Mmm, punchy.
Makes you punchy to get a good big dose of that slack coming off the airwaves.
Go ahead, hug that radio speaker, friends.
Mmm, good.
Mighty, mighty good.
Oh, thank you, Bob.
Put your socks on.
Thank you, Bob.
For cleansing my memory.
For helping me sleep.
And, Bob, I'll follow you always.
That's right, Bob.
Until that next day.
Thank you, Bob.
For sending them pills.
For finding me willing.
Teenage girls.
And, Bob, I'll follow you always.
That's right, Bob.
For making sure that you have a good day.
How about that?
Boy, how estamos?
¶¶
That was Buck Naked and the Jaybirds, friends.
This is KNON 90.9 FM.
¶¶
of men many times.
But each time have I killed myself, for thy stench offendeth me.
Yea, thy stench of the spirit is like unto a million slaughtered swine, and in these
times thy planet is wreathed in foul vapors of thine own making, which is of mine own
making, and where there was a sieve to catch the ill light of my glory of the sun, there
now is none, and the full glory cometh through the clouds, and thy children shall be bent
and changed, and shall bear the new plague for ever after.
Pretty depressing, huh, folks?
Yeah, well, that's the way some of these religions...
are, and we can't help it if Bob predicts terrible disasters for the future, and I
can't help it if only one of the cassette decks works in here, and I can't queue things
up ahead of time and see whether they're X-rated or not, so let's hope this one's not.
Reading the pamphlet, over and over again.
Friends, have you been reading that pamphlet?
I mean, we literally demand that you read the subgenius.
We don't read the material until you memorize it.
And if you don't, then that's fine, I mean, you just don't get to board the escape vessels
in the end times.
Friends, we're gonna play that one at the very end of the broadcast, because that one
always gets requested, but we've got some strange times coming up.
Listen.
Listen carefully.
Join me in knowing that the world is not mine.
I'm reading the headlines of tomorrow today.
I'm not gonna judge you, but I'll see you, Julia, if I'm judging you.
I predict public executions will be shown on television, sponsored by your local gas
company.
Securing the faith that the future is filled with good things for you and yours.
I predict that LSD, marijuana, and speed can change your sex.
Listen now to the headlines you will be reading in the coming prediction period.
School built on sweet potato pie.
Gee, that's a headline.
If it were possible to spray small doses of LSD from an helicopter into the air, people
would soon quieten and not be hurt.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
She is a cutie, isn't she?
What a girl!
Right on campus is part of getting high.
I mean, uh, getting higher.
Isn't she?
This is just wonderful in any language.
Here's Bobby.
LSD is running its mad course, with babies now being born hideously deformed from women
whose chromosomes are permanently damaged by this drug, which was invented originally
by the Chemical Warfare Branch of the United States Army.
as a vicious weapon to be used against an enemy.
Here you see the heroic robots, the Lettys, who defended San Francisco against the dastardly attack.
Alright, I've seen enough.
Well, you know, who knows what could happen here.
Bob got to Reagan in time to save him, President Bush...
We are all interested in the future, for that is where you and I are going to spend the rest of our lives.
And remember my friends, future events such as these will affect you in the future.
You are interested in the unknown, the mysterious, the unexplainable.
That is why you are here.
And now for the first time, we are bringing to you the full story of what happened on that fateful day.
We are giving you all the evidence, based only on the secret testimonies.
The testimonies of the miserable souls who survived this terrifying ordeal.
The incidents, the places.
My friend, we cannot keep this a secret any longer.
Let us punish the guilty.
Let us reward the innocent.
Let us give them a chance to live.
You can relax and enjoy this quality product.
Secure in the knowledge that it has been specially created for the lover of fine things and the man of good taste.
Oh, sorry, you can edit that out, can't you?
Yeah, no problem.
Well, I'm going to do my mystery call.
Get the bright this way.
Roll up to the mystery door.
BOOP!
Sound begins.
See the light.
I'm not very happy.
Feel the heat.
We'll be in bombing in five minutes.
See the light.
Feel the heat.
There's it.
Get, get, get.
Get down.
Get, get, get, get down.
We're on.
Nancy!
Get down.
We're on.
I'm not being pushed around.
I'm absolutely ridiculous.
Let's not kid ourselves.
I make the decisions.
We're going to try to give it to them.
We shouldn't delude ourselves.
See the light.
Those nuclear weapons.
Feel the heat.
We're not looking out.
See the light.
You're dealing with human beings.
Feel the heat.
And don't forget why we're doing this.
That is right.
Why?
Geez.
I know all about you, but there's nothing you'll understand.
I don't know what's
Mm-hmm.
lives in public.
Yes.
Wickedly lives in public.
Okay, i我才
Yeah, that's right.
We want you to
Yes.
Bob either wants to be a county clerk or a over-God of all reality in 1984.
The two positions he's running for.
This ain't no video game church.
It ain't no church of bingo.
It's a church of Bob.
It's a Bob Rice's church.
I don't see what the hell's going on here.
What the hell?
Did you know that heaven, Christian heaven is hotter than the Christian hell?
Yes, the Christian heaven is hotter.
That's because there are seven sons.
Hell is fun.
Oh yeah, all your friends will be down there.
There's seven sons.
There's seven sons around the Christian heaven.
This is true.
You can find it in their own Bible.
They admit it.
And seven sons would make it much hotter than the gaseous multi-threshold of brimstone.
That means that heaven is hotter than hell.
They've been lying to you all this time.
Without a deal, then they lie about friends.
They lie that the world isn't coming to an end right away.
In 15 years.
Of course it's coming to an end in 15 years.
It can't last any longer.
It wasn't built to last.
It wasn't meant to last.
It's inferior.
Bob, it's a Spartan universe.
And I think the biomorphs out there will be pleased to find out that the third sex will be accepted by science.
People will finally accept the third sex.
That's not the one you think I'm talking about.
Yeah.
It like has, uh, the one hand is rough and hard like a man's and the other hand is soft like a woman's.
But, uh, and the sexual organs, well we won't even go into that, but it will have half of one type of sexual organ.
Everyone has been told that they'reing'm going to have to leave for the next stage of their life.
And that they'll eventually cease the whole millenium, as somebody was adamant for what they were thought to be good.
But you're just seen with your hands off, crushed with fear, and receive to hard with calm.
Even at that time when the sun is stand IPS motion, people are afraid of that person.
Can you tell...
They're ready.
You have signed the application.
cultist or someone with his theological wires crossed.
It's almost like listening to someone who knows only a few words of English,
but soon they're rattling off in a completely unknown language
when they haven't even been to kindergarten spiritually.
We eat more, drink more, play more, and do less to earn a good living
than any other people in history.
We have at our fingertips the world's greatest music,
and I might add a lot of its worst,
else the cultists would have no following.
We are a people grasping nervously, sometimes almost hysterically, for more.
I know that I know that I know that I know that I know
that I know that I know.
Whenever we read the obscene stories, the voluptuous debaucheries,
the cruel and torturous executions,
it would be more consistent to call it the word of a demon.
There are little eyes.
There are little eyes upon you, and they're watching night and day.
With a vocal and activist minority ready, apparently, to burn the bomber steel of kill.
For more.
And most, incidentally, are in their teens or their twenties.
And that's Bosch and Pipple, I'll tell you that.
They dwelled in caves, not high-rise apartments.
They may not have found a key to affluence, but they found...
an endless supply of dope.
Uninhibited sex.
An endless supply of money.
Free access to a jewelry, I suppose.
Ah, yes, the harlot.
You can count on that.
Or kill.
For more.
Why, friends, we could feed another nation with our garbage.
What more than a space hogger on Earth?
Is the church of the most subdued?
I don't know.
But how many of you are really genuinely intelligent?
Bang.
Are you blaming God for atom bombs?
Atomic warheads?
Don't. I don't know.
I only know that it will signal the end of time.
Why?
Bang. Bang. Bang.
The past blotted out, and the future assured.
Ah, yes, the harlot.
This is the way they did it in the New Testament.
God scolded his people in the Old Testament.
The greatest people on Earth.
And you walk in with the Judas tribe, and the wife of Judas might be one of the ladies I'd laid to make a socialist.
I knew I couldn't trust anything but communism and the principle in me. Yes, best of you.
I knew that that's what I had to depend upon, not depend upon the arm of the flesh.
And never put all your eggs in one basket.
So, honey, I put my eggs in many places.
This is Jim Joss.
You can figure that out if you want to.
Some of you do.
You're naive. You don't know what Jim Jones is all about.
You can't even follow him.
You haven't even smelled where he's at yet.
Much less followed him.
You don't even know who he is, and you might miss him if you didn't have a real good look at him.
You wouldn't even know who he looked like.
You really haven't got an x to him.
But I've got all kinds of things in store.
Ah, yes, friends.
This is KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
FM.
That was Jim Jones.
From one of the subgenius cassettes we recorded.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
That was Tim Leary.
It's so easy to get them mixed up, you know.
In Dallas, Texas.
FM.
That was Jim Jones.
From one of the subgenius cassettes we recorded.
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
That was Tim Leary.
It's so easy to get them mixed up, you know.
And before that was a little cut by puzzling evidence in Oakland, California.
And I just hope that this time, this show, we don't have those guys showing up into messing with our airwaves.
It's like, I don't know if you've been listening for very long.
We are actually having, literally having trouble keeping a California subgenius show, the KPFA show in Berkeley, more than an hour less than a show, out of our airspace.
They always seem to come in right at the worst time.
And, okay, I guess we could.
If you could bring the rags down here, we'll start that job right away.
It's a bit early in the morning, but we can clean up because these fabulous studios down here are equipped with showers and a full sports gymnasium right here next to the can.
That's right.
If you want a radio, hose out.
To a pastoral line here.
Nobody lives in South Dallas.
Hobo fam said hello, Dallas.
Hello, South Dallas.
Since that meltdown, nobody's been here.
I was talking about the incredible sports facilities.
Brewers and bunkins.
Bunkins, yeah.
The bunkins that are all here.
There's incredible everything here in Dallas.
There's incredible giant golden lights.
You should see the new thing in the Dallas skyline, Ivan.
I know as soon as we go downtown tonight, you'll see it.
They got that pretty, that's all right.
They got that pretty building all lit up now.
Yeah, I know.
There's one out here, too.
There are hotels. Look at the windows.
There's hotels out there.
Sittle tattle radio.
Oh, man.
All right, everybody, let's all get together and get naked and do something dirty.
Thank you.
Yeah, let's all get together and fuck.
That's right.
Yeah, let's all get together and buck in a big car.
And book.
Hey, man, I'm booking.
More book.
Yeah, we want more books.
So if you're, say, Paul Simon.
Or Art Washburn.
Or Irving Schuster.
Or any of those people.
This is what was playing.
This is what I was listening to the last time I saw Bob.
Live.
Pretty incredible.
.
. .
. . .
He is my true son and finger.
Don't just eat a hamburger.
Eat the hell out of it.
My kingdom is on the earth.
Nothing I want is...
A good deal is in the wallet of the beholder.
You know you did.
All of you bright people deserve some of this.
Not a one in three.
That's fair.
All of you bright people deserve some of this.
or the church.
But not just any church,
for the church to which we belong
just happens to be,
beyond a shadow of a doubt,
the world's only bogus true religion.
Of course, I am referred to
the church of the subgenius.
This one's dedicated to Reverend Cleve Duncan.
Now the church of the subgenius,
as founded by
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and his salesmaster Slack,
1953 is the prime religion of the future.
United,
superior,
mutants,
social renegades,
twisted geniuses,
and sci-fi sinners
in a worldwide rampage
of immorality
and profane
yucks and grins.
Yucks and grins,
which will hopefully,
inevitably,
lead us directly
to a commercialization
of society.
Don't put us down to luck.
スパンテй
Today's Modern Jet Age
a global society.
And the commodity he's have
cream
gets beauty voted for.
gets voted
Face the
comments
and and
yeah but
...applying yourself, please apply the needless shift in the person or number which compares the degree of the parallel structures amplified by the capitalization which we employ in the first word of every sentence, which is otherwise pointed to the name.
I don't understand the nature of these charges against me. These alleged, uh, these accusations have absolutely no basis in fact, Doctor, and I am thankful if you would dignify them with a remonstrance or two.
...pay strict attention...
Let me make one thing perfectly clear. Am I then accused of mental obesity? Of obfuscating? Of over-erudition?
It seems I am accused.
Accused of trying to choke the show, to choke the philosophical esophagus of the show with the roughage of knowledge, to bloat the entrails of the show with theophagous apophagems and quiddity.
Accused me of over-reading? Nay, rather say I gourmandize on the sacred vericundial throb of the ages.
...the final consonant before centricing it with the...
Now, are there any questions?
...the answer to them all is six, six, six...
...the answer to them all is five...
So hold on just a moment while Doctor X reads you a list of the most valuable products found in your home or office which rub together to cause an enormous fire and even a nuclear explosion.
Ah ha ha ha, I wouldn't touch that one with the ten-foot...
...house or not.
Even a plastic free one?
Well, uh, that's a different matter.
You know, they don't have Cracker Jack prizes anymore and we've all had to grow up and lose a little of the starry-eyed, dew-dropping innocence that used to conflagrate our little world.
But now they're just a fossilized memory in the substratum of time.
You really think so, Doctor?
You really think so?
Well, in a sense, they live forever.
And proud of it.
Look at these rather tiny...
...organ which cannot even be imagined yet and...
The cult is full of superstition and mysticism. We're scientists.
You've got...
As evangelist David Brothers of the Church of Jane Mansfield lays the groundwork of the new atomic age and instructs you on the essential precepts of the social gospel of Jane Mansfield as she spoke from the grave and appeared in a bizarre manifestation to the prophet princes.
Let us go forth now to Brother Brothers and this week's inspirational message in the name of her holiness, Jane Mansfield.
...sample of how she cuts the cheese.
Oh, I can't do it.
Oh, darn it.
Now you want to do it the other way?
Better this way.
Oh, God.
Can't you see that he's dead?
Yeah, the moon will be turning red any time.
I mean, the signs of the times are everywhere, friends.
You just look around you, these...
The econocataclysm should be hitting right around, what does it say here, in Scrooge's 1985.
Oh, I don't think...
Isn't that around the...
...toxic point?
Yeah, that's when the radio stations start having their own little earthquakes.
Well, dear friends, the lovely subgenius radio ministry hour of slack is still afloat, although just barely.
You can hear the zombies slumping around in the background here.
Let's see. There we go.
Slump, slump, slump.
You can hear them zombies.
Slump, slump.
Yeah, it's pathetic.
Pathetic, indeed.
Friends, Bob is dead.
Yes?
We hear nothing.
Bob is not dead.
We see nothing.
Bob is dead and smelling worse.
Bob is not dead like a fish-scale purse.
Bob is dead.
So what?
There's dead people in the White House.
Bob is not dead.
Neither is Corbett Monica.
Bob is dead.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Bob is not dead.
This isn't a urine test.
Bob is dead.
Long live what's left of Bob, dear friends.
Help me!
The noise is heard.
Resident believes possibly M.M.A.s are...
...planetary systems.
When you sit down, you look deep into your soul and you say to yourself,
I'm not dead.
I can't take this anymore.
I gotta kill somebody.
Not just one person, but a whole lot of them.
And you gotta just keep killing.
Do you find that interesting?
Yeah, praise Bob.
Praise Corbett!
Kill.
Kill for the love of killing.
I don't know why I'm smiling, but I feel this urge to grin.
I'm not dead.
Time for the fourth.
Are you hooked on narcotics?
People that are once we've determined are not dead,
are not rehabilitative.
Okay?
What did you say, Bob?
I said, good Lord, what's to lose?
Hello, Tom.
2024.
When we were raised.
You're listening to UFO five
No, thank you.
You don't want to hurt me.
ed.
24 hours to go, I wanna be sedated.
Nothing to do, nowhere to go, I wanna be sedated.
Just put me in a wheelchair, get me to the shore.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, before I go cold.
Can't control my fingers, can't control my toes, oh no.
No, no, no.
24 hours to go, I wanna be sedated.
Nothing to do, nowhere to go, I wanna be sedated.
Just put me in a wheelchair, get me to the shore.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, before I go cold.
Can't control my fingers, can't control my toes, oh no.
Oh no, no.
Ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba.
I wanna be sedated.
Oh, yes, friends.
That was the swinging erudites.
That's actually the same Reverend Cleve Duncan,
a great preacher in the subgenius church,
whose stuff I can't usually play
because it's got too many four-letter words in it.
Like a skee-ball.
A skee-ball.
That's a...
Hey, we're not supposed to say skee-ball on the radio.
Oh, shoot!
Hey, okay.
Friends.
Backwards is a lot of eeks.
You know, it's so frustrating not to be able to mix cassettes.
See, I'm really geared up for...
Oh, Norm?
Norm, I'm warning you on the air ahead of time.
This deck is not plugged in again.
Nuke it.
Yeah, kill it.
Kill it.
Kill me.
Kill the traitor.
To the church.
All but one man died
There at Bittercree
And they say he ran away
Branded
Marked with a coward's shame
What do you do when you're branded?
Well, you fight for your name
He was innocent
Not a charge was true
But the world would never know
Branded
Scorned at the one who ran
What do you do when you're branded?
And you know you're a man
Wherever you are
You go for the rest of your life
You must prove
You're a man
Are you kidding?
Hey, now, wait a minute.
Hey, hey, we are the monkeys
You know we love to please
A manufactured image
With no philosophies
We hope you like our story
Although there isn't one
That is to say there's many
That way there is more fun
You've told us you like action
And games of many kinds
You like to dance
We like to sing
So let's all lose our minds
We know it doesn't matter
Because what you came to see
Is what we'd love to give you
And give it one, two, three
But it may come three, two, one, two
Or jump from nine to five
And when you see the end in sight
The beginning may arrive
For those who look for meanings
And form as they do fact
We might tell you one thing
But we'd only take it back
Not back like in a box pack
Not back like in a race
Not back so we can
Keep it but back in time and space
You say we're manufactured
To that we all agree
So make your choice
And we'll rejoice
In never being free
Hey, hey, we are the monkeys
We've said it all before
The money's in
We're made of tin
We're here to give you more
The money's in
We're made of tin
We're here to give you
Well, friends
Boy, yeah, I hadn't heard
Any of that stuff in a long time
See, when I put a cassette in
On this show
I don't know what it's gonna be
Oh, that feels good
Oh, here it comes again
Those heliops, it's that other show
Nope
I don't know what's going on here, friends
What's coming up next
This is Lord Buckley
Not too many people even know who he is
He's a sort of a pre-Lenny Bruce
Beatnik poet of the 60s
He's a weirdo, you know, in other words
But, um, uh, let's see
Oh, he's a weirdo
Oh, I ought to give some credit
The last few tapes I got in
Was playing in there
It's negative land
I'm using as a segue
Of course
Um, the branded
And the monkeys thing
Came from Pope Flores
The Pope of Chicago
I'm gonna praise the Pope there
He sends a lot of great
Japanese animation videotapes
To the church
So we have strange religious icons
Some people might not get into it
Four big hits
And seven licks of gold
Are before me
Before daddy swung false upon this sweet groovy land
A swinging, stomping, jumping, blowing, wailing
New nation
Hip to the cool groove of liberty
And solid scent
With the eighth lick
At all the studs, chicks, cats, and kitties
Red, white, all blue
Is created level in front
You can straight talk the same
Dig what I mean?
Now we are hung
With a king-sized
Main day
Civil drag
Sounding of whether that nation
Or any up there nation
Dig so hip and so solid scent
Can stay with us
All the way
We is here to dig this chop-beating session
On the site of the voice jazz blown
In the entire issue
Get his mother boy
We have stomped out here to turn on
A small soil stash
Of the before mentioned hassle
Site
As a finer sweet sod pad
For those who laid it down and left it there
So that this jumping happy beat
Might blow forevermore
And we all dig
That this is the straightest lick
There
But digging it harder from afar
Will be the best way to do it
We cannot take no wailing bowels
We cannot mellow
We cannot put down the stamp of the nails
On this sweet sod
Cause the strong non-stop studs
Both digging it and dug under it
Who hassled here
Have mellowed it with such a wild mad beat
It not now slumbers
What can it take?
Does not find its cheer
Way over it
Ain't handsome
So wouldn't take Aquí
No t'em
No plan
No chance
Three make it
Damn good
What do you sound?
Cha-ching
This is the time and this is the record of the time.
It's important.
Oh, there we go.
Well, anyway, folks.
Yep.
We're sitting here praising Bob to the beautiful sound effects that go on forever and ever.
Listen to that.
Hideous slack squishing and mushing around in there.
Oh, Bob.
Bob.
There's absolutely no truth to the rumor that members of the church,
need passes from Dobbs committee in order to urinate.
We do have permission to urinate at any time.
Not like asked in those other groups where you have to ask permission to go to the restroom.
Some geniuses can go to the restroom.
It's always that body of God.
They don't even have to go to the restroom.
That's not a message from Bob, is it?
Well, in 1987,
Orson Welles will come on the radio and tell people that the aliens are landing.
But this time, no one will believe him, but it will be true.
Laser beams shaped like vampires,
with glow in the dark brains.
I seen a vision, ma'am.
So play your cards right.
Yes.
All you deaf ears down there.
Heads up.
Look out below.
There will be plenty of distractions to take your minds off the real problem as the time of P draws to its violent close.
For instance, beware.
The fake God Junior, the anti-Bob, will come before long.
Bullets cannot stop him.
He's one of the deceptively human-looking advanced supersonic Nazi hell creatures from beneath the hollow earth.
Parasites of the elder gods.
But most people will think he's the second coming.
And his age.
Alien hiney will be kissed all the way to world dictatorship and beyond.
And if the true messiah were to show up at that time,
everyone would just know in the bottom of their core programming that he's the antichrist.
Because he'll cuss and spit and take the lord's name in vain and hang out with whores and bulldigers and dope addicts and cops.
Another down-home sort.
This is a warning.
Danger.
Danger, you poor devils.
Things are more mixed up than you ever dreamed.
What was up is down.
The priorities are all screwy.
You're fretting if your hair looks okay while some new kind of bladder cancer is bursting out the front of your designer jeans.
Yes, this is bad talk.
Nobody will listen to anything else.
You won't look at TV unless body parts or cars are jiggling or crashing on it.
You won't taste your food unless it has some nerve drug in it.
You haven't used your other senses since you were five.
And you sure as hell won't stop what you're doing.
Until someone much bigger, much stronger, and much, much more self-assured makes you stop.
And you'll thank him for it.
And then just before you fry in a flash of radioactive hindsight, you'll realize that he stopped you from doing the wrong thing.
Good God!
What in the name of sweet screaming Jesus is this world coming to?
People bitch.
People gripe.
This is a sign of the end times.
That's a sign of the end times.
When you should all be hollering, it's all a sign of the end times.
Two months ago, the observatory issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end.
Now that's the same story the cult of the book of Revelations had been preaching.
Now when a scientist backs that up, it's news.
Our conclusions have nothing to do with the cult.
Well, today we deal with Bible prophecy.
We have two free features we want you to write for right away.
I wish my mommy did not smoke.
How you can have the miracle you need in August of 1982.
There may be a brief lull in the fighting between the Arabs and the Jews.
That will be a temporary peace.
But the word of God tells us we can expect nothing but trouble and turmoil in the Middle East until our Lord returns to be the Prince of Peace.
Bob?
It's been known for some time that the fossil record contains several very pronounced mass extinctions.
Clowns and ballerinas here and there.
Once it's finally happened, so discuss it.
Bob, the now victoriousantes glimpsed
I don't know that Gesichter anything.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This music that's playing right now is by D.K. Jones,
Reverend Dennis Kelly, great friend of the church.
In fact, some of his music is on the background
in a whole lot of the subgenius tapes,
a lot of stuff we play, the slicker.
A little bit.
Anyway, friends, we're about to go off the air.
Let me read the sacred P.O. box of the Church of the Subgenius.
For those of you who are in need of written slack,
we'll send you beaucoup information,
truckloads about the church.
If you'll just write, got that pencil ready, friends?
Write for information.
This is the Subgenius Hour of Slack signing off,
and we want you to write to Bob.
Bob at P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's Bob at P.O. Box 140306,
Just send in that letter, that postcard,
and you'll find out just what we mean by slack.
Yes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha.
Hang on for Norm and Monday morning,
and it's going to be a hell of a deal.
¶¶