Smoking. Smoking. Smoking. Smoking. Smoking. Smoking. Well, I smoked a pipe. What? Pipe was smoked.
It's smart to try smoking. I know, Mom. There's something real good about it. Yes, the pipe. We
smoked it. Well, that's fine. Gee, maybe I'm rich already. Well, I'm glad you said that at least.
I just imagine the beaver smoking that pipe. Well, I guess that's just one of the unwritten
rules of childhood. Dad smoked it.
From PR News in Washington, I'm lopsided. Senator Ted Kennedy is undergoing brain surgery in
Michigan today. PR says surgeons are trying to remove as much of Kennedy's brain as possible.
GOP presidential candidate John McCain is closing in on the International Space Station,
which he accused of funding terrorism. McCain also urged a campaign to limit the flow of PR
news in Japan. On Wall Street 16521, a judge in Texas must take part in parenting classes.
He was 79 years old. Marlee Meisner with the Texas Child Protective Services says probe the children.
It's indescribable. It's beautiful. We've been pointing out different things, and it's incredible.
Rock and roll pioneer Barack Obama is calling for the U.S. to impose financial penalties against PR News in Washington.
For almost two centuries, Americans have enjoyed neglect of our duties as citizens.
Now, God join, make, help, learn, work, produce. God join, make, help, learn, work, produce.
God join, make, help, learn, work, produce. God join, make, help, learn, work, produce. God join, make, help, learn, work, produce.
Then...
The Self Genius Power of Squash!
Bob.
Yeah.
Well, that's what you get when you start messing around with dynamite.
Why should you buy a Bob Radio?
This is Bob.
Radio is all about Bob and at the heart of every speaker that makes voices come alive.
When you turn on Bob, you can hear every word clear.
Then you've heard it a long time.
And it's simple.
There's five memory buttons on top.
And when you push one, Bob doesn't tip over.
Give Bob a try for the best listening.
Bob.
The High Performance Radio and Light Company.
Attention, attention.
The listeners are listening.
Not again.
What program is this?
I want to know what program this is.
Somebody shooting face in my mouth.
It's that man with the funny mustache.
I feel tired.
He's doing it.
It's him.
He's listening to me.
It's my Bob.
Bob.
Afternoon Bob.
Beginning Monday over most of these stations, two of your Bobs will be coming.
Coming, Mother.
The first will be Bob and his quips and comments.
And by the way, Bob's guest editor this coming week will be Bob Bob.
The second will be that master of the easy style, Bob Bob.
So listen at the new time for two of the most entertaining Bobs in radio.
Now it's Bob.
Now it's Bob Bob.
Bob Bob.
Bobs.
Bob.
Henry, don't you know you shouldn't whistle?
But dear, I really think we should.
Henry.
May I have the hot cakes and sausage, please?
Here, dear.
Hot cakes and sausage.
Because milk toast is better for you.
Henry.
Yes, Mother.
Yes, Henry.
But first, this is Bob.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, Bob.
Bob Dobbs.
It was many moons ago that I gave Dobbs my money.
The minute I yeet got my thirty dollars.
The minute that peace stench whiff was red.
And good old Stang scribbled my name in the book of life.
I gained the one thing the pinks do not have.
I gained inner slack.
Deep within the recesses of a warped and mangled mind is a slack that cannot be stolen.
That slack is faith in slack.
Blonde, deaf, and dumb faith.
Faith that the luck plane will tilt my way.
The saucers will arrive and the sex goddesses will reward me for my faith.
Hello, this is the flattering tongue of a seductress.
Lust after her beauty in your heart?
Let her allure you with her eyelids.
Understanding.
Slack.
He who does so, you are my sister.
With the attire of a harlot and a crafty heart.
And I have found you.
Come, let us take our fill of love until morning.
As an ox goes to the slaughter through Moses.
To lust for her.
Yes, early in the morning he came again.
He whores.
To lust for her.
I guess he was talking about that harlot priestess.
Yes, Pisces, who we heard earlier.
On this hour of slack number 1159.
Before that, friends, a whole lot of audio choppery by Fernanda Nande-Lemur
and some Norelpref ones, too.
We also heard and will hear some classic puzzling evidence show from the 80s
saved by Phineas Narco with puzzling evidence and Dr. Howe.
More of all of that to come, but first and later,
some radio synesthesia call-ins from WCSB Cleveland with yours truly
and Dr. Sinister, Priestess Pisces, Rocknar, and No Money Mark seen here.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hi, I'm here to save the remainder of the show.
Mark to the rescue.
Yeah.
Okay, I have a question for Reverend Stang.
What do you see as the future of the Church of the Subgenius?
Oh, vast riches, incredible power over...
Entire countries.
Yeah.
It may not be immediately.
I'm not talking about this summer.
The subgenius sphere.
That's going to be a whole new sphere of influence, a whole new culture.
Yeah, it might be another year or two before we start seeing...
Bob predicted it a long time ago.
He said it.
I read it.
That settles it.
I had a question for you.
Why are you called No Money Mark?
I hope that's like an ironic nickname,
like when they call bald guys,
or big guys hairy, or...
Well, I wish.
The way it came about was I was calling 669,
and sweet as a five, I needed some sort of nickname.
And my real name is Mark, and he suggested Money Mark,
you know, after the DJ.
And I said, no, No Money Mark, that's more appropriate.
So that's where it came from.
Awesome.
A divinely inspired and selected name.
Right.
Versus my nickname was just picked at random
when I jumped on an IRC channel,
because I couldn't think of anything.
Is that your astrological sign?
It is.
Oh, so you were cheating.
It actually made some sense.
Oh, look what happened.
He got too near the reactor car.
These callers don't even know how to approach the subgenius show.
A little flaming fleck of phlegm
in the dying entropic superstructure of the cosmos.
Oh, you mean this closet here?
Whoa, that's a good one, Gary.
Now I suggest you close that monster closet
before we're attacked by unthinkable things
that might come oozing out at any time.
Oh, here they come, slithery.
Get back.
Whoa.
Oh, no, it's the tambourine people.
And the march of the things now is...
Now, this is a beautiful float.
It's the Thing Society, and those are the thingettes
in their beautiful abbreviated uniforms
waving and winking at the crowd now.
And they're throwing what appears to be candy of some kind,
because look at those kids go to scoop it up.
Those are candy.
Candied Thing Baby eggs, Hal.
Have one.
Oh, uh, thanks.
You sure you don't want it yourself.
As the subgenius parade goes by in all its splendor.
Are you there?
Are you there, Fuzzling?
Yes, I'm here.
I'm over on the other side of the street.
You can see my scarf.
Oh, yes.
And this, I believe, is supposed to be Bullwinkle the Moose
pulled on all these ropes like a giant cloud.
He's Bullwinkle.
He looks like Bullwinkle.
This terrain is just like that.
And that next boat is, I believe,
this is Bart Simpson,
the famous television character
and Supreme Court justice.
You don't have a f***ing fun, man.
And as the station loses its license,
the KPFA closes.
We're slowly defining here in front of everybody.
It's too bad that we can't stop moronic colors
from jeopardizing the show and its very existence.
And now,
the little babies with instruments
sewn to the front of their vestments.
Aren't they cute?
You know, their moms and dads must be standing
mighty tall this day.
As the juvenile infant cadet
marches the last time
just before it's shipped off to the Persian Gulf.
I guess it's our nation's leader's theory
Look at that.
On the side, the computer is spelling
that must be a foreign way of saying
that English babies will also be sent
into the Persian Gulf.
I guess so.
Always Homeric, those kids.
Those kids.
Those Englanders.
Yeah, I remember Eric.
He was always at home.
He never came out, you know.
You know, in the afternoon of September 8th, 1926,
a short stocky man in a baritone coat
and a pearl-grey fedora
walked this balloon down the street
for the first time.
It was a historic occasion.
Yes, well, you know, of course,
Here comes the military folk
with the U.S. Marine Hawk missile.
Oh, yeah, dreaded torpedo.
You know, the generals who command these men
do seem confident of victory.
Yes.
They say that overconfidence
is a generic disease on the eve of a shooting war
in the Persian Gulf.
Oh, and there's the first pro-council of war
who has been saying that we can go to war at any time.
According to this information I have here,
this float represents Pocahontas,
the Indian princess,
and Captain Miles Standish engaged in a furious copulation
while Indians watched him behind a tree.
Oh, yes, I see.
They're powering that siren with their activities.
How amazing.
That siren is played by a man named, uh,
by the White Christians for Decency
and the Caucasian Christians for Commerce
whose float brings up the rear, as it were.
Well, I don't know anything about trees.
The majorette is, uh, gesturing with her baton.
The Indian dips in the flaming solution and up it goes.
Wait, look where she's putting it.
Wow.
Well, at least that put out the fire.
Sure did for that majorette, anyway.
And here comes the drunk, drunk, uh, oops,
uh, slight mishap at the edge of the crowd.
Yeah, I think that was the alcoholic's float.
That was the DWIers from, uh, Oshkosh, Wisconsin.
Oh, so it was, so it was.
Yeah, I don't have one of those neat sheets, so...
They're, they're cleaning up the mess and, uh,
it seems that they're bringing in the cute kitty cat.
And here's Philo's, uh, float, which is in every year.
A great favorite for the kids.
It throws candy with little razor blades in them.
That, uh, giant Filofax was created by the Boy Scouts of America.
Hello.
Welcome to the lips of an immoral woman, honey.
Aliens go down my mouth and say,
breasts satisfy you at all times.
In the Bible.
Sexual intercourse.
Yes, and finally, pornographic literature,
pornographic films, pornographic television programs,
and drugs.
In the Bible.
Ho, ho.
Honey.
Yes, I, Dr. Howell,
am the mightiest of the submen, the undermen,
the greatest in the lowerarchy.
Of course, we're inferior to normal people, we undermen,
but nonetheless, of this enormous army of gimps and wimps,
I, Dr. Howell, approach common humanity the most.
Though subhuman and a subgenius, I am almost a human.
At least we undermen understand what we undertake.
What we take down under the surface of what we understand,
down and pulled down with the undertow into the underpinnings of the unconscious mind.
In this sub-scratum, we, the undermen, move in.
We will cause a Ellen, whenever does she change her mind it will with a hug
after a once disgusting pig release,
this submin aviation has done enough good of us
are off the charts.
We do anywhere from 500 to 5,000 a week.
Oh, it's revolutionary.
But I pray that the Lord would let me marry someone who is a rat.
That will be the focus of the rest of this program.
But don't give me that garbage.
I'm sucking tired of religion, church, the Bible, and Christians.
You're going to get a thrashing.
If you ever touch me again, I'll kill you.
Right.
But can you believe that?
From PR News in Washington, I'm rising to the highest level since last October.
Iowa Governor Chet Culver has floodwaters.
It's been one heavy rainfall after another.
Storm formed over and over.
Water was over the water treatment plant.
Over.
The small town of New Hartford was in Ames, Iowa.
The National Guard is now underwater, and PR News is adding to the misery.
On Wall Street, 12-7-2-15.
Democratic presidential candidate Barack Obama will only continue President Bush's failed policies.
McCain, for his part, responded by saying that this is PR News.
New Palestinian poll.
Popular PR supports.
Palestinian poll.
Policy percent poll.
Polling poll.
PR News.
The government of Saudi Arabia says the kingdom will work with other OPEC members to, quote,
guarantee the availability of PR News in Washington.
PR News.
Welcome to Darwin Rocks.
Darwin wrote the theory of evolution.
Rocks.
Darwin wrote at the same time.
Slack cannot be explained.
Slack rocks so rapidly, we must shape or rock.
Rock.
Soft parts are very soft.
Intense heat.
D-E-M-O-N-O-K.
Have a good.
Come.
Well, in saying, do you think there's any truth at all in astrology?
Me?
Yeah.
Oh, I can always tell when Mercury is in retrograde.
Yes.
Which it is a lot of the time.
Because everything is screwed up.
Everything is screwed up all the time.
What are you talking about?
Yeah.
In fact, I blame a lot of things on sunspots and astrological misalignments and things
like that.
People don't even blink.
You know, they'll swallow anything.
Well, the Mercury retrograde thing is supposedly...
It's basically that communication and anything that involves the transfer of information.
Now, why is it that Mercury in retrograde means that?
I don't know.
I just know.
I mean, I'm no scientist.
I just know that...
Could that have anything to do with the fact that Mercury is the messenger god?
Yeah.
Exactly.
Now, why is that planet called Mercury?
Because somebody named it that.
Because we named it that.
Yes, precisely.
Yeah, some wise guy.
So is it really a property of the planet that was named by us?
No.
Come on now.
This is nonsense.
No, it makes a good story.
There you go.
It makes a good story.
And that's all it has to do.
And all you've got to do is stick to your story.
It just has to...
You're right, man.
Thank you for some intellectual honesty there.
You know, if I love or don't love astrology, the way that you're supposed to be able to
determine a person's entire personality just based on what time of the year they were born.
I've seen them do it, though.
I mean, of course, it's hard wash.
And yet, it's amazing how they can pull that off.
Oh, yeah.
It's awesome.
It's a very...
It's a skill.
Like, doing astrology for people is not something that any idiot can do.
It definitely takes some practice.
It takes some training.
It takes some research.
And when you are really, really skilled in the arts of BS, then you can...
You can tell them what they want to hear in ways that no one ever imagined.
You know, like, you can memorize all the details and all the characters in the Star Trek universe
and, like, you know, like, know all the details about, like, where the...
Freaking...
What part of the Delta Quadrant the board are from or whatever.
You know what I mean?
Like, you can memorize all those details, too.
It's, like, just another set of information that you need to memorize and, like, know...
Be aware of the consistencies of it.
And, you know, it's a rule system like any other.
Even though it may not have a basis in reality, it has its own internal logic.
Anything can be a religion because you don't use your mind to think about your religion.
And if I remember correctly, the border from nowhere near the Delta Quadrant...
I don't...
Thank you, Mark.
It was a guess.
Whatever.
I guess I just proved your point.
Yeah.
Does it matter?
Is what I'm saying.
You know, like...
Of course not.
If I wake up tomorrow morning and decide that I want to worship my cat's turd and base my
day upon where the turd lands in the litter box...
Then you will get toxoplasmosis.
Well, that's another story altogether.
But the point is, is that it's just like reading feelings.
Yeah, or chicken.
And trails.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
I think that...
No, what's great is they've done, you know, a study where they get like a hundred people
together and say, you know, do you believe in astrology?
Okay, well, we're going to get customized.
Just fill out this questionnaire about, you know, where and when you were born, and we're
going to return you a customized astrological reading.
And they all got back their readings a few weeks later, and they all opened them up,
and they were just blown away by how accurate these were.
And then they said, now trade it with your neighbor.
Yeah.
And they all got the exact same reading.
And like 90% of these people were...
Thought it was a perfect reading that was perfectly accurate.
Right.
And they gave the exact same reading to everybody.
And you can repeat that experiment, too.
Do you think that people ever conform themselves to what they think their...
Exactly.
If you live in a world, in a psychological environment where you think, you know, Pisces
means this and Leo means that, you know, then, you know, you're...
That's...
That's going to shape your attitudes, you know what I mean?
I'm a Leo.
Yeah.
Well, you are.
And I'm a Pisces, obviously, but I'm not a stereotypical Pisces, because a stereotypical
Pisces is very shy.
And anyone who's met me at X-Day knows that shyness is not part of my psychological makeup
in the planet.
Hey, O'Connor.
I don't know how the astrologers explain that.
I know a lot of outspoken Pisces, Pisceses.
Yeah.
I mean, but we're also supposed to be moody and emotional, which I...
I can...
I will confess to that.
I know a lot of people of all stripes who are moody and emotional, you know what I mean?
This product is intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.
What they're doing is they're making this group of people, because I can take that person,
low-income and uneducated, because once you take a person who's a low-income or uneducated
or a combination of all, you're screwed.
I can't believe it.
That's why I'm so passionate about...
Peace.
Look at that.
Steam your clams.
Steaming the clams, you can do it.
Oh, man.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hey, do you mind if I bring up something about 9-11?
Is it going to be conspiracy talk?
Is it going to be what?
Conspiracy theories about it?
I...
Somewhat, but...
Goodbye.
216-687-3515.
You're putting the cover up, man!
Oh, good night.
I'm so sick of that subject.
I just...
And particularly not in the last eight minutes of the show.
I'm sorry.
It is very annoying.
Try again next week.
Try again next week, a little earlier.
Yeah.
Okay.
I was part of the Kennedy cover-up for a while,
but then the book came out that explained everything I was hiding.
Yeah.
But you have so much other things to hide.
Right.
In the future...
Of which things are secret and which ones we're supposed to advertise.
I was actually the guy on the grassy knoll,
because in the future I'm going to invent a time.
I'm going to invent a time machine.
I know it's because I've been visited by my future self.
Because if Kennedy hadn't been stopped,
he would have ended up becoming 10,000 times worse than Hitler.
Ooh.
That was the part they don't tell you in elementary school.
Wow.
Really?
Yes.
Really, Pisces.
Really.
And in fact, part of the cover-up is this book called
Ultimate Sacrifice by Lamar Waldron.
Actually, it's a really good book about...
The JFK one-bullet, one-vote episode.
And another part of the cover-up, friends, is X-Day,
which is about to happen here in subgenius land and across the globe
any year now.
And since we're getting ready for that,
which involves a lot of slack abuse,
we shall let the rest of this episode of Hour of Slack morph
into an episode of Bob.
Slack Time Funhouse!
From WREK Atlanta.
And in this case, Reverend Susie the Floozy's absolutely incredible show
on the specific subject of the specific conspiracy.
Praise the Flooze!
Damn black helicopters!
Hey, get out of here, dammit!
I'm trying to use a frickin' phone!
Jesus!
I have to live in a flyover zone.
Open channel D, please.
Reverend Susie the Floozy here.
Uh, yeah, um, uh...
I'm experiencing some really weird phenomena here.
It seems to be localized in my closet.
I thought you and the lymph node institute were...
like in prison.
Now when I'm at your service,
my으니까 here's just like mine.
and, you know, discouraging einfácil,
is something that came with 언 Einkuen opinions
and, well, at nine,
your good old nation takes you off track,
love lapses a small piece of slime...
You would get used to the won Kaifling's
firetrap right out to the ground,
and in this grade 1 lights that,
you've never married.
Why, forget I,
was the Rosetta Never.
I don't want to come on any further,
i'm a bird
Perfect all the way up to number 17, but when I got to my chupacabra skin hot pants remember that outfit
It was all covered with some sort of weird gooey ectoplasm
No, you don't understand what I'm trying to tell you
Something is seriously wrong with hanger 18
Hello
Oh
We've been cut off I
Tell you seekers, it's it's like it's some sort of conspiracy
or something
We are
to
employ
you
I
Information can destroy
So we'll treat you just like toys
We are the men in black
Let the truth be known
A truth unlike the Roswell incident
Hanger 18 and so on and so forth
The Bermuda Triangle stuff they have
And for the Philadelphia experiment
And on and on and on
It just goes on
And let the public know
If you're listening to your ham radio
Or as they say amateur radio
And you get some kind of strange signals
On your radio
And you hear something that sounds
A little something like this
Welcome seekers to Bob's Slapton Funhouse
Now if the FBI doesn't get you
Or the FCC
The KGB sure did
But anyway
That's what you do if you get this
What the hell are you talking about?
A conspiracy bigger than the prophecy
The Bible says there is coming
A world government at the end of the age
No one would be stupid enough to believe that
It'll last for three and a half years
It's going to be an absolute dictatorship
And it does not give the names
But we're watching world news
It's going to be through
The United Nations organization
And it's going to be through
But how did this world government
Get its foundation?
How did it begin?
In 1776
A man by the name of Adam Weishaupt
That you see on the screen with me
Founded the modern day version
Of the Illuminati
Adam Weishaupt was a member
Of the Jesuit order of the Catholic Church
And the Pope suspended that order
Because of atrocities
And dealing in demonic activities
And witchcraft
And Satanism
This man believed in Lucifer
As God and worshipped him
So Adam Weishaupt actually founded
The modern day Illuminati
Illuminati means illuminated ones
They were illuminated by Satan the devil
They preferred to call him Lucifer
And so the modern day version
Of the Illuminati was founded
May 1st 1776
Approximately the same time
When the United Nations organization
Was being formed
He put the accent on American
As opposed to the world socialist revolution
Now smothering the American people
The world communazi revolution
Which he reminded me
Was launched in Germany May 1st 1776
The same year the American revolution was launched
For we shall be governed by God
Or we shall soon be ruled by tyrants
Adam Weishaupt who launched the socialist world revolution
In Germany May 1st 1776
Laid down as one of the six cardinal doctrines
Of his Illuminist
Now called communist revolution
As being
The abolishment of all religion
When in the same year 1776
We laid the foundation of the American revolution
We proclaimed
In God we trust
As though God himself raised up his people
To confront the devil in the form of
Adam Weishaupt and the world revolution
As time went on
The Illuminati began to penetrate
Every government on the European continent
They began to send individuals
Over to the United States
Who were 13 lodges of freemasonry
Where those at the very top
The 33rd degree
Which is the honorary degree
Were a part of the Illuminati
They had one lodge in each of the 13 original colonies
A very obscure man
Who had six children
And most of them starved to death
By the name of Karl Marx
Was actually contracted by the Illuminati
To update their program for world government
He put it in the form of the communist manifesto
It laid down their goals
And the goal was to have
Public education for all students
So that they would be able to
Propagandize and to socialize
The mind of those individuals
Who attended those public schools
The speech is short
But it's the most rousing speech I've ever read
It's been worked on here and in Russia
On and off for over eight years
I shall force someone to take the body away from him
Then Johnny will really hit those microphones
And I'll be able to get the body
And those cameras with blood all over him
Fighting off anyone who tries to help him
Defending America even if it means his own death
Rallying a nation of television viewers into hysteria
To sweep us up into the White House
With powers that will make martial law seem like anarchy
Who controls the British crown?
Who keeps the metric system down?
We do
Who makes Atlantis off the maps?
Who keeps the Martians under wraps?
We do
Who holds back the electric car?
Who makes Ye Gutenberg a star?
We do
Who robs Capish of their site?
Who rigged every Oscar night?
We do
So it is
International communism socialism
under the control of the Illuminati
worshippers of Satan the devil
Soul-less, spirit-less, corporate little bitches
We're suckers
of Satan's
Suck it
It's only your dignity
I have a document which shows that a world currency is already being setup
A word bank is already being setup by the Trilateral Commision
headed by David Rockefeller
Of which, by the way, President Carter is a member
of the Trilateral Commission
And there will soon be a universal currency by which there can be a global economic control.
My goodness, Ivan, I'm stunned.
With my brothers, the stonecutters behind me, this is the beginning of a better world for all of us.
We gotta kill him.
Take it easy.
Let's hear from the stonecutter world council before we act too rashly.
I knew we were in trouble with that damn egg commercial, that guy.
I knew that was the government's take on drugs, believe me.
Here's your brain.
Brain.
I've never, ever, ever, ever, ever looked at an egg and thought it was brain.
Not once.
So one of those egg council creeps got to you too, huh?
Oh, you got it all wrong.
It's not like that.
Kill him.
Kill the fool.
Great, I have to disagree with Orville, Jack, and Mister.
Can't we just do something to his voice box?
We might as well face the truth.
As long as we're stonecutters, he will control our lives.
Now with computers, we have the first time in history that what John predicted 1,900 years ago
would change.
It's going to take place.
Because now there are computers, in fact, there's one in Brussels right now that could do the job very easily,
where every person on earth will receive a number and they can be kept accountable.
Computers don't make errors.
What they do, they do on purpose.
By now, your name and particulars have been fed into every laptop, desktop, mainframe, and supermarket scanner
that collectively make up the global information conspiracy otherwise known as the beast.
The mark of the beast.
People now.
Who have implants in them.
It traces their movements.
It helps their health means, but it's also an invasion of privacy.
Soon there's computers that are apparently being developed that can read your brainwaves,
that can read your thoughts.
I mean, this is not, these aren't toys or beyond the realm.
People have to grapple with whether they want that big brother screen, which will be there.
Click.
You can turn it off.
Yes, Winston.
That privilege.
Well, shall I say it or will you?
I'll say it.
That thing is really turned off?
Yes.
Everything is turned off.
We're alone.
All right.
We have come here because we believe that there is some kind of secret conspiracy,
some kind of secret organization working against the party and that you are involved in it.
We want to join it and work for it.
That can be arranged.
Oh!
Ah!
This club better be worth it.
Oh!
Ah!
All right, all right.
It's Lisa's turn.
Ah!
This is a .
Oh, that.
We are enemies of the party.
We disbelieve in the principles of Ingsoc.
We are thought criminals.
We are also adulterers.
I tell you this because we want to put ourselves at your mercy.
Yes.
First, let us all take a drink.
Woohoo!
Now, let's all get drunk and play ping pong.
Yeah!
It is big brother at its worst.
Oh!
This is the United States Army.
We've got 30 seconds to throw out any weapons that exist at the premises.
No!
No forms.
No computers.
We were never here.
Don't feed the beast.
It's just phenomenal.
The amount of information that's out there in the secular media that would lend us to believe that chimp implants are going to be used to identify us.
What are you talking about, man?
Chimp implants.
Chimp.
No!
Don't feed the beast.
Because you see, there's a conspiracy, and a lot of our own officials in America are a part of that conspiracy, and we're no longer the free land that we ought to be.
Now, here are some of the executive orders, and I believe you need to know what some of them are.
This is not all of them, but there they are.
There's some of the things that they can do.
Take a moment to read that, please.
They can seize all communications media, seize all electors, power, fuels, minerals, both public and private.
What do you think, Carl?
That's awful.
What do you want to know?
Most are doing things تھ SARAT and if they can Psalmune
in some sense, they're little born Silicon.
It's still in that faith.
And there are people in that faith whose contents are crazy, nonsense.
We got a little Growing Size and then another United States, also in our book called Missionberg Threat, The Great upholding Jenn, which blah, blah, blah, blah.
IS reduced from 316 to 225 people.
things all go down at once, that was not a happenstance or an accident. That was a trial run.
I like to call it what it really is, a dress rehearsal. And if you've ever been in a play,
when do you have the dress rehearsal? Right before the real thing. So when I say that a
takeover is imminent, I am giving you the reasons why I have said that. Mr. Reagan doesn't believe
in economic sanctions against the government of South Africa. Secretary of State George Shultz,
representing the Council on Foreign Relations and their international global plans for one
world government, very often he makes decisions related to the CFR, not to the Secretary of State
that would really be to the benefit of the United States. Frankly, he makes me sick,
but that's a personal opinion. Meanwhile, you have produced some what I call subversive
organizations that aren't necessarily Union Jack, Old Glory, Apple Pie, and July the 4th.
And the CFR, in my estimation,
works far more for world government than it does for the government of the United States.
And that brings me to the other one that you saw on the screen, TLC. That is not tender loving care.
That's the Trilateral Commission, which, by the way, is part of the Fed, in a sense,
because they're all tied into the Federal Reserve System, the Council on Foreign Relations.
I happen to believe that this nation needs to be able to conduct deniable covert operations.
I believe that this president, like all presidents,
needs to have an ability to dissociate himself from those activities,
and that the U.S. role should remain hidden or deniable and not be revealed.
God bless America.
Oh, no. Aliens, bioduplication, nude conspiracies. Oh, my God. Lyndon LaRouche was right.
My fellow Americans, you have a choice to make on Tuesday. You choose whether to continue forward
on the path which we've forged or to move on to the future.
We're going to move in a different direction. America is at peace and we're prosperous once more.
The dreams of the next decade lie in your hands. On Tuesday, I hope you'll vote Republican.
Up and down the ticket. To continue the change, we begin...
It appears as though something has happened in the motorcade group. There has been a shooting.
I repeat, a shooting in the motorcade in the downtown area.
We needed the theory of some guy on the grassy knoll who's responsible for all this,
and lo and behold, it's Falwell.
What grassy knoll? Someone still needs to explain.
But I don't even want to hear the words grassy knoll.
The Illuminati, worshippers of Satan the devil, is now infiltrated into the United States of America.
The very highest office of the land is now occupied by one of their agents.
And it goes right on down through the Congress, the Senate.
Realize who you're talking to. I am the commander-in-chief of the Army, the Navy, the Air Force.
What?
Call on all loyal Americans.
Now pick at the White House, write to your congressmen.
Don't let them pour an ink of water.
I am the foe.
Oh, for God's sake, let us sit upon the ground and tell sad stories to the dead of seeing.
Once more into the breach, dear friends.
Once more into the breach.
It was after the Washington State and East Lap.
What you foes flew in triangular formation over the White House.
You see, the brain of Charles Darwin is preserved in the British Medical Museum in London.
I've opened the skull and looked at the brain.
Now, their heads are a little bit large.
But after all, you see megasophallic little people yourself.
Many little people have heads that are a little too big.
Oh, yeah.
Well, he helped the oil man.
Who made the talk.
He is the one who told the oil man all about it.
These groovy cats could care less about what happens in Washington.
It's really not their bag.
Like, uh, getting into the aliens and all.
Going back and remembering when I first became an alien.
Now the big one.
Why?
Why is all of this being done?
What have they built you to do?
I don't know.
I don't think anybody really knows except...
that it's all on Moscow.
And my American operator here.
Or whatever it is it's supposed to happen soon.
Like at the convention.
Maybe it...
I don't know.
There's apparently a conspiracy to stop all of this.
It's part of our work and causes us to lose the franchise.
Oh, I see.
This is some sort of conspiracy.
No, no.
Oh, yeah.
Just some trumped up occupational therapy.
Like leather craft.
Or basket weaving.
I swear to you it'll be a best seller.
The great story here for anybody willing to find it and write about it and explain it
is this vast right wing conspiracy that has been conspiring against my husband since the
day he announced for president.
And by saying conspiracy they're saying lunatic.
They're saying mad.
They're saying out of the mainstream and therefore not to be taken account of.
You know if you find a turtle on a fence post, it didn't get there by accident.
And I just look at the landscape around here and I see just lots of big old turtles sitting
on lots of fence posts.
Possibly the best book ever written on the subject of turtle stacking.
She's got that right.
The length and extent of this conspiracy is absolutely fantastic.
Actually, that's where I'm going right now.
There's a vast conspiracy meeting downtown.
The proof of this, the sophistication of this conspiracy is the utter absence of evidence
for the conspiracy.
That's how clever the conspiracy is at covering itself up.
This is about as conspiratorial as a steam calliope.
He didn't believe there was a conspiracy.
He didn't believe there was a plot.
Let's talk common sense now.
Right.
Yeah, common sense.
Please call it conspiracy.
Would you give me a chance to talk?
It was a first class mess in my estimation.
Aren't you glad I never get political?
So anyway, Lenny and Carl are never around on Wednesdays.
And they don't talk about it.
They don't tell me where they go.
It's like a conspiracy.
A conspiracy, eh?
You think they might be involved in the Kennedy assassination in some way?
I do.
Oh.
Sources within the United States using perhaps Cubans in this conspiracy.
I still believe that it is a conspiracy.
Thank you very much, Mr. Chairman, super patriots, fellow crackpots, members of the constitutional
underground, Republicans and fellow Democrats.
And my name is Lenny.
I'm glad to be here again.
Because he had a lot of troubles with the brothers Kennedy.
He was very much upset.
Very much upset about what Kennedy had been doing to Hoffa.
And he felt sympathetic towards Hoffa, described him as a man of the workers.
Very much.
Bobby Kennedy, our Attorney General, the most outrageous appointment since Caligula named
his horse a consul.
And I'm very happy to be here.
And I welcome and honor with reduce round shaking hands the next dinners with the
witnesses upon the House of Representatives.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome, my name is Lenny U Harbor, I'm the Chief Regionals
Commissioner for Cadets.
This is a group of scientists,Com PUBG Educational Sciencecoders and candidates.
However, we ought to be very frank here.
Why?
The Federal Department of打children!
I know the law.
But they are not elegant.
those owned by gangsters.
The next steps of the collectivists
is to send gun collectors around
to each home to pick them up.
It's sort of nice to have
an equalizer around for four-block
nuts on the door,
regardless of who's knocking.
And my informant heard him say
very distinctly that in order
to do away with Bobby,
you had to get rid of the president
of the United States,
and that you had to find that nut
who would be capable
of assassinating the president.
Khrushchev doesn't have to bury us.
Our leaders are burying us.
Stupid as I am sometimes,
I started needling about the Kennedys.
Gee, wasn't it too bad
that Bobby Kennedy had you picked up
and deported to Guatemala?
Just to see what he'd say, you know.
And then he said,
don't worry, we're taking care of that.
And I said, what do you mean taking care of that?
He says, you know, you kill the head,
the tail drops off.
You gonna kill Bobby Kennedy for what he is?
He said, no, you kill the president,
Bobby gets taken care of.
Once upon a time,
a hunt on his dog
was lost in a deep forest.
Out of food,
the starving hunter
sat by his fire one night
and finally he could stand it no longer.
He whipped out his knife
and whacked off his dog's tail
and put it on the fire to boil.
When he was through,
only the clean bones were left
and he tossed them
to the whimpering dog
who devoured the remains
and then licked his master's hand
in gratitude.
That's the story of federal aid.
Later on,
he'll put fire
every tree
by the fire
to keep them afraid
Plato said the penalty
good men pay
for indifference
to public affairs
is to be ruled
by evil men.
I think we are being ruled
What can one person do?
And now,
fire!
What are you trying to do?
It appears as though
something has happened
in the motorcade.
It's a good thing.
I repeat,
a shooting in the motorcade
in the downtown area.
He shot that guy
and killed him too.
The president's car
is now going past me.
Now traveling at
a very high rate of speed.
Secret service men
standing up in the limousine
in our arms
with sub-machine guns.
I am convinced
beyond any question of a doubt
that the first shot
that was fired
did not hit me.
Ms. Connelly
has the very definite
feeling,
a very strong conviction
that the first shot
that was fired
hit the president.
The second shot
that was fired
hit me.
The third shot
that was fired
hit the president.
Unquestionably,
when the first shot
was fired,
I recognized it as a shot.
I thought of nothing else
but that it was
a rifle shot.
I thought of nothing else
but that it was a shot.
I turned to my right.
I had time to think.
I had time to react.
And I turned to my right
to look back
over my right shoulder
to see if I could see
anything unusual
and particularly to see
if I could catch him
out of the corner of my eye
because I immediately thought
the president.
Because I immediately
thought of an assassination
the moment I heard the shot.
On November 22nd,
Mr. Dodd,
what did you see
and what did you hear?
Well, I seen the president
roll over
and slump over
in his seat
and then I saw
Governor Conley
slump over.
And did you see
anything
which might indicate to you
where the shot came from?
Well,
we all three seen,
four seen
about the same thing
as the shot.
The smoke came
from behind the hedge
on the north side
of the plaza
and a motorcycle policeman
dropped his motorcycle
in the street.
He was shot in the head
with his gun in his hand
and run up the embankment
to the hedge.
And yet he was not called
by the commission
for what?
Well, I always thought
it peculiar,
but I thought that's
the way they did business.
Well, I and really most
of the early subgenius apostles
were in Dealey Plaza
at the time.
We were probably about
nine, ten, eleven years old
most of us.
But we had our little dart guns
and our, you know,
little ray gun toys
that make sparks
and our squirt guns.
And we were stationed
at the grassy knoll
in the,
in the drain,
storm sewer drain,
ready to do our patriotic duty.
You don't believe a word of this,
do you?
Sure, it's fantastic,
but it happened.
Don't just sit there
measuring me for a straight check.
Do something!
Get on the phone,
call for help!
Get on your radio
and sound all points along.
Block all highways
and stop all traffic
and call every law enforcement
agency in the state.
Operative,
get me the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
Yes, it's an emergency.
Over the last seven years,
Lamar Walton has built up
a formidable database
on this secret agenda
and its relationship
to Kennedy's murder.
There were very low level
operatives and informants
working for the CIA
whose primary allegiance
was to the Mafia.
And these people
had been working
for the CIA
with the Mafia
for much longer
than they had been working
with the CIA.
And the Mafia paid them
many, many times
what the CIA did.
Those people not only told
the Mafia bosses
like Traficante and Marcello
about Project Freedom,
but they worked with the Mafia
in ways to use those plans
to kill President Kennedy
and use the secrecy
surrounding Project Freedom
to cover up the Mafia's
role in it.
Warren Report found
no significant links
between Jack Ruby
and the Cuban issue
or with organized crime.
It was incredible.
He really believed this stuff.
In the fall of 1963,
Ruby made an unusual number
of long distance calls
to associates of
Johnny Roselli in Las Vegas,
Sam Giancana in Chicago,
and Carlos Marcello
in New Orleans.
And Oswald was also
very close in 1963
with a man named David Ferry
who was working on a daily basis
for Carlos Marcello
in the fall of 1963.
The committee believes
that President Kennedy
was probably the most
likely to be assassinated
as the result of a conspiracy.
I guess the easiest thing
would be to blame it all
on some sort of vast
right wing conspiracy.
But that would be lame.
No one would be stupid enough
to believe that.
I would love to see
a computer faced with
the problem of coming up
with the probabilities
of the assassination
taking place the way it did.
With all of these strange
incidents that took place
before and are continuing
to take place
after the assassination.
I think all of us
who love this country
should be alerted
that something is wrong
in the land.
Kind of like going up
to Jackie Onassis
with a rifle pendant on,
you know?
I was thinking of John,
Jackie, we love him.
Do me a favor,
don't love me that much.
Okay, get a hobby.
His death is an incomplete story.
The conspiracy report
was an explanation,
not a case.
It was issued in 1979
and by then the trail was cold.
As cold as Kennedy's grave.
No evidence was ever presented
in court.
No suspect ever indicted.
The story of the conspiracy
to assassinate President Kennedy
serves nothing but history.
History, like humanity,
needs to have its history.
It keeps filmed
달라res and rears
There has been a history
of fully wymorbable
human beings in колумб.
Actually,
Huh, must be my nose hairs or something.
Don't f*** with Mommy, John John. Keep saluting or I'll nail your other hand to your forehead.
What'd I do, Mom?
Oh, Christ, I need a drink.
Oh, hello. I'm your hostess, Ilona.
Ilona. Ilona Sasson. And I'm here to explain to you the single bimbo theory.
Oh, man, look at these nails. Huh. I gotta take a gemstone file to them.
Ah, yes, as I was saying, the myriad pleasures of the godfather of all contemporary conspiracy theories, the JFK hit.
Oh, you've all heard the coincidence or conspiracy bit.
That old saw about Lincoln and Kennedy, how Lincoln's secretary was named Kennedy, Kennedy's secretary was named Lincoln,
and how Lincoln was once in Monroe, Maryland, and Kennedy was in Maryland, Monroe a lot.
You know, that sort of stuff.
Oh, but the JFK assassination mystique gets weirder the longer you soak in it.
The unassailable truths of the situation are so damn weird that...
The most deluniac crackpots are only following the trend set by the serious researchers.
The theory that JFK is still alive and hiding out with Elvis, that pales next to the documented stuff.
Bizarre facts that even Oliver Stone missed.
Like the creepy, hairless, chicken-hawk David Ferry's secret monkey virus labs.
Or that guy on Air Force One winking.
Or that guy on Air Force One winking at LBJ after the swearing-in.
Or how one of my favorites, the fact that the Warren Commission's Stooge Gerald R. Ford
just somehow happened to become our first unelected president ten years later.
And yeah, now that I think of it, why the hell does assassination have two asses in it?
Oh, and those are the real facts, too, if you can believe that.
Oh, there's a lot of them.
There are lots of juicy, tasty, conspiratorial nuggets to snack on here, but...
Oh, let's not make a rush to fudge-mint seekers.
After all, these goobers have already found thirteen of the three gunmen.
Oh, just a second here.
Hey, hey, Krasner!
Paul, out of the coffin there, fucko!
Yeah, you! That's an exit wound!
Not an entrance!
As I was saying, I'm personally steeped in the JFK world myself,
and I've been stuck in it like a fly in amber for years.
I've even had the dubious honor of seeing Lee Harvey Oswald's bedroom furniture
at the Tragedy and U.S. History Museum in St. Augustine.
Oh, and I can always be persuaded to attend the JFK,
the JFK assassination symposia, when they're held in Dallas, that is.
Oh, these JFK nut affairs are like sci-fi conventions, but with scarier geeks.
Oh, and the excitement breaks out all over,
because every clutch of theorists hates every other clutch of theorists,
and pointless, hair-splitting intellectuals' catfights
and embarrassingly pissy spats erupt in the lobby,
and ballroom as lunatics collide.
Oh, at that point, I gave up.
I gave in to madness.
Because when you stop disbelieving,
isn't the path of a single bullet like a lyrical aerial ballet?
Did the MK Ultra clone who played the part of Lee Harvey Oswald overact alone?
Is Cary Thornley possibly the other boss?
Bob, too?
Hmm, I wouldn't discount it.
But luckily, I have the rarefied ability to pass among the multi-layered strata of JFK buffs
by treating them all like a bunch of bums in a strip club.
Ooh, whoa!
Hey, I'd better stop that tape right there before too much of that particular conspiracy is laid bare.
Yeah, too much of that JFK stuff sure does get ugly.
Ugly if you get exposed to it too much.
Oh, yes, but what a huge, sprawling conspiracy it is.
But you know, when you get down to brass tacks,
they can't hold a candle to our hated conspiracy.
Oh, and there's plenty of con to go around, too, Seekers.
The real conspiracy.
Not the piddling little penny-ante one.
Tiny conspiracies like the Freemasons and the Illuminati.
Oh, no.
I'm not talking about pikers like the Trilateral Commission and the Elders of Zion.
Oh, no, baby.
These guys are like street-corner three-card Monty Uzzlers next to the real conspiracy.
I'm talking about a conspiracy that has stretched back through the mildewed mist of time to Atlantis and beyond.
A conspiracy.
A conspiracy whose roots extend to the center of space and time.
A conspiracy that is working night and day to steal your slack away.
That's right, Seekers.
The conspiracy.
Need I say more?
So, if you want to continue to poop and pee-dog in your own diaper for the love of Bob,
you can always write for free information on what this lunacy is all about.
Right now, if you want to read this book, just write to Bob at P.O. Box 181417.
You'll find him waiting for you at P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And, oh, dear, now that I told you that, I'm afraid one of us has to die.
I'm afraid one of us has to die.
Hey Flooz, I need you to pop something.
Ah, jeez.
Well, plenty more where that came from.