Ich bin ein...
...Au...
Ah, ja, liebe Freunde, es ist wieder die Re-Run-Zeit.
Aber ihr werdet glücklich wissen, dass wir das gleiche alte
dreimal die Weihnachtszeit der Slack-Show-Re-Runs in einer Reihe machen werden.
Nein, ich werde es ausdrücken.
... in nur dieses eine intensive, totale Rerun-Show.
Außer, dass es nicht die ganze erste Hälfte ist.
Es wird mit einer neuen Weihnachts-Sickheit verbreitet.
Für die Weihnachten und die Heiligen Tage.
Und die Heiligen Tage, wie es für einige Leute ist.
Eigentlich muss ich doppelt arbeiten, weil es die Saison der Verkaufszeit ist.
Das ist so schrecklich!
Du würdest nicht glauben, was die Elfen in diesen subgeniösen Katalogs gemacht haben.
Aber, äh, äh, äh, ja, glücklich, äh, was auch immer du tust.
Ah, äh, ja, diese Musik im Hintergrund ist von jemandem namens Kenny Wayne Shepherd.
Ja, es gibt ein Album namens Merry Axmus, ein Gitarre-Axmus.
Es ist cool, Mann, cool!
Und, äh, äh, äh, äh, äh, Praise Bob!
Und, äh, ho, oh, oh, oh, oh!
... Musik ...
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong
And stuck my butt upon this Christmas tree.
... Musik ...
Und stuck my butt upon this Christmas tree.
Who put this stomp in my rompapompapomp
Who took and jammed it in my rammalammadingdon
Who stabbed the wood where I poopshi-poopshi pop
Who put the stick up my hip-di-dip-di-dip
Who was that man?
... Musik ...
Er hat mir die Schnauze auf den Kamm geschoben und mich auf diesen Weihnachtsbaum verliebt.
Wenn dieser Engel hörte,
ein schreckliches Fehlschmerz ging direkt in mein Herz.
Diese Pinzentrie-Nebel stürmen mich.
Rämme, jämme, rämme, jämmele, ma ding dong.
You'll never know how much that smarts.
So, who put the stump in my rompapompapomp?
Who took and jammed it in my rämmele, ma ding dong?
Who stood the wood where I boop-sheep-boop-sheep-boop?
Who put the stick up my hip-de-dip-de-dip?
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush?
He made this angel beg for mercy, please.
I might squeeze him too tight.
It's that psychedelic time of the year.
Do you know where your brain cells are?
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-ate him.
Don't go walking down to the bar,
cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard.
I mean, I'm in the apartment store.
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
He ain't brought back the chains.
Oh yeah, I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
till I get the damn chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday.
Now you boys be good and I'll give you some of this here.
You ain't no good of a child.
That dog's running off with them brain cells.
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to...
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right.
What?
Merry Christmas!
What we as manufacturers sell you is fun.
The fate of a child.
Spend all the money you've got.
The Christmas Trough.
Oh, look!
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
Oh, he's like a cowboy Santa.
Oh, jolly!
Oh, Jazz is giving-
Gives Dave the show pills.
Oh boy, I really need one of those.
What am I gonna do about Laundromat and his suit though.
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave. Look, it's swelling.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills, they make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feels like it's a puddle of liquefied crystals.
I'm shocked by the...
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels, we have heard on high
Singing about mountains
And those mountains in reply
Saying we wish we had some too
Oh, warrior
In excelsis deo
Das war's für heute.
Barbie-Dolls.
Wie wird die Waffe von Gut gegen Schicksal
in deinen Marketing-Schemen vertreten, Mensch?
Gut hat Waffen und Muskeln.
Gut.
Gut!
Die primitiven Welt-Sozieten
sollten diesen Wert-Gesetz akzeptieren.
Gut hat physische Attribute,
je nachdem, was man will.
Sexualen Wünsche.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984
in mean Palmer Veedies.
Angels We Have Heard on High
was by The Philistines.
The Collage called All the Money You've Got
is from the great Obtuse Christmas Collage album,
which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website,
obtuse.iuma.com.
That's obt...
Excuse me.
Ah, yes.
And next up,
The Real Story of Christmas
by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time
there was the baby Jesus
and he had two eyes made out of coal
and he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree
and he wanted his two front teeth
and he got McDonald's gift certificates
and he had a dog named Santa's little helper
and he took all the presents from Whoville
and his friend Yukon Cornelius
came with the three wise guys
and he wanted to play the drums
and be the little drummer boy
but he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s, 10s and 20s
and he...
and he got McDonald's gift certificates
and he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
So separate.
New from Tonka.
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob.
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal.
Shut up, pink boy.
No way.
I'll never sell out to the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien tool.
I'll eat you.
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher,
jayner device, oligarchatism, fighting Jesus
and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required, batteries not included.
This toy falls apart in three days.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
From Bob Dobbs.
Gorgeous.
We girls can blow from head to toe.
Everything you see here.
Ken Dowsell separately.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
will be back after this message.
Santa Claus.
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind,
even to the table where he was going to set it up.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe.
He turned the roulette.
und was er für eine ganz lustige Trainingsstrecke mit Lokomotiven und freien Autos,
der Station und der Gateman,
der Motor-Tower und all den ganzen wunderbaren Equipmenten und Accessorien.
So rand, dass man vielleicht denkt, dass Tommy für etwas gewinnt, das nicht existierte.
Aber Tommy wusste, was er für eine Wünsche wünschte.
Es ist die Zeit des Jahres, an der alle Dinge verkaufen, die End-Jahr-Sale.
Also kommt alle her und kauft unsere Produkte.
Ich bin ein wenig überrascht, was Weihnachten alles umsieht.
Ich habe mich überrascht, dass es so viel Geld gibt.
Sehen wir uns an den Geburtstag von Santa Claus oder an seinen Tod, als er ihn gekauft hat?
Das ist das alte, alte Subgenie.
Aber das präsentierte Subgenie versucht, dass wir unsere Inventare jetzt abklappern
und alles an die Pinks verkaufen.
Oh ja, ein einmaler Pagan-Holiday und jetzt eine Shopping-Saison.
Und es war etwas anderes dazwischen.
Nachdem es ein Pagan-Holiday war und vor der Shopping-Saison,
war es etwas anderes.
Aber ich denke, dass sie sich darüber gewandert haben.
Ja, ja, ja.
Aber eigentlich war das alles zuigh joking and
das war die gemachte Er Venus.
idée
مش
Vieh
Country
To Making
Koose
Beauty
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
U search in U, YouTube auf YouTube und 그럴pe. In chorus!
esto
Am 4. Juli.
Juli.
That real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records
All-Star Holiday
Extravaganza. I'm playing a lot
from that. So check out
www.triage.com
For that one also,
the Tarkin Records is also
on www.triage.com
and now
the Jethro's.
Jethro's
oder dass sie Santa Bob sind am Abend.
Und sie gehen durch die Schnee auf ihre unbekanntes, hübsches Errens,
der Geruch von Bob und der Geist von Santa Claus und der Pipe des Herrn,
auf ihre Füße gestanden.
Sie stoppen die Locken ihrer Türen und fliegen einfach in den Schlüssel.
Oh Freunde, es ist schwer. Und du weißt, dass es nicht genug ist, nur in der Kirche zu gehen.
Du musst dein Geld an den Santa Bob schicken.
Als Fakt, die Leute auf der Straße von mir haben ihren Kindern gesagt,
dass Santa Claus sie für die Türen, die er bringt, bietet.
Kannst du das glauben? Die Kinder fragten, ob Santa Claus uns zwei He-Man-Erektor-Sets bringt.
Und die Mutter sagte, dass es nicht so ist.
Und die Mutter sagte, dass es nicht so ist, weil er uns billt. Wir können das nicht erlauben.
Santa Claus schickt uns eine Bille nach Weihnachten.
Ja, aber zumindest hat er die Note geklopft.
Und dann hat er uns geklopft.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Jetzt blamierst du Jesus, du blamierst unseren Herrn.
Ich verstehe es, weil...
Ich verstehe es, wie jeder alte Schwester es versteht.
Es gab keinen Jesus.
Keine alte schwesterische Frau, die ihre Hände auf dem Berg wackelt.
Es ist nicht so, dass du es nicht willst, es ist nicht so, dass sie dich nicht lassen.
Nein, es ist nur ein Schmerz, der die Welt in der heißen Bewegung der Wälder, überall im Hintergrund, verursacht.
Ich bin schuld von ihnen.
Es ist kalt.
Ich verliere das Stadtleben hinter den radioführenden Menschen.
Ich kann meine Finger nicht mehr.
Ich kann sie nicht mehr.
Es ist sie.
Was ist los?
Musik
Music
der Konspiration.
Yes.
There was a
down-home Norman Rockwell
style, it's a wonderful
life type of Christmas.
It was a
kite-flying
Coca-Cola-drinking Christmas,
not a crack-smoking,
rubber-snapping Christmas.
Holy dough.
It was a...
When your little brother
broke through the hole, it fell through
a hole in the ice, and you
went and saved him. You didn't
laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful
life back then.
But today
Christmas is now.
It's me.
Scott,
you're
You made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected
me.
And to your eternal soul,
you have found that only
could you afford
to give to God that which was his.
But you could not afford
to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
In the outer
darkness, where there is
wailing and gnashing of teeth.
Sir, please give me just one more
chance.
Sir, I don't wanna go to hell, sir.
Sir, no, no.
I don't wanna go to hell.
And the children say
you could laugh and play just the same.
You and me.
The tail bearer will be at the judgment.
Everyone in heaven Far intern mean!
Oh no, oh no, oh, it's all what I get.
let's live in peace.
My head hills.
Ahh!
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Die Antwort? Ja, definitiv.
Nehmt das und schüttelt es auf die Tube, markt Sicherheit, in die fülle Stelle, nenn es die Twilight Zone.
Play right to heck
Right to heck
Right to hell
Long cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Choco de combo, good day ya.
No, no, no.
It was the night before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creed
horse klares
Merry Fucking Christmas!
Musik