I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
The Self-Demons Power of Swat Team!
It's called blindin'.
Shinin', it's blindin', it's ridin'
My eyes outlaid again with my crazy jaguar friends
And I can't even pretend it'd be okay for me to spend more time
Time, hey anybody here got the time?
My head is floating like a bone
And I'm just a little bit scared
Feels like it's coming off my shoulders
So I just love when my day starts like this
Useless and clueless, I do this each time
Just when you think it might start to sink
And it's gone in a blink and I'm back to the brink again
Again
Hey anybody here see my friends?
My head is floating like a bone
And I can't even pretend it'd be okay for me to spend more time
And I'm just a little bit scared
Feels like it's coming off my shoulders
So I just love when my day starts like this
I just love when my day starts like this
Don't know where I'm goin'
Don't know how I got here
Don't even know where I am
Seriously
Seriously, can somebody tell me how to get back to fifteen?
I don't recall too much of last night
Left my car on the east side
How I got here was some guy
Really all I know
Southernville down a bridge
A bridge, some big green tumbleweed
A bridge, wasted
Yeah, face it
I spaced it
It's fine
What do I do now?
I'll somehow get downtown
Freak out anyone around
Cause I gotta feed the clown inside
Inside
Hey anybody here give me a ride
My head is floating like a boulder
Feels like it's coming off my shoulders
I wonder just how many disasters
Between now and the Sweetie Raptor
My head is floating like a boulder
I just love when my day starts like this
Are you plagued by bad luck?
Is some smiling little imp knocking the last bite of candy bar onto the floor?
Yeah, I'm not!
Or drying up your ink when you're trying to take down a message?
Maybe you're stalked by some larger hellspawn
Who causes your doors to automatically lock
While you scrape ice off your car
Or causes your mortgage to come out of your bank account
At the exact moment that your car payment, your insurance, and utilities do
You know, on the day right before your paycheck
Perhaps you're being tailed by a really large fucker
Who physically disables some part of you that used to work just fine
Or maybe he offs a family member
Or maybe he burns down your house
Or maybe your problem is a more insidious and creeping depression
Maybe it's just some formless phantom clinging on your back
And with every moment of embarrassment
Every feeling of failure or despair
Every wrong word or bungled gesture
Every time you feel ignored, isolated, or alienated
He just grows larger and larger until he can barely be carried
You, my friend, have bad brain
That niggling, fretting waste of energy
That keeps your brain spinning in a centrifuge of negativity
Until you think it's going to just splatter against the walls of your skull
That dragging heavy weight of futility
And frustration that just pulls you ever lower
The constant, insurmountable, intolerable, ever-growing heap of problems
Of setbacks and failures
What are you going to do about this?
I wonder
Will you allow yourself to be chained inexorably to your bad brain?
Will you mope and sleep and lament your luck?
Moving yourself from one day to the next listless, lifeless, and lost?
Friends, when that bull of bad brain comes at you
You don't grab it by the horns
Oh no
You don't plant yourself
Against a wall
To push against what you already know is an immovable juggernaut
The bad brain can't be bargained with
Or made to leave by sheer force of will
When that bull of bad brain comes tear-assing through your mind
You climb aboard
And you ride that fucker into the ground!
You withstand the bucking and tossing
You grit your teeth
And you dig your heels
Sure, you're bound to get thrown a few times
You get the holy hell kicked out of you by this beast
But you're going to get back on
Not because you want to
And not even because you have to
But because you are a subgenius
And you're too goddamn stupid to know when to quit!
No!
Because you're too stubborn to let those yokels in the audience have the last laugh!
Because you're too proud to wait and be saved by some rodeo clown
So you hang on for dear life
And you wait!
We know that the only form of time control that we have available to us is...
Patience
So you wait
You wait for that bull to become exhausted
You wait until it's worn itself out
And when it collapses
Unable to take you for a ride any further
You get up
And you wait!
For the next fucker who wants to try to take you down
The next past due bill
The next car breakdown
The next hard time
Because if you're not riding the bull
You're sitting in the stands
And that's the end of the story!
That's only fun for so long
Let's face it
Life is boring without a challenge
Life is boring with the same day in, day out
The predictable routine
So when that bad brain comes roaring at you
Remember
You're a subgenius
You're not going to quit
You're going to put on one hell of a show!
Or just fucking kill me!
Yes!
Praise Bob!
God and God!
Hallelujah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
shooting shall outlined
But right now
They got stuck in a
will never decay.
Look away, look away, from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
The responsibility's getting heavy to bear
when you're blind, walked through life so severe.
There's a hypnotic man who is beckoning from
where there's this body that always there.
Look away, look away, from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
If your conflict with normals brings struggles and strides,
then onward your end brings them too.
Fail away from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
That's a waiting in the town for you.
Look away, look away, from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
The same hypnotic for the generous like me,
look away, look away, look away, for you'll buy it back.
But that's not all ya'll say,
look away, look away, from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
Look away, look away for you'll Grimm's here to back.
And from the pigs to the billowing pipe,
look away, look away, from the pigs to the billowing pipe.
blowing by.
Well, I was going to read the rest of
the good Reverend Rogers
rant.
Some notes on an inconvenient
universe. This would be
part two.
I had to kind of burp a bit there.
Clear things out.
You can do it!
Is this like a Slim Jam
or something?
Sure.
We'll see.
What's the matter, Bunky?
You say things aren't what they
used to be. That the
future has made you uncomfortable.
That things would be
much better if the
gays weren't quite so
gay about
things. And maybe if the blacks
and the women would
go back to being quiet about
what and who they are.
That a black president
was okay the one time,
but re-electing him has made it
look normal. Now you worry?
Well, fuck you,
Bunky. You'd be more comfortable
if roughly 54%
of the population was less
comfortable.
How nice. How
very fucking
nice. All it would require
to make you the main
character is for
all of those people, almost
200 million human beings,
sit down and shut up about
how they've been treated and continue to be treated
on account of brown skin
and or female genitalia,
homosexuality,
transgender issues,
whatever.
But has it occurred to you
even once that none of you are going to be able to do that?
None of those people give a fuck about your feelings
on the subject any more than you give a rat's
ass about their feelings.
Do you not suppose it irritates
them when you open your face
and weird rationalizations
as to why they're inferior
and should shut up and vote for their
own oppression? It irritates
me, and I'm as white
bread as you are.
It irritates me
because it's dumb, and you
are a dumb shit, and it really
wouldn't make the world a better place.
If you'd shut up, or even
maybe accidentally crash into a gas
truck on the way home from work tonight.
Because what all
your whining really says
is, I'm afraid to
compete for jobs or mating
chances with that many
people. And
I may be a
po-bucker swine, but at least I'm not
on the bottom of the heap.
But you are, aren't
you? Yes,
you're viewed by the vast majority
of the population as a
useless throwback.
Too ugly in spirit
to associate with, and too dumb
to hire. Your day
has been over for
50 years.
You will soon live under a
bridge, and your children
will drink filthy water
for the rest of their
lives. Because
you were too lazy
and too cowardly
to stand up on your hind legs
and act like a human being. And
the world will not
miss you, nor will
I.
That was the end of part two.
Nenslo,
eat your heart out.
I'll go ahead and do
part three.
A lot of people think
America is addicted to
McDonald's, or TV,
or porn. And
we may very well be, but America's
number one addiction,
the 500-pound monkey on our
backs, is
punishment.
We love
punishment. We love
to see no good shits
get theirs, even
especially
if we do or at one time did
the very same thing we're
hollering about.
This ranges from the public to the
personal. Publicly speaking,
we have 5% of the world's
population and 25% of the world's
incarcerated population.
I think he's talking about the
USA.
We lock kids up, as recently
happened in Alabama, for 26
years for a pound of pot.
Given that kid is 19, he'll be
middle-aged when or if he gets
out. His whole life is gone for
a pound of pot.
A large minority of the
population believes that this is
reasonable.
We arrest six year olds on
felony charges for acting out in
class. Then Facebook and Twitter
and all the other social media
sites fill up with outrage that
would be appropriate if the
people expressing that outrage
hadn't spent their entire lives
voting for asshats who promised
to, quote, get tough on crime,
unquote, in a system that is
already very tough on anything
even remotely resembling a crime.
Hell,
they ran out of crimes.
Now they're after six year olds.
This is what you screamed for,
America.
This is what you demanded.
Why are you complaining now?
In the private sector, we punish
people by firing them, not just
for things like non-performance
or being drunk on the job, but
also for posting things we don't
like on social media or for
having the wrong friends and or
police.
We punish people by not
having political beliefs or
expecting a living wage.
Hell, we even punish our own
friends and family, and not
always by obvious physical abuse,
but also by withholding attention
or affection to show them what.
By deciding that they need to
feel your disdain for a while so
they won't do whatever it was
they did to give you the urge to
punish them, then we wake up one
day, won't want to do it again.
We wonder where everyone went
and why we're so alone.
It's not a mystery where they
went, really.
They're in jail.
Or under a bridge eating from
garbage cans.
Or they got sick of our emotional
manipulation and just, you know,
went away.
But we console ourselves that
they deserve the punishment they
got because they were no good
shits anyway and we are an island.
We are better off without their
company.
And that, friends, is how you get
the utterly psychotic society that
frightens and depresses you so much.
I don't know if I got slack from
that, good Reverend Roger.
I thought I'd be doing this Church
of the Genius thing, good Reverend
Roger, I thought I was going to
get slapped for that, Reverend
Roger, but I'm glad I was able
to get that one out.
I wonder what good Reverend Roger
really sounds like.
It could be that he's a, you know,
would be a really good stage actor
or he might be a mush mouth, you
know, scared stage fright.
You should have seen me the first
five years of my life.
Preaching in Bucknaked's backyard.
Everybody give good Reverend Roger
who is not here a round of applause.
I don't clap my hands,
I don't believe in the earth.
Culture is on the ground.
But I don't pay for it,
I don't owe anyone.
I'm just letting the
thieves of the world run.
But the good people don't
give me a round of applause.
There's another one,
a heart of gold.
No, the good people don't
give me a round of applause.
I don't like that in a heart of gold
you lie about me.
Except when people
know how to believe.
Now for those of you out there
that don't actually speak French,
this song is called
La Mauvaise Reputation,
which means Bad Reputation.
It was written by a phenomenal
musician called George Brassens.
And basically,
I fell in love with this song
because it's the ultimate alienation.
It's a song about a man
who likes to go his way,
but the people in the village,
they don't like it
when you go your way.
So he feels that they're all
singling him out.
And when they don't like
what he's done,
they point their fingers at him,
except for the ones without hands.
And when they don't like
what he's done,
they talk about it,
except for the people without tongues.
When he sees a couple of
apple chasers
running away from a man
he stole an apple from,
he trips the man chasing them.
Because what does he care
if somebody wants to steal
a couple apples?
Pas besoin d'être Jérémie
Pour rediviner le sort
qui m'est promis
S'il trouve une corde à leur cul
Il en peut la passer au cou.
Ça ne fait pas tant de tort
à personne.
On se fait voir les chemins
qui ne m'aiment pas.
Ah, mais les braves,
j'en n'aime pas que
l'on suive une autre route.
Les braves, j'en n'aime pas que
Si je m'en viens de voir
pendu
Sauf les erreurs
Mien entendu.
Have you ever noticed
that you owe
the conspiracy
a big vote of thank you
as well as a big vote of fuck you
but mostly the thank you.
If it wasn't for the conspiracy
filling your minds with crap
filling the airwaves
with cautionary tales
of child damaging
horseshit on the learning channel
If it wasn't for constant
reminders of how you're not
going to be any good at anything
unless you're a celebrity
what would we have to rail against?
What would be our calling other than Bob?
How many of us would even know
if Bob was out there looking for us
if we didn't rebel against the bullshit?
There has to be something for us to
take offense to
in order for us to know who we are.
We all should be able to
Because we are defined by our adversaries.
Like any good hero.
Of any good story.
Batman is shit.
If there are no villains to fight.
What is he?
He's a freak who wears a suit.
But give him a Joker to fight against.
It suddenly becomes interesting.
Is that genius?
It's not genius.
It's only interesting.
When we're.
Fighting the conspiracy.
And the conspiracy.
Thought like we did.
We would be the conspiracy.
And we'd have to hate ourselves.
Which we do far too often anyway.
But.
Not for the right reasons.
We sit there and we hate ourselves.
Because the conspiracy tells us we should.
Once in a while.
We believe them.
But usually they're just bullshit.
See the conspiracy.
Lies to you.
Daily.
They hit you over the head.
Every hour.
Of every day.
To tell you you're not good enough.
You're not smart enough.
You're not pretty enough.
You're not going to get that promotion at work.
You're not going to finish school.
You're just going to be.
One more cog in the machine.
But you know what the subgenius's job is?
To put a fucking wrench in that machine.
The subgenius is the wrench.
That destroys.
The machine.
Or at least fucks it up for a little while.
Until a mechanic can come out.
And figure out why it's not working right.
The conspiracy can only work.
If the people.
Who aren't in the conspiracy.
Who are being downtrodden by the conspiracy.
Choose.
To remain.
In their subservient position.
Of being fucked by the conspiracy.
And most people do.
Most people don't even question it.
But you question it.
And you question it.
Or else you wouldn't be here right now.
You'd be sitting at home.
Watching American Idol.
Jerking off.
Drinking beer.
And eating potato chips.
Getting fat and stupid.
Like every other fucking cow.
Sitting on the couch of America.
But you're not there.
You're not waiting to watch fireworks go off.
And some stupid.
Televised.
Fourth of July.
Bullshit.
Flag waving.
Raw.
America.
Fucking pro.
Program on television.
You chose to be here on the Fourth of July.
You know why you're here on the Fourth of July?
Because this is your independence day.
Not American independence.
Your own independence.
From.
This world.
From this culture.
Which is poisoned and rotten to the fucking core!
This apple.
Has no good seeds in it.
Boys and girls.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It has borne the seed of rotten fruit.
But that's what the subgenius is different.
You see we don't grow from that tree.
We don't fall like the rest of them apples.
We find ourselves on the ground with those other apples, but we're not apples.
We're not from that apple tree.
I don't know what the hell tree we're from, but it ain't a fucking apple tree.
It ain't.
I guess we're an orange tree.
An orange you glad you found Bob.
Praise Bob.
And you wonder why that goes out of tune.
Harmonica players blow.
Uh-huh.
We found a sweet haven of sunshine at last.
The exists are biting above.
They'll scoop us with tentacles luridly cast.
And smoothly they'll sell us some love.
The dead.
The best is all.
I'll live evermore.
What slackness, what rupture is not.
The danger will pass.
We're rescued at last.
The end days are here by and by.
He sees us endangered and sends out his men to pilot our ping bait and so.
The imps have teased.
He says we will repell the
It's start to figure it out.
But when we look ahead.
At the end of thesecurity.
Oh Autoboo!
Equestrian
There is who
I
am
r
world
black
I
did
by and by.
We're discovered
Scrantz, Jalkin, Trollme, through life and in death
Unbob all my money, all speddened
All praising each hour of my last fleeting breath
Repent and slack off to the end
The tempest is o'er, not safe evermore
When darkness but rupture is nigh
Yet pain through his past
We're rescued at last
The end is our nearby and by
The tempest is o'er, not safe evermore
When darkness but rupture is nigh
Yet pain through his past
We're rescued at last
The end is our nearby and by
Uh, yes, dear friends.
It's not from this earth.
Is it?
Uh, no.
It's from the Twilight Zone.
And from, uh, 17X Day.
That was the Mutant Mountain Boys, Dave.
Who also sang, uh, the billowing pipe earlier.
But the, uh, the rant just before that was Reverend Manx Darkpaw.
The French song was Fat Man D of Pittsburgh.
The squeaky rant was Baby Bear, Reverend Baby Bear.
And Andrew the Impaled started the show.
And Dave will destroy this show.
Ha ha.
Man.
Oh, ha ha.
Well, I was so proud of you.
You look pretty well put.
You know, it was basically the last part where you, you know,
the way you said, uh, whatever the hell you said.
And I just want to, I want to offer my sincerest thanks
to all those people who make me.
Thank you.
Of the, uh, what the hell is it?
You, um, the, the people's choice of the people's choice,
I think something like that.
Wasn't it?
No, it was the, it had something to do with Eucalyptus T
or Euclidean logic or thinking or.
Well, in that case, we're all lost.
Yes.
I thought you were going to say we're all lost.
No, no.
Lost is different from lost.
I'm screwed.
I think.
Yeah.
Yes.
It's not quite screwed.
It's just lost.
Well, it curls my eyebrows and it's pushing my teeth out real far.
So, you know,
Well, Dave, are you still, are you still walking funny?
Yeah.
I'm walking funnier than ever and more normal than ever.
It's it bedevils me.
Yeah.
But, you know, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not walking funny.
I don't know why you find that incidental or coincidentally curious.
Well, the last time we saw you in the flesh, we actually saw you walking funny as you walked away into the sunset.
You walked even funnier and funnier.
The more we looked, you were doing like a Charlie Chaplin and then all kinds of funny walks.
Princess, I'm afraid that wasn't an act.
Oh.
Well, doing the Ministry of Silly Walks routine, Monty Python, kind of makes it, you know, doing some exaggerated, like when you said Charlie Chaplin, some exaggerated motions like that.
Or doing Wobble Knees or Uncle Grandpa or the Toyotor or any of those characters, you know, Popeye.
Oh, man, the list is really, really long.
And if you use the same guidelines that you've been given by the Church of the Subdue,
you're going to be a little bit more of a character.
I assume.
I don't know.
Yeah, but a funny walk isn't funny anymore if that's the only way you can walk, is it?
Or is it?
I don't know.
No, no.
What I meant was if I do one of them funny walks, one of them silly walks, it makes it go away.
The actual.
Oh, the actual cripple.
I know what you mean.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you exaggerate emotion?
You have these problems also?
Well, I just assume that that's why you talk the way.
That's why you do also.
The funny talk and the funny walk.
The funny talk and the funny walk kind of cover the not-so-funny reality underlying the problem.
Unfortunately, that's true.
But I thought there would be brighter, more extravagant things to poke tonight than the draggled body of an old fuzzy pig
that's been barbecued.
That's been barbecued too long.
Well, you know, some people probably would say,
well, I want more excitement in the hour of slack and in my own life.
But you see, I'm not sure that excitement is all it's cracked up to be.
I'm not either.
Almost every time I had a real exciting time, it was also a real terrifying and inconvenient time.
Yes.
The yogis claim this is true.
They claim that, you know, aversion and traction.
Being the only force, major forces in the universe tend to cancel each other out.
And that the wise, you know, the sages say that it all pretty much sucks.
Well, that's why I get excited, you know, or something like that, I guess.
In the last few years, I feel like I've been seeking out something closer to boredom than excitement.
Yeah.
I put my music in the background.
That wasn't very exciting.
Oh, suddenly everything's more exciting with this old Twilight Zone music in the background.
Yes.
The third character.
The background music.
The ploy used by most con artists and secret delivery men to get their point across when there's no plot.
No theme.
The Twilight Zone.
Ain't no burping or barbecue pigging allowed, man.
What?
I was just thinking about the last time I had, well, last time I had anything.
You know what I mean?
Metaphysically speaking, I think it's so deep.
What about like a bathroom session, if you had one of those in a while?
Because that could account for a lot.
Bathroom sessions?
Yeah.
If it was the last time you went to the bathroom, maybe that's what's missing from your life.
Is that possible?
Just this.
A few brief moments ago, before calling the show, I relieved myself.
How about you?
Pics or it didn't happen.
JPEGs or it didn't happen.
Always chastising our poor dear Dave for taking things to the bathroom and then you go bringing it up.
Tsk, tsk.
Well, actually, why do you think we play a half hour of canned material at the first half of the show?
So I can go to the bathroom.
Okay.
I know some subgenius shows, they put on half an hour of canned recordings so that they can go out on the porch and smoke pot.
No.
Let's just say it plainly.
Some subgenius radio shows, that's what they do.
Oh, come on.
What do you think they mean when they say rock it away?
You don't do that anymore.
Let's go rock it away.
Jeez.
Duh.
So, like I say, I can't.
It's an industry that's now collapsed into itself.
Well, I don't see what, you know, you're taking, going to the bathroom.
I mean, going to the bathroom regularly is a good thing.
If regularly means going every five seconds.
Yeah, exactly.
But it's, it has somehow replaced going out to the porch to smoke pot every five seconds.
At least during these radio shows.
Back in the day, it was different, of course.
Heck, back in the day, we'd smoke pot right on the air.
But of course, you know, now we have lungs.
They've made us wear lungs inside of our bodies and we can't do any of that stuff.
Just think about it.
Not to mention the cameras.
The ashtrays we used to have in the studio.
Right in the studio, not in the lounge, but right next to all that delicate equipment.
Yeah.
There were ashtrays.
Right.
And coffee cup holders.
Because you do this gig and you're going to go smoke a bunch of cigarettes and drink a lot of coffee.
So you're all loquacious and lugubrious and stuff like that there.
There's not.
Meanwhile, the people in the.
Huh?
Nobody.
There's no, there's no ashtrays around here.
There's not even a coffee machine.
No.
I have to drink all my coffee before the show.
So does that maybe explain the first half hour now?
Do I have to go dribble and leak?
There's no flexible devices allowed in that place either anymore now, thanks to you.
Well, I'll admit we got kind of carried away that one time with the devices.
That was on Chaz's show, though.
That was a long time ago.
You were just too close to the window.
That's all.
You thought you were God.
Or Dobbs.
And perhaps, no, you weren't.
Well, it wasn't that.
I thought that if I was near.
You weren't a God or something.
If I was near the window, I thought nobody would be able to see me.
I could smell the sex devices that we were using in the station.
Sex devices?
Yeah.
What kind of radio show is this?
That was over seven years ago.
So it doesn't matter.
The spirit of discernment has run out, or whatever you call it.
Goodness gracious.
The law of atonement, or the seven-year itch it's over with.
So we can admit that we did it, and nobody can throw us in jail.
But we can't admit that we do it anymore, because we can't do it anymore.
Because they've made us wear these lungs inside.
Why am I laughing?
It's the most horrible thing I've ever heard in my life.
You're talking about the degenerative decay of your multiple bodily tissues,
including not only our puritan bodily excretions.
That's why they put defluoridation in the water.
Right.
You're saying mal-create, miscreate, and stuff.
You're coming up with, man.
Well, that marijuana stuff is bad for your lungs.
It's bad for your brain.
It's bad for the bathtub, the sink, your pets, your car, and your soul.
Now, that's different from frop.
Subgenius is, of course, smoke, habifrop, zippulops, meriphase, alumina, lupina.
It's completely different.
What keeps happening to my background music?
Oh, it keeps ending.
It just fades away.
It's fading down, man.
It fades.
It just fades.
You know, that's why we're all smelling so bad lately.
What, because the music ended?
It has nothing to do with Bob Dobbs.
He's a slackmeister, a B-slackmeister, sure.
Sure enough.
Sure.
Sure he is, man.
He's the abattoir of slack.
An abattoir has two Ts.
Abattoir.
There isn't even a word abattoir.
There's abattoir.
What's abattoir?
No, abattoir.
An abattoir is like a slaughterhouse.
Yes, it's the place where blood goes when it's being drained from a slaughterhouse animal.
Yeah.
And also, they used to drain humans to do experiments on them in the early days of embalming.
Yeah, and so Dobbs is the abattoir of slack and the saint of sales and all that.
Right, right.
So you get a reward after you slash your wrist and put your glimmy in a frying pan or something
like that.
Well, but it's more of a slack abattoir.
You know, it sounds pretty, you know, denominational to me if you understand my lack of cryptography.
Well, the abattoir of Dobbs is where the slack runs out of his products and gathers in this
sort of a basin.
They throw the bones of the slack into the...
What do you call the place where they keep the bones?
The...
Estuary.
Yeah, I...
No, that's a river...
A tributary.
Yeah, yeah, a tributary.
No, I shouldn't have...
Transsexual factory.
Osteo...
Universal...
I don't know.
I think that frop we smoked earlier today was almost as harmful as the marijuana that
we were referring to.
I have no idea what you're...
That's why.
That's what I mean.
That's what I'm saying.
It was either really, really good frop or really bad frop, but that's why none of us understand
or can remember any of these words.
Well, sometimes words were not meant to be remembered.
They're meant to be experienced as an emotional discharge of Bob's food nostril mucuses, which
are delicious and delightful in every, every way you want to make one.
Well, I put a little bit of...
I put a little bit of yellow rice and some beans on top of that.
Now you're talking some trash talk.
Are you talking about that mucus soup?
Maybe like a little ragu bolognese, you know, like kind of a meat sauce with a...
I'm sorry.
You're talking about the...
I like the meat sauce part.
The Dobbs mucus.
Let's go back to the meat sauce.
Mucus soup.
Let's stay away from anything mucus.
What do you think was in that soup that made it so good?
That big pot of soup I made yesterday?
Not mucus.
The Dobbs runoff.
You know, when he leaves the room, there's always that...
Well, I will not be eating any more of your foods.
Just so you know, Reverend Stang, I'm done.
You'll have to eat your own foods now.
Well, that means you're going to have to go back to cooking for me.
Because when I'm cooking for you, I'm using...
You know how to cook canned chili.
And you expect gourmet whey every night when you come home from staying at home.
Yeah.
I believe it.
Yeah, I do.
And she's supposed to be wearing one of them French...
Made uniforms and all that stuff like that.
I remember all the stuff.
She won't do that anymore.
The feminists got to her.
Now she doesn't wear anything when she's cooking.
Just an apron.
And there's a little cloud over your head.
It's not a bad or a good cloud.
It's just a cloud.
It's a formation of ice crystals and pure water.
Clowns are made of ice crystals and pure water?
I don't know.
I learned a word for the fear of clowns.
But I then lost it.
It's like chlorophobia or something like that.
Yeah.
And it is real.
It's a common fear, the fear of clowns.
Well, I just saw a poster of a clown that was appearing at an event that really...
You know, I poo-poo all of that stuff about clowns.
I thought that was so nice.
You know, their lack of humor and their...
Their feelings of terror that they instill in some people.
And yet, at the same time, this guy was trying to make me depressed, man.
Same with him.
What, a clown was trying to make you depressed?
You're lucky he wasn't trying to kill you.
I don't know what kind of laughs he could get.
He looked like his father beat him up a real lot when he was maybe a little boy or something like that.
Clowns are the saddest.
And then drank and stuff like that.
They're the saddest people in the whole world, clowns.
Oh, man.
It was serious.
That's why they're so fiendish.
I'm not going to let myself laugh about who I am.
I refuse.
I would not go in there.
Something like that.
I don't know.
The fear of clowns has existed much, much longer than insane clown posse.
Well...
More than what?
I have a fear of being a clown.
I'm not afraid of other people who are clowns.
I'm afraid of...
I have...
Oh, yeah.
I have been...
I have been being a clownophobia.
Oh, yeah.
I was traumatized by...
Really?
You think your job can be bad, Dave?
You were abused, right?
You were abused by a circus clown.
At one point, the only job I could get was as a mime delivering balloons to parties and dying people.
Yeah, I was Snoopy one time in front of a mall that was opening.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, the sad thing about me running around as a mime...
I had to wear this.
I had to wear this white face makeup, right?
Like mimes do.
I was instructed not to ever speak on my deliveries.
And I wore a little tuxedo and stuff.
But one afternoon, I and my balloons got into an elevator and the doors closed.
And I turned around and there was a mom holding her little kid who instantly went into terrible hysterics.
This kid was so panic stricken at the hideous white faced man that it...
And I...
And it was in an elevator.
And we couldn't get out.
I couldn't just open the door.
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
And leave.
You know, we had to wait until the door opened.
So I was forced to sit in here scaring this child to death, dressed as a clown.
Later that day, my car broke down outside the Salvation Army in Dallas, Texas on that hot, sunny day.
And I had to get out of my car, go into the Salvation Army, holding my balloons and call the office and the tow truck.
And so forth.
And as I left, all these homeless people, by lining the hallways, were going,
Can I have a balloon?
Just one balloon?
You're a clown.
Won't you give me just one balloon?
But you know, somebody had paid 50 bucks to have an idiot deliver 10 balloons to the dying lady in the hospital up the hill.
Oh, man.
And sure enough, I had to trudge up the hill to the hospital.
To get rid of the balloons and finish my job.
And there was another homeless man camped in a box near the road.
And he didn't like this white-faced person walking by his homeless encampment.
And he came out and yelled incoherently at me.
And since I was a mime, all I could do was turn around and yell silently at him.
And that scared him back into his cardboard box.
Right.
That was my...
That was my life as a clown.
And by the way, it paid minimum wage.
It was about two bucks an hour.
And it was a rip-off job.
Because one of those jobs where you have to drive your own car and pay for the gas and repairs.
And you only get 15 bucks a delivery.
And you only get one delivery a day.
Yeah.
So it's a sucker job.
Well, Stang, you know, according to common neocon logic,
had you the acrimony and the fastidious testicles to endeavor yourself to working 24 hours a day without resting at any point in time during that 24 hours,
you could be as rich as, name a billionaire.
Lunch and Cowboy Day.
Ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I don't...
I think I might be some kind of political lunatic lately.
You might be in a political lunatic?
What?
Not the asylum itself, but kind of like the scabbard of inequity, if you might.
If you're, you know...
The scabbard of inequity?
Metaphorically implying some kind of, you know, some kind of...
No, I don't know.
No, I feel like that, you know, we're like, remember...
What's his name?
McNee or...
No.
What's his name in Prisoner?
Patrick McGee.
Prisoner number seven?
Yeah.
Yeah, number seven.
I am number...
Who is number one?
You are number six.
I'm not a number.
I'm a Freeman.
A Fremen.
Fremen.
You're a human being and you live on donuts, you know?
No, I'm a Fremen and I live on Dune, the desert planet.
I'm a Mentat Fremen.
I'm a Fremen Jedi Vulcan.
You may call me...
You may call me Mr. Smarty Pants.
Smarty Pants?
I will call you Monsieur Smarty Pants just to further the stupidity of your Smarty Pants.
What do you think about that then?
Sometimes.
Eh?
Oh, he's a Frenchman now.
I see.
A wee-wee.
A wee-wee, Monsieur.
Don't poo-poo his wee-wee.
I won't poo-poo his wee-wee.
Right.
Yeah, Mr. Smarty Diapers or something.
Do you have any grey poo-poo?
Boy, this show sometimes just dives right off the edge into the garbage can.
Sometimes?
Not all the time.
It was good the first half.
Remember all the canned stuff recorded at 17X Day?
All those people with their carefully written out rants and stuff?
As if we weren't reading a script right now.
Right.
Really?
Well, I lost two pages in the process and I had to read the script.
I had to write the script and stuff upside down thanks to my machine.
Who can tell the difference, though?
That's the marvelous thing about the sub-genius radio ministry.
Hour of Slur.
That's the Rudy Schwartz project in the background.
They're projecting.
I thought I was behind there somewhere.
Yep.
I'm no Rudy Schwartz for one reason.
What he was?
I know Rudy Schwartz back then.
I know him.
I appreciate his work very much.
I hate to sound so normal and maudlin and human and, you know.
Jethro Tull was a member of his band.
Rudy Schwartz and his guitar player, Jethro Tull, used to jam a lot.
He had a guitar player named Jethro Tull?
Well, Rudy Schwartz is like Jethro Tull.
It's the name of the band, and there's not really a person involved by that name.
A lot of people probably didn't know that.
No, after 25,000 years, I did not know that Rudy was not a real duty.
No, Rudy is like Ivan Stang or Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Or Princess Weed.
Yeah, they're just made-up characters.
Part of the aggregate spew.
They're just weird characters created by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs created these characters.
And, uh...
I understand Marvel just settled out of court
so they can finally do the subgenius movie without ever paying any of the creators.
Really?
Actually, I read that Marvel just settled with the Jack Kirby estate
after all these decades.
Jack Kirby was the guy who actually created half of those superhero characters
that are making billions for Disney now.
So you can imagine the Jack Kirby estate.
The Jack Kirby estate would want a tiny cut.
They don't want to end up like the estate of the guys who created Superman.
Or Bob Kane or Jim Yard.
Well, even worse than Jimi Hendrix's bandmates.
Who didn't get anything.
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of bands, Dave, do you remember a musician named Tom Lehrer?
Yes, of course.
Of course.
Eric's probably played Tom Lehrer records, right?
Yes, he was a satirical aardvark for the left-wing superiorities.
Well, he was a Harvard math professor who also...
Oh, I thought...
...had a gig on the side doing satire original songs.
Long before Eric Idle and Monty Python and those guys were doing their funny songs,
Tom Lehrer was doing funny songs.
And the reason I mention this...
...is because...
Because there was a Tom Lehrer song performed at 17X Day.
Did you do it in the first half hour?
No, I'm going to play it in the last five minutes, which are coming up in about one minute.
And that's why I mentioned that.
Reverend Andrew the Impaled suddenly launched into the song Masochism Tango.
He wasn't on his own.
I was thinking of it.
He was not on his own cognizance or his own keyboard.
That's what it is.
He had to borrow somebody else's keyboard.
So it's kind of sounds strangely broken and funny.
But I'm going to play that in about one minute.
Hasn't our time together flown ever so quickly?
It always does.
Well, now, sometimes it crawls interminably.
And I keep looking at my watch going, oh, my God, it's owing.
Only 30 seconds have passed.
That seemed like three hours.
When is this god awful show going to be over?
That's what the listeners are all saying right now.
No, they're not.
Yeah, especially if you're the wrong monastery.
You know, who can tell it's going to show up at your doorstep?
Well, Dave, you know what show this is.
The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And you know what number it is.
Number 1485.
Whoa.
We're coming up on 1500.
Boy, that's prestigious.
That's grandiose and humorless.
It's get a life is what it is.
I can't.
How many weeks?
One thousand four hundred and eighty five of subgenius.com,
which is where you can find out about all the stuff.
It's a proud.
Buy that by 52.
And it's 300 weeks.
Or no, 300 days of pure show.
Of 300 days, a whole year.
There's crazy people out there who just listen to one show after another.
Oh, man.
That's all they can do.
They were like real devoted listeners out there.
What we've done to their brains.
The ones I feel sorry for are the ones in Germany.
In Germany?
Yeah, because they can't stop listening.
Anyway, I'm going to go ahead.
And play this.
That's kind of our team.
Yeah.
I'll leave you on, Dave, so that you can hear the masochism tango.
As performed by the great Andrew the Impaled.
I ache for the touch of your lips, dear.
But much more for the touch of your whips, dear.
You can raise welts like nobody else.
As we dance to the melody.
Masochism tango.
May our love be a flame, not an ember.
Say it's me that you want to dismember.
Blacken my eyes.
Set fire to my tie.
As we dance to the masochism tango.
Bash in my brain.
And make me scream in pain.
And kill me once again.
And say we'll never part.
You know too well.
I'm underneath your spell.
So darling, if you smell something burning, it's my heart.
Your heart's burning.
It's hot as stone or mahogany.
That's why I'm in such exquisite agony.
My soul is a fire.
It's aflame with desire.
Which is why I perspire when we tango.
You caught my nose.
In your left castanet.
Love.
I can feel the pain yet.
Every time I hear drums.
And I envy the rose.
That you held in your teeth.
Love.
With the thorns underneath.
Sticking into your gums.
Your eyes cast a spell that bewitches.
The last time I needed twenty stitches.
To sew up the gash.
You made with your lash.
As we dance to the masochism tango.
Bash in my brain.
And make me scream in pain.
And kill me once again.
And say we'll never part.
You will never part.
You know too well.
You're underneath my spell.
So darling if you smell something burning.
It's my heart.
And take your cigarette from its holder.
See I know I'm in the right place.
And burn your initials in my shoulder.
Fracture my spine.
And swear that you're mine.
As we dance to the masochism tango.
Alright.
Andrew the Impaled.
And now Six Fisted Tales of Connie.
I will.
I am.
I have been.
Subgenius.
I will.
I am.
I have been.
Subgenius.
I will.
I am.
I have been.
Subgenius.
I will have.
I have had.
I do have.
Slack.
I will.
I am.
I have.
Fought the conspiracy.
I will.
I have.
I am.
Fighting today.
I will.
I have.
I am.
Subgenius.
You are.
You have been.
You will be.
I can't do it.
Subgenius.
Yeah!
Hey Sun T.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Good idea Dobbs.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish harkaback flattin' wharton fill a bucket burton.
Purkaluma burton duckin' buster night.
Oh!
Beep.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show.
but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.
P.O. Box.
1-8-0.
1-8-1.
4-1-7.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
4-4-1-1-8.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Get lucky!
If
a
September
of
Follow us on Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram and find out where you're going to watch a weekly show.
Callup.com and sit outside and catch guys.
This is anicaenedallana.com.
westlake.com or smileay.com.
It's a comedy, because when you blowjobs meet up with houses.