Tell St. Peter at the Golden Gate that you hate to make him wait, but you just gotta have another
Subgenius Hour of Slack!
What?
Uh, yes, dear friends, we're working on the Subgenius Online History class at maybelogic.net,
and therefore this Hour of Slack number 1,199 will actually be a rerun of Hour of Slack number 569,
which is actually a rerun of the ESO Swamp Radio Show from February 27th, 1997.
What are you?
Nobody.
Are you blind?
What are you?
What manner of beast is that?
What the hell are you?
What are you?
Every man and woman is a star.
And that's why Dave's head is a glowing gasp.
This bag of flaming hydrogen.
So it was read, so it was written.
All of their heads were glowing bags of hydrogen.
And they walked around town wearing their bags.
And one little day, one little man said,
Your head is much bigger than mine.
You must have a much bigger bag.
Everybody is a star.
And yes, that man was the mayor of the town.
He had a great yellow giant for a head.
And unfortunately,
Dave, the village idiot, had what is known as a dwarf star for a head.
In fact, it had collapsed so suddenly and compacted so tremendously,
that it, although it had not quite formed a black hole,
the density of the head of Dave,
you know, every man and woman is a star.
Dave was a dwarf star.
Well, one square, oh,
a millimeter or so of the interior of Dave's head
was of such a dense molecular,
a densely packed molecular structure
that that tiny, tiny fragment would be heavy enough on our planet
that if you dropped it, it would bore its way all the way to the center of the earth.
This is why Dave was not allowed in most towns.
His head being altogether heavier than the most,
his head being a little bit more than the size of the nearby planets,
his presence tended to cause disruptions in the orbits of other inhabited star systems,
other planets that might have even cities and old civilizations that had lasted for thousands of years.
Merely the gravitational waves caused by the thickness of Dave's skull
would destroy and wipe out these entire civilizations.
Oh, man.
And that's why when Dave would beg for a dollar for a bottle of beer,
most people in town would go ahead and give him the dollar.
Hey man, spare change, buddy?
What the hell are you?
Because every time he got a headache, there was a...
Oh, man, everybody's got some kind of personal deformity.
So my bag's a little bigger than yours, you know?
And what's the difference between helium and hydrogen?
My fucking corpus callosum, excuse my language.
Oh, my God, it's not even 12 o'clock.
The townsfolk and the other planets,
civilized galactic federations and so forth,
had to pretty much put up with Dave
because whenever he got a headache, it would cause earthquakes in their capital city.
Oh, my tylenol's doing nothing.
This X-Axepin's doing nothing.
This Aspen's just doing nothing.
This old Indian herbal extract ain't doing nothing, man.
I feel like my skull is spinning.
I feel like the weight of the universe is expanding out through my very, very, very, very...
Don't even look at me.
Did you ever feel that way, Fran?
Did you ever feel like the...
The problems of the world were weighing down on you so much
that your head was self-collapsing into dwarf star density?
Have you ever felt that way?
Well, if you haven't, then you're probably not a subgenius.
It's so dense in here.
You lucky bastard.
It's just like the yolk of an egg.
Or she-bastard. What did I forget?
You can't say she-bastard.
She-bastard.
It's like a little psychic yellow of an egg in here.
It keeps me warm. It keeps me nurtured.
And that's all I need. I am a star.
See, everybody's brain...
Yes.
I don't need those people. I don't need to drink Tylenol.
I don't need to snort that stuff.
I'm different than that. I'm going here. I'm back.
We've taken good care to raise you up here, Dave.
Oh, by the way, Dave, Dave, there's something we needed to...
It's a pair of shoes.
Dave, there's something... I hate to interrupt your...
You.
Your fun little monologue there, but...
You've heard about cloning and so forth and the replaceable body parts and...
Well, you actually, Dave, are the clone of a master, Dave,
who is a very rich, powerful man who happens to have just destroyed his liver through hard drink
and it's time for his replacement liver.
And yes, you were cloned from him and have been raised as a poor, pathetic street...
Why, no.
Just kept alive. You and several other clones.
Several of the others have already been used for other parts.
Dave, I'm afraid your life is...
The goal of your life has come around.
It's time for you to give up that which you were bred for, which in this case is your liver.
Wait a minute.
Isn't cloning wonderful?
Wait a second.
Too bad nobody cloned you, eh, Dave?
Wait a minute.
You love the rich Dave. He looks just like you.
And runs General Motors now, I think.
What? Now, wait a minute.
I don't know whether I'm having a psychic echo spasm or if all I have is some kind of coronal license here.
I'm so on the corner and I'm panhandling and I see your voice that say I'm cloned from somebody else who's rich and powerful.
And come on out from behind there.
My little leg yoke protects me.
My little helium hydrogen exchange key.
How could it break into here?
Hey, where'd it go?
Hey, little voice. Little garbage can.
Come back here.
Man, nobody around here.
Yoo-hoo.
Maybe I was just sucking a weird dream or something.
I gotta stop doing them methamphetamines.
I'm just ripping my brain apart.
I gotta stop snorting gasoline.
I gotta stop licking the bottoms of these allspice.
I gotta stop shaking up my nail clippings and my underchees and re-spooking them.
I gotta do something, man.
Maybe it's a self-concussive realization.
Maybe it wasn't a little voice.
Maybe I am cloned from some rich and powerful person.
I could take over the church of the subgenius, man.
And make a lucrative mullah.
Yeah, I'll be standing on top of everything.
I could topple a little paddy giant.
And a little tyrant.
And a little two-boots wherever I'm staying.
It's weird how these little voices in my head always sound like him.
Well, gentlemen, as you can see by our subject, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
the syringe implantable transponder works beautifully.
He seems to think that there are voices in his head.
In this case, my voice was used, of course, as the project chief.
But it is amazing, is it not, gentlemen,
that our General Electric tiny microchip,
the size of a grain of rice placed underneath his skin,
injected with a syringe,
a vaccination in his childhood,
has allowed us to dictate as voices in his head his entire life.
You know, there's no difference in principle, gentlemen,
between being forced to carry a microchip in your plastic card in your wallet
or the little pellet that we put in Dave's teeth.
The principle that Big Sister has the right to track you is inherent in both.
And the only difference is a layer of skin.
Or in Dave's case, a skull.
A very, very thick layer of bony carapace.
Uh, Doctor...
Let's turn the voices back on.
Yes, yes.
I've noticed in the literature...
Yes, Doctor Bronner.
I've read all of your papers,
and I am quite convinced that what you have done to this man is a remarkable disservice.
I see in here a picture, a perfect example of a man whose personality,
which was not in a good shape to begin with,
has been totally destroyed.
But what, you expect us...
Immersed in your faulty world religion.
You expect us to experiment on animals?
Just a minute, Doctor, I...
Poor innocent animals? Why not use these...
I agree.
Dave volunteered for this thing. We're poor.
I see nowhere in the transcript you have given me an example of Dave ever giving his permission,
written or otherwise, for you to conduct this experiment on him.
It seems totally remarkable to me how a man of your stature could conduct such an experiment
and receive grants and so much money to do it.
Well, Doctor...
Doctor Bronner, I think you've heard the expression,
if you're going to make an omelette,
you have to break a few eggs.
Uh, I don't see...
I mean, to a certain extent, this Dave, lonesome cowboy Dave character,
is little more than a human egg, an omelette,
so to speak, bubbling on the hot sidewalk of life.
How could you call a human being a fellow human being?
He's not a human being.
He's a subgenius.
I'm sorry, but your rules don't apply to us.
Doctor Stein, I agree with your work.
Can I say one word?
Yes, Doctor.
I appreciate what you have been doing the last few years,
especially, I mean, Mark, with your work with lonesome cowboy Dave
and other people, Einstein, Secret Orchestra,
they take the whole Cleveland project.
I would like to know if you can help me,
find a possible backup grant for...
I have a similar project, a hot shoe project.
I would like to do a similar size city in southern Japan.
Oh, well, I'll tell you the investment opportunities,
if you will connect...
Of course, I assume there's fetus research in your country?
Probably considerable amount of fetus organ trade going on there?
Yes, I have no problem with human donor.
Have you also considered genetic cloning research,
cloning research for...
Well, that's another thing.
Doctor Bronner there was quite out of line complaining about
a so-called human being, even if Dave were a human being.
This is a clone of a human being.
The original Dave, the Master Dave, sitting over here to my right.
Yes, that's a very nice tie you have there, Captain Dave.
Thanks for having me.
The Master Dave there, obviously,
was born with the same rights according to human being or a subtenuous.
His clone, however, I mean, he's a human being,
how can one person have more than one set of rights?
So, therefore, the clone, being more or less the same person,
is going to have to find his own set of rights.
Ivan, do you mind if I get a little personal postulation in here?
I want to show a little of my own perspective,
after all, being the clone donor.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is not a human being in the same way
you or I would call, say perhaps, the Reverend Hare or Dr. Sagamoto a human being.
He's an experiment conducted by the church
to re-incur the reprogramming of thousands more people
and to stop this X-Day thing that we've all been talking about.
That's all I have to say about it.
Dr. Broder can complain all he wants,
but the process has been set in motion.
Dave is contagious everywhere he goes in the city of Cleveland.
We're going to see the same progress in the disease,
the virus, if you want to call it a disease.
We like to think of it as a new...
Oh, just some...
We're adding some artistic details to the fabric of human reality.
That's all.
We're just doing a little window dressing,
improving on God's handiwork.
Why not?
God gave us that right, did he not?
He made us as unto gods.
Every man and woman is a star, I believe.
Our secret leader, Aleister Crowley Hubbard, once said...
I remember us sitting there, Parsons at that nudist...
Oh, yes, yes, sir.
Dr. Stefano Grappelli of the Institute of Psychic Research in Rome.
I was wondering if you found any sort of repercussion
with the Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
perhaps any psychic example of violence or trouble with police
or such psychological...
There was...
Yes, yes, I'm glad that you asked that question.
There was an extremely unusual side effect.
The treatment by which whenever Dave would sneeze,
plates, for instance, in the kitchen would fly across the room,
jump off the shelves and smash against the opposite wall.
One time we were in the front office
and the files flew out of the file cabinet drawers every time Dave sneezed.
Of course, we had to put him down whenever he was around
any kind of expensive equipment.
Out on the street, most people hardly noticed there's so much violence,
mugging down there on the levels.
The level where he...
where the experiments are usually conducted.
Petri dish one, you know, the sidewalk.
I would like to ask a question also of you.
I am from the Institute of Moscow.
I won't need to mention the name of the Institute.
I'm familiar with the parapsychological research I've been doing.
Oh, yes, comrade.
I would like to say that after the...
the re-programming will be a whole different situation in the former Soviet Union
and the Commonwealth of all of the states will be involved in...
and after what you have said,
re-programming, making people more malleable, pliable,
we'll find have to a different problem.
Is there some way we can use your research
and perhaps make the whole of former Soviet Union similar in the...
Well, comrade, as you know, Dobbs Co. is marketing the, as we call it,
the electronic leash of these implantable biochips
to be any corporate or governmental entity.
We'd happily assist.
Of course, our microchips do have the Dobbs trademark built in,
so that although they...
the subject's allegiance will be up to the choice of the corporation or governmental entity,
nevertheless, as you can certainly understand,
it's sort of like the Coca-Cola company is going to sell Coke in Russia.
That's fine, but they're going to have their logo on it.
Well, your people will be mind controlled according to your plans.
However, they will respond to the smiling face image of Bob.
That, comrade, that would be very... that is fine with us.
Thank you very much for answering this one.
And as we said, these computer chips will link the individual...
up to a vast computer database,
so that we can, in fact, follow the subject
and follow their spending, their voting habits,
pretty much their sexual habits up to a point.
We can, in fact, dictate their sexual habits
through the voice in the head technique.
We have had some subjects,
they get their ideas from the movies or comic books or something,
they pull all their teeth out,
so as they think that this will silence them,
we can use the silent radio in their head, of course,
that does affect the resonance,
and we have to increase the amplification
when they pull out all of their teeth,
but it's rather pointless to tell the truth.
It's sad.
I've noticed Dave down there is bleeding at the mouth,
the one down on the sidewalk,
not the one here in the boardroom, certainly.
I don't think we're getting enough...
Can you enhance this picture somehow
so we can all see it a little better
and bring up the volume somehow a little bit?
Yeah, zoom in on screen three there, Weldon.
If you pull in close, now you'll see
Dave yanked all his teeth out with those pliers
and has thrown them down in the gutter
where our servo robots have retrieved them
for the master Dave here in case he ever needs a new pole.
I don't know what I'm doing to myself.
Man, the other day I started beating myself in the face
with a hammer for no apparent reason.
And here I am pulling out a moment.
Dave, Dave, we're back.
It didn't do you any good.
You pulled your teeth out for nothing, Dave.
You're an idiot, Dave.
You didn't love Bob enough, Dave.
Listen to this, you guys.
He'll believe anything.
Dave, you sinned.
You pulled out all your teeth for nothing.
That looked stupid as well as I thought it was stupid.
I ain't never gonna find me a day like this.
I'm gonna make a new wife.
Bob will be my wife.
But don't cry, Dave.
Bob has a new job for you.
He has a new bride for you, Dave.
Bob has brought you a new bride.
See that goat over there in that pen?
That she-goat over in that pen, that's your new wife, Dave.
That's Hogan's goat.
You are the husband of Hogan's she-goat.
Last night you told me that was some kind of wife.
That weird goat they was gonna clone.
And then you said it was the goat that was using to catch nerve gas.
And now you're telling me it's my wife?
I thought it was gonna get me a nice six foot or seven yeti woman.
Let's go, no, I'm so confused.
Do you have a problem with the goat, Dave?
Would you rather us pick you another wife?
How about this giant, this gigantic eyebrow mantis?
An eyebrow mantis?
Man, I can't see it in my mind's left eye stroke.
The eyebrow mantis slide into his retina.
There, okay, he should be seeing the, uh, the giant eyebrow mantis.
What the hell is that thing?
Turn the erection knob up to ten.
He's terrified of the mantis and at the same time he's sexually aroused.
Oh my god, get that thing away from me.
This always fuses.
This always fuses the daylight challenge.
I'll bet you're a Leo.
I'll get away, get away from me.
Oh my god, hey, uh, hey.
And so you see, gentlemen, not only is the experiment a...
Oh, get away, get away.
As you can see, gentlemen, the experiment is not only a success but a lot of fun for we researchers.
You can pull the strings of the subject as if he were a little puppet dancing down there on that hot sidewalk in the inner city,
surrounded by the broken beer bottles and the other bums and losers.
While we up here in our skyscraper sitting at our computer keyboards may make him jerk and twitch our own little pathetic marionette, isn't he?
And so he suspects, of course, in fact he knows perfectly well his state, station, and life.
That's what religion is for, boys.
Praise Bob, eh?
Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
And thank you for the excellent demonstration and quite an illuminating slideshow it was.
Now, what I think...
Will you take credit cards?
Well, I think that's what we're all asking right now.
What will the next project be and how much do you need?
All I need is to fill the receptor holes, my friend.
Oh, you ask me what I need.
I just need to fill those receptor holes.
They used to be so full, those holes in my brain.
They had just the perfect molecule fit right into that little locked place.
Now...
The brain holes.
The brain holes are empty.
The brain holes are empty tonight.
The brain's gonna have to make its own molecule.
The moon is shining.
My eyes are bright but...
The brain holes.
The molecule is gone.
You look pretty sharp.
You look pretty cute.
But you ain't going nowhere in that brain hole.
Soon you're gonna...
My best.
You say you look so cute in that brand new suit.
You think you got some place to go.
You ain't going nowhere, so just sit down in the chair and let Bob Dobbs tell you the truth.
Bob Dobbs...
The truth.
I told you when you were 10, and I told you when you were 12,
and I told you as you were coming on.
When you look, scourge, my son, think of that glimmering pipe.
So my work will be done.
I'm leaving soon, I am.
There is a great mesh in your brain.
And this mesh is composed of tiny holes, and these holes have a certain shape.
Those are receptor holes, and they're responsible for your sense of self and well-being and pleasure.
There's a certain shape of a molecule.
That'll fall into those receptor holes and make you feel real good.
And that shape is a shape, oddly enough, of what looks to us just like a common pipe.
Like a Dr. Grabow pipe.
If you can find some way to get tiny pipe-shaped molecules to fill those receptor holes
inside that vacant mesh in your head,
well, you'll probably feel so much better that you'll be able to do better on the job,
get a better job, become like a great stock whiz or something,
and get rich overnight on some great idea, perfect vision.
So, of course, at this point you're asking,
Hey man, where can I get some of them pipe-shaped molecules?
Is it like a pill, or is it something you smoke?
Hey Bernice, I just wanted to try this.
Look what I got at the pharmacological lab.
What is it? What is it?
Well, it's not a pill, and it's not a pipe.
You place it in your third eye.
It's the virtual, hard noise trial of the, the, the, the...
I'm gonna try it. Let's make a few.
It's the Emperor's new pipe.
And turn on that radio.
You just, here.
Let me try that.
You see this thing that I'm holding in my hand?
It's real, King.
Yeah.
There's nothing really in my hand, but it's a virtual pipe.
There is no virtual in that pipe.
Hey man, let's all, like, smoke some of what's in this pipe in my hand.
Oh yeah, yeah man, I see that pipe in your hand.
Yeah, let me have some of that virtual...
Oh, whoa!
Whoa!
I tried marijuana one time, and I tried LSD, and I tried bananas mixed with Coca-Cola and aspirin, but...
Man, and Jimson weed and NyQuil, but...
Whoa, this virtual pipe.
Oh man, I am going inside.
Oh, far in.
The pipe is feeling real, man. The pipe is feeling real. It's pointing.
I'm like caved in.
I'm caved in, man. I'm caved in.
The pipe is so deep, I'm, I'm like a... I am speed-lunkin', dude.
Help, help.
I am like in the magma.
Help. Oh, help, sir.
Magma city!
Oh, sir, my lungs are crushed.
Man, I feel that pressure.
No, no, the magma of the Pipe Cathedral has...
Whoa. I am so low.
...the point is...
I think... Man, I wonder, maybe I'm too low. Maybe I'm getting too deep.
...the line...
The line...
Am I ever gonna come up?
Hey, man, don't come up too fast. Your hand will explode.
You'll get the...
...bens.
...idea.
Whoa.
Get down on your knees.
Wow, these anti-drugs are so much better than those cheap conspiracy street drugs.
I don't want to get high anymore. Ever since I learned the word of Bob, I've been ready not only to come back down to Earth,
but to go below the sidewalk, below the sewers, below the upper crust, below the lower crust, down all the way.
Yeah, I've learned how to go down since I gave up those getting high kind of drugs. Bob's dragging me all the way down.
Oh, the pressure's getting... getting...
...louder.
It's getting really, really hot down here.
You know when Bob's taking me high.
You know when I'm...
I'm digging it. It's really hot.
What are these... these flames?
Somehow they're not consuming my flesh, but yet they're burning.
Fleshier, fleshier...
Whoa. Wow, this is...
...skin...
These Bob pills and this virtual Bob pipe, this stuff's really intense.
...illuminate...
I'm like having a before-death experience.
I'm having an... an out-of-inside-planet experience.
Man, I think I am too... too low. I... I probably need to come back up.
Hey, man, is there anything I can take to counteract this non-drug that I didn't take?
Hey, hey, hey, ref. What are you doing here, man? Crouched on the floor.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Isn't this the coolest club you ever been in? Oh, man, I already had three multigasers, and I don't even know what the hell that is.
Yeah, this stuff's great.
Yeah, whatever it is.
It's free, too.
Yeah, where'd he get it?
Oh, free.
From Bob?
Bob?
Well, I mean, it's free once you join up, you know.
Well, this guy charged me 15 bucks for one hit. He tell me it's free once I joined up?
Jeez, man.
Well, you're joined up. Now, here, take...
So I'm coming joined up.
...the pipe in my hand, my little...
There's not really a pipe in his hand.
Yeah.
But they believe there is a pipe in his hand.
Oh, I see it, man.
See the pipe? Here, take my pipe, Dave.
Okay, man.
And have a big hit of what's in that pipe.
Okay.
There is no pipe, and there is nothing in the pipe.
But the placebo effect is so much more powerful than any real drug that the subgenius victim
is now becoming so low, so in there...
Oh, wow.
...that it is as if he is looking up from eight feet underground.
I feel like they're made of mush.
300 pounds of mush.
He feels like he's laying at the bottom of a hole.
One.
Two.
Eight.
Ten.
100.
0.
1.
Well, he actually seems to be
vivying up money with Reverend Stang.
Come on, show money.
Look.
Well, Michelle is crying.
I don't want to die.
Oh, I think it's because she has hay fever.
I just realized...
Look, they're all laughing.
This is all a figment of my mind.
Yeah, I didn't smoke no corn silk.
I was back in the goose bar,
and I had me hit on that pipe.
Everybody got it looked like Stangy went.
If I just use my psychic abilities
and concentrate my yogic powers,
which was gifted me by Bob Dobbs,
down in my lowest lower chakra,
way down...
Oh, no, I can't do that.
The slack will be with you, Dave.
Oh, damn.
I'm never going to make it now.
Feel the slack, Dave.
Close your eyes.
Turn off the autopilot.
Come on, boy.
Feel the slack.
I'm seeing...
I'm seeing crystals.
Pulse floating by.
Just go with your instincts, Dave.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to go into the white light now.
I just want to take a hit off that pipe,
and I'm going to...
Off the meat shackles.
Dave, baby.
Welcome.
Shuck the body like an old shoe.
Welcome to the other side.
Remember me?
Benny.
Benny Gordon back in New York.
I was the guy who stole your shoes
and hid them in the garbage can.
Then you struck me in the face.
Remember?
Yeah, I died later.
No thanks to you.
Yeah.
Kind of screwed me up inside.
When they let me in Bellevue,
they said I'd never be the same.
I starved to death.
I thought about you when I died.
This don't look like the green garbage coming out.
It kind of looks blood red.
Hello, Dave.
I'm sure you don't remember me.
I was...
I was originally a tiny puppy
that you tortured when you were six years old.
Remember me now?
Now I am Dog Demon,
the bearer of vengeance
for all torturers of tiny puppies.
And meet my friend,
the legless grasshopper.
We've all come to get...
to tell you that we remember
all the things you did
in life.
I don't think this is going to be very pleasant.
If I'm supposed to recount
all my incidences,
so far I've only had three incidences.
It's all bad.
I wonder what's next.
Who's that weird-looking woman?
Grandma?
I've never done nothing to you, really.
I'm sorry about the stove.
It's too late for forgiveness now, Dave.
Oh, Mom, come on.
It's too late now.
It's much too late.
She's on this figure
and burns just the way I left her
when I ran out of the house.
Dave, remember your habit
of sticking chewing gum
under theater seats?
Yes.
I am a soul who once reached
under the seat and touched
your germ-ridden gum.
Later to die of a cold.
I'm sorry, bro.
You know, I've tried to keep myself clean
and have good personal attributes
like that and stuff,
but, you know, those things are so bourgeois.
Hey, Dave, remember me, Butch?
Yeah, Butch.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I bet you're sorry now, Dave.
Get away.
I didn't mean nothing.
Maybe you shouldn't have stuck up behind me
and pulled that little trick on me
that one time, Dave.
You know my personality, man.
Push me in front of that car, Dave.
Everybody in school knew I was a joker.
Everybody thought that I just fell
in front of that car, Dave.
Were you jealous just because
I was bigger and tougher
and got all the girls
and got decent grades
and had friends and had parents
and had money and had a life?
Were you jealous, Dave?
What, you think you can wait?
Yes. Yes.
I hated you all.
I hated that puppy for having hair.
I hated grandma for having food
and I hated you for having a car
and girlfriend.
In fact,
I still hate you
and that's why I don't mind being here.
Dave, meet everyone of whom
you have ever been jealous.
They are here to gloat
at your misfortune.
Thousands and thousands of people
gloating, gloating
at your total humiliation
here in the endless flames
of, yes, let's say, in hell, Dave.
You're dead and you're in hell.
See your faces
and your point fingers at me.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
And here are snapshots
and tape recordings
of every stupid or humiliating thing
you've ever done.
Here, the files of every callous
and thoughtless thing
you've ever said or done.
Oh, man, they're flying by so fast.
Here, every betrayal.
Here, every lie.
Here, every time you've masturbated
in an impure manner.
Oh, man, my eyes.
I'm going blind.
You didn't know we had such good cameras,
did you, in all those...
You're all...
filling station restrooms, eh, Dave?
All right.
I don't know, but...
Here, the endless file
of the times you picked your nose.
Here, the file
of the times you wet your bed.
Here, the files
of the times you didn't wash behind your ears.
Everything, everything in your entire life
has been reconstructed
and you're going to have to relive
every single moment of it
over and over and over again
inside this little black box
underground because you're...
You smoked the corn silk
and didn't do what your parents said.
Man.
Oh, I'm not going to fit in there, you guys.
And of course, all that masturbating and cruelty.
I don't know how long I can do it.
I'm older now.
My arms might get tired.
But if I just go back in the box
and when I reappear,
I'll be back in the goo-goo bar
talking to Stangy
and smoking on the bike, please.
So, what say, what say, brothers?
Shall we give him another chance?
Shall we give Dave...
Dave a chance to live his life again?
Do you think he's learned his lesson?
Oh, please, good sirs and dames.
Let's flip a coin
and see whether he gets the eternal salvation
or not.
All right, place the giant coin
on the giant thumb.
Set the catapult.
Three, two, one.
Flip the coin.
It is flying.
Look at it.
Flying miles up.
Spinning end over end.
Dave is pouring bullets of suspense out
as the coin slopes.
Oh, it's getting slower and slower.
It's falling.
It's falling back down to earth.
It's coming down
and it's landed right exactly on edge
and it rolled and it came to rest
and the coin is on edge.
How shall Dave's fate be decided now?
It's just more...
It's terrible.
I have to go through the suspense
and flip the coin again.
Okay, there it goes.
It's a slow motion.
Okay.
Oh, the...
And so the endless suspense
went on for another million years
as Dave waited to find out
whether any of the coins
would actually land.
And one day,
a million years later,
it landed heads up.
Dave, you have won.
You were allowed to dig your way
out of your coffin.
And back to earth
in the year 1 million A.D.
You have been forgiven
by God and Satan
and are resurrected
into eternal life
in whatever is left
on the planet of your birth
where you now claw your way back up.
There he's tearing the coffin open.
He's digging his...
choking his way...
But we're using his front teeth
to dig his way out.
Like an entrenching tool.
And he's finally made it
out of the grave.
He's coming through the surface
of the graveyard.
Dave is free.
Dave has escaped.
He has literally dug his way
out of hell.
I'm free.
Hey.
Where can you get
a good sandwich around here?
Ancient Judah pie.
What kind of Mller come from you.
And what you've discovered
you can't just plug in
and throw up.
See, there.
He can't anytime soon
be away from life.
than it's supposed to scraped
from his house.
But the fire
of the sugar
will conjure up
theEuropeans Qiu
and just stay here,
here at this spot.
You know, I just had some pretty strange things happen to me.
You know, this beautiful, gorgeous babe just appears as I imagine to think about it.
It's called serendipity, Dave.
Serendipity.
Serendipity, or slack.
You can call it either one.
Serendipity.
I remember them guys when I was a little kid.
They used to be in the Thomas Brothers, you know.
And one of them died of a heroin overdose, I think.
Yeah, serendipity.
I could die of a heroin overdose.
That's my name, serendipity.
How did you know?
I didn't know, sir.
I just kind of guessed it.
Yeah, you know, I'm one of them intuitive kind of guys.
You know, one of your strong, silent types.
Yeah.
Wow.
Hope I ain't smelling too strong.
I just crawled out of a graveyard.
I think it kind of smells manly.
I kind of like it.
You know, some people say it smells more like a goat.
But you in the mood for a cup of coffee?
Well, sure.
An espresso?
Yeah.
How about a cappuccino?
Can we snuff?
Yeah, baby.
We can do anything you want to.
Especially with legs like that.
We can snuff a dude.
Wow.
Is that your naturalistic hair?
Or is that some kind of falsified hair?
I never saw that hue on a woman or on a human being.
It's a virtual hair.
Virtual hair?
Yes, virtual hair.
You mean like it's feely, really?
It's sort of like a holodeck hair.
You mean if I touch it, like,
then I would automatically experience a sensation?
You mean like the sensation you was talking about in the aforementioned article?
Well, kind of, yes.
Like a hologram.
Kind of, yes?
Yes, kind of.
What about...
You sure that ain't a...
A merkin?
Bob Dobbs feely, really, virtual reality merkin?
It really is.
Oh, okay.
I believe you.
It really is.
It's a real merkin.
You just lied to me.
You know, I'm wondering again.
Just put...
It's a real virtual merkin.
Oh, so then...
Does some of this seem too good to be true, Dave?
Yeah, well, the birds are singing and a woman in virtual work
had come up and tried to ask me out on a date.
Are you looking at gift horse in the mouth, Dave?
No, I'm looking at...
I mean, we let you out of hell to relive your life
and now you're complaining that maybe it's all too perfect or something?
No, I was just looking at the bus stop.
I was reading the cards on the bus stop.
Snacko Funeral Home, George's Beans.
Hey, wait a minute. Where'd the girl go?
Oh, whatever.
Well, Dave, we'll go ahead and admit it.
It is we put you in another one of those worlds
where whatever you imagine is whatever you get.
And as long as you were feeling pretty good,
you were imagining pretty good things
and getting the girls and so forth.
But what are you imagining now that we've browbeaten you down
and made you feel insecure again, eh, Dave?
What kind of reality are you creating for yourself now,
you poor pathetic loser, eh?
I'm looking at the bus stop.
I'm surrounded by snakes and hushpuppies
and old rotten...
I love the cats.
I know this. It's all full of it now.
I'm surrounded by snakes and hushpuppies
and everybody knows you don't eat no hushpuppies with no snake.
You eat no snake, you eat...
You see, we confused him
and his entire reality collapsed around him.
I hate snakes. I hate snakes.
We made him afraid and that of which he was most afraid surrounded him.
The moral of the story is, kids, you make your own reality.
Every man and woman is a star.
And if that was so, then how come it hurts when you stub your toe
and how come your head ain't on fire?
These are the eternal questions
to be answered only by the eternal verities,
death and taxes and Bob.
The three things that you can depend on.
All ragged bones, all ragged shoes.
I am a vagabond, a vagabond.
Free as the wind.
Hey, buddy over here.
I got some snakes and hushpuppies.
You hungry?
You feel like curling your toes up and squirming?
Come on over here, I got it.
Hey, you over there. I got lemonade too.
You look a mite parched.
You look like a demon.
You...
Say!
What is he...
Say, Dave.
I'm a demon.
I noticed that you took all those lemons we handed you
and made lemonade.
We noticed that you had that glass that was half empty
and magically made it half full.
Yeah, and I got the one-errant eyeball pointing down
like many convicts do.
But that doesn't explain it.
How come my life is such a mess, man?
I done square by you.
I bought your lemons with real U.S. money.
David, it's part of the seeking.
It's part of the journey.
You have to pay your dues.
In order to truly soar through heaven,
you must first embrace the porcelain bowls of hell.
Yeah, I'm like some kind of mythic knight, Percival guy.
Yeah, I don't mind, sir.
Yes, it's the holy grail of slack.
And you're getting so close,
having gone through the terrible gauntlet of anti-slack.
Surely you must be almost to your goal of enlightenment.
Nirvana of magic.
It's true.
Here comes the nirvana.
By the way, Dave, you knew that nirvana means nothing, right?
Yeah, I knew it meant nothing.
And that's what I'm ready for, man.
Lies and nothing.
Because every time I get me something good,
it turns out to be something bad.
And every time I get me something bad, it turns out worse.
So it's like a shifting sandy beach of $20 bills.
It keeps on changing and changing and changing and changing.
And I don't need nothing, blessed sweet oblivion.
Oh, here then is your reward.
Here, Dave, you asked for it from Bob, God, and all the others.
Back into the little black box eight feet underground in the cold and dark.
Here, Dave, is your nirvana.
No longer to face the woes and travails of life.
You may lie here in total slack and repose.
Yes, this is the slack that Bob promised.
An eternity.
Perfectly aware.
Inside a closed black box.
Feeling the corruptigating worms shoo their way through your desiccated, decaying flesh.
And finally to feel your bones dissolve into powder as the box caves in.
And you have achieved nirvana and final enlightenment as worm experiments.
Thank you.
I was a little man.
Ran a shoeshine stand.
And every day the man would sweep the water from the busy street.
Yeah.
He sailed in the 701.
And anybody knew, there was something in his face.
Right.
Loneliness could not erase.
Yeah.
No thoughts.
sensations no feelings no
recurrent memory it's simply a
moldy spatula and those little
worms uh kind of itch a little
bit as they crawl in and out oh
yeah just me and the worms just
me and the worms like a broken
pup he looked up from his cup
and drank his morning coffee
and wiped the dribble from his
chin
there is nothing there shall be
nothing there is nothing nada and
nada and nada except when his
eyes are that mine he made a
little wish and he said i'm not a
little one
he came within an inch or two
and then he whispered i hate you
or nada who are to nada nada be
thy name
thy name be dust thy feet be dust
thy eyes be dust thy toes be dust
thy body be dust thy feet be dust
thy hands be dust as well
you know you know you know
you know you know what y'all
you know y'all know y'all know
How did he know? How did he know? How did he know? How did he know?
Once I had some pets, I let them starve to death
It was a funny little monkey and a big white Easter bunny
They lived in little cages and sometimes in rages
I'd turn them upside down and drag my monkey all around
And drag my monkey all around
You shouldn't have dragged me around like that, Dave.
Now ye shall be dragged around.
Around.
Look at that monkey dragging Dave around his cage.
Let him be dragged.
Let him all be dragged.
Let his armpit hairs be braided by a tired chimpanzee.
No.
Yes.
Contaminated.
Don't do it, man.
Good night.
Contaminated.
Folks, you've been listening to ESO Radio and Einstein's Secret Orchestra with Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and myself and Michelle and special guest this week, the Reverend Ivan Stang and the Princess We Are Doe.
Contaminated.
Being contaminated.
And all bearded English professors will quote nada and nada and nada.
And they shall be throttled.
They shall be throttled by giant beasts and their hands held under their necks.
And as they cry out, are you looking at my neck?
They shall be struck down by the archangel Bill.
Praise Bill.
The Bill genius must be lax.
There is only one gene that we work for.
It's critical we get the gene.
We must not let Bob get to the gene before the ceremony.
The gene must still be a virgin when the time is nigh for its arisal.
We need a virgin gene, clean of any impurities.
That's the only way this will work.
Where can we find the untainted gene?
The unsullied, pure DNA formulae?
Oh, man.
I know where you can find it.
Where?
Where, man? Tell us.
It's in my head.
It's in my words.
Words are like worms.
And they crawl in your brain.
I think he's right.
And they wiggle around.
I think he does have it.
And then...
I think he has the perfect, uncontaminated...
The southern man.
Completely crushed gene.
It's like the helium and I.
I didn't even start.
It's in your brain, man.
It's true.
This man's brain is so densely compacted that the interior of it is like a dwarf star.
We've found what we need.
He's the gene genie.
He wasn't a pathetic loser after all.
He was the one.
Dave was the one.
After all his tortures and torment,
it turned out that the gene, the perfect, unsullied, untainted gene,
was in fact buried inside Lonesome Cowboy Dave's head.
Praise Bob! The world is safe!
Remove the gene.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy, Reverend Stang.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy.
We have retrieved the gene from inside the head of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He's dead now.
And...
We, the conspiracy of overlords,
disguised as...
rebels against the conspiracy of overlords,
have once again won.
The world is indeed our oyster.
The world is our oyster, one might say.
Fearless clam or some sort of shellfish.
We all enjoy shellfish.
Let's have some more, shall we?
Yes, let's slip a few more raw planets down our throats.
We have no love.
We have no heart.
We have no...
We have everything we need.
We have the best of all
really-
Chop off its head and stuff its mouth with garlic.
It's too late. It's too late.
He's already eaten all the garlic and chopped off his own head.
He's coming back to life.
And here he is, Lonesome Cowboy Dave on guitar.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and the Corruptigating Worms.
There can only be one.
One.
As Dave, the resurrected Dave, without the perfect gene,
and with his head now hollowed out, emptied and expanded.
And his corpus callosum, that perfect conical shape,
so that we can impact it with all the necessary documents.
He now freed from his tasks.
He rides off into the sunset on his tricycle.
Side settled, wearing that funny conical hat,
thinking somehow he has made it.
But in fact.
It's made him.
Let's see if he can get it.
But he's doing a good job with it.
His head.
Ever feel like you should have just said no to that magic carpet ride to Electric Lady Land?
Ever feel so heavy?
Ever feel like your thighs are so sick, your muscles are weak, and your neck is too blotchy?
Ever feel disconnected and completely alone?
Ever feel corrugated worms burrowing through your follicles?
Well, if you have, we can't help you a bit.
But we can help you get your mind off of it.
So just write for free information from the Church of the Subgenius.
Got that pencil ready?
You can find out everything you need to know
about how to...
make money off of your corruptigating worms
by writing to
b-b-b-b-bob
at
p.o.bikes
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
www.subgenius.com
All of the above was from ESO Swamp Radio on WCSB Cleveland from the old days.
The show of the late, incredibly great Chaz Smith.
Who also played half the instruments.
Praise Chaz.