The sickest, sickest, sickest thing coming up I ever heard.
Why, yes.
Oh, listen to those interesting new buzzes come in as I push buttons here and there.
Hmm.
This is Side 5.
Follow in your book and repeat after me as we learn three new words in Turkish.
Back off, you bum! I kill you!
If anything goes wrong, we may have to...
We may have to scrape you off the landscape with a soup spoon.
Come on, I want to be slammed against the pavement and scooped up with a soup spoon.
Okay, now we're doing it, and here's the soup spoon.
The Soap Genius Hour of Swag.
Swag.
Radio violence is possible.
Without...
I got you on the trigger.
Give up now. Tomorrow is another day.
They believe their dream minds are just as real as their waking time.
It's my mind.
It's not stopping.
It's not stopping. How do you control this thing?
It's one of these newfangled car interactions that thinks.
It thinks, but it doesn't think the way I do.
Hey, what's going on here?
Hey, what kind of...
I've been fouled. I've been fouled.
Some big San Diego chicken.
I've been flashed.
My, uh, my...
What's the catch?
This show is not for children.
I don't believe this either.
That is that driver of the limousine that turned around and shot John Kennedy through the forehead, according to Bill Cooper.
That's why they wait until they turn the corner, so the driver could get a better shot when he turned and started going on that street.
Slowed down to almost a stop there.
That's when he turned around and shot Kennedy.
I have not seen that.
Yeah, well, Bill Cooper's got that.
He's got...
He had one of those guns that slid up his sleeve, and he just turned around.
They were driving.
You could be like your Kennedy, and the chauffeur turned around like...
He turned around this way, didn't he?
Oh, a palm-accompanied...
Yeah.
Turned around this way when Jackie was trying to put his brains back in.
It's the time travelers must have placed the chips in Kennedy's brain.
I heard it was just tubes.
Vacuum tubes.
It was great technology.
Well, Truman made that deal with the group in 1990.
I hear that Kennedy was struck with a bullet that was made of sintered uranium or something,
or some really dense, heavy metal that splatters.
Well, some people think it may have been a mini black hole that actually...
Not possible.
It's certainly...
That's why there was so much disturbance in the brain material.
It's not.
Hey, Matt.
Matt, I heard the song that refuses to die was in town.
I hope it doesn't come by here.
I hope this song doesn't come by here.
I don't hear the music, but gold.
Baby, gold.
Coming up in 10 seconds.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Mark.
What happened?
Okay.
Hey.
Yes.
It's okay.
We'll have the show under control.
Well, no, we won't.
We're never going to have the show under control tonight, my friends.
Because tonight is the show that refused to die.
The surreal hell show.
It's a surreal bunch of hell.
Think of what that sounds like.
Uh, I thought probably if it felt like it, like you're trying to get a situation out
because we'll have to take Lonesome Cowboy, Dave back to hell
and the Swing in Love corpses are having to…
Well, we've already given birth to it.
It's here, it's on the show.
The song that refused to die will continue
And of course, puzzling evidence in Dr. Hal Robbins will have us in for all sorts of trouble.
In the meantime, before we go completely deep, deep, deep down in,
first we're going to try to figure out what in the world is going on.
Come on!
In the world is going on.
Who can figure out what money's about?
I don't want to talk about it.
What goes on in the realm of the high priests of human value,
these souls forever, these souls so long?
I don't want to think about it.
I can't understand it. It's too complicated.
I mean, I don't know what goes on.
I don't want to talk about it.
What can I do about it anyway?
Well,
what is it you don't want to talk about?
About it?
I don't want to think about it.
I don't even want to hear about it.
It's like a tune that keeps haunting your mind.
What in the world is going on?
I don't want to think about it, okay, let's not.
I don't want to talk about it.
Don't tell me I don't hear you that I don't know why you don't want to.
Don't tell me why you don't want to talk about it.
I don't want to hear about why you don't want to talk about it.
I don't want to think about it.
Let's get into total denial.
But I do kind of actually wonder about it.
I just don't know how to talk about it
because I don't even know what it is.
What in the world is going on?
Who owns the world?
Whose world is it?
Who owns whose stuff?
Should you stuff your stuff when someone screws up?
Who pays someone sells weapons to Iraq or Iran
and there's a problem?
Who pays?
Somebody made billions off these fiascos.
Was it a race war?
Was it a class war?
Who cares?
We can fight over anything.
What in the world is going on?
I mean, we spend fortunes to develop and build them.
And then we spend tons to agree to this time.
And then we spend twice as much to dismantle them.
People are hungry.
What in the world is going on?
I mean, we're spending our spiritual,
mental, and physical resources to create weapons
to kill each other over ideologies
that are supposed to make our lives better.
What are we doing here?
What in the world is going on?
I mean, we need to get clear what we really want.
I mean, what do you think I mean when I say I'm really mean?
Do I mean I'm mean or do I mean angry?
Do I mean angry or do I mean mad?
Do I mean mad or do I mean crazy?
Do I mean crazy or do I mean insane?
Or do I just mean incoherent?
Quick.
My mind is going to go crazy.
Find me an enemy.
Quick.
Find me someone to hate.
Do I mean hate or do I mean blame?
Do I mean blame or do I mean unload on?
What in the world is going on?
Think about it.
Is it true or not that your thought structures
and belief systems limit your ability to be present,
creative, and authentic?
Think about it.
Is it true or not that you're prejudiced?
What do you live in denial about?
That you're motivated and manipulated through hot buttons?
That you react more than you think?
Do we see the invisible forces that shape our lives?
Do we want to think about it?
Or are we too busy to care?
I mean, how free is the human spirit?
What in the world is going on?
So we're here because this is the best dream we can come up with as a group.
Pay attention to how you feel.
It's habitual.
Careful what you think about.
And what you don't think about.
What in the world is going on?
Oh, the tube of gloom.
The Will-O-Dobs brought me this tube of gloom.
It kind of, uh,
fits the financial situation of the church.
But that was, uh,
the new juke savages.
New improved juke savages.
Once again, dear friends, I'm so glad to
be able to present them
on the show.
Uh,
they and, uh, Krishna Fats and the Night Nurses
on their album Radical Militant Vegetarians in Nazi Land
from
Holy Funk Records and Tapes.
Yes, and, uh,
I'm gonna give you their address right now because I don't think you can...
You know, I don't think they have these records in stores
and I can't play most of the tape on the radio.
But it's Holy Funk at P.O. Box
2329 San Anselmo, California
949.
seven.
nine.
That's Box 2329 San Anselmo,
949.
seven nine.
Yes, and we'll play their other song, The New Age Nazis, in
just a minute if this show will ever, ever die!
Guys.
For several reasons, I'd say it was gone.
Battered enough, you know.
For the first three weeks of training, he tried to move in on me.
Even insofar as to tell me he'd had a vasectomy.
So Guy did have a relationship with Olga.
Yes.
As far as Olga was concerned, Guy was interested and available.
They had their affair and...
She got pregnant.
Exactly.
Then he killed her.
He didn't have to.
Olga could never go public about her pregnancy.
Her husband would have had her killed.
Guy was perfectly safe.
He knew eventually she'd have to have an abortion.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
You're welcome, Guy.
Thank you.
This is a message for world peace.
Bob!
No, you can't kill me!
Bob doesn't make me sick!
No!
No, no, no!
Bob doesn't make me sick!
It's the song that refuses to die.
The song that cannot die.
It wants to die.
It wanted to die so bad.
It wanted to die so bad, but...
It just can't.
It just couldn't die.
As soon as one drummer died,
another one would just pick up the fifth old beat.
Until pretty soon...
Oh, my God!
The song came back!
Goddamn, I could've died!
We gotta sing this little stupid song now, man.
Examples?
We can always set our own examples.
We can't set examples for others.
Are you a voice box?
Uh, no, I'm not even that.
I'm a hallucination that you're having right now.
Actually, I'm just a bad dream.
Quiet down.
Our music...
Precisely, Professor.
We must increase the megavoltage to...
We're speaking from Guam.
Aganya, Guam is where the studios are.
We patch in the special glass fiber line right here at KPFA.
Woo!
It's itchy out.
In fact, somebody else is dreaming about us speaking,
and once that person wakes up, poof, we're gone.
What if that's a scary and mad killer?
Well, this isn't scary. This is wholesome.
Very mad killer?
This has a sense of family value.
Sense? Just sense?
Just a sense.
Rin Tin Tin.
Yummy family value.
Did you know that Rin Tin Tin,
who was a dog who lived in the 19th century at Fort Ridiculous
with Rusty, his little pal,
was revived recently as a TV series?
And guess what?
Now Rin Tin Tin is a cop.
He's out sniffing out small-time drug users and blah, blah, blah.
You know, what did they do?
Did they find him frozen in the ice at Fort Ridiculous
and revive him or something?
How did Rin Tin Tin get to the 20th century
and then he turns out to be a drug-sniffing cop?
Well, just like Walt Disney, isn't it?
Walt Disney has a wonderful world of law enforcement.
Walt's my cousin.
Oh, man.
Well, that's too bad. May he rest in peace.
Oh, Walt Disney.
Oh, Walt.
As he rests in cryogenic suspension,
60 feet below the surface of the Disneyland amusement park.
It's actually Saturday, but it's Friday.
It can't be a face-transfer.
I've never quite understood that.
Neuromotor functions slowed down
by the suspended animation procedure.
I'm over here, yeah.
Mr. Disney rests comfortably,
awaiting his revivification in the second century.
There's no phone to get from here.
No, I'm not talking to you.
Right.
And this is all an illusion.
But it's very tiresome.
It's a mold bugger.
This is boring.
Those callers aren't doing anything.
We should poke them with sticks and make them jump.
Here's a little Bernie stick.
A little Bernie stick?
Yeah, it's got little Bernies on the end.
Okay, you callers, here, take that.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Hey, they're trying to do things.
It just doesn't reach.
I need a slightly longer stick.
We'll have to waltz back over to the KPFA fireplace
here at the KPFA ski lodge and get other little sticks.
Let's not burn the place down getting too enthusiastic.
That's true.
I guess all this newspaper around here might catch on fire.
Look at that.
Bernie numbers dropping down.
I have some mighty fond memories connected with that.
Dr. Howell, what's happening?
Well, my pleasant imagination is soaring now,
up into empyrean realms.
A jug of wine, a loaf of bread, the stereo on at night,
in a lonely cabin, I call.
Honeymoon Hotel.
Yes, this was our honeymoon of horror.
This small, inconsequential muttering voice
takes me back to that mysterious room and that strange occasion
when I was not sure whether I dreamed or was awake.
But the more I tried to make sense of that maniacal,
I felt like, hey, you're not supposed to be there.
It was the song that refused to die.
Nobody wanted it.
God almighty, they could have used some sleep.
But the song refused to die.
The song started two years ago, but still, still it refused to die.
It wasn't a very pretty song.
You couldn't even call it an interesting song.
But it was, unfortunately, an immortal song.
All it, all it'd do was keep going and going.
Every now and then it would get on some semblance of an emotional tone.
But then somebody would get on a mic and couldn't even sing.
Then it would just splinter into a sargassional sea of sound
and maybe even a happy little emotional song.
Then it'd start to get murky again.
Nonsense.
I see Jane Seymour with a large,
midget.
Midget?
I think those are only extremely small giants.
They are giants in embryo.
For does not the small and the very large meet somewhere along the cosmic loop?
The average Protestant
has a very dim notion concerning the angelic hierarchies,
the great hosts of beings of another evolution than ours,
though children of the same heavenly Father.
The Kabbalah, however, is explicit on this point
and classifies them into ten archangels and ten orders of angelic beings.
Buddhist, Hindu and Mohammedan theology are equally explicit.
We may therefore reckon that in this agreement of witnesses there is surety of testimony,
and it may serve our purpose best to take for our guide that system from which Christianity took its rise,
mystic Judaism.
We will not go into the elaborate classifications employed by the Jewish rabbis,
which have their importance for purposes of magic,
but are not germane to our present issue.
It is enough that we realize that there are divinely created beings of various degrees of greatness,
from the mighty archangel whom Saint John the Divine saw standing in the sun
down to the nameless heavenly messengers who have from time to time visited mankind.
Well, what good is it to be unrestrained when you're sexless and bodiless?
Well, that's part of the fun.
They just get to do the will of God all the time.
And lots of space sex.
Or time sex.
I didn't know that time sex was an Olympic event, but apparently it is in my year.
Funny you should bring that up anyway.
Well, one day maybe. I don't know.
Maybe someone can call up and tell us what angel sex is like,
or what they imagine it might be like. I don't know.
I feel like making an adventurous enquiry here into the ether.
And maybe my angel will look down on me and say,
angel sex, that's something to look forward to.
Yes, this was our honeymoon of horror.
What I have to do to satisfy you?
Fiction on us.
Why don't you shut up?
What?
Hasn't it occurred to you that I'm having a tough time keeping my hands off you?
Oh, I'm having a real tough time...
keeping my voice off of you listeners.
Because I like to caress you with my hideous foul breath and tongue.
You...
You would think...
Welcome to the new age.
We're the new age Nazis.
We hate everyone.
We hate those wimps and cowards who had to pick on someone in particular to hate.
We're the new age Nazis.
We hate everyone.
We hate everything.
We even hate ourselves.
We especially hate ourselves when we really look down on those wimps
who can't even stand their own hatred and try to protect it on other people.
We're the new age Nazis.
We hate everyone.
Let's kill everyone.
Don't give me that old-fashioned half-Nazi attitude.
Let's get real.
I mean, let's get real mean.
No one's good enough to live.
Let's hate and kill and not limit it to blacks or Jews or Asians or Republicans.
You know, just pick on someone who's different than you.
Come on, get creative.
That's been done.
Every asinine culture does that.
Let's hate and kill and really get into it full on.
Let's hate the 49ers.
Let's hate Billy Martin.
We're the new age Nazis.
We hate everyone and everything.
We hate the rainforest.
We hate the industrialists.
We hate the workers.
We hate the air.
We hate the oceans.
We hate the earth.
We hate being out of control.
We hate thought and religion.
We hate time.
We hate feelings and ideas.
We hate the banks.
We hate the homeless.
We hate the spotted owls and vegetarians.
But most of all, we hate life.
Where we can't keep it up is we love hate.
We love hate.
We love blaming.
We love killing.
We love hurting and projecting our pain on others.
But we're the new age Nazis.
Where we shine is we don't stop.
They're like the old fashioned Nazis who naively thought they just hated other people.
We hate ourselves.
We poison our own air and water and our own minds and souls with hatred and bad thoughts
and feelings and toxic waste and television for God's sake.
We're the new age Nazis.
We hate everyone and everything.
Join the party.
Kill for peace.
Join the new age Nazis.
Send us your dues.
And get put on the list.
Welcome to the new age.
We're going to turn the whole earth into an oven.
We don't have to round people up.
You can't win.
People love to hate.
So we can't lose.
Welcome to the new age.
Join the new age Nazis.
No offense.
Don't try to featured into the documentary.
ировayIlhoseunic.com
The New Age Nazis.
Welcome to the new age.
And the church of the sub geniuss zaten ist EN dal Normal.
Der New Age Nazis Unver38 acontece is fram pity gewaltig hier läh het.
Ut es verlag hier.
savages, the New Age Nazis, radical militant vegetarians in Nazi land.
Oh, just lovely.
And just before that, you heard some of Reverend Velveteen Sly,
the lovely Reverend Velveteen Sly, and the lovely Reverend Angus McGamora
talking about angel sex.
And as usual with any hour of Slack show, you get little bits and pieces,
sometimes long bits and pieces from the show that dare not speak its name.
They're from KPFA in Berkeley with puzzling evidence and...
Doctor Howell.
Oh, that feels good, yeah.
And people hoped it would be able to die, but it kept twitching.
Its heart wouldn't give up.
It might have been a nice song to begin with in some remote town,
but now it just wouldn't die.
Just when you thought they had given up,
it would scream and just keep getting uglier and uglier.
Oh!
Oh, now it's playing again.
Okay.
Oh, I bet that's what it was.
Okay, where's the, um, thing that adjusts the level?
Uncover the viewing dome.
This one?
Uh...
Okay, I'm talking, talking, talking.
All right, let's take a good look at this.
Okay, I'm talking now, and you're trying to adjust me to zero.
Adjust image size to zero.
That looked about right.
Yeah, I think...
Okay, this is a long, continuous tone.
Now we'll retrieve the signal.
Scratched out as it passes cosmic distance in interstellar space.
Hey, Hal, look, Bob's talking.
Oh, that blowhard, why doesn't he sit down and shut up?
Oh, is this an open channel?
Well, just joking, as you know, we maintain high standards of radio standards.
You see, that board is lit up like a Christmas tree,
and in fact, it is an old Christmas tree which we never did jettison
and is growing to be a fire hazard here in the control cabin.
I say that, and I don't mind anyone knowing.
For better or for worse, we've got to live with our usual telepressions.
One social critic.
A dangerous cult of techno-shamanists
whose mental health is at risk.
Members worship its billionaire founder.
E. Howard Higginbottom.
What do you think of that, caller?
That's your cue.
Can't you pick up your cues faster than that?
They always try, but you see, they never learn.
Even plenarian worms can learn,
but horrors can never learn to take their turn.
Very good.
Unusual group of true believers,
and...
...animalistic worshippers,
generally from backwoods, remote portions of the country.
Rural Texas, Arkansas,
and the darker woods of Iowa.
The desperate, the lonely,
losers, pencil-neck geeks, wimps,
the maladroit, those with yards,
all found under the aegis of subgenius fandom.
The
This is an authentic Bob lecture,
one of the first of seven seminars given by Bob in 1956.
He's divine.
And look at them lap it up.
There they all are, sitting in the front row in embryo.
The embryo jainer and the embryo stang.
And the embryo sterno.
He's divine life.
Even the embryo phylo.
And you will live in eternal bliss.
It went through three generations of musicians.
All the musicians who start playing the song are dead.
But not the song.
Oh, no.
No way.
Yeah, that old song ain't gonna die.
No siree.
Oh, you can pray for the song to die.
You can call up your mom and say,
Oh, ma'am, make the song die.
My ears hurt, ma'am.
But it just keeps getting louder and louder and louder.
It's like it wants to hurt you.
Just when you thought it was over,
when you thought you killed it,
oh, God, it brings you back to life.
Oh, no.
You just have to keep listening and listening.
Oh, a guitarist may die,
but someone else will come along.
Maybe they try to kill it,
but no, the song will just keep playing and playing itself.
The song that refused to die.
It was the song that refused to die.
What? Is it dead?
Is it dead yet?
Is the song dead yet?
No!
Ah!
And I said,
Hey, you.
Hello, guys.
What's that voice saying on the radio?
Yeah, I know you.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good idea.
This is Conor Red.
Red alert.
This is not a test.
This is an alert.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Take cover immediately, everyone.
Yeah, yeah.
I repeat, this is not a test.
This is Conor Red.
Yeah, yeah.
Take cover immediately.
We are under attack.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yeah.
The drums were broken,
but that wouldn't stop the song.
Uh-uh.
The power went out.
You think that's gonna stop the song?
Whoo, you wish.
The song that refused.
Refused to die.
Bullets couldn't stop it.
Flamethrowers couldn't stop it.
The nuclear bomb, the harmonic convergence.
They tried everything they could think of,
but the song refused to die.
It continued to live,
relentlessly tearing into your eardrums.
You think it's dead?
Uh-uh, forget it.
Oh, this song's gonna be around longer if you're dead, boy.
Listen, listen.
It's heartbeats.
Oh, no, fibrillations.
Has the pain ended?
Oh, God, no.
Look at that EET.
It's incredible that it can keep in a coma for this long.
You still go on and on and not die.
State short question, please.
But hurry, because that volcano's molten magma will soon be upon us.
But you must hurry.
There's a computer file here of Bob images.
Must leave me, children.
Things are like this in California.
This is where Bob was screaming on the edge of the volcano
and he threw the Virgin in,
and that ought to portend a good harvest this year.
Sorry.
It's pretty neat.
Wow, there's Bob.
Look, he's an old man now.
He's standing on that glowing piece of pumice.
Oh, I see.
He's just a fake bum.
A hologram of projection.
And now we've got the vibrabed at the Toreador Inn
with Bob and his concubine.
It's just like that.
He's got thousands of tiny fingers telling him to let go.
And look, he did.
Oh, yeah, so he did.
He's let go and he's become free.
Floating free at the end of his tether in microgravity conditions.
Yeah.
Looks awfully small to me, too.
Okay, now he's floating over to the bathroom.
...forced him to flee.
Bob is needing to discharge his ballast in Earth's orbit.
...massive clips make it invulnerable to those who wish to get on...
Wow, look at that place.
Great place in the Pyrenees there Bob bought to get away from Arkansas.
...the only things on the mountain...
...are this 700-year-old village...
...compelled by the space tether to this giant mountain...
...and surrounded by a 700-year-old village...
...the temple is turned into a place...
...into a sort of shrine.
...an English archaeological shrine.
Hmm, yeah.
...who is it?
Oh, oh, oh, strangling the collar.
Now wait a minute.
At the top of my script here it says...
...we...
...oh, there it is.
Excuse me, sorry.
...a little escape button.
You just press this and whoop, there it goes.
Right off the screen.
That must be the cough button for some reason.
Yeah, sort of like that.
And, uh, he's got a little, uh, little, uh, little, uh, little, uh, little, uh, little,
Now, here we go.
Oh.
We've got the Heo people here.
These obnoxious child actors, I've never liked them.
They're all trying to get me to Heo, but all I know is lie down, roll over and play dead.
I'm sorry, I can't understand them.
And I refuse to participate in this cult-like mass insanity.
Can't you people understand me?
I'm unburdening my bosom to you.
Why, you cold, unfeeling...
It was too much for them.
And I wondered, was it also too much for me?
My heart was beating like a trip hammer.
I reeled, doubled back, lurched forward, and...
...collapsed.
My pain is gone.
You are the divine power.
He's turned the village and the temple into an armed fortress.
Oh, don't mention it all.
See these white lights?
They represent armed watchtowers.
Those green lights represent the checkpoints.
The roving band of guards.
In two weeks, the brotherhood will be in the last game
of its annual baptismal rituals for new comers.
From sunset to sunrise, they observe this night
with celebrations and indoctrination.
Look.
A year ago, two hot organizers abandoned the court.
We got through before the assassination was.
We developed a new prince diagram for West.
We even smuggled out a key to the temple's main entrance.
Oh, thank you, Dr. Howell.
That was lovely, Dr. Howell, and puzzling evidence.
I'm afraid things won't be quite so lovely anymore.
Because now, Sister Mary Squared au contraire.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Courtesy of Brainrot Radio Theater in WCSB, Cleveland.
In the town of WCSB, in the state of Cleveland.
In the country of Ohio.
In the universe of America.
We'll take...
Lonesome...
Cowboy Dave...
Back...
To...
Hell.
Sorry.
Hold.
Ha ha ha ha!
I wanted to kill people and stuff.
I just didn't have the guts.
Ah, now he's starting to catch on.
I didn't have the balls to do it.
I didn't want to be good.
I actually...
Really wanted to, like...
Oh, now he's trying to talk his way out of it.
... torture people and stuff.
And remove, like, ligaments from their kneecaps.
Should we play him the tape of him trying to talk his way out of it the first time?
Oh, we've already played it. Oh, now he's trying to talk his way out of it the first time?
We've already played the tape of him trying to talk his way out of it the second time.
Did I hear the tape the first time the second time?
Don't you remember, Dave?
I thought I remembered that one.
See, if you had remembered, the contract would have been voided!
But no, you didn't remember!
Mm-hmm.
So, it's still on.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's all right there in the print.
In the...
In...
It's not even fine print.
It's perfectly legible, Cyrillian, uh, text.
I remember...
You said you understood!
When Saint Cyrillus Methodius...
Why, I'm just gonna screw up again. Just listen to this.
This one is not the Swing Ship Manuscript.
Saint Cyrillius Methodius...
This is the Verdango Key to Freedom!
We... we dangle it right in front of his face, and then he just, like, that's the part that he misses.
It's true.
It just goes for everything else. He tries the pleading, the begging, the lying...
It's true. David, David, David!
Don't get Ren! Get Zen!
Become... become one with the key!
Become... become one with the... with the... the freedom of the... of the whole kingdom,
and the theme park, and the contracts, and the...
and the multi-million dollar movie screen. It's all yours! You can have it, Dave!
It can be fun if you accept the pain!
Yes! Enjoy the pain!
Learn to love the hate!
Love it! Embrace it! It's yours!
Learn to just sink into the pain, Dave!
I'm sinking into it like a four-year-old child.
Not that it's going to get you out of here any sooner!
What?!
But it'll seem... the time will seem to go by faster, although that's fairly, uh, moot point, when you're...
talking in terms of utter timelessness and eternity of awareness of the pain forever and ever and ever!
There's no place like my ego! There's no place like my ego!
Oh, Dave, we were... Hey, Dave! Dave, we were just kidding.
We were just kidding. We're really going to let you out of that box.
We're going to unhook you from the machine. It was all just a joke.
It was a... it was just part of the theme park! Yeah!
You're not really in hell. We didn't want you to get totally freaked out.
No. A little freaked out. We've had problems with people who believed it, you know, because it was so...
it was so convincing, but no, no. You'll be disconnected very soon, and it's all... it's still just a ride.
What do you mean by disconnected? You don't need to be upset.
It's fine. I guess I owe you that dollar.
I didn't believe when you turned it up to ten it would really do that.
What do you mean by disconnected, you guys?
Technology.
What do you mean by disconnected, though?
Does that mean, like, she used to exist or something?
Oh, would you rather stay hooked up?
No, no, no. I...
We'd be glad to leave you here. That's no problem.
Sure. I'll babysit you, Dave.
It's fun. Oh, I think he likes it. I think he likes being connected.
Okay, Dave. We won't disconnect you.
No, no, no. No, no, wait.
You can stay right there in the little box.
Wait a second.
Shooting the ticks.
No, no. All I meant was...
Oh, we missed that one.
I just want to explain.
You're confused.
Oh, I meant that, you know, I wouldn't get killed or anything, right?
If, say, for instance, when you said disconnected...
Oh, now I...
Oh, I was worried about being killed.
Be killed.
Oh, Dave, around here, that's truly the very last thing you have to worry about.
Absolutely.
Killed. Killed.
You'll be...
You're gonna be smoking packs of cigarettes ten a minute trying to give yourself cancer
when you figure out what's going on here, boy.
You're gonna pray for a car wreck and there won't be any cars.
You're gonna be banging your head against the wall.
Uh-huh.
No, we were just kidding. Really, really.
Let's be nice to him.
Oh, okay.
Let's be nice to him for a while.
We've been nice to him.
Actually, we...
Yeah, we could show him what it would be like to not...
Not be nice.
Hey, that's a good shoot here.
I have a nervous breakdown.
I can feel fish going in the middle of my brain.
Could that be?
Perhaps he's lost his mind.
Oh.
That would almost be a blessing, wouldn't it?
He could just give up.
He wouldn't have to think ever again.
Not a single thought for eternity.
Guess what, Dave?
We thought of that already.
All of your little tricks, losing your mind, trying to commit suicide and so forth,
everybody tries that.
Everybody down here does that.
I did it myself.
Sister Mary here, I remember the time you jumped off those...
That Empire State Building over and over again.
I just couldn't get it off.
Surely this time.
It was almost like a game, a pastime.
We all go through these little fates.
The only thing that we realize, is you'll become more accepting.
Of course, as soon as it becomes more accepting, you know, what's the point of that?
No, we're just kidding, Dave.
I do.
No, you're doing everything right.
You're doing exactly what the script said.
They always follow the script.
That's the amazing thing about it.
It's always the same.
But no matter how differently you set up the environment or the reality around it,
they still follow the script.
The curve is mightier than the sword.
If you can't go straight, you can always go around.
And around and around and around.
Around and around.
It's a big wheel, babe.
It is a wheel.
It's like, you know, you're true.
You're not on Earth anymore, but it's like Buddhism, you know?
You can just, perhaps someday you'll be able to escape the wheel.
Can I at least grab a spoke?
Let's dangle some hope in front of his eyes.
Yes, yes, you can be a spoke in the wheel.
Oh, and if you graduate, you can be a tack that pops the other wheels and gives them flats.
Or perhaps the tread of the wheel.
I remember when Andrew was caught in the body of a pig,
and then Klishner or Vishner or whatever the hell his name is
cut him in half and let the pigs come out,
and he realized he was injuring them.
That doesn't have to do with this either, does it?
No, no, that doesn't have anything to do with it.
No, no.
The pigs?
Absolutely not, no.
I don't know anything about the pigs.
No, that might be a way.
Get out, Dave.
Can we get the pigs out of here?
You might try the pigs.
Move the pigs.
Go ahead.
Let's help him.
Maybe with the pigs he can, he'll stumble onto the special thing.
Oh, there.
What's the matter, Dave?
Not the kind of pigs you're used to?
My toes feel like plastic.
Oh, what a porker.
Oh, my aching feet.
Please.
I'll get this.
I'll get this away from my groin.
Oh, jeez.
Oh, he's complaining.
Well, for crying out loud.
He's complaining that he doesn't like the blue pigs.
It was a pretty sharp little nuzzle there.
You know, I'm only human.
Davey, Davey, behave.
Slaughter them.
Slaughter all of the pigs.
Cast the madman disease out of them and throw them off a cliff or something
in some hideous parody of some religious superstition of ancient days.
It's just like mythology, man.
People who thought they could somehow escape.
What has exactly happened to Dave and what happened to you and me?
But look at us.
We graduated.
We did.
Now we get to do it to him.
Well, come here.
Dave, you'll get to do it.
It goes around.
It's the wheel and the spoke thing all over again.
There you go.
Uh-huh.
In a nutshell.
Soon you'll be the highway.
You won't be the wheel forever.
Someday you two could be the roadkill or even the highway itself.
I've been the possum plenty of times.
I don't see why you have to keep on getting re-boarded and ignaminated all over again and
keep on doing it.
I don't see why you have to keep on getting reconstituted and coming back and be tortured
by you two again.
I don't even know who you are.
That's the question that has bothered mankind down through the ages, Dave.
And you know what?
You know why?
Because we've actually got nothing better to do.
That's the answer right there.
I thought so.
Nothing better to do at all.
It's just to pass time.
We've got lots of that, Dave.
That's right.
Lots of that.
All for nothing.
I know.
We suspected that.
It always seemed so aimless, so fruitless, so pointless.
It's just another soul torture to hell.
And he's too...
He likes things.
Walking around, talking to him about Bob Dobbs, making him experience all kinds of...
He's probably just like a dream thing.
You got your money back.
You got triple your money back.
And a free glass of ice water, too.
What more could you want?
And the brochure.
I wanted thrice...
And the maps.
I wanted thrice my salvation, like you had promised in this brief document.
No, it's...
Twice your money back.
Salivation.
You didn't...
Twice your salvation.
Salivation, Dave.
And what do you think your shoes are full of?
You've got the salivation.
You've got the $60 check.
You've got the handbook.
And you've got the game control.
And the callus.
You've built up quite a good callus on yourself.
And yet you still can't get it.
You just...
It's simple, Dave.
If I got...
They're shooting ticks for nothing, man.
If I got a massive talus on my hair, and if I have got, like, whatever...
What's one thing that I have said before?
Why do I...
They all do.
I'm salivating in my shoes.
I would do if I were...
Why would I need to do that?
That's right.
That was good.
I like that.
I do, too.
All right.
Oh, that's another flashback.
Would you like Sister Mary to get into the little box with you?
Is that what you really think you'd like?
That would help me out a little bit.
I mean, you know, why just...
Okay, Dave.
Well, why don't I just pop right over here next to you?
There.
Are my tits in your way?
I'm sorry, Dave.
That's right.
I didn't mean to get that close to you.
Keep shooting, and those ticks will be killed.
I'm controlling a joystick now.
Those ticks are coming over...
Oops, I'm sorry.
Oh, jeez.
You distracted me.
Are you missing you from your game, Dave?
I keep missing you.
Are you missing the ticks?
What's this down here?
Is there a bit less blood on the desert floor?
I can't see them anymore.
I can't see any more ticks.
I can't see any more ticks anymore.
He's never going to get another life this way.
All right.
Now, turn her into the pig.
Get off!
Oh, squeal, Dave!
Squeal!
You ever see that movie, Mike?
That one where the rednecks...
What?
Right?
The poor guy out in the woods.
It was like, squeal like a pig.
We could do that.
We could put him into that.
I hear that every week.
Do it for the rednecks.
We'll do it the other way.
I hear that every week.
I'm tired of being sodomized and being confused by these weird Archon figures who aren't real.
If they're not real, then I'm hallucinating this, right?
Then this is all sinners around me.
I am one with myself.
I remember I must have taken a drug.
I have taken a drug.
And I'm not...
Oh, and you out listening?
They're not going away.
It's not like we're mentally tuned in to you and know that you did, too.
Don't worry.
That's not happening.
I pushed my hand through the window.
Oh, yes.
We can see.
Three of them did.
They won't go away.
Through the microphone.
Three young men and that one young lady.
Yeah.
They're all sitting there going, how did they know we were going to do that tonight?
Why are they doing this kind of show?
Let me out of here!
They must have known.
Their parents are angry!
They don't realize, like a child thinks, wow, there are people inside the television
that we can communicate with.
Yeah.
We're inside the radio.
They just don't realize.
Oh, no, that's not...
The people in the TV can see you, but they can't read your mind.
We're on the radio, so it's like the other way around.
It's the silent radio.
We're broadcasting in your broadcasting.
We've got...
Go away!
You can turn the pig back into Sister Mary.
Oh, Dave, what a big shaft you have.
He's good at getting them ticks, ain't he?
He's got a real eye for them ticks.
And that's even though we didn't give him the best gun.
Oh, yeah, he's got a hell of a callus now, don't he?
Oh, but you guys have a good gun.
I didn't know I was supposed to get so many calluses on this deal.
So far, I have calluses on my feet and on my hands, and now I have one on my protuberance.
And I don't understand exactly what the...
You're going to need it when you start having to club the ticks to death, man.
When you run out of ammo...
What does he think he's going to club them with, anyway?
Well, that's what the callus on that thing is for.
I thought it was for the love-pain-death thing, whatever you were saying.
Oh, yes, yes, the sex hurt.
The sex hurt.
Love-pain-death.
Yeah, that's what I thought it would be for.
I'm not just going to walk around with this stubber on my bodice like it was growed there for no apparent reason.
Love-pain-death.
I like the dichotomous sound of that.
I don't like any of this.
This makes me feel nauseous.
I'm confused.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
Would you like a drink, Dave?
We've got some beer wine gas.
I could go for some more meat.
Is there a meat market in this theme park?
Where can I go shopping?
Everything in this theme park.
Oh, I just love all those rows and rows of hot, juicy sausages.
Could I get some food in here, too?
Huge, giant bologna.
Food land.
That's it.
He'd love food land.
Whoa.
Oh, food land.
Can I get some veal?
Somebody's talking about veal picada.
And now he's got the pigs to deal with.
Yoo-hoo.
And the hologram of you.
So, why not?
Food land.
Hey, Dave, you want to go to food land?
Hungry?
I thought you'd never ask.
I've been banging on the window here.
Yeah.
Right.
All we need to do is...
That's the butcher over there.
Go see that butcher.
He'll prepare...
One of the weird guys dressed up like cocktail onions with, like, the flute feet and stuff.
One of these...
Those were...
They were gluttons in their other life.
Oh, just look at all those men packing that meat into those tight little containers.
It's a sin, Dave.
Oh.
Oh, it's kind of lewd.
And the way they split that squid.
Oof.
Did you not in life eat seven more Slim Jims than you were bequeathed in the word of dogs according to Prescriptures 914?
Who is this?
The patties and the steaks and the cattle.
Recording angels, play the tape.
How are you?
Now, Dave, you ain't supposed to eat more than them seven...
Slim Jims.
I told you you could have seven Slim Jims.
That was all.
Oh, I don't give a damn.
I had 12 birds.
I can eat as many Slim Jims as I want.
You so, you lonesome cowboy Dave, claimed that your rules were greater than the rules of Bob and took the extra Slim Jim.
And so, for this sin...
Sister Mary, does his name appear in the Book of Humans?
So, I drank brackish water.
I don't know, Ivan Stang.
I don't know.
There is yet more testing to be done.
More probing.
More inspecting.
More, more...
Meatpacking?
You lonesome cowboy Dave.
I just want more.
Because...
I want more.
Please, let me back in the box with him.
Let me back in the box with him, Ivan Stang.
Because you have proved to be so attractive to Sister Mary Square.
You are given a second chance.
I need lonesome cowboy Dave.
Yes.
You will be allowed to prove, reprove...
Don't put that woman back in here with me.
She's crazy.
Oh, who, Dave?
You do not have to go to the void of eternal naked beautiful girls.
But will be allowed to stay here in theme world to go through the rides...
Crikey.
...again and again and again...
...over and over and over.
Throw the other sinners into the lake of naked women.
The male sinners and lesbian sinners.
And women...
Well...
And vi...
Throw the female sinners into the lake of naked men and...
...whoa, men.
And also the gay male sinners into that self-same eternal squirted lake.
For anybody, really.
Just throw them all in.
We'll make a big salad full of meat.
We'll add some meat.
We'll add some turkey.
We'll have lots of fun.
But put Dave back on the pig ride.
That's right.
Put him on the pig ride.
Turn him over on the street.
He did not like food, lad.
Light a fire under his pubic.
Where are some more oinking sounds?
Let's send him to boredom, lad.
Land.
Oh, let's not send him to boredom, lad.
That would be too easy.
No, but yeah, it would be too easy because I'm queuing on the wrong pa...
I'm turning you on a par...
...participle.
I'm going back now and I...
Shall we let him choose his own path?
Perhaps he will find his way to escape land.
Though none have ever done it before.
That's true.
They thought they did.
None have ever escaped from escape land.
It's like a place where you get tickets in and you can get out of here and stuff?
Are those...
There are legends.
There are legends of those whose strength was so great they were able to arm-wrestle Bob at the gates and to pass beyond into the next zone.
Into the harmonious fish.
Louie, the guy with the bird legs, he did it.
He told me about it.
I know somebody who did that, who wrestled Bob.
And he got past the gates of Panoply or Pangloss or whatever his name is.
His name was Louie.
Louie the bird leg, they called him.
Oh, yeah.
I thought it was Louie.
The robots are already pre-programmed to tell him everybody's...
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's...
I was in a lot of trouble.
Were we saying anything?
I was saying...
Dave, what you just said carries more weight in this land than any other.
But it won't do you any good yet.
You'll have to say you're sorry in many, many, many ways.
Ways even we have not dreamed of yet.
For you may be the first, Dave, to depart from the script, yes?
If you can just find a way to...
To change the script, you could get out of here.
It's like saying...
The answer is right in front of you, man.
It's been hanging right in front of you this whole time.
Log on and off correctly.
Every minute must be counted for.
He's trying to pass the word.
Example.
Past cracking.
Yes, if you can find the password...
The via password is five minutes ob clonko before the law.
He did it!
I can't believe it.
He was just guessing.
The 100th monkey exploded right in the Daily Face.
It's a frozen world.
Dave, you can leave.
You're king.
You have the choice.
You can either be god of this realm or you may leave and go back to your previous glorious
existence as an unknown radio comic.
Can I take another, like a different one other than those two?
He just lost.
He could have.
He had it right there.
He had it.
They always do.
I'll be turning it up to ten now.
Up.
Yeah.
I want to go home now.
It's sad, but it's amusing to me.
I would like to really relieve myself first and then like remove, you know, expunge some
of these like weird garments you guys got me dressed up in.
Forgot about the bathroom.
Take some of the feathers off my hat.
Go ahead and go.
I look silly as hell.
Go on!
Go on bathroom break.
Go on to the bathroom, Dave.
Go right ahead to the bathroom.
You'll love the bathrooms in Seamwork.
Just don't hook your thing up to that thing.
I don't have anything on my thing to wish upon.
with which to hook it.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Oh, how he looked recently.
That's changed too.
Remember when we changed Monica
into Psychopath Finder?
Oh, he doesn't remember.
He thinks that really is Psychopath Finder.
Oh, he's checking.
Oh my God.
Did you see what I had to be in that cube with?
Do you see what I had to look at in that cube with?
I tried to like it.
I tried.
I can't keep up.
Thank you, Mike.
What's the matter, you guys?
Nothing happened.
Maybe we should send him out.
Maybe we don't even want him here.
I looked down there.
There's absolutely nothing down there at all.
I did my best piggy voice.
I just couldn't keep up the schlick.
I've never seen anything like that.
In fact, I didn't see anything there at all.
I can't be in made-up pork butter
for someone else's amusement park.
And then once it's inside...
That is creepy.
It vibrates.
What does?
Yes, my friends.
No, I'm not going to get it.
And I'm afraid you're going to have to keep playing the game
forever and ever and ever.
Oh, that was Lonesome Cowboy Dave in hell
with his S.O.B.
Scorch, Sister Mary Squared, Au Contrere,
and your host and prayer partner,
Reverend Ivan Stang and friends.
And now is when I have to give you
the post office box number for Bob.
That's right, Bob.
You got that pencil ready?
Bob at...
Box 140306, Dallas, Texas,
7...
5...
2...
1...
4.
Now, just in case you didn't get that right,
the last 401 shows,
that's Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas,
7...
5...
2...
1...
4.
And you'd be surprised
what you would get back in the mail
if you express even the slightest bit of information.
Of course, you may...
want to avoid just that.
Uh, yes.
Good night.
Good night...
It's a'és about the birth of God...
Maybe just another rap
But you're running out of sap
Yes, you're running out of sap
Well, you better take a rap
Dying under daddy's cap
Shrivel up
It's at the top of the list
That you can't get pissed
No, you can't get pissed
It's rule number one
Living right isn't fun
Cause it's a God-given fact
That you can't go back
No, you can't go back
It's a God-given lie
That you're gonna lose your mind
Yes, you're gonna lose your mind
Time-tested and true
You gotta put it on, put it on
Gotta put it on, put it on
Well, it's a God-given lie
That you're gonna get small
Yes, you're gonna get small
Maybe just another rap
But you're running out of sap
Yes, you're running out of sap
Well, you better take a rap
Dying under daddy's cap
Now, oh, shrivel up
Shrivel up, people
Now, shrivel up, people
I'm saidаль
I can't believe it
This is the holiest time of the year
on the Christian calendar
and I just can't believe it
What do you have to say for yourself?
It better be a silver board
Doctor, do you have any idea
how much your family's
phone company spends each year just on puzzling evidence what do you have to say for yourself
i've never really thought about that well i guess many people don't but those billions of miles
what do you have to say all those exchanges why just the maintenance on our who are you
and that's not even to mention our holding stock the cars and trucks the airplanes and satellites
and then all those fine people who are actually on the payroll to take care of all that
do you understand
now to look at that hand
let's take a closer look
you
and a possessed hand brings fatal results
what can i do for you what do you want
either you cut my hand off or i'll kill you
no straps no gas just cut
thanks to the science of microelectronics
you are looking at a complete telephonic receiver and transmitter