You are now about to begin a great adventure, the journey out of a mile.
Oh boy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Everything's gonna be all right this morning.
Have a listen.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the church.
Oh, the subgenius.
This little radio is a monotropical, highly complex one-way homing device.
It will be scanning the airwaves, seeking out a complicated set of alternating frequencies coming from...
Showtime, kid.
Kill me, I'm here! Kill me!
Radio contact is practically impossible.
We have scratched records in static, but like wrinkles and memories.
Oh, well, I wasn't really prepared for this. Let's see.
What...
Hey, go on, here.
Let's see, is there anything else?
Oh, the helmet, tell me.
In one huge federation.
We are happy people.
We dance and sing and drink.
We are not monsters anymore.
No, not anymore.
We like to play with the etch-a-sketch.
Yeah, that's it.
We have a few little wrinkly guys.
Yeah, we did Coyolas and stuff.
Hey, here we go.
We're counting down.
So, run for it, right?
Yes, I'm not rolling tape.
Oh, no.
Who, me?
And on your three.
Two.
Hello, and welcome to radio...
No, that doesn't work, sorry.
Is it?
We suggest those wishing to leave their turn to their radio dial, which is not what I was written.
No.
It says there, but it doesn't work.
No, ma'am.
Sorry, friends, we're having a little bit of trouble getting started here.
Well, let me just read this through before I read it.
I think it's a good idea.
Yes, go ahead, Barbara.
We're going to start again.
This comedy ride may contain material that is hatterous.
Great.
Yeah, comedy.
This isn't...
It's not supposed to be a comedy show.
This is like a...
I was waiting for you to do something else silly.
Sorry.
Okay.
I didn't know if that was a real one or not.
No, it is.
It's not a real one.
No, friends.
That's not a...
It's not a real one.
That is, in fact, from the radio shorts tape happening somewhere back in there.
And...
But I wanted to just get the church off to a proper start here.
Oh, yes.
Well, I just got out of the shower.
My hair's all wet.
I'm probably going to get electrocuted by these headphones.
I bet you wouldn't mind.
I need her.
You wouldn't care.
No, no.
But...
Let's see.
But I've got my incredibly strong cup of coffee here.
And we're ready.
Ready to do a show.
Things are getting back to normal here at the Subgenius Foundation headquarters in Dallas.
Yes, we've been answering the three and a half foot stack of mail seen here in the background.
And we've got about half done with it yet.
So far, I've got a huge stack of new tapes has come out of that.
And an even huger stack of wonderful written things to share with you, dear listener.
Oh, but are you puzzled, dear friend?
Why not talk to Bob?
About being...
A real subgenius?
Puzzled, you say?
Yes, I am.
There are so many conflicting ideas about religion.
Will you please tell me what it really is to be a genuine subgenius?
Well, my friend, as it says in Bob 1315,
I have given you an example that ye should do as I say, not as I do.
But, you say, an example is always better than an explanation.
And you, Bob, were perfect.
But, at the same time, you were divinely idiotic.
What about us ordinary abnormal people?
My friend, as Bob said in Prescriptures 1-8,
Hast thou considered my servant Stagg, that there is none like him in the earth, a twisted and uprightly bent man?
One that feareth, Bob, and turns away from boredom?
Oh, yes, you say.
But Stagg lived way back in ancient days when conditions were different.
What about, what about these modern times?
Well, my friend, I can answer you that from Galoshes 1-27-28.
A servant of Dobbs saluteth you, always laboring fervently for you in sex-return.
That ye may stand perfect and eager to buy in all the will of Dobbs.
Slack in ye the hope of glory, whom we preach, warning every subgenius and teaching every subgenius in all idiocy,
that we may present every man perfect in slack Dobbs.
Ah, yes.
And does that mean that you can become a real subgenius?
Well, friend, you just listened to Mark of the Johns 9-23.
If thou canst believe,
and have thirty dollars to spare,
then all things are possible to him that believeth and spendeth.
Ah, yes.
And you know, it's so beautiful to be back here with you on the radio.
I'd like to share with you this lovely piece of music we just got in.
This is just the most heartwarming piece,
and it makes me think of the Kennedy mask that I bought today while I was out at the supermarket.
This is a little piece by a band from Richmond, Virginia, called The Trouble with Larry.
And I think it's gonna bless your heart.
I think it's gonna bless your heart.
I want a 62-link gun
With a drop-top painted black
And a .458
I don't need no redneck Cadillac
Driving to Dallas
At the school book building
Way back on sixth floor
Through the daily buzzer and off into history
Kennedy Death Card
I'll be riding at the back
With my Jackie by my side
I won't care if I die
I'll be wearing a smile
Mile after mile
I'll be riding high
in the day
my Kennedy Death Car.
Kennedy Death Car.
And I'll stop and take some time with Jack Rudy's rabbi and watch Marina smile.
Spies of curtain rush.
Make it in 63.
On the cusp of history.
In my Kennedy Death Car.
Kennedy Death Car.
You know.
Time goes slowly.
Sometimes it freezes.
Into one deadly frame.
Through blood and agony we reach immortality.
162 acres.
With a drop top painted black.
And a 454.
With hardly felt trees.
I don't need no Rhythmic Cadillac.
Kennedy Death Car.
Here boy.
Womits Bib almost killed.
And he plenty here.
Has yummy speed.
I thought it must be a dream.
I saw a sun in the sky.
Hi.
Your light?
Your majesty.
Yes?
I have a new estate.
Majesty, the law clearly states that sorcerers are to be put to death.
I'm going to rule.
No, not even seven kills, I know.
Surely some managed to escape.
Find one.
One there again.
I don't know who to fight.
This is puzzling evidence, show.
I'm not sure.
No, this is reverent staying, show.
I'm just using puzzling evidence as tapes.
And where does it all go?
Well, it goes sometimes over to the east coast in a direct hiccup.
Wait, what's going on?
Yeah.
W-R-E-K.
There'll be a show crash and we'll just see if this works.
No, not another show crash.
It should be plugged in.
What again?
Looks like we've got the...
I hate it when they mix all the shows together.
There we go.
Show antenna plugged in.
No, let's not do this.
Let's split these trash bags over the microphones.
We do get kind of juicy when we start playing.
We are visiting the program of Suzy the Cluesy on W-R-E-K.
Atlanta 91.1.
And hold on, Jane, we're going to start just a minute.
When do we start ranting and clapping?
Yeah, in a minute.
In a minute.
When they see this light over here go on, then we'll rant.
Wait, I'm going to stop the tape and start over.
And in attendance at the show is Papa Joe Mama, Jane or Hypercleet, Ivan Stang.
The subgenius hour.
There they go.
I think they're...
Nope.
They can't see us and they can't hear us.
Our mics will be open at times they do not know that the mics are open.
Let's start over.
And right now, they apparently don't know that we're listening.
Yeah, we're not listening to them.
Notice how Wellman cuts when they're about to say,
The subgenius hour of slack.
But, dear friends, let's have a check out this radio shorts tape.
Eh?
And we'll see what happens.
Tonya thought it would make Nancy look bad.
Every reporter wants to do this.
Right.
Had you heard that story?
Nancy, they did it.
No, that's not true.
Denial is strong.
Getting nowhere fast.
There have been many disgusting statements.
The whole world will believe it's a lie.
Why?
Hopefully, everything's gonna work out.
God will take over and he'll make everything right.
Michael has paid three-quarters of his little boys $200,000.
Why?
These statements about me are totally false.
Meanwhile, the FBI is now examining scraps of paper.
Repugnant.
Malicious.
You always say the first thing.
These statements about me are totally false.
Malicious.
You're repugnant.
Deep spirited.
But I wouldn't read too much into it.
The truth is I'm not gonna stand here and listen anymore to this foolishness.
I was waiting for you to do something else silly.
Sorry.
Okay.
I didn't know if that was a real one or not.
No, it is, it is.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Ah!
Intolerance is a beautiful thing.
I was a guitar player and an organ player and I wanted to play rock and roll.
Intolerance.
Is a beautiful thing.
God is intolerance.
God accepts all things equally.
And that's just not true.
Well.
I don't know what the devil is into it, Hal.
But I can assure you the lyrics of those bands, not the music per se, but the lyrics, the message of those bands, is definitely devilish, hedonistic, abusive of women.
Devilish.
Hedonistic.
Abusive.
Of women.
Hedonistic.
Sincere.
Abusive.
Sinister.
And I would certainly think it's demonic.
Demonic.
God and the Bible.
We believe there's one Savior.
His name is Jesus Christ.
It is not Uncle Sam.
Uncle Sam is not the great Savior, the great healer, the great deliverer, the great food producer.
We want a nation that fears and honors God.
If we can produce the manpower and the momentum to outlaw child killing, we will then have the momentum and the manpower to outlaw pornography, to take the public education arena out of the hands of a pagan elite and restore it to parents and the community.
It's an issue of getting the God-fearing community, the Christian community, out of its views, out of its apathy, and into the cultural arena, cultural battlefields of our day.
I think this is the first blast of the trumpet.
We are going to see this country enter into the next millennium in convulsion.
Our cities are going to be ravaged.
What we saw in Los Angeles is just the beginning.
We are going to have more and more severe weather patterns hit us.
We're going to see an economic collapse that is going to produce mayhem for millions of people.
Unless we repent, we've got to slow the ramp.
But once he begins to move in judgment, he won't relent.
And I can tell you that God has a hundred hurricanes and a hundred droughts and a hundred floods and a hundred terrorists at his disposal.
I believe even that the recent beginning stages of terrorism against our nation are the judgment of God against us.
It's like God saying, okay, look, you want to terrorize babies in the womb?
I'm going to let you taste what terrorism really feels like.
This is the horrifying nature of sin and judgment.
When Sodom and Gomorrah was destroyed...
When Sodom and Gomorrah was destroyed by fire, there were little kids who were destroyed.
But it was the raving homosexuals that brought the judgment down.
What's shocking is not that God would bring judgment on the Mississippi Riverbed.
What's shocking is that he hasn't obliterated the whole country yet.
Let's just hope that we wake up before he chooses to do that.
Isn't the providence of God an amazing thing?
Intolerance is a beautiful thing.
Intolerance?
Yes, dear friends, and we're with Radio Shorts on that score.
Indeed, we are with our Radio Shorts on that hideous, hideous score.
The score of this tape, well, one of the Radio Shorts tapes.
And darn it, it doesn't have an address on it.
And why I would love...
I'm going to give you a bunch of addresses for all the material that we have just been playing.
And I think you're going to have your pencils.
Pencils.
I'm ready for that at that time.
But, you know, it is quite serious, dear friends, the way that the kids are getting these days.
In fact, I think I should switch to some more family-oriented music for this.
There, that's more like it.
Now, friends, you know, say your child comes home late every night.
It's developed a curious habit lately of listening to heavy metal rock music.
It no longer pays you any attention.
It seems preoccupying.
It spends more and more of its time away from home.
You suspect that your child is experimenting with drugs.
What can a parent do?
Well, like millions of other American youths, your child has most likely joined a satanic cult.
Though you may be shocked when you realize the truth,
it's important to bear in mind that all teenagers at one time or another join cults.
It's something that most parents don't want to face or deal with, so they try to ignore it.
Discussing devil works.
Repair systems.
You can become crafty at that and
it's a realำ
people don't want to spend half the time
Can you imagine going to high schools in rick depending on what school you think you are?
You might even want to experience the last lightest melancholy in your childhood,
with the family. While you and your spouse have been secretly worshipping
Satan in the privacy of your bedroom, you should have been sharing this intimate
ritual with your kids. Children want and need to be involved in abusive rituals
to create bonds between other family members that are strong and lasting. Now
that you know what you need to do, where do you begin? By and large, the main
reason your children should worship the devil is to help them develop
multiple personality disorders or MPDs. These are very special traits that most
children need and most likely will not receive in school. The more you tear away
at a child's self-image, the stronger it becomes. A child can only develop healthy
MPDs after experiencing years and years of cult abuse. Remember the first time
your parents abused you during a satanic ritual?
Remember how good it felt?
Well, let's talk about the discussion. Choosing the right time to speak with
your child is very important. Probably the best time for a discussion is when
your child urgently needs to use the restroom. Sit it down and tell it that it
can take care of its needs after you've had a little chat. Abruptly slap the
child in the face and tell it that it will not be allowed to leave the house
at night anymore.
If the child puts up a fight,
slap it harder. Do not allow the child to go to the bathroom until it agrees to
your demands. When it returns from the restroom, tell your child that it will be
required to attend satanic cult rituals with the family beginning the next day
after supper. Slap the child again and send it to bed. Now you may ask, why
practice rituals? Well friends, torture and pain release energy into the family
circle and increase the spiritual power of the individual.
Rituals must be precisely completed as prescribed to prevent the wrath of Satan
and his demons. The main reason for participation in rituals is to destroy
self-esteem and self-confidence. Therefore, if anyone complains that the
rituals make them feel bad, tell them that this is exactly how they're
supposed to feel. Now friends, on this family radio station, I cannot describe
to you all of the different rituals that are in this Parents Guide to Satanic Cult.
I do not know the exact description, but I can tell you that this is the first
ritual of the day. This ritual is called the L.M.N.O.P.
Yes, this L.M.N.O.P. is the author of this, which appeared in Baby Sue Magazine.
But I can tell you ritual number three, sacrificing the dog. As you and your
children should already know, any dog that is truly loyal is a dog that must
be sacrificed. Begin by petting your furry trusting friend and giving him some
to the floor. Do not bind the snout of the dog. The dog must be allowed to sing about its pain.
Each person in the family then takes part in removing the dog's skin, taking care not to
burst any main arteries. The dog must remain alive during the skinning. Once the dog has been skinned,
20 thick needles are inserted through its muscle tissue. The dog's urgent strained cries are
heavenly music to Satan's delicate ears. After it's been tortured for a minimum of 90 minutes,
throw the dog on the fire and do some serious chanting. When it stops breathing,
the ritual is over. The family can now begin discussing what kind of dog they want next.
And let's see if there's any other. Oh, well, here I can read to you the end of ritual number five,
known as the like father, like son ritual.
Women can never work.
Oh, no, I can't read this because this might offend women. But then we get into this other part.
The vials are then heated over an open fire. As soon as the semen boils, LSD is added to it.
Each family member then ingests a small amount of the mixture. Once everyone is tripping,
the family takes turn branding each other with a hot cattle prod.
Remember, any pain that may be experienced is imaginary. The ritual ends with the family playing
jingle jangle on kazoo.
The sixth ritual is relatively simple, friends. After donning black gowns and meditating for a few
moments, the family simply tries to kill one another. In this ritual, anything is game.
Individuals may use knives, sticks, bats, or anything they deem useful to them to adequately
injure other family members. The only stipulation during this ritual is that each individual must
yell, Satan is Lord, prior to delivering any cuts or blows.
Thus endeth ritual number six. And friends, if you've performed these rituals correctly,
your child will be permanently affected. The things your child should have learned are,
number one, obedience. Number two, the importance of listening to others.
Number three, respect for parents. Number four, how to play a kazoo. And five,
the difference between right and wrong. So the next time you think about going out for dinner
or to a movie, perform a satanic ritual instead.
Only save your family money, you'll save their souls as well.
Well, friends, that was from Baby Sue magazine, the new issue of Baby Sue.
And I will give you the address to write to for information on Baby Sue.
That's box 1111. That's easy enough, friends. 1111 Decatur, Georgia.
P.O. box 111141.
There. Decatur, Georgia. 30031. That's right. That zip is 30031.
And I should also give you an address to write for information for this wonderful devil-worshipping
music by The Trouble with Larry. This CD was sent to us by our good friend, Reverend Vogt.
Or Vogt. And the address to write for Trouble with Larry information is Good Kitty,
records at 201A North Davis Avenue. That's North Davis Avenue. 201A North Davis Avenue in
Richmond, Virginia. Yes, Richmond, Virginia. 23220. That's 23220.
Oh, and we also heard some radio shorts from, I believe those there. That's the other brain rot.
Brain Rot West in San Francisco. I don't have their address handy, but I will next time.
Oh, and some wonderful little piece by Reverend Nathan Vincent. And I'm tempted to put some more
Nathan Vincent on right after this lovely instrumental music that Nenslow sent us.
Oh, yes.
So to you, hanger.
When the pot goesínhmor.
To stay.
How special it is.
I'm sorry.
with another golfer about courtesy on the green.
Under least competent persons, we find Timothy Sprouse, 18,
was arrested in Cedar Rapids, Iowa in May
and charged with vandalism for painting graffiti on cars.
Sprouse had not used spray paint, but rather ordinary cans of brush-on paint,
and police were consequently able to follow a trail of paint drippings
from a car to the front door of a house on 2nd Avenue,
down the stairs, and into a storage closet
where they found the paint-speckled Sprouse hiding.
It doesn't say whether he was using red paint,
but he was certainly caught red-handed, dear friends.
And speaking of family values,
here's a couple who brawled over whether the woman who plays Peg Bundy
on Married with Children is prettier than Christina.
Christina Applegate, who plays the daughter.
First, the wife slashed Mr. Rottie in the groin with a wine bottle as they scuffled,
but she dressed his wounds, and they sat down again
to watch another episode of the show Married with Children.
Moments later, the brawl erupted again,
and Rottie, who suffered a broken arm and shoulder,
stabbed his wife in the chest, back, and legs
before they implored neighbors to call an ambulance.
Now, see, friends, you thought that that show,
uh, uh,
Natural Born Killers was some sort of a fictional, fictional thing.
Okay, uh,
and, oh, oh, here's one, this is one I can follow up with, friends.
In March, elementary school teacher Myra Obazi,
now you've heard this one on the Hour of Slack before,
this was a local Dallas piece of news,
uh, elementary school teacher Myra Obazi of Shreveport, Louisiana,
was brought bleeding from the eyes to Parkland Memorial Hospital,
Dallas, by her two sisters,
who eventually were charged with having gouged out Obazi's eyes with their fingers
because they thought she was possessed by the spirit of her father.
Detectives were unable to question Obazi for several hours
because she refused to stop chanting,
Thank you, Jesus.
Well, friends, a few weeks ago,
the Dallas papers started carrying stories day after day on the trial.
Um, it seems that, in the first day of the trial,
witnesses said that they,
they saw the two sisters holding Ms. Obazi down
in a front yard of an Oak Cliff home
and pushed garlic into her eyes.
Um, the sisters have told family members, friends, and the police
that they were fleeing a voodoo curse,
but don't remember.
They just can't remember how their sister lost her eyes.
And she has said that she doesn't want her sisters prosecuted.
Um, but they say she was possessed.
Her attorney said,
Myra's will,
was not Myra's will.
In the presence of the defendants and other family members,
she changed dramatically.
All the while, according to witnesses,
the sisters pummeled and prayed
with an apparently willing Ms. Obazi.
Almost every witness,
hotel clerks, police officers, strangers,
reported something odd about Ms. Obazi's eyes.
Her eyes were very red,
said Dorothy Hughes, a Dallas teacher,
who ran into the women during a morning walk through her neighborhood.
I just had not seen eyes like...
like that before.
They were blood red.
Waxahachie police officer Nathan Bickerstaff
spotted the women at their next stop about 5 a.m.
Between praise the Lord's hallelujahs and I love Jesus's,
they advised me that their car was possessed by the devil,
he said.
Ms. Obazi told him that her sisters got her free from the devil.
Ligalia Jones watched the police come and go,
drove from across the street.
For most of the next seven hours,
Ms. Jones testified,
the sisters shouted and prayed on her block.
At one point, she said,
they pushed garlic into Ms. Obazi's eyes
while she made, quote,
strange noises.
She was sounding like a man,
Ms. Jones said.
Then the next day,
Myra Obazi herself testified,
and here's a picture of her
with dark sunglasses on.
And she really cried,
a lot on the stand. She had trouble testifying. She said, I had an evil spirit in me. It was
controlling me. She said she did not want her sisters convicted of assault, and she denied that
they had hurt her during the two-day trip that took them from Arcadia, Louisiana to the Parkland
emergency room. Several people in the southwest Oak Cliff neighborhood where the sisters ended up
said they saw the sisters hitting her and rubbing cloves of garlic. Oh, they reported that Ms. Obasi
spoke in two women's voices and one man's voice. Like Ms. Obasi, the sisters said they could not
remember the crucial few minutes when the eyes were removed. Both said that a local hoodoist
named Benny, Benny, along with their father, Chester Crawford, had made them afraid that
another sister was involved in a cult that sought their deaths. They said Ms. Obasi was first
possessed by a demon.
She drove towards Dallas. Ms. Obasi leaned over the steering wheel, Mrs. Crawford said,
and when she turned around, it wasn't her. Ms. Obasi's eyes bulged weirdly, Ms. Crawford said.
Her tongue was long and strangely colored. Quote, mist came out of her mouth. Her teeth
was black and scattered. By the way, I'm not doing these sisters' accents as they probably
were spoken.
But close enough. The evil spirit said it got her and it was going to get us, too, in a gross man's
voice. Earlier Tuesday, a doctor who worked at Parkland had explained that removing someone's
eyes would, quote, not be exceedingly difficult, unquote, if the victim were properly restrained.
The biggest problem would be cutting the optic nerve. But Ms. Johnson testified that neither
she nor her sister ever had long fingernails, which could have been used. Ms. Johnson said,
to sever, yes, friends, sever the optic nerve. And the next day, why, those two sisters were found
guilty of gouging out their sisters' eyes. The jury just didn't go for it. But the prosecutor said
that, oh no, this was the defense lawyer, said Ms. Obasi's reluctance to press charges was based on
her dependence on her family and her sisters.
He said, quote, because of family influences, she's blinded to reality. He told jurors that they would
send the wrong message by acquitting the sisters. Oh, this, yeah, this is the prosecutor. Oh, yeah,
come on down to Dallas County and say the devil made me do it, he said, and we'll set you free.
The jury apparently agreed, convicting both sisters of aggravated assault. And the judge asked the
jurors, quote,
what is the price for a pair of eyes? And finally, the very last story, the next day, the sisters were
given, here's the price of a pair of eyes, 10 years probation. Ms. Obasi had asked prosecutors not to
pursue the case and testified on her sister's behalf. She said she thanked God for the probationary
sentences, but was unhappy with the guilty verdict. I don't agree with that, she said.
I don't agree with that. She said she thanked God for the guilty verdict. I don't agree with that, she said.
Oh, and my sisters are my best friends. They love me, and I love them. I know that they did not do this.
Only true, oh, and one of the sisters said, and I quote, only true believers in Christ can understand
what we went through. If you're a Christian, then you know there's a devil. And the most amazing,
quote, came at the very end of the very last article about the blinded Ms. Obasi.
Ms. Obasi said she looks forward to spending time with her siblings and doesn't fear a recurrence of
the demon that she says took her sight. I know it won't come back, Ms. Obasi said. I believe God and
his word. If there's anything I want people to realize from this case, it's that God is real.
I am living proof that he's real.
Uh, yes, friends, the tales of the two sisters. Or the three sisters, rather. And, uh, let's see,
what other horrible, horrible, horrible news of the weird. Actually, I go through these and mark
the ones that I think are particularly interesting. At first, you see, don't you see? In January of
this year, the year of the dog, the city of Beijing, China, prohibited its citizens from
trying to hide dogs in their homes. Recently, a park opened north of the city to rent dogs for
patrons to walk at the price of about 23 cents for 10 minutes. In April, Feng Kuantang filed a
lawsuit in Shenyang, China, asking for damages from the government because inspectors allegedly
beat his illegal dog to death in front of him. Well, see, there just ain't no human rights,
ain't even no canine rights in China.
Friends, in April, in New Orleans, a fleeing bank robber fired several shots at a police
officer, but nearly hit a nearby 38-year-old nun from the Sisters Servants of Mary Convent.
The nun's wound was slight because the bullet first passed through the prayer book she was
carrying. And here is, uh, these guys got the award for most dysfunctional family. In Oxnard,
California, Dale.
Rochester, 22, was sentenced to three years in prison for raping the pregnant girlfriend of his brother, Ruben.
His brothers, Leonard and Samuel, are serving long prison terms for the violent rapes of five women in
separate incidents, and Ruben is serving time for robbery and assault. Their father is a local pastor,
and their mother, a Christian missionary. And police and prosecutors say there's no evidence of the
childhood abuse that typically portends such adult violence.
And, uh...
In Italy, Italian physics student, Lino Mizzio, 26, announced in Rome that he had just patented a condom that will play
Beethoven if it breaks during use. The condom is coated with a substance that changes electrical
conductivity upon rupture, setting off a microchip that produces the sound. Uh, Mizzio said he might
include, instead of music, a verbal warning to the participants to stop what they're doing immediately.
Uh, huh.
Beethoven upon rupture.
Oh, and here, here, I'll, I'll, uh...
Well, now, here's some art. Some stories of great art. This is what passes for great art in our world these days, friends.
Uh, reviewing a body of art by minimalist Richard Serra in November, of which a large drawing consisting only of a black rectangle within a white circle.
A square was typical. A Los Angeles Times critic described the work as known for its, quote,
inflexible austerity,
ungiving impenetrability,
and stubborn bombast.
Also, the work was described as
sensuous,
exquisite and delicate,
extremely weighty,
grave and authoritative,
and of fugitive beauty.
That is what an art critic can find to say about a highly enough price to pay.
A modest black square with a white frame.
Oh, and here, great art moves all the way to Beijing, again, in China.
Police raided a performance art show that consisted of the artist Ma Liu Ming, naked, cooking potatoes in a pot along with a watch and an earring, and then burying the potatoes.
Li Ming and ten audience members were detained by the authorities.
And, uh, here's another. This artist, Ronnie Nicolino, is trying to collect
10,000 bras to string across the Grand Canyon
to symbolize the chas- the chasm between human nature and America's obsession with breasts.
Uh, he is now has over 2,000 bras,
but prospects of his getting permission to rig the Grand Canyon are still dim.
Uh, well, dim indeed.
Oh, and here, I gotta go, I gotta do this one.
Recent tragedies befalling people while worshipping.
At least 250 Muslims were trampled to death while inching toward a cave for the symbolic stoning of the devil during the annual pilgrimage in Mecca, Saudi Arabia.
Ten Tanzanian Seventh-day Adventists drowned trying to walk on water as a test of faith near Dal Es Salaam in October.
More than a hundred people drowned near Canaan.
Two people were killed in Calcutta in January as two boats returning from a Hindu pilgrimage collided.
And three churches were destroyed and 19 worshippers killed during Palm Sunday services when tornadoes struck in Piedmont, Alabama.
Seems like God just ain't fair.
Just- it just ain't fair, my friends.
Well, okay, enough news of the weird, and we'll pass on or pass out to, uh, whatever's-
Oh, oh, I should!
Hey, would you like to hear a funny joke?
This isn't news anymore, these are jokes, and they come from funny pages.
Oh, and now you people remind me to give the address of these things when I get finished here.
What's the difference between Rush Limbaugh and the Hindenburg?
One is a flaming Nazi gas bag, the other's just a dirigible.
What do you get when you cross a Jehovah's Witness
with a Unitarian?
Someone who knocks on your door for no reason.
Why did O.J. sit in the Bronco for so long?
Because Rodney King told him he better not get out of that car.
Uh, yes, friends, there's, uh, funny pages, actually.
I'm not good at telling jokes, I know it.
I tell, uh, you know, as they say, I tell jokes like a subgenius.
I can only spew and spout,
but I have trouble repeating other people's stuff.
In fact, even common ordinary clichés, I always get them mixed up.
I, I mix two into one without knowing it.
But, but here's some subgenius jo-
actually, these weren't originally subgenius jokes, but they work just as well.
How does a subgen- how do you know a subgenius has ju- a subgenius gal has just lost her virginity?
Her crayons are still sticky.
Hehehehehe.
Eh.
How do most subgenius men make love?
Right-handed.
Uh, why did the subgenius massage parlor go out of business?
It was self-serve.
When is a pink girl good in bed?
When she's trying to dry her shoe polish.
Well, well.
How do you, uh, do you know how to get a nun pregnant?
Dress her up like an altar boy.
This traveling salesman is out in the middle of nowhere and his car breaks down.
So he goes up to the nearest farmhouse to ask for a hand.
The farmer says he can take the salesman to town the next day, but he'll have to stay the night.
The farmer says,
There isn't much room, so you'll have to sleep with my son.
The salesman replies,
Oh, I'm in the wrong joke.
Hehehehehe.
Heh.
Time packs.
We're not the best product in the world, but we're right up there next to it.
Why do you have to take two Mormons with you fishing?
If you only take one, he'll drink all your beer.
Why do men have a urethra?
So oxygen can get to their brains.
What did the missionary bring to the cannibals?
A little taste of religion.
And, dear friends, why did Bill Clinton cross the road?
To meet the chick.
Did you hear that Michael Jackson was taken to the emer...
Did you hear that Michael Jackson was taken to the emergency room?
He was choking on a small bone.
And finally, what's a feminopsy?
A woman who wouldn't sleep.
With Rush.
Thank you.
And, uh, yes, those are all from this amazing little newsletter, Funny Pages,
which most of the jokes in here are too foul or un-PC, what have you,
for me to say on the radio, but I can give you their address,
and you can get information from them.
That's Funny Pages at P.O. Box...
Got that pencil ready?
317-025.
That's Box 317-025, Dayton, Ohio.
That's O-H. Dayton, O-H.
45437.
Okay? That's 45437 for Funny Pages.
Excuse me, I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
I was... I forgot.
I...
It seems time has come.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to say time that way, my friends.
And News of the Weird, you can get information about News of the Weird
from Chuck Shepherd at P.O. Box 8306.
That's Box 8306, St. Petersburg, Florida.
8306, St. Petersburg, Florida, 33738.
That is, once again, 33738.
Yes, friends, and at the end of this broadcast,
we will tell you just what all, uh,
there is to get from the mighty Church of the Subgenius.
Uh, well, actually, we'll just tell you where to write for that information.
But in the meantime, let's just listen to some instrumental music here by So-So Donna.
So-So Donna Haddon
That wasn't my part.
Couldn't you sunbathe a little prettier?
You're a dead man, Amy, this welcomed Phineas.
Try really hard, you with me.
Thank you.
But I think that it's wrong to shut down Robert Tilton for fleecing little old ladies.
Because think about it.
Who's spending the money more wisely?
Bob Tilton or the little old ladies?
Hell, they spend it on him.
It's better spent.
Bob Tilton might be tempted to spend it on the church of the subgenius.
He might be in here at Starwood for all we know with the long-haired wig on.
I wouldn't put it past him.
He's a slack preacher.
There's another great preacher named Dr. Gene Scott.
Dr. Gene Scott.
Anybody familiar with Dr. Gene Scott?
He's the one.
He looks kind of like an old gray-haired hippie.
Wears a cowboy hat.
And he actually, he sometimes, like if people aren't calling the number on the screen, thank you.
He'll sit there and go, well, nobody's calling in.
I'm just going to leave.
And he'll leave.
They'll show the chair for hours and hours.
But other times, he'll say, you want to know what we spend your money on that you're pledging to us with your faith prayers?
Roll that.
Take, Bobby.
Hurry up.
Roll it.
And then Bobby will roll the tape.
And it'll be nice home movies of his racehorses, his girlfriends, his mansion, his swimming pool.
And the great Gene Scott would say that he'd go, now all the other TV preachers do the same thing with the money that I do.
But I've got more respect for you as viewers.
Because I know that you don't want a stupid preacher.
Praise.
Honesty on the airwaves is so hard to come by, dear friends.
I want to have those racehorses.
I want to have that mansion.
All the subgeniuses.
We're running around here using old throwaway technology that they consider normal.
They actually invented for the space wars they did back in the 60s.
We could all be space traveling billionaires.
And instead, they've got us working jobs.
A lot of us anyway.
Well, I should speak for myself.
This is my job.
It doesn't pay worth it.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to, got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Stay tuned and praise God.
Thanks, Bob.
God is standing there ready to say to you, hey, don't order this.
It ain't what you need.
But we don't listen.
God can heal you.
God can heal our land.
And it's all going to begin with prayer.
I am a Christian.
And as I read the New Testament of the Bible, I discovered something about Jesus.
Oh, by the way, I'm not supposed to mention the name of Jesus.
We don't want to make this a Protestant affair.
We don't want to make it a Christian affair.
So I'm just going to refer to the Son of God as Bob.
As I studied the life of Bob in my Bible,
I discovered that he didn't teach the disciples anything in Greek.
He didn't teach them how to build a great church or how to market it.
He didn't even teach them how to take offerings.
You know what he taught them how to do?
He taught them how to pray.
Kill Lord!
Kill!
Kill those who do not believe!
Kill wretches!
Kill accusers!
Kill long-haired, maggot-infested children of the sixties rejects!
Satan, kill your mom!
Satan, kill your children!
Lord, help us deal with the death and the emanation of the forces of evil!
I pray!
Die, all ye that I pray!
Please, Lord, help us in our war against Satan!
Kill!
Die!
Kill Satan!
Die for God!
Can't you see what's happening in conspiracy?
A seeking battle of war and God!
But now the war on Satan!
The killing of Satan!
They're killing Christians!
They're killing Blacks!
God, they will kill Whites!
They kill Jews!
They kill Moslems!
They kill Ori and Iultim, Malus!
Friends, you're listening to the Church of New Faith.
You may reach and send donations to Church of New Faith at P.O. Box 9152, Virginia Beach, Virginia.
That's Box 9152, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 23450.
Thank you.