Now you've turned your record over and you're all ready for some more Sing Time sing-along songs.
Matthew 5, 16. Let your light so shine before men, that they may see your good works and glorify your Father which is in heaven.
And welcome here to Polka, Polka, Polka.
Polka, Polka, Polka.
Very good. Well, it's delightful to have all of you with us here today. Beautiful family here. You should all be very proud.
As we all are. Let's go back up to the stage here and pick up another song here. Another Polka or what? What are we doing here this time around?
I think it's the Soul Genius Powerhouse.
What?
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo.
Hello.
You gotta tell him. You gotta tell him.
I'll tell him.
You gotta tell him.
What?
Silent free this bomb.
Oh.
Oh, my.
Oh, dear.
Eat, eat.
My own pie.
Right, Bob?
Bob.
Bob?
Hi. My name is Rachel and my telephone number is 351-0527.
I wanted to tell you that you're evil, horrible people.
You're awful people. You represent horrible ideas.
God hates you and he wants to kill your children.
You should all burn in hell. Bye.
I'll sue you for this.
Oh, superstitious, eh?
Hey.
Right, Mrs.
I Prem, ran around and took out my cellphone call.
Oh, too bad.
I'm sick and tired of yelling out that he's so stupid,orous little pass.
Just syrup the things that my religion was telling me I would.
Quite with you.
You didn't miss my first trip?
You just cut me off.
Steve, I beg your pardon.
Oh, God.
You broke it.
Are you sick?
Rose, dear friends, did that marvelous old angst mine, as they call it.
And this is the first show of the year 2005, conspiracy year 2005.
But mine is not angst, friends, but slack.
Because we brought all these great recordings back from our subgenius frop tour of Jura.
Heard in the background.
And the artists of alt.binaries.slack brought up all these cool mixes from their scary tours into their own minds.
Such as the new intros by Mr. Sister and Fernanda Nende-Lin-Mur.
And so, friends, without any further or future or dure, let us go back into that digital tape recording.
Of this live revival at The Bad Kite in Amsterdam, Holland.
Just as it really happened.
We should all join together.
I know some of you are new to our congregation here.
And perhaps curious to see what sort of a hideous freak show it is.
It's really a little worse than you expected, to tell the truth, I promise.
But if you could just join us briefly.
We could bow our heads for a solid...
Yeah.
Quiet moment of sacred damn NOPE!
Yeah!
It's so good to see the children of Bob.
And these particular children of Bob.
He's been very busy.
You know, he's a very horny messiah, you might say.
He's a cross-species lover.
But not...
And not just Earthlings.
He's a very earth animal.
He's like this mighty museum-quality prairie squid here.
But also non-Earth creatures.
Well, I don't know if he's real proud of that.
So let's not linger on it.
About 300 years ago, a bunch of really clever, highly developed European countries,
like this one, England, Germany, and so forth, decided,
Hey!
Let's get rid of our insane religious nuts by sending them to the New World!
Well, that was probably a good idea at the time.
But now we have come back to haunt you.
Actually, not the church of the subgenius I'm talking about.
Unfortunately, I mean George W. Bush.
And just to get this over with, believe me, I'm tired of this.
But on behalf of, really, most Americans,
almost all of the US subgeniuses, and even some Texans,
Please liberate us!
You must free us from the mad dictator!
We've been taken away!
We have no free elections!
Our women are forced to wear makeup all the time!
They teach creation science in our schools!
They judge us for our fitness, for work, by our pee!
They judge us by our pee, my friends!
So please, you must...
We were allies in the war, he was coming to liberate us!
We need freedom in America!
We must have slack!
Woo!
Slack!
And, my friends, slack is getting harder and harder to find.
And there's more false slack everywhere we go, it seems.
Woo!
We've been traveling through Europe this trip.
And it's been a lot of fun, but it's also frightening,
because we would go to these nice little traditional towns,
like Lüneburg in Germany.
It's a nice little traditional town, these beautiful old houses,
and ancient churches, and you look down the street,
it's like a classic theme park of Germany land or something,
but there, at the end of the block,
McDonald's.
Starbucks.
And no Bob!
And no fucking Bob!
If you're going to take this stupid bullshit from the US,
make it Bob!
Not the conspiracy, but try a new conspiracy for a change.
Really, it was, it's so sad.
But we will continue seeking the perfect hamburger.
The hamburger of perfect slack, you might say.
That's what we're really looking for.
That and a little more money.
But we'll continue.
But once we get that burger, that perfect burger,
we will not just eat it like the normal humans do.
No, we will be subgeniuses!
We will eat the hell out of it!
Or in another way, to quote the great saint of Amsterdam,
Jeroen van Bram, who might, who knows,
maybe he'll be here later tonight,
as he told us, you have to shout and make a lot of noise,
or whatever, because when you die, you shut up like hell.
Yes, and so, later on, even I will shut up like hell,
and I'm sure you'll be glad.
But friends, in the meantime, open your hearts,
unzip your lips and your trousers,
pull out your wallets and bend over,
because I am going to preach the word of Bob!
You know, they say that Moses,
Moses parted the Red Sea,
and that the great scientist Oppenheimer split the atom.
But Bob, Bob cuts the crap, my friends!
He cuts through the bullshit!
Actually, he uses powerful bullshit to cut through the bullshit, but...
We're here, that's right, we're here in Ludenburg, Germany,
in our subgenius crusade of slack,
trying to put a Dobbs head in every German's hand.
Praise Bob!
Putting a Dobbs head on every ancient painting hanging in the church.
Yup, yup, yup, yup!
Yeah, we covered all those crucifixion pictures with Dobbs heads, it was funny.
It's going to be hard to peel those off of those ancient canvases.
That unicorn over there...
Einhorn apothecary.
You know what is less sinister is that was a Lutheran church.
Oh.
That was, there's a Protestant church.
They break away from the Catholic...
It was built as a Catholic church, but it ended up breaking away when Martin Luther was...
And now it's a McDonald's.
Now it's a McDonald's, yeah.
Well, that's, I guess that's, there's a horrible or wonderful history lesson in that.
Depends on who wins, how the history will come out.
Now where to?
Follow me.
Martin Luther.
Martin Luther, the leader of the German Reformation, was born in Eiselben, Germany.
Life in the Luther home was simple and religious.
At the beginning of the dry season, they construct a sort of mud cocoon or burrow.
Martin Luther's father sent him to school to become a lawyer.
After going to Preparatory schools, he entered the University of Erfurt in 1501.
He had barely begun his study of law when he decided to enter the Erfurt cloister of the Augustinian Order,
in which they remain until the next wet season.
Since the life of a monk was considered a sure way into heaven, he entered the monastery to save his soul.
It usually weighs from 15 to 20 pounds and is covered with scales.
A bowl of excommunication was issued in January 1521, and Luther was called to appear at the Doctrine of the Church.
In April, Luther was ordered to retract all of his openings to admit air.
Luther replied that he could not in good conscience breathe air like a reptile.
In May, the Diet condemned him as a heretic.
On the way back to Wittenberg, he was kidnapped by friends who took him for safekeeping to the Wartburg Castle,
where they often make a cave-like mess for themselves.
There he made his translation of the New Testament into German.
When Luther was sapphira希ipp, he was a friend of Paul as a Muslim
who decided to do seuph Utah, one of the authority powers here in Lutheran fabric,
where it is found that his family müsste le pione and he did heresia di Trinit passhead d'Union,
who died just 15 time after Muslims had first convenient.
drugs, adultery, prostitution, prostituting ourselves like we're doing now.
Remember to call that number and make your pledge.
We're all whores, friends.
We're all whores for the man.
Come on, face it.
If it's going to be the man, which man do you want it to be?
Big Brother or Bob?
Bob's cool for the man as the man goes.
I guess that's not saying much.
But if you've got to have a man, let it be Bob.
He's the lesser of two evils as far as we know.
Bob sucks less?
Bob sucks less.
He blows more.
He blows far more.
Bob blows more.
Blow Bob before he blows you.
She said Bob blows more.
Again, we have to scabble our truth.
Brother of Roger Moore.
You want to have fun on me?
You exotic, narcissistic people.
It's time for a shift change.
I need to take a shift.
And I think that we need to hear more English voices on this show.
More English voices, huh?
Well, let's go to the Hamburg revival at the Fundbüro
to hear an Englishman preach to some Germans
while the German...
...trains run on time overhead.
I am proud to introduce to you
one of the greatest preachers
because he speaks for such a short time.
Oh, Mickey Finn!
Yeah!
Oh, and he's not kidding.
When he's in a short time,
I mean a short time.
Well, I think there's nothing for us here to join together now.
Put your hands in the hand of the person next to you
and let's sing a spiritual one because...
Bob.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Alistair Darman.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
No, brethren, sisters and Bob don't ever change.
Well, that's not strictly true.
Bob changes all the fart of getting time.
One day, Bob's your friend.
Bob's your daddy.
Bob's your buddy.
Bob's your uncle.
Next day, you're sponging up the blood from your tattered anus
and you're wondering where your credit card went.
But this is why Bob is by far the fightingest,
violentest, sexiest religious figurehead there is.
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
How many of you lost a girlfriend you only ever treated with respect
and consideration to some arsewipe with a personality disorder
and a hygiene deficit because he was more exciting than you?
Women, how many of you lost your chap to whom you were only ever faithful
and understanding to some skanky hoe with no knickers?
All of you, all of you.
And if you haven't, you will because that is the law.
So just accept that steady and reliable is a dead end spiritually.
Bob is nebulous.
Bob is fibulous.
Bob is fabulous.
No, sir, accept Bob into your life and you will not tire of him and his shit-eating idiot grin.
Bob is wider and tighter, wetter and more ribbed.
Harder and softer than any other saviour in today's crowded metaphysical marketplace.
Bob will turn your sins into sex.
Bob will wash your feet with somebody else's pubic hair.
Bob will cure your blindness but give you herpes.
You can get high off Bob tonight and then drink your own urine tomorrow
and get twice as high.
With so many things these days, you build up a tolerance.
On your seventh straight day of acid, you can pass your driving test.
The so-called law of diminishing returns.
Not with the outlaw, Bob.
With Bob you develop sacred intolerance.
Every trip with Bob is 99 times more intense than the one before.
The law of astonishing rug burns.
On your seventh straight trip with Bob, you can't even pass water.
Your brain, once wrinkled with knowledge,
is now smooth and shiny as if boiled.
And once you have created that blank mental canvas,
what wonders you can be reprogrammed with.
The very real machinations of the Church of the Subgenius
make the Manchurian candidate look like a magic eye picture.
Bob will program you to assassinate him.
He'll ring the doorbell of your soul and then he'll run away.
Bob is the ultimate absentee deputy.
He'll beat Dad.
You may hate him, but you can't help wondering if you look like him.
For make no mistake, we are all Bob's children.
And I'm not talking metaphorically here.
That was one busy fornicator.
You think screaming Jay Hawkins was busy?
Uh-uh.
Compared to Bob, he looked like a eunuch.
Show your mother a picture of Bob and see the anguish in her eyes.
Show your father the same thing,
and see the resignation.
Bob begat you.
Bob will beget you.
The circle is complete.
Death taxes Bob.
Yeah!
Ladies and gentlemen, you've given me 40 minutes of your time.
Thank you very much indeed.
Yeah, every time you say those words, it means a month and a half of trouble for me, Bob.
It means hundreds of thousands of taxpayers' dollars.
I know.
We gotta pay to keep the company quiet.
We gotta pay damages.
Erase memories.
Relocate your family.
Every time it gets harder.
Money, money, money, money, money.
We can't keep doing this, Bob.
We appreciate what you did in the old days, but those days are over.
From now on, you're on your own.
Uh, but you see, my friends, you can be alone with Bob.
And it's not like being alone with, say, a giant rubber inflatable octopus.
It's sexy, though that might well be.
And, friends, the pope of all spirits, Bob,
the great Rombo Bach, used just such a giant inflatable rubber octopus
to demonstrate his point during his sermon at the Amsterdam Frop Cup Divival of 2004.
I'm gonna explain the octopus to you.
Great Rombo!
Can you see the octopus?
It's big.
It's yellow.
It has eight arms.
And it's just big.
It's not like the conspiracy.
It's got this stupid grin.
It's got something like a pipe.
But he's not Bob!
He's trying to tip you.
He's trying to sell you something that is not for real.
He's trying to give you false slack.
He's a false prophet!
He came here.
See, they blame me.
I took care.
I didn't take care of other people.
I've stayed around here.
He's here.
He's a imbecile.
A real rebel weapon.
Moron!
Aeremos
H истории
Te
Des
No
Musik
That's what you have to do with the conspiracy!
Burn it over for your own needs!
They own you alive!
Get it back!
Get your fucking slack back!
Because if you don't, they will eat you up!
Now I want to explain another thing.
I want to explain more.
Look at that man!
What kind of man does have that face?
Or this face? Or this?
Or that face over there?
That's a happy man!
But he's not just a normal happy man.
He's a satisfied man!
And what kind of satisfaction gives you that face?
Rolling stone satisfaction?
No!
A slack satisfaction!
You get enough slack, you get that face for yourself!
So walk away!
Burn it!
Until you get that fucking face on you!
And now I want to explain one last thing.
I want to explain this.
Most of you can't see this.
This is one of the most stupid, ugly, ugly things I ever saw!
This is completely stupid!
But as Bob said, the more stupid it looks, the most important it is!
So right now, this is going to save our lives!
I don't know how.
Bob knows!
Ask him!
But this will save your life!
Thank you!
Praise God!
That's right!
God's power!
Once you've had Bob's microphone rammed up you from behind, you never, ever stop talking again!
It's like a continuous scream.
Once Bob has had you like that, you're never going to stop preaching!
Your scream, your preaching, is like a continuation of that initial
that you feel when Bob comes into your life.
Ah yes, yes, yes...
That's the spirit!
That's the down home spirit.
We're not making fun of those crazy old preachers.
We're trying to bring that back.
We're trying to preserve that.
Don't you see?
They're trying to rob away the passion.
But I'm not a number.
I'm a free man.
The loudspeakers spoke up and said,
colonialism is good.
Subgenius is stupid.
They were right.
As long as, until the revolution comes, the subgenius will party and bullshit, party
and bullshit, and party and bullshit.
That's all there is to it.
That's bullshit.
We'll bullshit and bullshit.
Bullshit, bullshit and bullshit.
Enada, enada.
It's artistic.
Spew and spout.
Spew.
It must be just about out of battery, so.
It must be just about gone.
I'm going to do some serious chugging.
Oh.
Mama's staying.
Oh, my God.
What is he doing?
He's outside.
It's awesome.
Now you said a lot.
Oh, God.
There are those who the fire of Bob is lit under them,
and they can't stop spouting.
And there are those who every now and then a tiny nugget will come up
and fall out and amaze the world.
That's true. It takes all kinds, Bob said.
That was one of his wisest.
It takes all kinds.
It takes all kinds, yes.
Bob was the first to realize that it indeed,
well, it's a silly platitude, actually, like most of what Bob said.
That it sounds good, though.
And that's what you want.
That's what you need in a religion, something that sounds good.
A platitude that you all want.
It doesn't need some work.
God forbid that it actually worked.
Then you'd be some kind of a religious nut.
But it nearly makes sense.
Yeah, it just makes you feel good long enough
to drag your ass through another long day at work.
Whatever gets you through the day, Bob said.
Bob said that.
Oh, that's one of his.
Yeah.
Many have ripped Bob off.
They steal from Bob because they're jealous of his slime.
And they think they've got away with it.
But when the huge corporate copyright case in the sky comes down,
shortly before 1998.
Oh, yeah.
Then they'll find out who's been golfing partners with old God.
John Lennon up against the wall.
Thank you for abusing my wife like that, Rambo.
Thank you.
I just wanted to come up here and announce,
one of the greatest sub-genius preachers
and one of the most holy men I know of.
He's been to both end-of-the-world celebrations.
The first one in Europe and the first one in America.
He is Al-Hajj, Al-Hajj, Haz-Kim, Haz-Matt.
Salak.
Haz-B.
The Kaiser, Carl X.
Salak.
I am here to do the sub-genius quarter century report.
In 25 years, we are the second biggest UFO cult on the planet.
We are much cheaper than Scientology.
But we have better genes than the Raelians.
What happened to some of those others?
Woo!
What happened to?
Heaven's Gate. Their saucers came and took them away. At least we think. Our saucers came and
screwed us. In 1998, in 1999, in 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004. But not in 2000. Another saucer cult from Texas,
Tian Chao. They came and went so fast nobody's even heard of them. They were down the street from me. I didn't even go. In 25 years, Scientology bought three crapped out freighters, sailed around the world and called their Apollo project and mostly got their asses kicked. In 25 years, the Mormons wiped out a wagon train passing through Utah just to settle an old grudge. In 25
years, we spiked the Olympics. The subgenius Olympic doping committee spiked the Olympics. It was in all the news. And we even said we were going to do it on the stage last year on the back of our shirts. So what will happen 25 years from now? What will we do in 25 years? We'll buy out Scientology. We'll buy that building and have it on the news side's forward call.
Next to the police station. We will clean out Al Ron Hubbard's desk that you see in the window when you walk by there every day. We will pry that head off that desk and we will launch it. And in 25 years, since the present government is dusting off the old blasphemy laws, it will be illegal to make fun of Bob. You won't get away from Bob. He'll be on TV. He'll be everywhere.
Yeah.
The Bob Channel.
I don't think that's about it.
Now, friends, it just dawned on me that this subgenius, the Bible, is missing something.
Yeah, an audience.
Now, there's one of the most sacred.
There's one of the most sacred rituals we can perform tonight.
And I want to ask the Reverend Ivan Stang to come up here and perform this ritual.
Ladies and gentlemen, we here tonight are going to perform a subgenius divorce.
That's right, my friends. We're going to have a divorce.
Because when you join the church of the subgenius, you marry Bob.
But when you join the church.
You divorce the conspiracy.
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob.
And I want Brother Stang to come up here and divorce me from this creature of Ivan's slap.
I've already slipped.
Pope Wyatt, now come back up here, Pope Wyatt.
The first thing I want you to do is give me your watch.
Give me that watch over here.
All right.
I took this man's watch.
Pope Wyatt, first, do you reject the conspiracy law that has done to you in your life?
I have rejected.
Rejected.
Pope Wyatt, is this your wrist watch?
Yes, it is.
Do you recognize the fact that this is a handcuff?
This is a leash that holds you, that binds you to that conspiracy.
Are you willing to give up this handcuff that you spent $150 on?
This fine gold?
This fine gold handcuff?
Are you really willing to sacrifice that much for your divorce from the conspiracy?
I divorce the conspiracy.
I give it up to the pawn shop.
Now take your foot off the microphone cord and watch closely as I symbolize your divorce
from the conspiracy.
Now get a close look, friends, because this is an expensive watch.
Yes!
Ah yes!
We have disemboweled the handcuff of anti-slap.
This was a- oh, it's still ticking.
No, actually, it's not.
It's dead, it's useless.
It's the visible watch.
You can see the intricate workings, just as intricate as the conspiracy that once controlled
you.
I'm healed!
Yay!
Woo!
This does mean that you'll still be able to pay me back the money you owe me, right?
No!
No, no.
Friend, because when you get divorced from the conspiracy, you're still not divorced
from J.R.
Bob Dog's.
Once Bob, once you've felt Bob's love come at you from behind, my friends, you'll never
get over it.
That opening will never shrink back down to its former size.
You will feel Bob every time you go to the bathroom.
Never turn your back on Bob.
You can't turn your back on Bob, friends, except when you bow down to him.
And that's the way you bow to Bob, is with your back to him.
And that conspiracy bitch can have her children, too!
Friends, the altar boy, Black, has been saved!
Saved! Saved! Saved!
Maybe we'll let him have his polka hat back one of these days.
Don't give it to Biggin' the Biggin'! Don't give it to Barry McGregor!
Mr. Trey!
Do you know me?
Have fun!
Praise Bob!
Oh yeah!
I'll destroy Bob afterwards!
Friends, that was Leeville.
And I'm going to spell that for you.
L-E-E-V-I-L
At the foundry.
In London.
The Second London Revival.
Oh, listen, you can hear the train going overhead.
We're sitting in the basement of the Fundbureau in Hamburg right now,
listening to the Avant Garde Orchestra.
Eh, friends, unfortunately, while the videos of Leeville are great,
because Leeville is great, the audio on those videos is not real good,
and so hopefully next week we will have some studio recordings of the great,
Leeville.
But now, let us hear this mix by Reverend Phineas Narco from the National Cynical Network.
I get like this funny feeling.
See?
You think it's a blessing to know what God wants?
All I can think about is like...
He wants to push me over.
Trying to snuff it.
I'm a liar.
I just want to die peacefully.
A hypocrite.
Like with no pain.
I feel very miserable.
I'm afraid of everything.
Very much down in spirits.
I don't ever tell the truth. I don't have the courage.
I feel very low in myself.
And I'm afraid.
I can't see much in the future.
I don't steal, I don't fight, I don't kill.
And I feel that...
Not because I don't want to, but because I'm afraid.
And I feel that any second, something terrible is going to happen to me.
I'm afraid.
Something terrible is going to happen to me.
Hi kids, I'm Casey Sausage-Casing.
Remember the 1990s when clinical depression and self-mutilation were all the rage?
Well now you can relive those self-deprecating golden years with K-Tel's new record offer entitled, I Suck.
That's the letter I and the word suck.
You'll get Bex, I'm a loser.
I'm a loser baby.
Radioheads, I'm a crook.
But I'm a freak.
Silver Shards, I'm a freak.
I'm a freak.
And you'll also get Living La Vida Loca and everything by the sales every week.
I'm a loser.
Kill me.
Shoot me.
Whoo hvis cual youngest
Kill me.
Rivers.
We're organisation shinning Balmungus gorgeous.
So many money.
All not funny
profile
Myself
Your
Other
My
flattery
Your
Myself
kill me
oh yes friends that was Phineas Narco
who mixed that part of
National Cynical Radio
you can get a lot more
at www.nationalcynical.com
Can you believe it?
This thing is still running.
The whole station is still running.
It's just amazing.
And look what we've done to it already.
We dragged it through the streets.
We drove it too fast.
We bumped it into things.
We got other shows all tangled up in it.
We hurt the show.
We embarrassed the show.
We shamed the show.
The show blushed.
The show blushed through the show.
We wrecked the show.
The show blushed and turned away.
And yet it is still here.
Oh, right.
That's the one thing you can say about it.
It may suck, but it's still here.
Enron?
No, they're gone.
Aren't they?
No, they live on in some other form.
There's another name.
There was some clever accounting there.
Enron will bubble up again.
It is like a...
Well, anyway, the point is we're still here.
And we may suck, but by God,
you know, that's...
It's part of Bob's point.
We're still here.
Unfortunately, lots of other things
have sucked so much worse than us.
That's the most horrible part.
Think how bad we are.
Most of them are worse.
It's true.
Face it.
As bad as this is,
it's worse on television.
Oh, you know?
Well, not for much longer.
I mean, after a while,
I'm sure you probably will be shaking the chair
when I'm setting it up.
But first,
but really,
you know,
deep down in your heart,
what I'm going to say next.
And that is praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
When in doubt, just praise Bob.
You don't even...
You just whip it out.
When you are faced with indecision in your life,
when you are at a turning point,
a crossroads in your life,
just unzip your pants,
pull it out,
and face Bob.
And say, praise Bob,
I'm going to go where Bob points me.
Spin around three times,
and head off in the direction you end up pointing.
And tuck it back in before you get to town.
And friends, if you are about to change the tunnel,
bear in mind...
Do it!
Bear in mind that you may have already heard too much,
and it may have got under your skin now.
And within the space of a couple of days,
you may still...
It's so subliminal.
Subliminal.
It's not the words we're saying,
it's the silence between the words.
That's why we've made our music.
We have to really let it sink in.
That's right.
That's a message.
Those unheard frequencies.
You can't hear.
Yeah, you can't hear it.
But your dog is going wild right now.
He's doing backflips
because of some of the information we're imparting here.
Subliminal.
I want you to put your hands together for the Pope of all Northern England.
And if we're lucky, we'll get to see both the Popes of England jello wrestle later.
But I want you to put your hands together for the Pope of all Northern England,
the Pope Phil Monty.
Good evening, brothers and sisters, boys and girls, friends.
Hello, Uncle Monty!
Once again, I stand before you,
having said I will never stand before you on stage ever again.
Not to rant, but to testify.
I want to testify about something that Reverend Stang mentioned briefly.
One of Bob's tenets.
Repent! Quit your job!
Slack!
To put my testimony in context,
we have to go back about 12 years or so,
to two days before I left England to visit America
to attend my first ever subgenius revival,
which was in Chicago,
billed as the World Subgenius Convention.
Two days before I left,
my place of work,
which I hated,
which I hated intensely,
and I would have walked out at any moment for free,
gave me the opportunity to move to the other end of the country
for less money
or to leave with a large wad of cash in my hand.
Well, what did I do?
It was a no-brainer.
I put my faith in Bob,
and I quit my job.
Praise Bob!
About three years ago,
this is a three-step process,
by the way,
about three years ago,
not long after being made Pope of the North of England,
right here in this city,
I was doing all right in the job I had at the time.
I kind of enjoyed it.
I had plenty of money to buy all that false slack,
but I wasn't enjoying my hobby.
So I quit my hobby for Bob!
Praise Bob!
As a direct consequence of quitting,
quitting my hobby,
I was a little bit upset.
I thought, had I done the right thing?
A friend of mine organized a party to cheer me up.
At that party,
I met the lady who is now my fiancée.
Praise Bob!
Hail Connie!
Step three!
Three days ago,
I quit my job for Bob again
for a lot of money!
Praise Bob!
I quit my job twice for Bob and my hobby once!
And so I stand here before you,
funded by conspiracy money,
money obtained from the bowels of the conspiracy.
I worked for a bank, ladies and gentlemen.
Ooh!
They funded me to stand before you on stage,
drinking whiskey.
Ha ha ha!
Here in the holy city of Amsterdam,
which I'm disappointed to say
has been tidied up by the conspiracy.
They're wanting to close down those coffee shops out there.
Those coffee shops that we treat as holy shrines.
They're trying to ban space cake
and turn it into a hard drug
because there are too many idiots coming along
and eating five or six slices
thinking it's doing nothing to them.
And then,
and then they just end up face down in a canal somewhere.
They want,
they want to just tidy this place,
gentrify it.
Yeah!
They're tidying it up to get all the yuppies in.
They want to close down the squats.
Ooh!
I say,
one day there'll be no coffee shops here.
No places for these subgeniuses to come
and get a little bit of R&R.
They won't let us smoke our pipes.
But I tell you,
I give up my pipe
the day they tear it from my cold, dead hands!
Praise Bob!
Amen!
I'll see what else get on this stage
because I have nothing else to say.
Woo!
Praise the money!
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Hallelujah!
Amen!
Praise Bob!
Hallelujah!
Amen!
Fuck Bob!
What the hell?
You know,
Fuck Bob!
You think I'm just some sort of funny little altar boy or pope wearing this get up.
I came here to look funny tonight.
I came here to tell you some,
I came here to tell you some funny jokes
or to speak background noise in your own little pathetic lives.
But let me tell you something brothers and sisters,
I'm here to,
I came,
I've walked 10,000 miles
to come here to tell you about the man with the dots on his,
his face.
I've come here,
I've walked here 10,000 miles to tell you about Bob Dobbs and those of you who carry
on talking about your own pathetic lives and your own personal problems because that's
the most important thing in your lives.
I got news for you.
The conspiracy is about to issue you ID cards.
I'm not going to lie to you.
The conspiracy is about to take away your individual freedoms.
The conspiracy has just made you the capital of cannabis in Europe,
taking away the trophy from even Amsterdam.
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Do I hear a praise capital of cannabis in Europe?
It is for us and nobody else.
I don't give a shit about what anybody thinks about what kind of performance I escape,
what about people I talk to.
I just care about Bob.
I care about the slackness that I've given to my brothers and sisters.
I'm going to drip.
I drip with sweat.
But I don't give a shit because I care how Bob Dobbs and nobody else!
Hallelujah!
Do you hear a praise Bob?
Praise Bob!
Bob!
Bob, how are you?
Bob.
Bob!
Help me.
Help me some help probably come in at any.
Bob, are you alright?
Butthole Surfers are Chip Genius as well?
Well, in the early 80s, we were doing a talk show in a station like this in Houston, Texas.
I think Helpo Pugh was the host.
And Gibby Haynes called up and said,
Butthole Surfers says praise Bob, man.
No one had heard of them then.
They were just a garage band.
They had a little EP called Cowboy Bob, at which they sent us.
I'm not very cool, so I never know whether these things are really supposed to be cool or not until much later.
I don't even know this, but one of the record sleeves of the Butthole Surfers actually has art from Revelation X.
That is...
No, that is art by Paul Mavridis that was used in Revelation X and then resold to the Butthole Surfers for quite a bit more to use on their album cover.
Yeah, the pencil in the ear.
Yeah, that's a Paul Mavridis napkin design that we both ended up buying from him.
But he gives it to the church very cheaply.
We get Paul Mavridis art.
Very, very cheap.
About 25 cents an hour.
It works out to him.
That's what I got.
Yep, that old Bob.
Come to Bob.
Abandon the conspiracy.
You'll step up to big pain.
Oh, yeah.
That's what Bob said, anyway.
Oh, we have a request here.
You have to go ahead.
Do I go to?
Oh, sorry, a different record.
Yeah, say something funny.
I'll try and put on this other record.
Bob did pay in Amsterdam for the first time ever.
Yeah, the Amsterdam Revival actually made a profit after paying for the hall.
We had a huge profit, 7,000 euro.
So that each of the preachers got 10,000.
Yeah.
No wait, no, not 10,000.
1,000.
Yeah, 1 euro.
And each of the 700,000 preachers was paid a euro.
It's the first time in history we've made so much, each.
So praise Bob, praise Bob.
Souls to be unsaved.
Yearning for Damn.
Souls to be unsaved all over Holland, all over Newport, this whole big, beautiful world.
Bob has been, allows to continue, stop like a little kid.
to exist yes that's why the world exists because love lets it so price back and we hope you have
slack happy holidays
ladies and gentlemen wait a minute wait a minute we have some other holy church
business to take care of and I'm not even going to pull up hands up to do it
shut up shut up shut up shut up
ladies and gentlemen I want you to go over there and buy our swag buy for Bob buy our t-shirts buy our CDs buy our buttons and stickers
put them on your chest put them on your car and pray Bob
thank you
praise lab bob praise that Bob praise mc voy tell you I'll wait for it
praise your God praise that Bob praise that Bob praise me praise lp praise rx
lly l a d l y r m o y d e c s w o zxr for my j u n gs I f y 2 todasugru ered
I am the king of the hill
It's the birthday of the bomb!
Hallelujah!
Praise Bob!
Hallelujah! Praise Bob!
There is two orders of business before we have to leave tonight.
And the first order of business is we have to pass the bucket of love.
Can everyone on the stage pass me the bucket of love please?
What is the bucket of love?
Where is the bucket of love?
Here.
What kind of love is that?
Ladies and gentlemen, you got in here for free tonight.
Yes!
But you have to pay to get out.
And that's why we have what we call the bucket of love.
Now I want you to dig deep in your pockets.
And I want, yeah, yeah, yeah, I want you to dig deep in your pockets.
Pass around, pass around the bucket of love, brother.
Pass around the bucket of love and give till it bleeds.
Till it bleeds, friends, till it bleeds.
And I think we got 24 pounds that night.
That was Pope Black preaching at the Foundry in London, England.
The second of our two shows in London in 2004.
The radio tapes that we've been listening to are all from Radio Patipu in Amsterdam.
Thanks to Lord Yeti, the host.
Our friend Yitzer.
And you can get, you can learn more about Radio Patipu if you check out www.freeteam.nl.
freeteam, F-R-E-E-T-E-A-M dot N-L.
Slash Patipo, P-A-T-A-P-O-E.
Oh, there's a little guy.
There's that train going by overhead again.
That Radio Patipu, friends, is on in Amsterdam on Tuesday nights at 97.2 FM.
Oh, yes, there is a very detailed report, photo illustrated with very weird photos at our website at www.subgenius.com.
More than you would ever want to know about the Subgenius European tour there.
And of course there's lots of detailed information about...
There.
What?
Oh, yeah?
Oh, they want to know where else also.
Well, you can also write to Bob at post office box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
And praise Bob.
A hail kind.
And thanks to the avant garde orchestra of Hamburg heard here in the background.
.
experience that you're getting now
and I hope the Red Alive
and Sting use this in the hour
of slack.
Praise
Bob.
Alright, you can cut the camera off now.
Subgenius
Olympic Doping Committee
Music
Applause
Thank you Michael.
Oh, bust it again
dear friends. But let us forget
these things and now
end with a happy
New Year song from Reverend
UConn Jack. Praise
Reverend UConn Jack W-I-C-A
up there in Wisconsin.
Eww.
Quit your job.
Continue to
go to the
to
the
end.
Southwest
Breeze
One
a
all
mm
only
thirty
times
Kill me.
Friends, you're listening to...
This is the end of...