Hello.
Now wait a minute there.
Kill me.
Hi.
Yeah.
Paul Wilbur.
Yes.
I'm overly attached to my horse.
Good.
Paul Wilbur.
Yeah.
Please.
Temporary insanity.
Oh, Wilbur.
Just promise me one thing.
You won't marry a horse.
You could give him love.
All right.
Goodness.
The size of that...
Hello.
Yes.
I gotta go.
Hello.
Firm but gentle.
That's it.
99.
Say, how did she take it?
Now let's all smile.
Pretend to be gay.
Yes, it's the new Gay Family Series.
Brought to you by the C oggi nios.
Power diverse.
ions.
Frontiers.
strate,
Big Chief Ogamog Og got a hab'n squad,
Oh he big warrior's better look around.
Big Chief Ogamog Og not a kid no more,
High time with beautiful gal him settle down.
Tribe gotta have a princess,
So we make a powwow,
You settle in powwow,
Big Chief Ogamog Og gotta have a squad.
Big Chief Ogamog Og gotta have a squad,
This population is kinda lonesome around here, don't you think so Olive?
Uh huh.
Are you still here Olive?
There's another one.
What's the matter, no gas?
I think we got a flat.
Now I want you to see the perp, perp, perp, perp, perp,
Realize, I want you to look at this very closely.
I really believe this.
I believe in, I believe in,
Pew.
That aggravates me to death.
I, I, I, I know I'm getting bigger.
Uh, and, and, more intimacy.
Funk, funk.
I want you to look at this.
Um, but I want to tell you something.
Funk, funk.
See I don't want that.
You see what I'm talking about?
Because why?
I, I love it.
My wife's tremendous at it.
It's too big to be formed by one person.
Funk, funk.
I want this big.
Um,
Hey, hey.
You know I'm build up.
Built up.
Man I was excited, wasn't you?
We'll explode.
We'll, we'll, we'll literally blow ourselves splitter and splatter.
Hey,
Excuse me.
Uh, uh, uh, um, uh,
Jugglers for Jesus.
Clowns for Christ.
Entertainment.
I want to have it my way.
Uh, um, um, entertainment.
And folks I want to tell you something.
Who cook meatloaf?
And who'll take it?
Get it together.
What, what's going on?
Jason's got a tool to help you.
Eat a hot dog in the name of Jesus.
And if you put some chili on it, you've had a part in reaching that's soul.
I'm excited about it.
Why?
I'll tell you why, then look at this.
Hey, I have reservations, um,
TOO MUCH IS ALWAYS BETTER THAN NOT ENOUGH!
TOO MUCH ALWAYS BETTER THAN NOT ENOUGH!
Too Much Is Always Better!
Too much is always better Too much is always better
Too much is always better Too much is always better than not enough
They'll never drag me under if I go over the top
I'm never in cause I'm outrageous If you place some bets I'm the favourite
Ready, get set, take it to the next step Step this way, we're pushing boundaries in every way
You know you need it, come and join us as you're getting the feeling
You better believe it
Too much is always better than not enough
Better believe it
You better believe it
Too much is always better than not enough
Believe it
Too much
You better believe it
Too much is always better
Too much is always better than not enough
Go over the top
Over the top, go over the top
Too much is always better than not enough
They'll never drag me under
Too much
Reverend Max Slack did that song, friends, too much.
And did this episode of Hour of Slack.
Number 1175 is heavy on the music
and particularly the bittersweet kind of song
and especially songs by Bob Walkenhorst
who you may have figured out by now I kind of admire.
Also bittersweet are the collages by Lee Murr and Nor Elpref
and the Popeye cartoon which features the last performance of Bluto
as Valkyrie.
Voiced by the great Gus Wickey, the original Bluto
who died in 1938 just after that cartoon was produced.
And now Nor El.
This is Valk's Weekend.
Writing about actually doing something
and cultivating a garden
boxed, processed, and filled with unpronounceable ingredients.
Moving from butter to margarine, we go overboard.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
Perhaps sex.
Dick margarine. Dick margarine.
I can answer that one.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Soft and smooth.
Very soft.
Very sweet on the tongue.
Pleasure is this extreme softness.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, Bob.
Meaningless.
Stroke, stroke.
You don't want your cucumber with a stamp on it.
The nuts have recently, you know.
This morning.
Boost your brain.
Um, I saw it in milk.
Genius.
Putting the fish in your yogurt.
You're listening to Bob's Weekend.
Welcome back to Bob's Weekend.
Distributed by PR.
Don't forget there was pleasure.
Meat.
Does not seem to be very healthy.
More cancer.
And other kinds of cancer as well.
Um, you're right.
Um, eat the French.
Or the Italians.
Or the Japanese.
Or the Indians.
Or the Greeks.
Take your pick.
Eat brains for brains for brains.
That's right.
Propaganda.
Bananas.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Distributed by PR.
X.
Ahem.
Blame it on God.
With me.
Do not do the things I say.
I'm caused to rethink.
Things that I previously thought.
This is not the right path to go.
And I just got into that.
You uncircumcised.
Hard.
You stiff.
Well, you know.
He's got a point.
Pardon it.
Word.
And then this guy.
Blah.
I am fed up.
Do evil.
You have made a big mess of life.
I'm hard as far as I can go.
Hey, come on now, you fella.
Get up.
Mm.
Well, push him off.
I'm trying.
Mm.
Oh.
Hey, get up over there, you fella.
Goodness.
He's as stubborn as a mule.
You know that, huh?
Oh.
I think maybe I should have changed his oil or something.
I'll take the high road.
And I'll take the low road.
Oh.
Here we go.
Big shit.
I'm a lot.
Doorbell, I'm awfully sorry.
Oh.
That's a, that's a, a, what the, what the, what the, what the, what the, what the, what the,
Me making a squat.
Beautiful.
Oh, Ray.
Oh, just my trice, too.
How did you get that?
You like a nice bracelet?
Oh.
Dog bracelet.
Who doesn't?
It fit perfect.
Oh.
It's beautiful.
Mm.
Me got another one.
Oh.
Look at him.
You like him?
Oh.
Oh, I love him.
Now, now, now let me make you a nice print.
This is for our big chief.
Oh.
Say you're not a bad guy.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh.
Oh, I think somebody's trying to make a donkey out of me or something.
Olive.
Hey, olive oil.
You know, it ain't right for her to walk out and leave me holding the nag like this.
Whoa.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
I want a big fat blonde to hold my hand
To keep the skinny boy from blowing away in the wind
I want a big fat blonde
A big fat blonde
Mama, mama, mama, keep your skinny girls at home
Cause this skinny boy wants a big fat blonde
Me and my big fat blonde, we like to fight and scratch
I know I'll be the loser of the wrestling match
With a big fat blonde
That's a big fat blonde
Mama, mama, mama, keep your skinny girls at home
Cause this skinny boy wants a big fat blonde
A big fat blonde
Well, I'm talking six foot sweet
Forty, thirty, forty
Amazon bombshell
Tall, deaf, and dirty
Talking six foot blonde
Mama, mama
Mama, mama, mama, keep your skinny girls at home
Well, me and J.D. Salinger
We're sitting on your porch
I want a date with your sister
I'm doing it for
A big fat blonde
Uh, uh, uh, uh
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Inside everybody there's a big fat blonde
If you don't believe me
Take a look around
Big fat blondes
Everywhere
Mama
Keep those skinny girls at home
Cause skinny little me
Wants a big fat blonde
A big fat blonde
A big fat blonde by the Rainmakers
Bob Walkenhorst, lead songwriter
And now, Rel
Thank you very much
Page 32 of the New Testament section
Uh, from God
From God
Wait, wait
Which, which prostitutes
The prostitutes
Sex workers are better than priests
Prostitutes are better
Prayers, prayers
Prostitutes are better than priests
The positions of Hispanics
If I haven't got redução
Are you also looking at me?!
Where are you?
Is this it?
Yeah, that's saying yes
What is it?
This boy still goes on
This old party
Let it be
Listen to put your knees
Here, here, here
I'm going to go away.
Killing babies.
The ass.
Ass.
Okay.
Born alive.
The abortionist.
We gotta kill the baby.
Abortion.
Non-viable fetus.
Think.
The woman wants an abortion.
Non-viable.
Lion.
I get it.
Limp and dead.
Lion.
Let's.
Here's.
It's abortion.
Abortion.
I.
I don't believe for a minute.
I get it.
I blows it.
I'm Dr. Laura Schlesinger and I am Dr. Laura.
R-U-A-L-D-R-A.
I am really defensive and snotty.
So, if you're in a car, shut it off.
Children are eroded and weakened.
Therefore, I hate the family whose function is to raise children.
The biggest reason is this.
I can't wait to bury his head forward.
And not backward.
They were real.
Wow.
That is stupid.
That's just like a woman of your sex.
I guess I have to stay here and protect you.
Oh, uh, big cheese ugly mug.
Would you mind stepping over here for just a moment, please?
You funny cat face.
I'll break you in half.
I'll dig a hole.
You push my daisies.
Oh, very interesting.
I heard every word you said and this is what I'm going to do to you, young fellow.
I go.
Slug bug nugs.
Slug them out.
There you are.
You see.
Watch out.
Let's go.
I'm going to get you.
Well, I guess that's the last of the mojitoffs.
Oh.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
All right.
Anyway, guess who?
You may have noticed that we, uh, this year handed out, uh, flyers, uh, showing your inner
gorilla and your inner demon.
This is your confessional sheet.
Please pick up one of these confessionals and, uh, fill out the slips, uh, describing
your inner demon and or gorilla.
These will be useful in the coming time.
As, uh, we analyze these documents, uh, minutely and resolutely.
We may even read them in funny voices.
So you might not want to sign them.
Oh, it's an avalanche of fun we're going to have.
But it requires some minor participation as you pick up these documents on the desk and,
uh, make sure they are well filled out in your most readable script or printing.
We also have a new one where you finish, uh, nursery rhymes.
Now, it's true that, uh, we're going to have to do this.
We're going to have to write the new one, so that you can get the books and the books
fact that these documents were originally designed for kindergarten children, but we're
subgeniuses.
And decide.
We should be able to reach any level of intellect from the very bottom to the very
top.
It's also worth consideration that outside the subgenius bubble, intellectual degeneracy
has continued so that most people don't even know
the nursery rhymes to begin with or anything else.
The last book most people out there ever read
was The Cat in the Hat.
That was their last literary experience,
which they honor by making similar hats
as they leap up and down in the dust
for hours at Burning Man.
Miles and Chester and Dr. Root's garden
Stealing cabbages and corn
Keeping eyes out for the tractor
Filling up their bags with pilfered harvest
In the marinated morning
Of potential disaster
Miles and Chester and Dr. Root's garden
Got a wife and seven kids to feed
And with those seeds I'll plant a farm
He's got lots of vegetables
And me and Chester, do you know?
Home
Sue and Edna in Dr. Root's back shed
Carrying wings off little flies
Smoking fags behind the tool bench
Singing as they daily burn the barn down
Running around the town
Coming gigglingly outside
Having salvaged but a pipe wrench
Sue and Edna in Dr. Root's back shed
We've got nothing else but two
A mule, a dolphin, funky lads
And a little wave
Dr. Root can buy a dozen barns
With all the taxes he don't pay
Dr. Root inside his secret chamber
Raising potters of disease
To destroy the world that you made me
Dr. Root inside his secret chamber
He can't wait to put a new scent into everyone's world
Dr. Root in his mind has got blame
But his workers made him feast
He is now prepared to blame them
Dr. Root inside his secret chamber
is secret chamber.
Oi!
They've been on my back
for years, and now my
little helpers are
escaping.
Everyone
soon will be quite
sorry for the trouble
they've been making.
We're sorry, Dr. Rude!
Ha ha ha!
Dr. Roots Garden by Chrysalis from 1967.
A quirky, weird old band.
Thanks to Reverend Baldin Kramer for that there.
Ellery Queen's.
This is Ellery Queen with a case I call The Big Mistake.
In this case, the charge was murder and police were holding a youthful suspect.
I told him, it's a good story, but you're a murderer just the same.
In a moment, I'll explain why.
In the case of The Big Mistake, most desk drawers are automatically locked by the middle drawer alone.
But a big one.
Listen again to Ellery Queen's.
This is the old trip, trip, trip.
We're coming on down there now.
We're looking at those, uh, studs.
Looking at those studs.
But let me tell you.
Let me go back, go back.
Buggy, buggy.
Day in and day out.
You know where we can get some men cutting logs somewhere in the woods?
Dictating.
Aw.
Fine ass.
Intimate knowledge and penetrating orgy.
Spasmodic erection.
Oh, and listen.
This is a state.
This is a cap, cap, cap.
Out of which all other things, uh, appear.
But listen.
And now.
I wish you'd listen.
Spasmodic woman.
They were openly.
Tinkle, tinkle, tinkle.
Ring-a-ring-a-ring.
Looking at, looking at, looking at.
Commit fornication.
Seduce that woman.
Drive home pagan idolatry.
Commit fornication and eat things.
Now, my friend, teach pagan idolatry.
I know homosexuality.
And I know that gets me hot.
But I tell you one thing.
Come here, sit down, and shut up day by day.
In the meantime, I assume that the question forms are circulating among you.
And if you have a question that you need to unburden yourself of, we will do the best we can.
And we're also collecting your valuable gorilla and demon forms.
I've been meditating on the gorillas and demons.
And I've decided that the gorilla in your life is the stupid person who calls you names
because he doesn't understand you.
The demon is the mean, intelligent person who calls you names because he does understand you.
In other words, the demon is the Nenslo and the gorilla is the Alcandor.
Or the gorilla is the brute and the demon is the malicious spirit.
Now, Dr. Howe, that was a nice poem that you just recited.
Yes. Lucifer by Starlight.
I have a poem I'd like to recite.
It's not original to me.
In fact, Dr. Dark, who brought us that farting Bob toy, originally penned this.
But I had to change it a little because it was too hard to read out loud.
Here it goes.
This is something that only alt.slack lurkers and regulars would know.
A racist alt.slack troll named Mikey hated everything Masonic or kikey.
He'd fly into a panic, say all things were satanic, asking, why doesn't anyone like me?
Oh. Well, that is indeed sad.
So even our most hated enemies we honor in a certain way because, you know, as Sterno pointed out,
the conspiracy exists to give us the energy to oppose it.
But if a sense said that the power was at stake...
That, in light of all the standoff system, there was led to us clashing in most many ways.
So here it is.
This reading asks us about the original story of the war and the creation of the human
disease.
Badunder cares not for makenh whenever doers of hell and mortals are head and shoulders
over الله that would dub their rights and peace.
Whether it made it that they were the priests of caliphate or had some relationship with
Allah or that they had or weren't, it, however, weareth a shadow of the talismano
from the Kalalcan commands.
The the people transforms by the eye and that of.
Their power and intelligence can stop a way to argue and better Раз.
Bucks an hour and working weekend.
I was ignoring the thief who was latched to the crawlers.
He cried, help me get this son of a bitch off.
I said I would if I could.
I can't, so I won't.
Well, I wouldn't want you messing your hair up so dope.
And I realized then that the wages of sin
was all the lumber you can carry.
All the nails you can bend.
The wages of sin.
The reward of fear.
It's worry and a threat every second of the year.
And heaven is guilt.
No sex and no show.
And I'm not sure if I really want to go.
I'm not sure if I really want to go.
The wages of sin.
The price that you pay.
It's worry and a threat every second of the day.
The church and the state.
You're God and country kind.
One gets your body.
The other gets your mind.
Mary, Mary Magdalene.
How about a date?
You've been wasting your time staying up so late.
Your boyfriend's dead.
The word is you're a whore.
Just about then I heard a knock on the door.
And I realized then that the wages of sin.
Was a bad reputation and too many friends.
The wages of sin.
So now we have come to that part where we go into some of your anxieties, fears,
aspirations and hopes.
All encapsulated in these invaluable gorillas and demons form sheets.
I don't know Ivan do you want to trade off the gorilla and demon answers?
Well maybe I could do the gorillas and you could do the demons.
That's very good.
Unleash your inner gorilla and I will unleash my inner demon.
Here our first one is and these are unsigned so it's hard to know.
They don't need to be signed.
The gorilla says to this person.
You should obsessively worry about what strangers think of you.
Good advice.
And now the demon.
It's not enough to do what is expected.
You are expected to do more than what is expected.
More than what is expected.
And that was a quote from this person's boss.
From my boss.
Oh yes the boss.
Mifling poo at stang.
That's my gorilla.
Well what's with the I don't know.
Here's the demon.
Mithro poo at stinang.
Oh stinag.
St nag.
That's been an inside joke.
St nag is my new name on all of Slack.
It's based on a typo by the racist.
Let's have the gorilla.
I will crush you under a bed frame and kick you in the until you decide to go home.
I'll tie you up with sheet if you try to run.
And the demon.
When you die I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to skin you, tan your flesh and use it as a carpet.
And you know he won't wipe his feet either.
I never had that kind of demon.
The gorilla.
Sometimes I pee when I laugh.
What's so unusual about that?
Sometimes I laugh when I pee.
Here's a wordy gorilla.
That's nothing compared to some of the wordy gorillas we've got coming.
I think about having violent sex with everyone I see.
Everyone.
Every time I think it's wet, it's dry.
And every time I think it's dry, it's wet.
It really rubs my skin bloody.
If you forget what all I told you, remember this.
The dog with two discs always wins.
Oh, the dog with two dicks always wins.
Last Christmas with my drunken uncle.
You know how much is too much.
None.
Wisdom there from our primate.
That sounds kind of Bob-ish.
Yes, the great apes have really got a handle on that.
You make everyone near you uncomfortable and you should go away.
I wish it were possible to hate someone to death.
Stop screaming down my throat.
Wow.
Is Nenslo here?
Well, it's a demonic Nenslo.
It's a Nensletic equivalent.
Dr. Howell at 11X Day.
Before that, the Rainmakers with Wages of Sin.
And before that, Noro Pref Collages and Lemurian Collages.
But now, the great Pope, Robert Anton Wilson.
The theories I find really dangerous are like anti-Semitism,
which led to unprecedented horrors in this century.
And horrors on lesser scales,
because they had lesser technology throughout the history of Christendom.
And I find a lot of feminism to be equally nefarious and implication,
although they haven't had enough power to do anything about it.
But some of the feminists, when they talk about men,
they sound just like Adolf Hitler talking about Jews.
It's really scary.
The parallel is so damn close.
And then there are these theories where all the Freemasons in the world
are part of one gigantic conspiracy for the Freemasons to take over everything
and run everything.
I know too many Freemasons to take that seriously.
Freemasons are as miscellaneous a group as the Presbyterians, the plumbers.
You find all sorts of people in the Freemasons,
and they don't all have the same ideas.
So the way you use the term,
it means a kind of absolute blanket generalization about any group?
It's treating a group as homogenous.
Homogenous would be a good synonym for fungible.
So you feel we can throw in the trash,
and put those conspiracies out just based on their fungibility?
On the face of it, everybody has different fingerprints.
There are no two brains that are alike.
So the idea that you can make generalizations about a large and miscellaneous group,
and they'll be true about every member of that group,
that I think is the most nefarious form of stupidity on the planet.
Well, what's so interesting with that particular form of conspiracy theory
is that it contains what you call a strange loop.
Oh, yeah.
When you say Bertrand Russell looked into the evidence
and concluded that the bankers of Europe consisted 90% of Gentiles
and only 10% of Jews.
So the Jewish bankers conspiracy is a myth,
and they'll come back with,
Bertrand Russell was Jewish himself.
He changed his name.
Then you've got to try to prove that Bertrand Russell wasn't Jewish.
I actually got into that argument once with somebody about Hugh Hefner.
They were convinced he was Jewish.
All pornography is created by Jews.
Hefner is a pornographer.
Therefore, Hefner is Jewish.
I told him he's a Presbyterian.
No, he changed his name.
Sartre is the only one who's ever commented on this,
the delight in being stupid.
If you make up your mind you're going to defend a really stupid position,
you can get every intelligent person in the room hopping mad.
No matter how rational they think they are,
they'll eventually get more emotional than you are
if you just keep repeating the same stupid thing.
This is in an essay he wrote
called The Anti-Semite and the Jew.
If you're not Jewish and you try to argue with an anti-Semite
about his prejudices,
the next thing you know,
you are yelling and shouting and acting like a fanatic
more than he is because he's saying so many stupid things like,
you must be Jewish yourself.
How about you?
Well, then your wife is Jewish and she's corrupted you.
No, my wife isn't Jewish either.
Well, then it was your grandfather.
When you get into this infinite regress like that,
eventually you lose your...
your temper and then you feel you're as dumb
as the guy you're arguing with.
Oliver Wendell Holmes called that
the hydrostatic principle of controversy.
The fools drag everybody down to their own level.
Sartre noticed this particularly in anti-Semites.
But I've noticed it in all sorts of dogmatic people
that hold this terrain like the flat earthers.
You get into an argument with a flat earther
and I guarantee you'll lose your temper before he loses his
because he's enjoying being stupid.
But he's enjoying making you angry just by sticking to a position
which he knows nobody else can believe.
That also gives you a feeling of belonging to the elite.
Everybody else is too stupid to see the truth,
but I belong to the small group that knows the truth.
After you believe that, you're ready when the leader says,
here's your cyanide Kool-Aid, have a drink.
Oh, yeah, sure.
And you swallow it all down.
Do you believe that most conspiracy theory or conspiracy theorists
are working from a base of belief?
Or is this a process of a rational and logical will
to determine the facts of a situation?
You know, is it scientific or is this completely some kind of emotional...
Well, it covers the gamut.
I like to think of things on a scale of 1 to 10.
And I would say some conspiracy theories on a scale from 1 to 10,
where 1 is sanity and 10 is total raving lunacy,
certifiably insane, as they say,
I would say most conspiracy theorists are somewhere around
4 above 5 on that scale, and a lot of them have reached 10.
But there are some that are pretty close to 1,
like Carl Oglesby and a couple of other offbeat historians,
Noam Chomsky, Buckminster Fuller, and me.
Conspiracy theories help make sense out of what otherwise seems a senseless world.
That's why so many people believe them, including me sometimes.
How much do you think our own government operates
on the basis of conspiracy theory?
Well, I think they worry about conspiracies more than most conspiracy buffs do.
I think the government is full of people with guilty consciences,
and they're constantly worried we're going to find out what they're really up to.
And so they hire more and more spies to spy on us
to find out what we're doing and saying
to see if we're getting to be a real menace to them.
And of course, that means they need more spies to spy on their spies
in case some of their spies are double agents,
which is well known in this...
in the whole espionage business.
So then they need a third order of spies to spy on the second order of spies,
and eventually you end up with somebody like J. Edgar Hoover,
who uses his power to blackmail the presidents of the United States.
Stalin murdered three chiefs of the secret police in a row
because they found out too much about his own secrets.
And nobody murdered J. Edgar Hoover, at least I don't think so.
I think he died of natural causes.
But he was blackmailing presidents from Roosevelt on.
He blackmailed every president who wanted to do something Hoover did.
Like Nixon said in one of the Watergate tapes,
well, if Hoover performed, he would have scared hell out of them.
He's got a file on everybody.
He's just sensed the envy in Nixon's...
He wanted a file on everybody too.
He was a rank amateur.
Hoover had been at it for 50 years by then.
And a lot of the files disappeared the day he died, by the way.
Nobody will admit they know what happened to them.
Somebody has those files and is still blackmailing them.
They're blackmailing people.
The government is more afraid of us than we are of them.
That's what I always emphasize when I'm talking to radical groups
who think their phones are tapped.
Well, of course your phone is tapped.
If you've done anything to annoy the government, your phone is tapped.
They've probably got a mail cover on you too.
But that just shows they're more afraid of you than you are of them.
The government doesn't trust the people.
And then they wonder why the people don't trust the government.
Well, the people don't trust the government
because they know we're being spied on all the time.
I heard there were over 200,000 lawyers working for the federal government.
You know how much harm a single lawyer can do?
A single lawyer can ruin your whole life, you know, just one day in court.
200,000 lawyers devising modifications and amendments to laws
and working for Congress and changing, you know.
The bureaucracy, the Kafkaesque world they have created
is so onerous, obnoxious, and unbearable
to most of the citizenry that everybody bitches about the government,
at least part of the time.
Ergo, the government knows they are not well loved.
And they're wondering how many of us are joining militias
or forming revolutionary communist parties like those nuts down in the South
or doing something else to overthrow them.
So they've got to keep spying on us to make sure we're not getting too ornery.
And the more the people discover the government is spying on them,
the more they distrust the government.
Too much is always better than not enough
Too much is always better
It's how we're stuck
Gotta join this race
Too much is always better
too much is always better than not enough
Too much over literally
Too much is always better than not enough
Too much in yards was not enough
Is always better
Accumulate
Too much
Is always better
Than not enough
Too much
Is always better
That's how we're stuck
Too much
Is always better
Gotta join the race
Too much
Is always better
Accumulate
Too much
Too much is always better than not enough
You better believe it
Linda, wants to be alone
Yeah
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda tells me when to sleep please
You know I try to get my key
The walls are closing in on me
All into the night
Every night I try to teach
Linda, she's so out of reach
The girls are swimming at the beach
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Doctor told me what to do
I gotta get away from you
He told me what was real and true
All into the night
Every night I try to teach
Linda, she's so out of reach
The girls are swimming at the beach
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda, and we were always so happy
We always got together on Friday afternoon
Then one day I was kissing Linda over in Berlin Park
And then she told me she didn't want to see me anymore
So she started sending me emails saying that everything was fine
And that it was just too much, too much, too much
And she was going back to Gary
So I was real sad
Why'd you leave me like that, Linda?
So I went to see Gary
Gary Wilson and the Blind Dates
I saw them in New York City
Then I went to see them in SUNY Purchase
And one day I'm gonna go to Endicott, New York
I'm gonna find the house where Gary lives
And walk the streets that Gary walks
And I'm gonna take pictures of all the street signs
You know, I went to see Gary last summer
All the way, all the way in Escondido, California
And he came and sat down with me
He sat right down with me and he said
What are you doing following me?
What are you, some kind of sick trip fangirl or something?
And I said, Gary, calm down
I'm gonna buy you a drink
Or maybe a nice green salad or something
And he said, you know, I don't like salad
I never developed a taste for that
But I know what you tried to do
You tried to take Linda away from me
Why would you do that?
Were you kissing Linda Robin?
I said, Gary, you're right
I want Linda for my forever lover
But did I ever tell you?
I wanna be your mannequin
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to be alone
Linda wants to eat alone
Linda wants to sleep alone
All into the night
Linda wants to
Zuora
You were there
What?
Why, why, why?
Who has written some biographical articles about him.
There's more at RobinRenee.com
and also at Audacious11.com
with 11 spelled out
if you want to hear her podcast.
And now more Bob Walkenhorst live at the record bar.
Are you looking for some answers?
Well, you've come to the wrong place.
You might find lines but no valentines.
Written all over my feelings.
I bear no grudge and wear no brown eyes.
I'm with Calisthenics.
And I don't mean to bring me down.
But there is no romance.
I've spent too much of my life waiting.
Hoping, dreaming, wishing, believing.
And way too little of it in the name.
Smashing it up and taking it away.
I wish someone there.
Worrying me why.
I was still a young man.
And save me lots of time and money.
There is no romance.
No romance.
Save your stories for the bartender.
And your crying for the beater.
And your poems and for tiring pages.
To give some time in your day.
Day.
And maybe God's who hear your prayers
And I will spend
Men who care and your words
The thing they will wait forever
Lies the good life
Movies and books
But the sooner that you learn this
The sooner you'll be your man
To get on with things that really matter
There is no romance
No romance
Happy quality time
One was hairy and one was smooth.
I was the hairy one.
And I was struck funny.
One was hairy and one was smooth.
Harry, compare these two boys, the hairy one and the smooth one.
Why them am I this way?
One who grabs, well, and yet, and then you go down.
And I don't think there's much.
There is a deep, deep desire.
I can tell you a story, what seems to be being said.
I'm one, our love, so there can be no love in the world.
I quit.
They're not coming.
Medieval church, all over the place.
Promiscuous, promiscuous, naughtiness.
Promiscuous, freely, freely.
Very, very profound.
You cannot really have love.
I'm the hairy one.
Bad boy.
Just because I'm hairy and like to hunt, I'm bad.
Grabber.
I, he was a dick, he was a dick con.
That's nuts.
When divorce court continues, violent behavior.
What happened when she took a tire iron?
I mean, she destroyed the taillights.
I did, did come a lot.
But you know that baby is your husband.
I mean, I'm a lying slut like everybody thinks, you know.
Yeah.
He was stealing car stereos.
I was on probation.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You were on probation.
Yes.
If you don't...
Anyways.
What was whose what?
Well, that's what, mmhmm.
And that's what my-
Just a moment.
Yeah.
Okay.
Crazy.
I was crazy.
Yes.
Uh, mental disability.
And, and that was, and, and, you know, and, and, and, and, and.
.
I got to tell you, I'm not too bad.
You know who you are.
Sometimes what it takes in life is a little anger
just to propel you on down the road a little bit.
I drove a ship, heard the cybersinkin'
Swam like a senator, I reached the shore
On the trip, the mutiny was proven
Now I am a puppet on the bad dream boat
I'm a lord
I'm in love with the old girls, singin' like it's cold
I'm a man without a country
I'm a boy without a home
I'm a casual man without a home
I'm guilty of the battle of the roses and the wool
Of the broken home
Yes, I got busted
But drank while thinkin'
Carrying a weapon under my coat
I trusted
The wrong
I'm a man without a country
I'm a boy without a home
I'm a casual man without a home
I'm guilty of the battle of the roses and the wool
Of the broken home
Yes, I got busted
I see a land of hope
divided, founded, little
and the sides are divided
and everybody again.
I see so many people
lonely, lover, hate, lover.
When you get split, I'm alone.
I'm alone.
The old world
saves you like a stone.
I'm a man without a country.
I'm a boy without a home.
I'm a casualty
of the battle of the roses
and the war.
Of the broken home.
Bob Walkenhorst,
formerly of the Rainmakers,
now of bobwalkenhorst.com.
Dear friends,
this is Hour of Slack
number 1175
from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information
about the church,
see subgenius.com.
And praise Lemur
and Norell Preff
for the extras.
The background music here
and the credits, by the way,
is by Save Yourself 7598,
also known as the Maverick MJ.
And now this from Schizopolis.
I'm just going to make
this brief statement
on behalf of ARHADL.
The spreading of these erroneous
and offensive descriptions
has gone on for decades.
And we find ourselves once again
having to make a public statement.
Race horses do not urinate
more frequently
or at greater length
than non-racing horses.
Or, for that matter,
any mammal of comparable size.
This organized,
publicly sanctioned slander
must stop.
Sir, he's not...
I disapprove of...
But I will defend to the death
your right to...
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just...
It's literally Bob.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I licked him and how well
there'll be no more powwow
with Popeye the same.
I love that.
Ellery Queen's.
This is Ellery Queen
with the case I call
The Psychological Error.
Police were befuddled
by the story of a man
named Ames
who said he had shot his neighbor
in a fit of shooting.
With these facts,
you can determine
whether it was mechanical failure,
human error,
or sabotage.
In a moment, I'll explain.
In the case of
The Psychological Error,
our ham operator friend
didn't realize there are
dozens of American Indian languages
still spoken at sea.
Listen again to Ellery Queen's...