Boys and girls, you've just heard a scientific demonstration which proves that the pitch of a sound is changed by changing the vibration.
Vibration, vibration, vibration is what causes sound.
Vibration, vibration, vibration causes sound.
Four hours of slack.
Yes, my friends, because hour of slack number 638 will fall on July 1st.
Only four more days before X-Day.
I guess it'll have to be reruns after that, dear friends.
I guess I'll just leave a big stack of reruns at the stations that may be left behind after July 5th.
And I guess we'll start all over again with hour of slack.
Number one, that'll be kind of ironic.
They're all so crude and silly back in those days.
And that'll be all that's left.
The poor survivors will have to learn it all all over again.
But how fruitless it will be, won't it, friends?
Because there really is only one July 5th, 1998.
And do you have what it takes to go the distance on that day?
Do you have what Bob asked of you, my friend?
Do you have that much slack?
Are you going to take the slack that is rightfully yours is the question.
You have that slack.
You have it and it's yours.
But you've been letting the conspiracy waste it for you.
No, no, you shan't let that happen anymore, my friend.
Because in only five more hours of slack, the world as you know it will be destroyed.
And you, yes, you, my dues-paying friend, my fellow minister.
In this church, you and I both together shall be ruptured up in glory and nakedness
into the arms, the veritable bosom of the sex goddesses from Planet X
in the escape vessels which will then become our battle planets
on which we shall haul butt forward out and into space
after, of course, wreaking vengeance on those who ever irritated us
in any way down there on Mother Earth below.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
I can feel it.
I can feel X-Day coming.
I can feel the blood rising.
As Dr. Legume says, the river is rising, my friend.
Bob Dobbs has that life preserver.
Are you going to take it?
He's ready to throw it to you.
Ah, yes.
Praise Bob.
Hail Connie.
Let there be slack.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, ah, ah.
There's something for everyone here in small town.
That's why it's such a swell place to live.
I was told that I had a power demon
where I thought I had control over, um, you know, the over God.
Ah, he got me!
Ah!
Set the dwarves to cranking the machinery.
How long do I have to do this for?
So that the great corkscrew razor dildo, uh, and the ceremony may begin.
Oh, good bro, friend.
Okay, you guys, there it is.
Only four and a half inches.
You want to start laughing now or what?
I wish I wouldn't be thinking about sex.
Uh, you know, I've got to quit thinking about sex.
Right.
If, you know, if you...
Is it going to think about it more then?
Yeah.
It's just going to...
It's going to make you all that much more compulsive.
Right.
Uh, the power of sin is in the law.
Instead, I want you, as soon as you have a sexual thought, to look at...
Bob.
Oh, my God, he's here.
Honey, I feel much better now.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius power of sweat.
Y'all brothers from out of the states
are coming with advanced knowledge
to help
human race.
Bob will save all true believers, though, in 1998, right?
Actually, Bob...
You better hope that Bob does some wheelin' and dealin'
for your soul come 1998.
He is the salesman of the universe,
here to make sure that the Earth and your soul
does not get sold to, uh, to the robot mutilators.
At least...
At least for not too low a price.
So you better read that book with all three eyes,
or however many you have left,
and, uh, leave the driving to Bob.
That's right.
You do the walkin', let Bob do the talkin'.
Who are these men from Planet X, children?
What is waiting there?
For me!
Bob.
Can't wait to strap on your groovy old man.
Ah!
Not ready with my beautiful body.
You got a lot of nerve buster tellin' me you're not ready.
All those muscles, except the one that really counts.
War of the academic community against everything that this country has ever stood for,
all of its basic beliefs.
It's a war against religion.
And for just one second, your eyes snap open,
and you remember that life is beautiful,
the world is wonderful,
and everything is just as psychedelic as that old T-shirt that you can't fit into anymore.
Now, hold that thought!
Hard to do, ain't it, dear friends?
You wanna know why?
It's cause of the conspiracy!
Oh, ho, ho!
Oh, I didn't mean to interrupt.
Oh, there it must be.
There it is, there it is, there it is.
Crash saucer.
Air Force CIA.
Roswell.
Area 51.
Ace of Louse.
Conspiracy.
John Kennedy.
The Nazi shoes.
It's all, it's all.
The apocalypse starts now.
The apocalypse is going on right now, all around you, everywhere you look, everywhere you see.
It's the constant, slow, steady degradation of mankind, of human society, as we see it.
The breakdown of the family, the breakdown of the psyche,
the breakdown of individual responsibility is going on all around you,
and there's nothing you can do to stop it.
And that, my friends, is, in fact,
the constant and present apocalypse.
I'm not part of it.
I'm not even necessarily promoting it or endorsing it.
I'm just here to entertain throughout.
I certainly don't want to.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm Andrew the Appellate of the Zurich and Spockalypse Sideshow.
I thank you for your pleasance.
I thank you for your patience.
And you're all sick bastards!
In the meantime, we have a special alien update.
From some subgenius that traveled a long way to give you this alien update.
Here they are.
Attention.
We have an update on the alien status.
Good morning.
I'm the sixth avatar of the alien status.
I'm a member of the alien revenants.
Me and Tahooti are members of a heretofore secret organization,
a secret arm of Bob's Secret Service.
We have just received special orders that were signed by Bob prior to his extermination,
authorizing us to inform you of our existence
and to also give you information that will help you survive the upcoming X-Day.
We have found through much experimentation that the alien mindset works in a collective consciousness.
We have also found, as we all know, the subgenius has individuality and works with rational self-interest.
Therefore, we have to be able to determine what the difference between the collective consciousness and individuality is.
It's a war against the mind.
It's a war against religion.
Kids, we're going to need an awful lot of brains on drugs if we're going to make the great omelet of Bob
and defeat the conspiracy of the normal people.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wonderful marinated Dave.
Just smell that brain cookie.
Lovely, lovely, lovely.
He's so famous and so delicious.
Here, have a fork and a knife, Princess Wee.
Oh, poked head, pretend.
Look, if you poke the front part of this sizzling brain, he remembers his childhood.
And if you poke the back part of this sizzling brain, his leg jerks.
Yes.
This is really delicious and fun, too.
And he's full of vitamins. Mom will like that.
I'm a sandwich.
Do they ever forget or forgive the whippings and the harsh, strict words of command?
I wonder.
How can you forget or forgive those over and above you?
Those tall, silly dictators?
Those parents?
There are a number of workshops, one of them on sadomasochism,
that was billed as safe, sane, and consensual sadomasochism,
an alternative way of loving.
Mommy, Daddy, where are you?
Peek-a-boo.
You know, we live in a time when we're gonna be faced with making some hard choices.
We live in a time when the conspiracy will do its best to limit the choices that we have.
But today I'm here to tell you that I'm glad to be affiliated with Bob and Slack.
If you have no Slack, you have no life.
If you have no Slack, you have no reality.
As the aliens approach our planet, we're gonna be the first ones to know that we're not alone.
As the planetoid hell-bop approaches our planet, we're going to face some choices.
And I will leave you with that.
It's been a pleasure being around those who espouse Slack.
We out.
Yeah!
No, when I talked to Bob, you know, he just grinned.
He said, there ain't no use fighting it, because he always wins.
Yeah!
There ain't nothing that he can't do.
If you won't do it yourself, he won't do it for you.
Now, psychologists tell us, or at least they theorize, that the reason most people loathe even the discussion of death
is that they are afraid of the pain.
That is associated with death.
That is to say, they're not really afraid of death per se.
They are afraid of the pain that they will experience while dying.
Well, friends, I'm here to tell you that that is a load of horse hockey.
The pain that you will experience dying will be nothing compared to the pain that most of us will experience after death.
We're going to discuss that pain right here, right now, in great detail.
Because the title of tonight's sermon is, Paying Your Dues to Dops.
Now, I'd like to ask you, how many of you out there right now know that when you die, you're not going straight to hell?
Let's have a show of hands.
Now, if you feel that way, why so?
Is it because you sent in your $30 love offering?
Yeah!
Is it because you read all the subgenius books?
Is it because you're good buddies with one of Bob's sacred preachers?
Yeah!
Well, all these reasons don't mean nothing come judgment day.
Because Bob does not measure your importance in how much money you spend on his merchandise,
or how much you read his books,
or how much suck you have with his special buddies.
No, sir! No, sir!
Bob measures your worth in one way, and one way only.
How much he ate?
He asks, have you held his ministry?
In other words, have you paid your dues?
Now, you see, the majority of people, pinks, normals, pseudo subgenies, are all destined to hell.
That's just a plain, simple fact Bob foretold in his scriptures.
There's only so much space on those pleasure saucers come X-Day.
And the rest are all going to be left screaming.
Bob could have bought more pleasure saucers, but what's the point?
He already knows the exact number of true subgenies,
and quite frankly, he doesn't want to waste the air or fuel on them.
The deadbeat bobbies and pseudo subgenies are wannabe warriors for Wotan.
If you're trying to establish a relationship with Bob,
or establish a utopian society,
the last thing you want to do is import problem people to the promised world.
Solution?
Leave them to fry in hell.
Now, some folks might think that's a little severe, but look at the big picture.
Bob is a pioneer.
He's establishing a new frontier.
He can't afford the luxury of pity.
All excess baggage must be jettisoned.
It's as simple as that.
A simple fact.
You either gotta live with it or die.
So now I ask you again.
How many of you feel secure that you're not gonna go straight to hell when you die?
Is it fair, you might rightly ask, that Bob saves only those who benefit his ministry?
I, for one, say yes.
Bob is up there in the heavens right now preparing us a utopian world.
While most of us sit around and do nothing, but pray.
Let the little pimples on our butts grow and act sanctimonious.
So many subgenies expect to be pampered.
They want Bob to entertain them.
They want Bob to validate them.
They want Bob to save them.
But when Bob says save someone else, they say,
leave it to the preachers.
No, sir!
Bob wants you to save your neighbor!
Bob wants you to save your neighborhood!
Bob wants you to save your state!
Bob wants you to save your country!
Bob wants you to save the whole damn world!
It's not like he's asking you to try something he didn't!
Yes! Yes it is hard!
But Bob isn't exactly on vacation either, friends.
I think, you want rest?
You can rest July 5th, 1998.
You want reward?
He'll give you eternal life on a utopian world.
You, what's that?
You want more?
More! More!
Well, how about a waiver from the fires of hell?
Yeah!
50 years ago, friends,
atom bombs incinerated over 100,000 people in less than a millisecond.
Most of their remains were nothing more than shadows burned into stone.
The unlucky living suffered unimaginable pain.
They refused food.
They refused water.
They wanted nothing but pain.
They wanted to put scissors to cut the hanging flaps off their raw, blistered bodies.
We've seen the pictures.
We've heard the testimony.
We know such pain as possible.
And yet, that pain is nothing.
Nothing compared to the horrors of hell.
Because those Japanese, my friends, had something that hell's inhabitants never had.
And that is called hope.
The hope of death.
An end to their suffering.
There ain't none of that in hell, my friends.
The pain just keeps going on and on, day after day, year after year, century after century, millennium after millennium, with no relief in sight.
Sounds like a person called Choo-choo-choo.
Kind of funny, ain't it?
You get eternal life either way.
You get eternal bliss or eternal torment.
Either way, it'll last forever.
But you alone must choose.
Not just with your words, my friends, but with your deeds.
Will you serve Bob?
Or will you sit around and wait for Bob to serve you?
No one said it would be easy, my friends.
I didn't say it would be easy.
Stang didn't say it would be easy.
Bob Dodds didn't say it would be easy.
What we said is that it would be worth it.
If you doubt us, go over there and start one of those little fires.
Get yourself a little skillet.
Put a little butter in there, maybe a little bit of salt.
Stir it up, get nice and hot.
Take your hand, roll it up your sleeve, don't want to burn those sleeves.
Send it in the skillet and burn it to the bone.
Then imagine that pain all over your body for millions and millions of years.
That is the alternative to Bob!
On my own, pretending Bob's beside me.
In the dark, his darts and pipe, they guide me.
Without Bob, I smell his scruff around me.
And when I have no slack, I judge my clown and Bob has found me.
On my job, the normals act like dumb shits.
Without slack, the sweat runs down my armpits.
The next day, I'll see the saucers coming.
And all I need is Bob and me forever and forever.
But until I spend my thirty bucks,
I'm just running to myself and not to Bob.
And although I know that I'm not alone,
I am screwed.
Still I say, there's a day of pain.
I love Bob, but when the rapture's over,
he'll be gone, the earth will be in ruins.
Without him, the world will run me.
And the world will be in changes.
The conspiracy is everywhere.
The malls are full of pink boys.
I love Bob, but every day I don't spend that thirty bucks.
I'm only just pretending.
Without me, Bob's world will go on burning.
And the next day, Bob will have to slack.
And all you'll never know.
I love Bob.
But only on my own.
Bob's World
Oh, how nice, how touching, so sweet,
and so poignant.
Oh-ho.
That was, uh, my, actually my own, uh... daughter.
Sivit Stang singing that song,
I'm Bob's Own.
Uh, of course, we're focusing on X Day
with only five more hours of slacking.
left to do on earth before I'm Bob's own we heard father Joe mama's superb rant
paying your dues to Dobbs from recorded at the X Day Drill 1996 in Brushwood New
York we also heard the Luciferian Liberation Front yeah to Hootie and
Avatar making some statements a little bit of dr. dinosaur and of course lots
of Einstein secret orchestra from the swamp night 1998 mixed in and of course
we're gonna you know friends you could join us in the final X Day celebration
we're going to open it up for a few non-members it'll be a lot cheaper if
you join the church at the same time but it's in the Brushwood campground
outside of Sherman New York if you want the information you can always send the
self-addressed stamped envelope to the p.o box that we give every show and I'm
gonna give it right now p.o box one four oh three oh six this is of course dear
friends the address of the office of jr. Bob Dobbs himself just address that to
Bob actually address it to X day p.o box one four oh three oh six
Texas seven five two one four check out www.subgenius.com which they tried to kill
last week because friends as X as the time gets closer and closer 38 days while
I'm recording this by the time you hear it it won't probably won't be 25 but as
it seems like as we get closer and closer to the end the pinks get dumber
and dumber and dumber
and so do we but that's besides the point but like Bob Larson himself said if
you're being shot at then you know you're on the front lines you know
you're right in the middle of the fight
you definitely ain't sitting on the sidelines watchin and whinin and when
you have three radio jocks all making fun of your accent and going ooh you'r real stupid
because you were running anti-religion logical conundrum
rings
around there, every vulgar dumbass insult, you know that you're fighting Bob's good fight.
And not only that, you know that Bob wasn't kidding. That in fact, Bob is right. As Pope
David N. Meyer, one of his new ringing pronouncements that we played on the show a couple of times
back, he said, back in the 1980s, children, we were funny. Now, in the 1990s, we're only
right. And we're still doing drive time, rock jock, quickie radio interviews. I don't know
what they're telling each other about us. But the last three have started out hostile,
friends. And the last one I did, it literally ended with these three jock boys making fun
of my accent.
And it ain't a great way to start the day, but today is a great day anyway, friends.
The air conditioning is fixed. My tooth is crowned. My jaw stopped hurting and my brain
stopped hurting and I have a new transmitter in my mouth. And it rained like gangbusters
here in Dallas and washed away the filth and the toxic clouds from the southern hemisphere
econocataclysm from our air. And all that happened to me, and I'm not going to lie to
you, I got paid for it. I'm going to put on the music to the show, It's called The Pink
I had a show with a band called The Pink Talk Show Drive Time, and I am raping the benefits.
I feel great! So bring on those pink talk show drive time jock chucks. Let me at them,
friends. And we ain't giving up. Jesus has been calling Howard Sterns' office every day.
Seriously, every day. Him and lots of other showbiz characters. And other doctors are
working on, like Jerry Springer, for instance. Friends, the pinks, as they fry eternally,
will not be able to say that we didn't try to tell them.
We have managed to be on the pink drive time top stations
in every big city in America just about in the last month or so.
And we tell them about X Day and how 30 bucks can save them
and they call us stupid and laugh at us.
And we sent out press releases to all media worldwide
and 90% of them threw it in the trash.
So they can't whine from within their cages of ever-burning fire
that we didn't try.
No, sir, ma'am.
Now, we are getting through to a few more of that tiny smattering
of unsaved subgeni among the population.
And even if each talk show thing, humiliating appearance,
only gets the message in the P.O. box to one lone subgenius
driving to work in rush hour, it's worth it.
Because one subgenius...
Subgenius, friends, is worth eight billion pinks.
Do the simple math.
Every subgenius is different.
Every pink is the same, the same being,
all sharing what might as well be one huge, fat, pink soul.
Well, if they can't not take a joke,
then let them mount up upon it, my friends.
All those rock jocks have bosses
and have to get up early and kiss butt.
And Jesus and me, our boss man is that man J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He lets us do whatever we want.
Whatever the Bob we want to do.
And when we Bob and Will want to do it, we do it.
And that's exactly what I think I'm going to do right now.
Praise Bob.
If you want it, it's easy, my friends.
Just keep on going the way you are now.
It's so simple.
But don't say, whatever you do,
don't say you weren't warned.
Because I warned you.
And I warned you.
And I warned you and you and you too.
I warned you all because I devoted my life to singing and screaming.
And warned in the word of Bob.
Because I know where I want to go.
And if you want to join me,
you better get on out there in that street corner
and start praising Bob like your fairy left a pencil on it.
Because guess what?
It does.
Some folks, they'll mock us.
And they'll laugh.
But don't you worry.
Come July 5th, 1998,
they'll no longer be laughing.
They'll be begging.
Screaming for another chance.
A chance they were given.
But chose to ignore.
Here into the world of all praise.
Amen.
Oh, Bobby, Bobby, there is pinkness all around.
Dobbs, bring forth all of the mighty in these last days.
Draw towards your church those last few worthy.
The covenant people, the children of the Yeti.
That the saucers may be full and that there may be enough for us.
The reap of the harvest.
And bring forth the holocaustal Dobbs to kill for you.
Bring forth the evangelicals Dobbs to screw for you.
And bring forth the connytites to bear the seed
and order the rest of us around.
Let X-Day come a-running.
The world will come.
Yes.
Last thing we're worried.
I know what's gonna happen on X-Day, friends.
I know exactly what's gonna happen on X-Day.
The men from Planet X are gonna show up at 7 o'clock in the morning
over the Pacific Dateline.
And let the Earth rotate underneath their armada of presences.
Rutshrowing up those $30 subgenius ministers starting in Pago Pagos.
Crossing the globe.
To Australia, Japan, across Russia, Europe.
Finally to these shores, friends.
7 o'clock in the morning, July 5th, 1990.
You got Brian B. and Sherman, New York, and Brushwood campground.
With my fellow subgeniuses.
Ready to be lifted up in power and glory.
The naked, the naked glory of X-Day.
Classic 1990.
The judgment on the dead.
I heard it hard away.
Come on, Bob.
Bring on X-Day.
Ruts me up.
Beam me up.
Scotty, there's no intelligence I have here.
If there was some, I'd want to get away from it anyway.
Please, Bob.
Please.
You won't get through when we're running out.
We want the world and we want it now.
Bob can give you the world.
Bob can give you a whole planet.
We want it.
We want it now.
When did you say you want it now?
You want the whole planet now or you just got to get it on?
You can have it in 80 days for $30.
$2 a day investment.
That's not bad.
It's not good.
Be part of the in-their-world.
And the beginning of your own new world.
And the best thing is, it's up to doing yourself.
New world.
That's right.
We're not giving you instructions.
We're just giving you all the parts you need for a whole new universe of your very own.
You want your Venus and we want it now.
We want Saturn and we want it now.
We want Mercury and we want it now.
We want the silence as we want it now.
Yes, dear friends, boy, I sure would love to get into the studio and do that up.
That's actually just off of videotape pointed at some speakers in a rehearsal room.
Einstein Secret Orchestra rehearsing.
For the big show.
Big show in Cleveland.
Actually, for the big show on X Day and any subsequent shows.
Friends, I'm about to go into the tapes, yes?
The tapes of some of the fun little moments and happenings from the 1996 X Day drill.
Which is, and the 97 X Day drill.
These events were held in the same place where we're going to hold our big farewell party.
Goodbye Earth.
And these are just some glimpses back behind the scenes as we try to prepare the audience and ourselves for such things as the breasts of drum and the exposures of the prairie squids.
The uses of the prairie squids right there in public.
It's really pretty perverted.
I've never been in a place like this.
I've been to an X Day drill before.
We've got some pretty scary stuff going on in the woods.
I know we promised free prairie squid to everybody.
As it turned out, we can't offer it free, but it's only 50 cents.
There will be a prairie squid tent.
We'll set it up tomorrow.
I didn't want to set it up today because they get kind of rank after a second day.
Somewhere right in an inappropriate place in the middle of the field, there will be a tent.
There will be a sign up.
The squid will be in there.
There will probably be a long line.
There's a de-beaking tool.
There is a slight charge rental for the de-beaking tool.
That's $100.
No, nothing like that.
It's $900.
Two-hour minimum on the tool.
Put the squid back in the cooler when you're finished with your business.
Have any cases of AIDS come from prairie squids?
Prairie squid, well, you take your risk.
Keep in mind that it's not a problem.
It's a safe sex.
There's a safe sex.
If you all saw that thing, that's a sign of hope, isn't it?
When you drive up to a place and there's a little booth up there, safe sex and something else.
It's condoms, dental bands, gloves, big red straps.
And with naked people behind the booth.
Yeah.
For those of you who have never seen these de-beaking tools,
or seen these before, these are called breasts.
What?
Duh!
Any of you old sub-genius members out there have never seen breasts before today,
except in, of course, pictures and on cable TV.
But these are not one-dimensional.
These are genuine, real breasts.
Oh!
Most of you will never see these again after tomorrow.
And your dreams.
So, don't feel shy about staring.
They're like $1, $25 an hour.
Yeah, don't feel so bad about staring at them.
Oh, he loves to be naked.
Now, one thing that I can say about this woman,
that it would set her apart from most sub-geniuses,
is that there's a real good chance that she's going to get to bed down a woman tonight.
Very good.
And how much makes her?
Better than the rest of you.
Keep going!
Yeah!
You're not getting a raised breast!
Raised breast!
Come on, baby, take a leave.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I wonder if we ought to...
If we put the squid out today, he's going to be pretty used by tomorrow.
I don't want to have to throw him out before tomorrow
because I think we may unveil the squid on Saturday morning
because the squid is not going to live forever.
Yeah, I've got to figure out what to wear.
I really do have the squid, by the way.
I prefer the mountain squid.
Well, this is a Mississippi Delta squid, which is not the...
They actually smell funny, unlike a mountain squid or a straight prairie squid.
Well, the smell is an aphrodisiac all in itself.
Well, for some people.
No, the smell of a good rotting squid,
inflamed squid, and a good little squid.
It just rams your pheromones all the way down.
It would twist up your DNA helix like an old mangled twist tie
if you're not careful, but the trip's an E-ticket.
Yeah.
So which night should I get naked, Doug?
Huh?
Which night should I get naked?
Saturday.
Saturday night.
Okay, so I don't get the squid on my bustier.
We're going to rape Bob.
Jesus is going to nail him to the cross.
The devil girl for Sunday morning.
There may be violence.
Some of y'all might have got it.
A little bit of blood splashed on you,
but not as much as you're going to have then.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
We're living in an age where you will see the corpse of the old world
and the broken bones of time.
Oh, yes, brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah.
You don't need a weatherman to know which way the wind blows.
All you got to do is follow the smoke.
Oh, yeah, because that smoke's going to lead you right back
to JRBob.com.
Oh, yeah.
The conspiracy's against you, brothers.
The conspiracy's against you, sisters.
Oh, yeah.
They want you to play the game.
They want you to cut your hair.
They want you to get a job.
They want you to behave.
They want you to obey.
They want you to die.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, brothers and sisters.
The Earth's going 90 miles an hour down a dead end street,
brothers and sisters.
90 miles an hour down a dead end street.
And Bob is just ahead.
Oh, that's one way to put it.
You thought you had a little fun with that Bob thing, didn't you?
Oh, I'll just get some extra slack.
Oh, why, hell, it's just a joke.
Oh, yeah.
I'll just get some extra slack.
Oh, just a funny joke, boys and girls.
.
More, more, more.
And I will never escape the eye.
.
And so there is an agent here.
We know it.
We don't know which federal agency.
It might even be bigger than federal.
.
a circle of ten should be...
I flew a black helicopter once.
Does that make me an elephant?
No, hell no.
Oh, sorry.
See, he could be the one
just trying to act like he's joking about it,
which would be...
That would be a good way to be a spy, you know?
So there's...
We just...
Well, we don't want to panic people
or, you know, get everybody worried
or anything like that.
But just keep your eyes open.
If you see anything that somebody doing something
that you think is suspicious,
tell me or Dr. Legume or the Lord.
You all know that at some point during the weekend,
ten people in here are going to die.
Cool.
Pray.
Me, me, me, me.
So you are one of them.
Legume now points out Jesus.
You stand accused, brother.
You stand accused of being Jesus.
And there's only one way I know of
that I could possibly...
could possibly deal with a man such as yourself.
Crucify him!
Jesus is now giving the cross piece of the cross.
Grab that board!
Pope Fred!
You, your cross piece, brother,
you're getting dragged to the Golgotha!
Crucify!
Pray to Jesus, everybody.
Amen!
Oh yeah, it's all just a drill.
But next time, it could be real.
They don't know their doom.
They're all trying to put up some token resistance.
But what if before July 5th, 1998,
the ATF were to swoop down and snatch up the poor public faith to the church?
How many of you out there will be burning your subgenius membership cards
when you see Reverend Stang or myself or Jesus hanging on the cross?
Hell no!
Will you be buying your time?
Not me!
Will you be taking up your shotguns to evade us?
Yes!
Or will you merely commit suicide and join us in subgenius hell?
Yes, brothers and sisters!
Mankind does not know it yet,
but time is a horny cellmate waiting for us to fall asleep.
Oh yes, and brothers and sisters,
your subgenius membership card is like a homemade knife
to smuggle out from under your mattress.
Oh yes, oh yes, and when time comes around,
looking for a little love at your expense,
you will be able to defend yourself against it.
You will be able to wield your subgenius membership card
like a flaming sword, like a smuggled knife,
like a gun made of soap at the very least.
Oh yes, brothers and sisters, time.
They say that time flies by.
Boy, the weekend flew by.
Time just flies by.
Shoot it out of the air!
You'll be okay.
Time does not fly by.
Time flies away.
Yes, brothers and sisters, and time is running out for them.
Today, we meet on this campground,
and we'll have a little fun.
A little fun.
But two years from now,
you better have the stomach for the sight of blood.
What is it?
Oh, yes, give me that primetime religion, friends.
Oh, seekers, yes.
It's good enough for me.
Praise Bob!
Yeah!
Well, welcome to the A.B. Semplevix Slack Four Square Tempeltown Bible and Cat Amputation Center.
And Bob's jack shack back on Highway 69 on the way into town as our big sponsor.
So we'll try to stop there on the way back, okay?
Oh yeah, welcome.
Come on.
from Seekers to the X-Day drill.
We're just tingling Oregon energy.
We can feel the Xs coming up over the horizon.
And it's a good feeling because Bob's in the mood
for a second coming and a third coming
and a fourth coming because X-Day is on the way.
Oh yeah, you can laugh about it right now,
but it's just too short, you're Seekers,
and what are you gonna do then?
What are you gonna do when the Krypton lasers
are slashing the skies overhead?
Where are you gonna plug your laptops in then?
Ha ha ha!
What?
I've done a little bit of thinking about it.
Oh, and I figure the best way to do it
is to take that despair, take that despair and fold it.
Double it back upon itself, fold it like origami
into a googolplex of slack.
Slack-sense tree.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to take a break
from JR Bob dogs.
Yes, yes.
Oh, they may have burned his body,
but they didn't burn his baby, I mean.
I mean, they can't burn his dream.
And as wet as that dream is,
we've gotta follow it, Seekers.
We've gotta follow it every step of the way.
And that's, basically it.
We're gonna follow it every step of the way.
We're not selfish, like a forest scent.
What is that?
You know there's something common
I remember when I went to town I used to say,
and everything is connected with numbers.
I had to- Nacho was also.
Achoo!
Gotcha.
Oh boy.
Dude.
from anarchy.
We're here to make sure
that those two hot meals
are just the cooling remains
of their neighbors.
Can I get an amen?
Amen!
Can I get a hallelujah?
Can I get a praise bomb?
Brothers and sisters,
let's hear some noise!
Amen!
Brothers and sisters!
You feel better
if you've got anything else
but your leave.
How are you going to know
that you're saved,
brothers and sisters?
I'm sure.
Sure you're saved,
but you've got two years
to work up your hate
for the normals.
This place here,
you can feel
the love in it.
We will cleanse
this place of that love.
Oh, sure.
The normals,
the pinks,
they have their petty hatreds.
I don't like the man
in that store
because he's Jewish.
I don't like
the people
that just moved in
because they're black
and they'll run
the property values down.
I don't like those people.
They just look funny.
I don't like those people
because they park
in my space.
I hate them.
Oh, I'd like to kill that guy
coming into my neighborhood.
Oh, yeah, the conspiracy
will try to hide it.
I'm sure pretty soon
Walt Disney,
with their incredible
knack for changing history,
will be making that movie soon,
you know, the one about
the poor people in Africa,
the fact they achieved
the lifelong dream
of coming on over
to America,
they've got.
Yeah, and Disney will be
selling the action figures.
You can get them
at Burger King
and all that stuff.
They'll be out there
singing and dancing.
I don't like that.
And somebody, of course,
Don't real life
somebody who could hate
somebody, OK,
then somebody should hate
you don't you hate
you because you're
some today.
Too, because you're
badly somebody.
Gonna ufz got
a funny haircut.
Oh, yeah.
That would be
worth hate you want
to make all those
movie that kind of
Hey, I say I.
Oh yeah.
We sends the paper
that legislates pocket
great.
Huh?
Who would be
You're the man who signs that paper to legislate hate.
President Biden!
Piss off! Piss off, little haters.
But what can we expect from them brothers and sisters?
I hate you!
They're only human.
Amen!
Rainbow! Rainbow!
Now it's time to pour the structure
We can't be mad
Mama, may I lower?
This is Major Bob's in ground control
I don't think so
Ah, I will read from the minutes of the last meeting.
And these are very soggy minutes, so stick with me.
Because I'm here in the name of sin to tell you to get right with Bob!
Now some of you may be thinking,
Who is this Bob guy anyway?
I'm here to tell you that he is the super salesman of your slack.
The conspiracy has bought and sold you and distributed you in little styrofoam cartons
And Bob is here to help you break through that lack.
And get the hell out.
Oh yes, when this mighty Yeti overman came along with eyes as bright as blaze
To kick ass across the cosmos on the supersonic Nazi hell creatures,
He came for us.
And he came again.
And again.
Oh Bob.
And I kind of lost count at that point because I blacked out.
Oh, I'm sure you remember that night.
Woke up in a puddle of slack.
And you knew that Bob had been there.
You know, you've got a choice here.
You can either accept Bob as the savior of your slack.
Or don't come crying to me when the saucers are so close that the heat rays are welding
your damn butt cheeks shut.
Because it's not my damn problem.
It's nothing to me if you have slack.
Or you.
You make your own slack.
But we are all here to give you something to slack off to.
We're here to provide that divine inspiration for power.
Perspiration for your justpiration.
Ah.
Bob is there.
He's got a nice warm leg to hump.
Oh.
Make good friends with Bob today.
We were inside the sun.
The sun will be ours.
We will be with you for life.
Earth will be made like a mill
For we shall own the sun
We want Saturn and we want it now
We want Mars and we want it now
We want Venus and we want it now
We want Saturn and we want it now
Hydrogen reactions cheap
Get your hydrogen atoms here
Ten billion year old carbon
Dinosaur shit
You're made of dinosaur shit
But the men of the future will be made from your shit
Hey, how does Bob
You're made of the old ashes
From stars that long ago went dead
If everything was God
Everything comes apart one way or another
Bob said
You better be glad of that
He used to take those words and smoke it
He used to say
What happens when the ashes rise
Like a mighty phoenix
Friends, join the church
Build yourself a noose
Build your own spaceship
Stick it in your pipe
Smoke it
Blast off
Don't be scared
You can find out
Go on, man
Everyone's gonna die
You're gonna die
We want the cosmos and we want it now
We want the universe as we want it now
What is the law?
The subgenius must have slack
That is the law
We are not men
We want to cause more life
To claw the bark of trees
That is the law
We are not men
To snuffle up our drink from the street
That is the law
To hold on
To hold on four legs and run
Run free
Four legs and run
We are not men!
To spill blood!
That is the law!
We are not men!
Praise Bob!
Bob!
83D Square!
Let's jam a Yeti dance.
Are we going to do the wedding here?
Let's do the wedding.
Well, actually,
we can do the wedding in a very fast way.
In a very high speed.
Anybody want to get married?
By the authority invested in me
by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
uh, by Brandon Stimpy,
the Three Stooges,
and all the dead great rock stars,
comedians, strippers,
you're all now married to each other
and to these
same squid,
which,
and these bats,
and these goldfish bats,
and back home, your goldfish, your little dog.
I have married my
faithful prairie squid.
Friends, you know
subgeniuses, like,
we take our cue from Bob,
and love all animals,
physically love all
the animals of the globe.
We love nature. We would
love, physically love a cactus,
a prickly pear,
were it, did it not hurt so much.
And there are probably some subgeniuses
who do anyway.
I did make love to a cactus when I lived in
Phoenix, Arizona.
Some of you
may have taken
too much and actually
had knowledge,
biblical knowledge of
a large cactus.
And, but who
among ye has not
lain with that
friendly
beacon of the lost,
that cephalopod that crawls
across our nation's prairies?
The prairie squid.
And friends, there is a vision,
Bob had a vision of a
a little rain
of prairie squids.
Billions of prairie squids.
And friends, we weren't able to provide
billions, but who did
provide, Bob provided
one prairie squid for each day
and until next day.
One prairie squid per day
for you to de-meet
and use as you see fit.
And the song is in our
official, official
Bob's Prairie Squids.
One,
two,
one, two, one, two,
three, four,
83-D squid.
Yes, dear friends, and as the hard to hear
lyrics of 83-D
squids
melts away in the background,
friends, I'm going to give that post office box
one last time. This is your last
chance probably to
pre-register for X-Day
in Brushwood. Write friends
to Bob or Hour of Slack
or what not at
P.O. Box
Dallas, Texas
Once again, that's
Bob at post office box
Dallas, Texas
or try Slack
at subgenius.com
or try Slack at subgenius.com
Oh, good job.
Thats good, Bob.
go to b fought
b fought
yes you can
B This year our
amazing
b
this year
best
And the queen is here!
Got a testicle!
Oh, a testicle!
Oh, look at this!
I ate it!
Oh, a tanker!
Oh, a tanker, a tanker!
Oh, that's a...
Oh, look at it!
It's such a hot stuff!
Oh, the birds!
They give them a little warmth!
Everywhere, testicles!
Oh, there's nothing.
Oh, never see anything good.
Oh, it's clean, baby!
Oh, oh!
It's going to make me fast!
Bob will be angry!
I'm the great, the identical cloak.
The witty god versus the greedy god.
So if you're ever out in your own,
things look good right now.
When you see some hairy pink snow,
you may pull it down on us.
Sure, it's kind of a stretch.
Coming down from the sky,
just pull your little drum inside.
Far-fetched squid is the best, best, best.
And you so dearly enjoy the ride of life.
Here we go.
Pretty, pretty squid falling from the sky.
Pretty, pretty squid.
Look at the edges.
You'll have it coming around.
Pretty, pretty squid.
Now, let's fly.
Get low.
Pretty, pretty squid falling from the sky.
Pretty, pretty squid.
We can't just wait.