Say your prayers, you pinko.
Salime.
Just sometimes we learn.
All right.
You and me together.
Gonna take this life.
Forget about the price.
Ain't about the money, money, money.
We need your money, money, money.
See your head.
Salime.
You guys need a prayer.
But in jaguar.
But fair.
You guys.
need a break.
Why don't I take barre with me to the children's bop brunch?
The war on drugs and stayed together.
Slativism, or, you know, I think the real.
activism works this is the real way you say what you really feel and people who enjoy your work
listen to you have you thought about seeing a psychiatrist on a regular basis
well i thought you'd never ask i mean professionally thanks doctor yeah thanks for the advice
be careful out there don't worry i can take care of myself no you can't you're going to get hurt
i don't need your help i don't need anybody's help i'll be just fine
are you okay
yeah i'm fine
oh
don't push me bob now's not the time you better relax bob damn it i hate that bob i don't even
want to talk about it anymore all right i failed okay let me just sit here and enjoy the one thing
that makes me a little bit happy this fresh delicious tasty meaty the so genius
i eat three every day to help keep me strong mr bobby you are magnificent
i eat your name by chance
hey screw you man i got nothing because of you and here you sit thinking well bobby is not a
thinker bobby is a doer and that's what you need to do you don't need to think you need speed you
need to go out there and you need to rev your engine you need to fire it up and you need to
grab a hold of that line
between speed and chaos and you need to wrestle it to the ground like a demon cobra and then when
that fear rises up in your belly you use it and you know that that fear is powerful because it
has been there for billions of years and it is good and you use it and you ride it you ride it
like a skeleton horse through the gates of hell and then you win and you don't win for anybody
else you win for you you know why because the man takes what he wants he takes it all and you're a
man aren't you aren't you bobby is here to see you oh you see someone i was talking about bobby
you know what you're a tough man to find you know that buster i prefer solitude the day before a
race look i need to talk to you walk with me you have a good lunch take care man bobby now we shall
dance and yes it will be a slow jam
hey all you politicians
quit acting like a bunch of children
work it out let's work it out
jesus and muhammad come from different neighborhoods but they both try to
testify to the truth and they both try to tell the truth and they both try to tell the truth
the people about a higher good how the meat shall inherit and the wicked shall cease and they
rode to jerusalem on a half a horse a piece have a horse a piece i have a horse a piece
they rode to jerusalem on a half a horse a piece
a democratic hermit a republican hymn and the parents said we'd rather see you dead than one
of them a fight broke out at the wedding feast
and the parents said we'd rather see you dead than one of them
and they rode to the funeral on i have a
hepone
were
Million baboons
living
on a ham
he wasn't
having
this
out
take
something
to
he
win
and
We can lead the nation on a half a horse apiece
I called up the president, said, how's it going, bub?
He said, I'm stuck up to my axle and I don't think it's good
What do you expect when the house is full of geese
And they rode to the capitol on half a horse apiece
Half a horse apiece, a half a horse apiece
They rode out of the capitol on half a horse apiece
You might lean to the left, I might lean to the right
Come on, dance with me, baby, till the wee hours of the night
If I can learn to dance with these two left feet
Let's hope for the nation on a half a horse apiece
Hope for the nation on a half a horse apiece
Remember, my friends, this ain't a sporting event
Nobody gets to lose, and nobody gets to win
The art of the compromise is what my baby needs
I'll meet you in the middle on a half a horse apiece
A half a horse apiece, a half a horse apiece
Meet me in the middle
I was wrong about you, Bobby.
You are not the one to defeat me.
Tell Cal not to take Bobby out.
Hey, Cal.
Listen, I hate to add to your tremendous moral confusion,
but I just heard he said to take Bobby out of the race,
and you're fired, buddy.
What are you talking about?
You tell him if he doesn't do it, he's done.
That's right.
Will you tell him Mr. Bobby is my best friend?
Bad news for Bobby.
Who's in there?
Uh, yes.
Who's out there?
Bob, sir.
Oh, I understand, sir.
And I didn't see you here tonight.
I really appreciate that, Bob.
Yeah, thanks a lot, Bob.
There he goes.
Me.
And Bob.
Then you.
And me again.
Then Bob.
You and I are a part of a church that has not only listened the message,
but he has given us incredibly the means of getting to the entire world.
We have these in a number of languages.
I can't even tell you all the languages.
But listen, our goal is to keep putting them in as many languages as possible.
If we, if we, if we, and, and, and, and what we're choosing primarily, listen,
and even today, the ministry is in the most spoken languages in the world.
Places like that, they have millions and millions of people in their languages.
And imagine sending these things all over the world.
And here's what happens.
People drop them, lose them.
Somebody comes along and says, hmm, looks like I got something here.
Turn that thing on and hear this voice and say,
I got something about it.
Use the milkshake.
Got it?
Got it.
Yeah, I'm slacking a bit.
Bobby is now convinced that whatever is in the house has become more aggressive.
Stay with Bobby's parents for the week.
Leaving Bobby at home, alone.
Even enjoy the calm of nine days out as its morning to bite.
But when the kı Construction.
Subtitle
Isso foi no tru roads,
at least no for the
ampreço de
I found out you were smoking in his newly renovated 88 Airstream.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, help Big Bob too.
Here.
Want one?
Go ahead.
In time of peace and too in time of war
I smoked two joints before I smoked two joints
And then I smoked two more
Oh, my daddy he once told me
Son, you be hard working man
My mama she once told me
Son, you do the best you can
But then one day I met a man
Who came to me and said
Hard work good and hard work fine
But first take care of him
So now I smoke two joints
When I get up in the car
I smoke two joints
I smoke two joints when I play video games
And at every ten thousand points
I smoke two joints
I smoke two joints in time of peace
And two in time of war
I smoked two joints before I smoked two joints
And then I smoked two joints
Another natural product made better by chemistry is
Marijuana
Years of research were necessary in order to improve the product
But it doesn't take long for the drug habit to make anyone over
In all the colors of the rainbow
A few years back the United States of America had nearly gone crazy
They were lining up dope peddlers and shooting them in the back of the head
Just take it or leave it
Then it's chemistry to the rescue
The answer is a simple one
Just use your head
But there's one sure thing
If you use narcotics
The horizon is unlimited
Talk to someone who has had the experience
All around us are the products of modern chemistry
Heroin, morphine, reds, crack, sleeping pills
Something that came out of a test tube
Created in the chemist's laboratory
By a miracle of modern science
Folded into a compact little package
Many times as strong
And the dope addicts say
Yes, chemistry has changed the world we live in
Something that came out of a test tube
Is going to have been transformed into the destructive forces
Of useful life
Most teenagers start off with marijuana
Some of the boys smoke them
You know, the ones with backbones
My girlfriend Ann and I went around with Bob
They both smoked pop
That's jive talk for marijuana
So I tried it
Funny what it does to you
Everything speeds up to a hundred miles an hour
There was something intriguing and different
When I came home high that night
You're real sharp and you laugh a lot
You're the biggest person in the world
All you think about day and night is
The radiance of sparkling colors
And then you pass out
But when you wake up it starts all over again
And that's the story
Unbelievable, isn't it?
Chemistry takes a turn
It's a hand in such commonplace things as
Dope traffic in the United States
It's certainly true that the increased use of narcotics
Is a thing of beauty
Carrying off the harmful fumes
From other chemical processes
There's always the gentle dew
Which cover the surface with a film of gritty scratching particles
It feels like your skin is being torn right off you
It does
Some young man may develop startling
Stupid, ghastly, tragic
Hidden secrets of nature
The pioneer of tomorrow
Did you get a little pinch of this, a dash of that?
Sometimes referred to in the trade as a sleeping beauty boilermaker
Take no notice if he begins to levitate
It's a common side effect
I don't mean to interrupt
I mean, I...
I'd like to mention that
Some of you young people
Might be especially interested
In our novel and quaint gourmet's drug culture
Here in the future
First off, you can try our atomic dirt
It's very organic
Some of our more rowdy and dissatisfied teens
Will eject only once, of course
Pure cancer for that indescribable three-week death rush
We have a disease called communicable stupor
Or the drug bug
A contagious hallucinogenic state
Which passes swiftly from one person to another
And makes them happy
Whether they want to be or not
Always a thriller when unexpected
Listen and see
porque te invito
to stop
I had a little ping
Then you wanted your bar
All right, back to there
Ch extension
awi
Daddy beat up Mommy and broke her collar
Moaned for good luck and everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking on the job
The farmer he got plowed
The bricklayer got plastered
The mechanic he got tanked
And the construction worker got blasted
In Kansas City, New York City
Great big city, itty bitty city
Now everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking on the job
Well there's a whole lot of places that I ain't been
A whole lot of things that I ain't seen
A whole lot of things I'll never be
The generation that would change the world
Is still looking for its car keys
The
Please
guitar solo
The terrorists got bombed
The president got hit
Security was tight
Yeah, the Secret Service got lit
The FBI, the CIA, DWI
USA, everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
Everybody's stolen
There's nothing, nothing gonna change it
Cause everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking all the time
Hey, Rich!
I got all the words, I just got them in the wrong order
Man, you should not have bought me all those Guinness before we started
I mean, man, this is our, this, this is our job
Good work if you can get it
And with your kids
Right in the front row, man
I love it
Oh yeah
I'm drinking
I said I'm drinking
Oh yeah
Oh baby, I'm drinking
Drinking on the job
I'm just not a coffee lover
I think what makes folks need to be taught about coffee
Is because some people drink it religiously
Yeah
They have to have it
They can't make them without it
They build their life around coffee
Like a drug addict does
And some folks build their life around RC
And coke
Yeah
How many more because I make, like, $2 impact water
Yo man ciao
发
prove it. You know, it was...
We'll come right back, ladies and gentlemen,
to Mr. Lynch and Mr. Greenwood
after these words from our sponsor.
Unfortunately,
dear friends, our
sponsor could not be
here tonight. J.R. Bob Dobbs
was busy elsewhere
out in the world, and
that's just
too bad. However, I did
get my headphones working.
Just barely. Yay!
And, um...
Uh...
Yes, yes, in any
minute now, we should be joined
by the
Lone Cow.
That song, Drinking on the Job
there, was by the
Rainmakers, of course,
who also did the opening song,
Half a Horse a Piece,
which I think may be the world's only
pro-compromise
protest song.
I really
like that one.
It's my motto.
Those are from a live
performance DVD called
25 On.
They also have a new album. The Rainmakers
have a new album called 25 On
of new songs, but the live
thing has a lot of
oldies, too. It's great.
Longtime
hour of Slack listeners are probably
going, oh, no, it's gonna be
nothing but Rainmakers for the
rest of the
year, an hour of Slack.
Yeah.
And it'll also be Lonesome Cowboy
Dave. Of the Huffytown
Poots. The Huffytown Poots.
And they were with, oh, and before
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and the Huffytown Poots,
the Toys did
Smoke Two Joints.
The main collage was by The Large,
although the Bishop did
the Marijuana Collage.
And there was a clip from my underground
movie, Let's Visit the World of the
Future, as seen on YouTube.
The background music is
The Psychoskeletons.
And this is
Dave World.
What a world it is, too.
Hardly anyone breathes above
the water. Most people's nostrils are
the size of dishes. Their eyes
and their ears were made for other things.
Supersonic listening.
Supersonic seeing.
Super hyper
engaging of the enemy.
You were about to say something dirty, weren't you?
Yeah, I was.
Something dirty.
More humorous to get engaged to an enemy
because then that would be a hell of a marriage.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
There's another Princess We Laugh.
I collected...
Delightful accent.
You know, I collect Princess We Are
No Laughs, and I got a
really good one one drunken night
at X-Day, thanks to those zombies
Reverend Nikki Deathchick
and Bob Wild were making.
And
I used it three or four times
on the last hour of Slack.
And people have told me
that they're trying to figure out how to use it
as a ringtone.
Well, you are one hell
of a woman.
The way you can see into the future
and predict the past is beyond reason.
What? You're talking about
a different space princess.
There is no future or past for Princess We.
Yeah, I noticed you predicated
with that space princess.
She's in the now.
Where times were laws of nature
and physics do not apply.
Oh, that reminds me.
I found a note I'd made to myself
to start the...
Something about the movement to eliminate now.
Now?
Yes, it was a movement to just end now.
The concept of now.
And allow only past and future,
but no more of that little micro nanosecond
of a nothingness point.
Sliding along the time bar.
That's where Princess We lives.
It's that non-existent point
where everything is the now.
The now.
Whereas I'm like a...
a...
band.
Who is old now.
But it doesn't have any...
Weren't you guys the Radio Alarm Clocks?
We were just the Clocks.
The Clocks.
They said there was some
band that just signed.
That used to be important.
They just signed with a major label in Chicago called
The Clocks. And they had just
adopted the name recently and they were a bunch of
punks in a bad way.
Well, there's some other Cleveland
band of the day called the Alarm
Clocks. I know when you heard that you wanted to
clock them. It's confusing to me, but I guess
if they want to steal from the
originators in the past of their own
dirty feet, then let
them pursue it. Well, we had
a friend whose
band, one man band, was called
Man.
Man Rock. He
played bass and drum.
He played the drum with his foot
and played the bass and he sang.
He did punk songs. They were
really good.
But it turned out there had been some
ancient British band called
Man. He had to change his name to
Man Incorporated, which just didn't have quite the
same punch.
The same punch.
Hey, speaking of bands
and paranoia in America, which is what I've been
thinking about lately.
Oh, there's music in the background?
It's not real music.
Yeah, it is.
It's in fact, Princess We is on it.
I think it's jamming from X Day.
Last X Day drill.
It has an effective undertone.
Actually, this isn't the part with We on it because it doesn't have the flute.
The flute part is coming up and it's like ten minutes long.
Oh, no.
I could switch to the instrumental by the it's the Rolling Stones.
Greatest hits as played by the Rockville Orchestra.
And Rockville.
Uh, somewhere.
Uh huh.
Yeah, somewhere.
And it's like elevator music.
Rolling Stones.
It's great.
It's perfect background stuff.
Anyway, Dave, did you hear about a some sort of rock and roll festival here in Ohio that
got busted on my or rather got harassed on my birthday called Root Wire?
Was it Root Wire?
Was it the Red Gate Festival?
I don't know.
It's called Root Wire.
It's held at Kempner's Woods near Logan.
Near Logan.
Yes.
And apparently it's like a music festival draws about 5000 people and 4980 of or and
20 of them didn't get busted.
But 80 of them did.
Unbelievable.
Well, it was one of those things where.
It's a mass arrest.
You know.
It was the cops did the thing that we've always.
You hear rumors about this at things like Starwood and it never really happened.
But in this case, it did happen.
I guess the cops just needed money for their department and they parked outside the the
festival and just stopped everybody coming and going.
Yeah.
And of course, they all had pot and they you know, so they managed to to.
There also was some idiot vendor who was selling for real drugs, LSD and heroin and
stuff fairly openly.
And he got busted by undercover cops.
But that also wrecked the owner, the campground owners liquor license.
And probably that town won't be getting the income from that festival anymore.
Nobody's going to want to go and get ambushed.
I used to do that.
I had a blast until they realized people might not want to come back to these.
Right.
That's actually there were there.
They were busting people at a Starwood about 15 years ago, but it wasn't for drugs.
It was for endangered animal parts like eagle feathers.
Yes.
I.
Yeah.
But but anyway, yeah, there was a there were there was a sad time there for those poor.
Oh, and this is a funny part of the.
The ones who only spoke Welsh.
Can you imagine?
Oh, it's a big nightmare.
You know, and of course, there would be the one cop who acts also speaks Welsh.
I heard what you said.
I thought like a lot.
And then.
Yeah.
But they the vendor who got busted, they.
Was a weenie man.
He had a lot of stuff.
And he had 68 fruity pebbles snacks that were laced.
63 brownies.
70 grams of liquid LSD.
Now, if that's for real, that's a lot.
That is a lot of a molecule.
And but here's the one that really got me.
The cops busted somebody with 25 pounds of nitrous oxide.
And since nitrous oxide is a gas, that's a lot of laughing gas.
Yes.
That's nothing to laugh at.
That's nothing to snicker about.
Canister that weighed 25 pounds.
Well, oh, you think they meant the canister.
We use those same.
We used to buy that stuff and just empty it out because we wanted to use the canisters
for subgenius souls.
And we do.
We still do.
That my basement's got 40,000 souls.
Yeah.
Something like that.
All told, I don't think all 40,000 souls weigh 24 pounds.
No.
Yeah.
They probably don't weigh an ounce.
I mean, I don't think they weigh an ounce.
Soul doesn't weigh much.
No.
It weighs a little bit.
No, it's like a microgram or something.
Just to, yeah, some guy kept weighing dead people before and after the moment of death,
and he was pretty sure that some people's souls are heavier than others.
Oh.
Yes.
Dr. Sinister, the poor heavy soul.
Look at how soulful and his soul looks heavy.
I can see your aura, by the way.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it looks awful.
What color is it?
Kind of a puke-ish.
Yeah.
It's a greenish yellow with lumps in it.
Nauseating blueish greenish yellowish.
It smells bad.
No offense, man.
I mean, but we're all here in this little radio studio.
It's kind of like that.
Yeah, I know.
You know, it's best for me to clean my aura out before coming into an enclosed space.
I understand it.
Bad soul.
I failed.
I know, and the place is littered with spiritual pubic hairs.
That's one of the weirdest things I've ever seen, heard, or smelled.
Now, you weren't getting Dr. Sinister's aura confused with the wall color.
I don't know what color in this room.
Were you, Reverend Stang?
No.
Okay.
Just wanted to make sure, because it is kind of a puke green.
Puke green wall color?
I have never puked up anything that color.
Except for this one time.
That's designed to relax the inmates.
They should have put a pink thing there.
It's up to the bad guacamole, right?
Yeah.
Brain-eating amoebas will do that to you.
There's been a lot of those in the news lately.
The brain-eating amoeba?
Nefertiti something fowleride.
Or something like that.
I can't remember its exact name.
It's a large amoeba.
Viva amoeba?
Yeah.
I wonder what Tommy Amoeba has to say about the brain-eating amoebas.
It's like, oh, he raises them.
He's got a whole collection of them inside his skull.
How do you think he got that way?
I've got a nice recording of Amoeba Knievel, his band from Pittsburgh.
How do you think he got those other parts?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Is that a pseudopod or are you just happy to see me?
They have trouble getting hard, the amoebas do.
Yes, I used that with a zucchini joke.
They don't have that spine or anything, or an exoskeleton, anything.
The brain-eating amoeba, though, friends, here in Ohio, we don't have to worry too much
because they seem to grow only in hot, brackish, freshish water.
That's the thing.
Presence of remains is the greatest.
You gave seasoned science students the opportunity to study Amoeba's needs.
And thebturn was going to pull something out of it.
Yes, im going to do a recent analysis of teachers say that fejustfive pennypl Nosy
i that only if i found an actual underlying religion of their Christopher
den ammo.
Hens and rattlesnake hunts in Texas, in that part of Texas.
Why not brain-eating amoeba hunts?
Yeah, why not?
The same way with a vat full of brain-eating amoebas.
They grow to be about, I mean, they're visible amoebas.
They're not so tiny.
You can't see them.
You know, there have been amoebas that were like this big.
No, I didn't know.
You must remember you're on the radio when you say this big.
One cell.
Yay big.
Yeah, well, I was holding my hand out.
This far apart.
Come on, man.
How specific do you want me to get?
I know it is TV.
Actually, the bigger a cell gets, the less efficiently it can exchange nutrients and waste products and whatnot with its outside environment.
That's why cells don't get to be gigantic.
Yeah, or at least the intense desire to do so.
Yeah, there was a time when the oxygen was richer.
Insects could grow to be about, oh.
Three feet long.
It was gold in the wind.
But since they breed through holes in their size, it's hard to do anymore.
Spiracles, those holes are called.
Yeah.
It's like a form of alien smock.
It's when these particles, I mean, these amoebiums and paracetamethiums get together, you know?
It's like their own little fun fest.
And sometimes 800 of them get arrested for wearing noxious clothing.
Well, it is pretty noxious, you know.
Their taste.
Well, when you show it.
Protostimates.
Their own taste in clothes is famous for being.
You can be checked twice a day, you know.
It's an old joke, but it bears fruit.
Let's see what else I have on my.
Well, see, I switched from staring at amoebas all day to staring at video games.
And that's been in the news lately, too.
Princess, you probably haven't heard this one yet.
Dang.
An eight-year-old should be staring at.
It's women's breasts.
Keep on saying that to yourself.
No video games.
It's called women's breasts.
Or you could, you know, say buttocks if you like.
If that had been the case, a little boy's grandma would still be alive today.
As a little kid who was being looked after by his grandma, who he loved,
he was staying at grandma's trailer court.
Carnally.
And he'd been in the other room playing Grand Theft Auto 4.
And he finished playing the game and he went downstairs.
And got granny's gun and walked up behind granny and shot her in the back of the head.
An eight-year-old was playing Grand Theft Auto 4.
Right.
Now, of course, immediately the Yahoo commenters were saying,
well, these video games make kids kill people.
And other people were going, no, guns kill people.
Others were going, no, guns don't kill people.
People were going, no, guns make it easy, real, real, real easy to kill people.
But Grand Theft Auto did, in fact, inspire an eight-year-old to go down and get some extra points.
By shooting grandma.
Actually, in the game itself, you would be penalized.
We don't know this as a gleaning of the news.
You might actually fail the mission if you were really playing the game.
Like multiple, I've played, that's one of my favorite video games, actually.
I'm looking forward to the sequel.
In a lot of missions, you are penalized for killing people.
Well, if you get caught, there's consequences.
You get caught in a lot of other missions.
Like you will specifically fail the mission if you kill, you know, certain people get killed.
No, but for the most part.
For the most part.
You kind of rack up general status by doing crime.
Not really.
You don't?
No, not really.
Well, I know some missions are really tricky.
Yeah, I mean, everybody plays the game differently.
Right, you can just run around killing people if you have cheap cards.
No, I've been playing, I've played the first couple of hours of three of those.
So I've, you know, I do like, I do enjoy the actual non-play.
I like the killing part where you have to.
Yeah, I get stuck, I get stuck just listening to the radio stations.
Right.
Yeah, the radio on Grand Theft Auto is better than what you're listening to now, I'll tell you.
Most definitely.
Well, they went to a lot of trouble, and that's why the subgenius game would cost so much to produce.
It would have to be better than Grand Theft Auto and have even more fake radio.
I think this is Reverend Angry Larry on guitar.
In the background, although it might be Suggs for sure.
Who's playing drums here?
Everybody.
Everybody but you, Dr. Sinister.
Well, there was a Reverend Bad Vibes, and there was a Reverend Biker Man.
And Ken Shover played drums.
That's Reverend Biker Man.
Oh, right.
Reverend, I peaked on you now.
Yeah, Reverend, I peaked on you now.
We, I don't, we've got to figure out what his real name is and put his name on the list.
Because Reverend Puked on You Now is not coming back.
The girls especially did not like Reverend Puked on You Now.
Very, very bad name.
Or Transgender Dressers, a very bad name.
No, no, you're thinking of somebody else.
Yeah.
You're thinking, I know who you're thinking of.
You're getting all burned on, aren't you?
Getting all hot and bothered, aren't you, Lone Cow?
Unfortunately, that's true.
Well, not really.
No, I hear some hooting.
There's some flutes in the background.
There's been a lot of hooting throughout this whole piece.
Somebody going,
Pantera had a flute.
Dave, I think you need to adjust the gag on your prisoner.
We can hear them.
Oh, actually, I should switch to different music.
I'll put on this Roqueville Orchestra.
I'm playing the Rolling Stones.
It's sickening.
It's really horrible.
Speaking of flutes, this is Sympathy for the Devil.
Obviously, elevator style.
I've been spending some time on the Internet and watching TV news.
Thanks, Dr. Legume and Pockets.
And the world is really scary on the Internet.
You read the Internet.
You read the news article, and there's the most horrendous, racist, strife-creating crap.
See, I haven't seen it so bad since I was a kid in 1959.
Let me tell you something right here.
WCSB talk shows were the precursor for Internet Message Board anonymous comments.
The trolls in your life?
Yeah, yeah.
We've had a troll problem for, you know, 20-plus years.
Well, your show was built on troll meat, so to speak.
I mean, you had...
Troll meat?
No, but I do wear a troll bone helmet.
But, I mean, the world of the Internet and the world of the news is not like the world
that I go to when I walk out of my house and, like, go shopping or go to a block party and
so forth.
I want to go to a crazy world.
The People's Republic of Cleveland Bluffs?
Yeah.
The people seem to be not only getting along with each other, they're miscegenating and
having babies together and making out and stuff.
There may be some...
In the parking lot?
I have no doubt.
Of course, there's still...
Breastfeeding children in public places.
You can tell by the people saying there's no racism anymore that it's as bad as it ever
was.
Yeah, I know that.
The way they go about trying to say that...
Ooh.
Yeah.
That's...
says it all.
But that's not what they're trying to say.
I wonder how sincere a lot of the racism
you see out there really is, though.
Well, and how much of it is just trying to
stir the pot.
How much of it is just
people trying to... It's media-driven
in a lot of ways because of your...
Just trying to stir it up.
When people get along and do
unto others, that makes zero
news.
And that's
mostly what's going on out there.
In the world.
If you never leave your house, though,
and you absorb
everything through the media,
it's going to make you
paranoid.
Big time. Mean world syndrome.
Yes.
And you wouldn't even have sympathy
for the devil.
The devil!
But it's not non-stop racial
strife where I live.
It only is on my computer screen.
Now, we live in a fairly nice
neighborhood, but it's mixed.
It's a very, very
mixed neighborhood, and it mixes
fine.
So, go figure.
You know what it is?
People in my neighborhood
tend to have jobs, so they're not
desperate.
And they're not angry.
And they may
be overcharging for
some things. But it makes for a
happy, peaceful neighborhood.
Yes, it's strange to say,
but those do exist in a few places.
Now, watch us get home and find
our house has been broken into.
There's another one, and we
laughed for you.
I had just released
a valve, and I noticed
an incident that actually
happened in my town, and I
saw the tail end of it. It was a bunch of police cars,
and there were a bunch of
racially mixed, normal,
American kids all together.
And some redneck had
exploded on them, and went
into the store and tried to pick a fight
because there were too many
darned N-word kids in front
of the store. She called the
police. She said, get your buns
out of here. Those kids are waiting for the mom
to pick them up.
And I know where this comes from.
It's media-driven. Just listen to
the AM radio.
Or sit in there reading.
People have nothing else to do with their lives.
Actually, if you listen,
to enough AM radio, you will eventually learn
that it is liberals who are the real racists.
That's all they ever say on AM radio.
That doesn't take long to get to...
Right. Well, I've noticed
that what they mostly talk about is
not what they have to say themselves,
but, quote, what
liberals say.
Yes.
What they believe.
I know a lot of liberals, and every now
and then you'll run into one that's the cartoon
that Rush likes to present, but
very rarely, actually.
Most of them are just
Joe Lunchvale going to work
or trying to.
Cussing at his
fellow drivers.
Going, you welfare queens.
None of them have jobs.
Well, then it's funny. It's like,
the people who are saying...
The people who say
all that sure seem to have a lot of time
to sit on other people's websites
and radio shows saying that.
They say that
a lot.
You wonder,
when they have time to get their jobs done.
And you notice many of these
people who complain about
all the different so-called
what you call it?
I forgot the word.
The privileges we get
from having a government that doesn't want us
to necessarily starve. What do they call those?
The...
Loll socialism?
The socialism. These people have no experience
with these things. They were calling
Senor Obama a Stalinist.
Oh, yeah.
To them, a Nazi,
a Muslim, a communist are all
the same thing.
And a liberal. Those are all the same thing.
Nazis, communists, Muslims, liberals.
They hate America.
They hate our freedoms.
I am told that all day long
on the media,
which in the same breath
is telling me that the media is controlled
by those same evil liberals
that they won't shut up about.
Don't dare investigate that
unholy trance.
I ain't old.
Who needs to investigate it?
If you have eyes to see, it's pretty obvious.
And if you do
the investigating, it becomes
really puke-inducing. Almost like
poor Dr. Sinister's soul.
I don't know what that means, but it had to...
You can't get no
satisfaction.
We know the oinkments do work upon
occasion.
I like the Devo version.
I have a
great rant that
the good Reverend Roger
wrote, but
now I feel like I'd be stealing
from Dave and
we and Sinister to read it.
So I'll do that some other time.
I'm warning. That's just a warning.
Take it and run.
I do
have a song that I want to play
at the end of this show
called
There's a Frop
Frop.
Frop Farm.
By the Mutant Mountain Boys
live at 6T next day.
That's five minutes.
We can do that in the last
five
minutes.
If we have the right diagrams and measurements.
I have those.
If we have the right feet like Mercury's
winged feet.
Reverend Stang has the time control.
Yes, I have the time control.
Everyone has
the space control.
Next.
I have the time control.
I was reading
a novel.
I was reading a novel
that's set in the late 1600s.
It's partially about the birth
of science.
And
these guys are really
excited because somebody has just
invented a clock with a second
hand.
Who's
making that noise?
That's Dave's prisoner.
I told him to adjust his prisoner's gang.
That is his prisoner.
Yes, it is.
Are you sure that's not one of the owls?
My dog wants out and I'm not letting him out.
No, I don't think it is.
I really think it's Dave's prisoner.
He wants to get out now.
He needs to adjust the ball gag in its mouth.
That old man named Jake that he keeps in his basement?
I thought he was dead.
He wants out now.
No.
I may have let him out
but I'm not letting him in right now.
Oh, it's okay.
I thought it was part of
the bad X-Day band.
It's actually a pretty good X-Day band.
Yeah, but now
it's not the X-Day band and we still
have the moaning. So you see?
You see?
It's Dave's prisoner.
Whatever made that noise,
it ain't human
and it ain't an animal.
It's cathode.
You go on down in that pit
if you want to, Professor.
Go ahead and try to communicate with that thing.
One of the seals on the
soul containment tanks
broke and there's a
soul on the loose.
Scary. That is creepy.
It's a very, very strange place.
Palm trees, nauseous golf balls,
all kinds of Mexican utensils.
I can't really make anything out yet.
Mexican utensils?
For picking up, like, you know,
corn on the cob things that look like little corns.
They look like little tacos
and you stick them in your taco
when you're eating your taco.
To hold it.
Gently between your knees.
Hey, speaking of golf balls between your knees,
Princess, we and I went to
a golf course that
failed or
went out of business and they're
making it into a city park.
It's a Cleveland Metro Park now.
But it's still a golf course.
A golf course that they're letting
revert back to nature, but in the meantime
it looks like a life
after people
golf course.
But it's the only
golf course where subgeniuses
can walk around
and fall in the sand traps,
which have an odd type of
surface growth
on them.
That's an actual kind of
an eloquent
superficial place.
A giant antlion at the center.
It would be a great place
for giant antlions
to get joggers.
Yeah, and little speed
to use it.
It's horrible.
I didn't want to sing it.
It is really awful.
The Rolling Stones performed
by the Roqueville Orchestra.
Well, friends, this will be the last time
we play this. I'm quite fond of it myself.
This particular song is just
not very...
Or Get Off My Lawn.
Sing it now.
Give me a shot to give me shelter.
Oh, I can't wait to hear that.
Sounds like we're picking out
some Amish food right now.
You have to actually stop it in order to be able
to change tracks with these...
Dave, what are you doing to that prisoner?
I'm using my
forward utensil.
Here we go. The elevator version
of Give Me Shelter.
That's Dr. Sinister
wrestling. That's cheating.
You're embattling it
even worse. Worser.
You want it to be worser.
He does want it to be worser.
I can't wait for the rape and murder to come up.
It's just a shadow wave.
Blast it.
It's just a snot away.
Well, that's sad.
It is.
Snot is kind of a sad thing.
It makes me yearn for the Tom Jones version
of Give Me Shelter, which is actually pretty good.
And it makes me yearn for it.
It spells U-R-I-N-E.
Well, Dave, we're coming near to the end of the show
when I wanted to...
Because we played a bunch of
froppy songs at the beginning.
That's all right. I'm already not...
Yes, he hates to interrupt, but...
Yeah.
I wanted to play
There's a Frop Farm Over Yonder
by the Mutant Mountain Boys.
And on his farm
he had some froppy.
Two of them
are good-looking boys.
One of them's just a boy.
Don't care about him.
I thought they were crustaceans of some kind.
The Mutant Mountain Boys?
You're going to go beat the dog up?
What?
Or beat up the dog.
Whatever it is.
For yelling and scratching at the door.
He's not such a bad dog.
No.
It really sounds like a person
pretending to be a dog.
Yes, it does.
That's worrisome.
A person in pain.
That only going out will relieve,
even if he doesn't take a leak and just did already.
Okay, well, I guess I'll be going.
First it's the buzz,
then it's the dog.
The moaning dog.
Oh, my God.
Dave?
He's himself hung up?
That's the first.
I've never seen that happen before.
Maybe the...
This dog was about to poop all over the floor.
The prisoner may have rolled over
and knocked the phone off the hook.
Okay, here's the Mutant Mountain Boys live
and unplugged since we lost power one night.
Not our fault.
Some guy ran into a pole.
The whole town lost power.
Yep.
And luckily, we had a sideshow marvel
and a bluegrass band.
A bluegrass divo band.
A bluegrass divo subgenius band.
The Mutant Mountain Boys.
Thank y'all.
Now, this is a very serious song.
So, just chill.
¶¶
¶ Once my heart was bound in sorrow ¶
¶ Like a mask and spare a say ¶
¶ When the toilet ¶
Back in Grindley
And it drew me to come see
And the sewage had formed a message
It said 1-3-0-1-3
I then heard a voice from the town
Gently saying, follow me
There's a problem down the valley
There's a problem past the rain
There's a problem in your sorrows
When your mind is going insane
There's a problem when you're burdened
There's a problem where you're
strained
There's a problem
Heavenly problem
For kill me he did say
The time my friends forsake me
And I'm tempted to despair
Then I summoned my dear Savior
Short duration
Amen
I'm not here.
You would pay to know exactly what it is you really do.
You'd pay to know exactly what you really do.
And I'll guarantee you my proper.
You are probably a saint.
And there's a frog farm down the valley.
There's a frog farm that's the rain.
There's a frog farm in your sorrows.
When your mind is going insane.
There's a frog farm when you're burdened.
There's a frog farm where you stray.
There's a frog farm.
Heavenly.
I hope you'll make it insane.
Yeah!
Yes!
Frog farms for everyone!
Frog farms for Ella, my friend.
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Sloth.
We're back!
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
From PR News in Washington, I'm on the alert for heterosexual killings.
The State Department is closed Sunday.
The State Department is possibly occurring in or emanating from the Arabian Peninsula.
It continues to plot attacks for the entire month of August.
This weekend, the U.S. is also closing all facilities, including PR News in Washington.
Secretary of State Same-Sex Kerry says the U.S. will begin processing sexual PR News in Washington.
The economy added 162 jobs last month, while the unemployment rate fell to 7,000.4%.
Wall Street 13 authorities now say you're listening to PR News in Washington.
The Department of Justice called the decision involuntary and says PR is, quote, a sham.
James Whitey Bulger will not be taking PR News in Washington.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show, and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us.
Keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.com.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.