Who owns this house?
Who dwells in here?
Who lives here?
And how long have they been here?
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius.
Our subgenius.
Ah, yes, dear friends, a fine tune there.
Happy Lizards by Helpo Puey.
And this Hour of Slack number 9-11, actually, yes it is, is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 530.
Recorded in the early 90s at WCSB Cleveland on Chaz Smith's show, ESO Radio, with lonesome cowboy Dave.
But also with...
The full Einstein secret orchestra actually in the studio playing along live as we sort of jammed all in one gigantic horrible take.
And so, and so, dear friends, here it is.
Hour of Slack
Night
Step into the sun, step into the light
Ooh
Keep straight ahead for the most glorious place on the face of the earth, farthest ground
Hold on to your breath, hold on to your heart, hold on to your hope
March up to the gate and build it up
deeply
hustle here and hustle there
New York City's vape
The place where they said, hey, babe, go take a walk on the wild side.
I said, hey, Joe, go take a walk on the wild side.
Hi, honey.
Hello.
My name is Chaz.
And we are Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And that's what you were just listening to was Einstein's Secret Orchestra performing for you.
That was last week's show.
Let's put last week's show away and create a whole new show just for you.
I think we should put this guy over here on the turntable where he belongs.
Oh, he didn't want to do that.
Okay, there he is.
Breakdown.
Well, by the time you get this communicated, it'll be too late.
The pigs are outside the door.
What I want to know is who speaks for Earth.
Hey, here's Moansome Cowboy Dave.
Michelle down in the other studio on that box there.
I'm sitting here with a keyboard.
And Dave's got his guitar.
And Lisa Lisa is over there.
And?
The Reverend Ivan Stang.
Standing right behind me.
And that's a dangerous proposition, boys and girls.
Praise God.
Praise you, Princess Lisa.
The KY Jelly is ready to go.
And everyone is standing around in line.
Look, they fell for it again.
They're back again.
Told you they'd do it.
And they always fall for it every time.
Always will again and again.
Thought you could get away, did you?
Look at it.
He doesn't even remember, does he?
No, no, no.
Just let him guess.
Or just let him drift in and out of realities for a while.
Who speaks for Earth?
Who sells for Earth?
And who will buy Earth?
Who will buy the Earth?
Here's one for Mother.
You are about to discover a part of yourself that you have never dared dream might exist.
This show will be a personal experience between you and the man with the pipe.
You are about to rip open a yawning chassis.
in what you thought was your personality.
You will stand on the brink of a hole
deep within yourself.
A pit, a pit, and a stinky pit,
and then the very deepest, blackest part of the pit
that is your mind.
You will discover...
Bob.
But first, let's step back out into the real world.
The real world.
Now that you have achieved trance state,
come with us.
Come and travel in the astral planes as we seek
that which is dark.
But first, you must pull loose from your own body.
Yes, it's easy.
Just a little tug.
Close your eyes.
Float upward and give your soul a little tug.
You see?
You are free.
You're free.
You never thought you are so.
A little tug.
You never thought.
It would be so easy, did you?
Then let's go upwards.
Let's float.
Upwards.
To get perspective.
Higher.
Towards heaven.
But we'll stop here in face, in space, first.
Just past the Earth's atmosphere.
You see?
We can go anywhere instantly this way.
And it was all so easy, right within humanity's grasp.
All alone.
And you know the secret.
You know the secret.
Really.
You can go anywhere.
Let's try something new.
Oh, it's beautiful down here.
We could just float along and watch the fish.
Or...
Roll on up on the party system.
Come on in for the best in town.
Take your pick and the pie is fine.
Lay your bets on the side of the...
Or...
I can plunge you into this trench in the middle of this blistering hell planet and
send you to sit in change in this ditch forever.
Just waiting, waiting, until the ticks come again.
Yes, just waiting, the giant ticks.
Here they come again.
I better start shooting.
Don't look.
Let me look.
Oh, keep shooting.
You could shoot another one and another.
Oh, you'll never kill them all.
Keep shooting.
Just keep shooting.
Oh, they're coming in.
See, just like your job back at home, ain't it, boy?
Yep.
You just can't get away.
You can't get away from them tics, my friends.
So join them.
My mother never answered one of my prayers.
I made obeisances.
Well, you paid Obias and today, but did you pay money?
Actual cash, green, and gravel.
Think about it, boys.
Don't wait till everyone in your neighborhood's got the bomb.
Nuke them.
Now at Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Hi, friends.
I'm Hiroshima Schwartz of Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse,
home of the Mini-Mag, the Pocket Thunder,
the baby neutrino that leaves their apartments intact,
and many other fine, low-range, low-rad nukes.
These teeny-tiny warheads actually fit in your wallets.
You can buy them at the
And what's on special this week at Hiroshima Schwartz?
It's the giant X-Day Drill Sale.
Now until the wee-wee hours of July 6, 1996,
we are literally giving away tons and tons of useless and useful weapons.
It's the Werner Von Braumeister Party Special
that blows away 50 party pinks at a time, leaving the party intact.
Disguised as a four-gallon keg, that first draft really packs a wallop.
But for paid sub-GT,
it's the smart prairie squid face-seeking special.
I'm sorry, I always get that wrong.
It reads your mind and literally knows where to send the warby.
Finally, now till X-Day, bloodier than any golf pro,
it's the exploding head of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
When the pipe lights, it's armed.
When launched, it zaps up to 100.
That's 100 useless bobbies at a time.
Friends, don't wait till it's too late.
Everyone will soon have the bomb.
Nuke them now, from now till X-Day and beyond.
We are literally...
Blowing off the competition!
Hiroshima...
Hiroshima Schwartz's X-Day End of the World Sale.
Till a mob sent you and received 23% off.
Batteries 92.
Some assembly required.
You know, I've been eating alien smegma pie for almost 50 years.
Since those first shoster crashes near Rosberg.
Well, my sons grew up on it.
His sons too.
Here in Wilburville, it's...
Wilburville, it's as natural as pie.
But many folks don't know about alien smegma pie.
Things kind of changed since we landed on the moon.
Some things, we didn't even go.
Some folks believe in things called graze.
Gramps, did you eat your pie today?
It's my daughter, always worrying.
Hey Gramps, when are we gonna go to the nude dancer's and worry in a massage parlor?
Phew.
And that grandson of mine always keeps me running.
Then, forget our little appointment.
Oh, nice and tidy.
I've been staying in a sack with Grandma for a long time, thanks to alien smegma pie.
All I know is alien smegma pie is made of a cheesy wax from alien genitalia.
It's made me sexually active again.
And it tastes great.
That's all I know.
Building a new race in this life is hard.
And nothing gets easier.
Because it is hard as alien smegma pie.
Alien smegma pie, the taste that's out of this world.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
No, he hates you, Dave.
He hates you.
Bob hates you.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has answered all of my prayers.
He even told me go and fling myself down the stairs.
I did it on a lot, but now I'm glad.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you.
You may love Bob, but Bob hates you, Dave.
He makes you fling yourself down the stairs for fun.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
We're sweet and slimy just like little bees on a tree.
He calls me on Valentine's Day and I'm sending flowers and chocolate.
And he loves me anyway.
I said it.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you, Dave.
What could be more pure?
It's the purest form of love anyone could imagine.
He answers all my letters.
He calls me up and leaves messages.
He's on my phone.
He's always with me.
The computer does all of that, Dave.
He hates you and I love Bob.
Don't be a sucker.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, I love Bob.
Bob loves everyone except you, Dave.
He loves me and I love Bob.
Because you were so stupid as to believe him when he said he loved you that first time.
He tells that to all the people.
He's a good boy.
He believes in you.
Bob loves me.
It's not a torture catapult.
It's pure and beautiful and shivering.
Bob loves me.
Stop.
You don't love me.
This is what Bob meant when he said, pull the wool over your own eyes.
I can't see anything.
Oh, I'm going blind.
I'm going blind.
But you can still see Bob in your mind's eye, can't you, Dave?
My mind.
You never stop seeing Bob.
You never stop seeing Bob in your mind's eye, such as it is.
My mind?
What there is of it.
What?
Your mind.
Your mind is no longer your friend.
I'm a physical person.
I'm in love.
I'm in lust.
I'm in love with Bob and I don't care what you say.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
Bob does love a fool.
That's true.
Bob loves the fools of this world and truly the king of fools is lonesome.
I love Bob.
He's like Power Cow Boy Dave.
Now performing the greatest guitar solo in the universe.
Rock out, baby.
I'm playing Dave.
You know I don't hear the music.
But, oh, thank you.
I can't hear me.
No.
What do you mean?
Which one?
I thought that was all on streams.
And you see, friends, you'll see how the love of Bob has freed Dave
from that ponderous nightmare.
real life around him.
He pays no attention to
what other people might think of him.
Sure, they think he's a
fool, an idiot, a bad person.
He's like a half-janger.
I'm blue value.
Watch him. He's happy.
You can hear the simple
happiness in his voice.
He's a form of existence.
I can't express how happy I am
when I think about it.
Don't think about it. You won't be so
happy if you stop and think about it.
Now, will you, Dave?
Why are my pants all wet and what's wrong with me?
How come I can't close
my mouth or open my eyes?
Why doesn't Bob ever call
a writer, answer my letters,
or leave anything on my
message machine?
You're not losing your faith
now, are you, Dave? That would be a
great sin, a grievous sin
indeed.
To lose one's faith.
To lose one's faith in Bob.
He has no faith in Bob.
Bob has no faith. He has no faith.
Meaning he only has a head.
He cannot have a faith in a head.
It's what the god Janus
had two faces on his head.
Neither one of them were looking at the same thing
at the same time.
And Bob can see you out of each one of those
dots on his face like
multifaceted eyes of the mighty
insect.
The mightiest insect.
Boing, boing, boing.
The mightiest insect
is the Dobson fly.
A tiny pea-like
into a
magnificent, magnificent
brain.
The sucking bugs
of the
amazing northern Ohio
area include
among the order
Hemptera. I said
the order Hemptera.
The sucking bugs.
The bugs who suck things
through pipes.
Such as the water scorpion.
And the rantrofusia.
And the giant
water bug. Did you ever see that movie?
The giant water bug?
That was great. The giant water boatman
was the sequel.
These are lovely and interesting
insects of the northern Ohio
swamp areas.
But aside from
the pleasant
happy-go-lucky order Hemptera,
one also finds
the order Neuroptera,
which includes
in the sinister
family Corridale
Day. Do you hear
the significance of that? Corridale
Day?
Salvador Dolly Day?
We find a creature, yes, a
living actual bug
of the northern Ohio swamp area.
It's called the Dobson fly.
The Dobson fly?
The Dobson fly, which is, you can go
see the Dobson fly, which is, you can go see the Dobson fly.
It's a stuffed mounted example
of this hideous, vicious beast
in the Cleveland Natural History Museum.
The Dobson fly,
while surrounded
by lovely butterflies
and not too alien-looking dragonflies,
you'll notice that the
Dobson fly has the head
of a vicious red
ant with hideous
clicking mandibles
and the body, a body
that resembles the tail of a
rattlesnake.
Horrible flapping
leathery wings.
Yes, the Dobson fly.
This is not
some biological
freak that we're making up. I'm afraid
there are thousands of Dobson fly
larvae. Now, they are
in their season, their 50-year season.
It was in the 40s.
In the 1940s was the
last time the Dobson fly cycle
reached its peak.
And thousands died.
As these pincher-like beaks of billions
of Dobson flies
attacked the suburbs
of Cleveland.
Oh, the days of Velikovsky.
I thought it was Wassily Kambusky.
And every time you
swatted a Dobson fly,
a million eggs would squirt
out of its ruptured abdomen.
Each egg
hatching into another million
Dobson flies.
And each time you tried to squash
one of those, it would
hatch another million.
Evolution has no plan.
You see, friends, man
likes to think himself
the grandest thing in all of
God's great creation. But indeed,
no, it is the great
order of the insectoride.
The great brain
of all collective insect
hives and tribes is
a billion times smarter than
any single ego-centered
human brain.
Certainly,
certainly,
one Dobson fly or one
tick may possess
a rudimentary brain,
but they can communicate by radio
with each other. And the millions
of each species, each
forms a great brain of that species.
And those brains
get together to form brains.
And let's face it, you're outsmarted,
Mr. Earth Boy, Mr. Human,
Mr. Two-Legged, Mr. Tool-Using
Primate, Mr. Thinks-He's-So-Big-Time-Smarty-Pants.
But you know, if you
took that human back into
the early Devonian
period, even here in the
lovely northern Ohio
area, you would find that
there was no Devo.
No Devo?
No Devo. There was, but
because there was a slimy ocean
covering the northern Ohio
plains. A filthy,
sewer-like,
shallow, but murky, muddy,
disgusting,
smelly ocean.
And in the
depths of these foul,
murky puddles, there
grew such creatures
as the
Dunkelosteus.
Yes, the Dunkelosteus.
And friends, I hate to tell you this,
but there is a, it's true that
there was an ancient plant
discovered, fossil
of this plant, and they named it,
yes, the Cleveland
Dodendron
Ohioensis.
4-4-1-1-0-E-S.
No, seriously, the Cleveland
Dendrodron
Ohioensis.
That was
merely, however, just a tube-like
plant with teeth and
thousands of eyes.
From Club Moss.
I mean, Club Moss was a great place back then.
I saw Devo at Club Moss in the Devonian
period.
Einstein Secret Orchestra, ESO Radio,
Boys and Girls, Ivan Stang,
in the house.
Now, as usual,
speaking of the
all themes of the insect kingdom,
we notice that through these
over-exaggerated sense of smell
that they also keep in a form
of ESP, extrasensory
contact with each and every
other member of their community.
And as we notice here, if I
expose one of these insects
to this molasses, all of the rest
of the insects will begin to come
within the air, even if they have been
exposed, or have been held
in this container, and
are incapable of actually smelling
the molasses. As soon as they're
released, they all begin exploding
because some of them have distillate charges
in the back of the vacuum.
Some of them have even approached
300 feet in length,
and some of them are well
over 2,000 pounds.
And I see them in my
dreams.
I keep on thinking of what's going on.
One of them was with Harry
that night when they went over
the edge.
These phobias can be
confident.
No, but those insects
were there the night
Harry went over the edge.
And how can we surmise that from this
incident, the head of J.R. Bob
Dobbs did emerge into the
lustrous as a numinous being?
I don't know, but you can
find out by coming to the X-Day
Drill in Brushwood,
New York, on July 5th
through 7th this year, and
every year from now to X-Day,
that's right Ivan, that's right.
Remember to call for free
information about the amazing
X-Day Drill. Yes, it's like
the legendary Dockstock
Gala. That's right Ivan, that's right Ivan.
You'll see the most
hated preachers of the subgenius
church. You'll camp out on a lovely,
fully developed campground surrounded by
geeks you'd rather not ever spend much time with.
by geeks you'd rather not ever spend much time with.
But by God, you'll know more about the church of the subgenius
because you'll be able to see the church of the subgenius.
Because friends, you will have practiced
for that fatal day,
that glorious day,
X-Day. Yes, only two years
from now in 1998, the
sex goddesses from
Planet X shall come.
And rupture up the
news paying fully
Dobbs approved subgenius
ministers. That's right Ivan. All
4,000 of us, and destroy
the rest of the planet. That's right Ivan.
Well, not destroy it, but
turn it back into the stinking swamp.
filth that it was before the filthy humans came along
and muddied everything up. But friends, you can come along and muddy everything up.
You can wallow in the filth.
You can dance all night.
You can pull your clothes off and county law doesn't care.
Because we are having the first
X-Day drill this July 5th
through Sunday.
Sunday! Sunday!
You'll see the pill.
You'll see the bleeding head
of Arnold Palmer.
It lives. It bleeds.
It bleeds for you.
If you don't vomit your money back.
Friends, you will see things
you wouldn't dare believe.
Things you never wanted to believe and
things you wish you never saw.
That's right Ivan. Yetis will be
copulating in the bushes.
The Loch Ness Monster will rise up
from the little pond.
The crazed
pagan drummers will drum all night long
and keep you from sleeping.
Mosquitoes the size of Dobson's
flies will devour you, but you aren't
going to care.
You won't care because you spent your money
and came to the X-Day drill.
July 5th through 7th
in Brushwood, New York.
Only three hours from Cleveland.
And friends, you can call for information.
216-
6-
I'll give that number again.
Write that number down.
It's the free information divinable hotline
at the Church of the Subgenius here in Cleveland.
556-
300-
959-
r
You won't be able to
see so much
trot
and rowing
At high speed underneath your sleeping bag
Tossing you around
It's like a giant funhouse
Yes, it's insane, it's crazy
But ain't it always been the crazy people
That were able to party like that
You have
Yes, sirree, bob, yes, sir, ma'am, sir, lady
You will
Finally learn what it's like to be
A subgenius
That's like Ivan Stang
Of the Church of the Subgenius
Oh
Oh, did I say that?
Well, then pick up on it, man
Praise Bob
This is it
Your last big chance to win back your soul
X-Day
Is coming
Kiss
All your calendars goodbye
And prepare yourself
To greet the men from Planet X
In power and glory
At the coolest campground in the United States
With sideshow marvels
Spontaneous doctor band combustion
Trained prairie squid
Frop enhancement workshops
Acubating
Psychic surgery
Human fights
Life
Freaks of nature
And acid casualties
Face-fucking
Bat sperm
Antidote pudding
Cook-offs
Private adult sex-hurt seminars
Self-mutilating preachers
And oddly normal-seeming people
Sex goddesses
Elder gods
And exes
X-Day is coming
Are you ready for the finals?
Which will it be?
Spaz outlaw holiday forever?
Or
The Last Roundup
Can you handle judgment day?
Will you simper while the world ends?
Or, Will you get slack?
July 5th, Brushwood Vultor Center, Sherman, NY
Brought to you by JR Bob Dobbs and The Church of the Subgenius
See www.Subgenius.com for more information
Experience the anxiously awaited moment
The nail-biting suspense of July 5th, 7 am
Only $30! None may stop us, and none may escape. Once the gate closes, raise bomb!
It's said that the end of the world shall come in a great flash.
I sure hope so.
Some people might go, and the other ones might last.
Will you be the one who goes?
Where will you be on next day, brother?
Where is your ass?
Will you be in the sauce with me?
There's still lots of room.
Or will you be down in the room?
You can hold up anything you want.
Will you be burning?
In this thing?
It's the perfect pleasure.
Perfect pain.
Which will it be?
It's up to you to choose.
Bob gives you free will.
But you can't feel anything until you sign on the dotted line.
And the next day is coming, so you better move fast, because where will you be on next day?
I've got plenty of time to spend my $30 on that bomb ministership.
I've got plenty of time.
That's two more years for next day.
Why am I in any kind of hurry?
There couldn't possibly have been some kind of a misprint in the book of the subgenius.
I mean, just because that first edition from McGraw-Hill actually did say that next day was on July 5th, 1996.
Well, they changed it after that.
I'm sure that, I mean, it looked like a mistake.
Probably it was a mistake.
I don't think I really have to spend that $30 quite yet.
Because that probably was just, it's probably not that the world's going to end.
In this year, 1996.
Probably not.
I could probably afford to take that risk.
I mean, I've got that $30.
That's not a problem.
But there's this Hootie and the Blowfish CD I wanted to get.
And, well, you know, I wanted to go to this movie about water spouts.
And, well, I just, I just, you know, I mean, Bob will wait on me.
I mean, Bob's a patient man.
He ain't a wrathful God now, is he?
I've heard Bob will love the subgeniuses even if they never spin anymore.
A patient man? A patient man?
Man, he ain't no patient.
Bob is the doctor.
He ain't no patient man.
Bob is the surgeon who will excise the filthy, rotting tumor that is America.
That is modern America today.
Yes.
My fellow rebellious citizens and untaxed payers and militia members, all the citizens of courts, we must come together.
We must come together.
Quick, they're coming.
They're trying to stop me from speaking.
All of us religious nuts and crazy, bright-winged maniacs, we must band together against the man because, oh, wait, they're coming.
I've got to get my message out.
The last true hope is 55603.
Call 55603.
Here they come.
No, no.
I'm not going to tell you how it's going to be.
I won't give your love to me.
You're not allowed.
I'm going to go down one day.
I'm going to tell you nothing at all.
I won't tell you nothing at all.
Hey!
Oh.
I got a cold crusade for a neck tie.
I got me a church by the roadside.
I laid out a rattlesnake hide
Bob is gonna ask you
Who do you love?
Oh, I tried to look at what the darkness was
You love me, got me around
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Hey!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh anywhere
I'm not that invite e
Not that I don't care
Oh, fot the time I was
But, it's just like
That I never saw
You following me
Oh, I who know
Obased on each other
You know I'm story
I fade away, I fade away, I fade away.
Bob's love fades like one missing dewdrop.
It's gone, man.
He hates you.
He hates you, man.
Give it up.
He don't love you, man.
Bob never loved you in your whole life, man.
He don't care one thing about you, dude.
You got to get it right, brother.
Your head's screwed on the wrong man.
Bob don't love you.
He hates you, man.
You understand the meaning of the word?
He hates you.
Ask yourself, are you worthy?
Are you really even worthy of his hate?
To me?
Am I worthy of Bob's hate?
Of course I'm worthy of Bob's hate.
Everybody hates me.
I'm one of the most hated men ever to walk the earth.
There's no reason why I dare on Bob Dobbs, the old hate master.
He wouldn't want to give me a few stabs at the old pole and eyeball.
I'm afraid you flatter yourself, Dave.
It's a form of love, Dave.
He beats you up because he loves you.
It's like a heavy thing.
You know, it's like a tough love.
You know what I mean?
Watch your pulse with that.
But you know, Dobbs did love Dave.
And there have always been Daves.
Yes, for thousands, even millions and millions of years, there have been Daves.
Lonesome cowboy Daves.
Generally ignored by science for obvious reasons.
But this month only in Cleveland Natural History Museum, there is, in fact, a new one.
A display.
A rather large exhibit called Cleveland Before Bob.
In which one may actually see fossils of the ancient peoples.
The precursors to the modern day.
The day that we unfortunately know now.
There have been, for instance, there's quite a wonderful set of artifacts that were raised up from the P-Dog site.
There.
That prove that even the early Davonians were tool using.
Not quite at the level of primates.
We're getting a finger all the way up here.
They had an unusual, there were an unusually large number of stone pot shards.
As well as, oddly enough, many pot sherds found at this dig.
Obviously pots were used, overused, probably.
Abused.
The abused, yes.
The abused pots.
They were broken all over the place.
Old clones.
However, we do know that the ancient Daves had a sex life of some kind.
As we can see.
I see in this a fairly well honed fluted point.
Carved from stone.
And notice here.
The wooden foreshaft.
One dot.
Of the ancient Daves.
One dot sounds like some huge.
Contained quite a wide groove.
So you could take that wooden foreshaft.
The ancient Dave, them old Dave men.
The old Dave men could take that wooden foreshaft with such a wide groove.
And the fluted point of it.
See now nowadays, modern days, it's not even made of wood.
It's just limp like an old Dosh rag, wash rag.
It's still got the fluted point.
But, you know, it ain't nearly as sharp as they used to.
Because the ancient, strangely enough, the Neanderthal Daves actually had a larger cranial capacity.
Than the modern homo-davian.
You see here, slide three.
Ugly creature.
But, yet, strangely enough, still our ancestors.
Well, yours maybe.
Friends, we poised on edge of evolution.
As we stand together here today.
A vast historic moment.
With brain much bigger.
And less to follow.
Must be one in the unknown to follow.
But even with its larger brain.
The ancient Dave men were able to build nothing but crude pipes.
There are thousands of varieties of pipes.
Shattered pipes found in the ancient settlement.
In which they smoked what, as far as we can tell, wild plant materials.
Including dogwood.
The bark of the dogwood.
Which was quite strong.
Quite a bit stronger than the bite of the dogwood.
Although it did have a good bite to it.
If he made you a dog stick, dogwood stick.
Rolled you up, run up some dogwood.
That does have a bite to it.
Has a hell of a bite to it.
Man, brain too big to do.
Come on dogwood.
However, the ancient Dave men had a natural enemy.
The mammothous primigenius.
Oh my god, here they come.
The primigenius, which is Greek for primitive subgenius.
I run a group far more intelligent than the modern subgenius.
I want to play all the old records.
As proved by the fact that you're listening to this show at all right now.
I'm gonna smoke all the props.
Here they come.
Unfortunately, the largest display in the museum showing the Dave men.
Is the items of unknown function.
A carefully carved and intricate.
Decorated bone and ivory fragments.
Which, the uses of which have yet to be discovered.
They seem to be senseless, randomly created.
Perhaps some scientists suspect they may have been used to dislodge unwanted objects from obscure body parts.
And orifices.
The early Dave men possessed more orifices than the modern Dave.
And made copious use of them.
Since the era of the Father Man miles down.
That is correct, why not.
Because if I know, something special about that field in question.
I don't know what he did there.
Or everything it consists...
Ofimmer will be more or less important than all either.
But there have been more orifices available, too.
And moth effoney, of which two have been gloves.
It could be tasteful feral.
Whether it be aIchd for black Facebook and JIvehVSMS.
The dames buried their dead.
Infant dames, fetus skeletons have been found,
which show the signs of having been ritually slaughtered by their parents for the delicacy.
The one item of diet that we know that the ancient dave men enjoyed was fetus nads.
We don't quite know how to put that, but certainly a serious delicacy.
Those things would go for $14.95 an ounce at least nowadays, you know, down at the Piggly Wiggly.
You can't hardly get fetus nads.
But the ancient dave men were able to harvest these from their...
Time, time now. Time to go out and harvest.
And harvest? What was it we were harvesting?
This was during the dawn of agriculture.
And these ancient dave men were, in fact, what we call...
Skull farmers.
Ah, there they are. Three hundred of them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha. Just waiting to be locked.
The women stay in the campground, mating with the men from rival tribes,
as the daves were out in the fields harvesting the skulls and the heads.
They tried to grow heads, but generally they were sold.
It's such bad news.
They told the skilled farmers that they were able to only grow skulls,
or else they'd forget to pluck their heads until they become skulls.
Ah, it is white. It is gleaming. It is ready to lop.
Ah, now what do we do afterwards?
We drink, we drink, we carve out the skull and we drink.
And boy, these are big skulls, because we have such big brains, but hard to drink heads.
In a vain attempt to gain the intelligence of the mighty mammoth,
the dave would drink the brains of the mammoth.
To gain the courage of the mighty, uh, cow, and its craftiness and speed,
the ancient dave men would drink the brains of the cows,
or rather suck them up through crude stone pipes.
Now remember, son, when you drink cow, you're imbued with all power of cow.
Strength, beauty, speed, fast, quick, small, tiny, little.
Ah, shut up.
This is what is known as sympathetic magic.
Obviously, today, in today's modern world, we know better than to fall for simple superstitions.
I drank that genius's urine just for a taste of brilliance.
That's true. There is the one exception.
Sympathetic magic does still work in the Church of the Subgenius.
If you will but drink of the fluids of fog, you will gain...
The wisdom of Bob.
His, his great intellectual acuity will be yours.
And you all know how smart Bob is.
He's from the Church of the Subgum Guys at Subgenius.
They're like all geniuses or something, right?
Isn't that what they're trying to say or something?
And, and Bob's this smart guy.
And so if you kill Bob and drink of him, it is an eat of his body, then you'll be as smart.
Nay! Nay, it's a lie, friends.
You can Bob.
From the land of the Ambulance.
Bob is not smart nor, nor intelligent, but only lucky.
So you don't drink of his brain, you drink of his other fluids until you have gained some of his luck.
Drink his tiny fluids for good luck.
Wear it on your head for good luck.
His armpits sweat.
His armpits sweat on fat, too.
If you can stand in front of Bob when he sneezes, you will be able to gain the viruses of Bob.
He knew this is most precious.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
If you clean up Bob's bathroom after he is finished in there, and I think you know what I mean.
Hey, I just came to clean up.
No, no, I wouldn't want to do anything like that.
Just trying to fix the plumbing.
You will gain his sales acumen.
I will own the plumbing business around the rest of the world.
I will control the plumbing enterprise of the planet.
It's true, folks.
You, too, could be just like the modern lonesome cowboy Dave.
This paragon of manhood and manly beauty.
This confident and stalwart stud and cool guy.
All you have to do is to know Dave is to know Bob.
And to know Bob, you merely must call the secret number.
Yes, this is a secret.
Don't tell anybody. Turn your radio down. Get your pencil out.
Call this number.
60338.
Go ahead, kids. Give it a try.
What if you got to lose a little time, maybe?
You did sign the application.
Kids, don't forget to get your special Bob Dom's decoder ring that explodes in your face for only $49.95.
Call now.
And get a nice, shining XS watch that works.
Just listen to Bob's recital as he decides to grab Bob and onions in a minute.
Give it a try.
Yeah, I will, dad.
I don't care if it's get to the bottom in 10 minutes.
I'm going to get the change of my life everything to enter Jim's north-west and he is setting a finger finger.
I'll give Brady the ball, and give Bob the ball, my child.
Hey, I want the speeding-up double to me!
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
Little darling, tell me why
I get so cold looking in your eyes
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
Little baby, leather in place
Take a minute to outer space
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
Henry?
Yeah?
Lou?
Show me now, somewhere, somewhere, somehow is it
Oh baby is it you
I look for a dreamer angel
Who speaks for Earth?
Earth.
Who smells for Earth?
Who flies in the face of authority for Earth?
Why is none of it in the webinars?
Who's paying the rent on Earth?
That's the question.
Who's gonna take care of this bill?
Who's paying?
It's passed by the pretty piggy.
Well.
Who will stand for Earth?
I don't know.
Maybe me.
Maybe you.
Maybe nobody.
Is that a dog?
It's really the same song.
No, really, down at the Cleveland Natural History Museum.
Have you been down there lately, Dave?
I had a dream I went there.
No, no, I mean, did you know that they actually had the jawbone of a yeti?
Who had the jawbone of a yeti?
Your proud city.
That's worth quite a lot of money.
They call it gigantopithecus, which is, of course, a scientifically inaccurate name.
It should be referred to as gigantanthropus.
Gigantanthropus?
It's more a primitive man than just merely some giant.
Gigantanthropus is an animal.
Gigantopithecus.
He's a misanthropist.
An animal.
An animalistic thing.
But this is, yes, indeed, the jawbone of an ancient yeti.
And how could you know such a thing?
Well, it says so right there on the display.
It's the jawbone of an ancient giant yeti?
Yes.
It is about a foot and a half long.
Looks like it weighs about seven or eight pounds at least.
You lie like dirt.
No, I don't.
There's a skeleton of a gorilla not far away.
That's conceivable.
It's a skeleton of a gorilla.
Even with its massive lower mandible, it is merely but less than half the size of the
gigantanthropus, the prehistoric yeti.
I would agree.
We call it prehistoric.
Of course, the yetis were keeping records long, 80 million years before humans knew
how to pick their noses.
Well, I would agree with a yeti.
And it was a gigantopithecus.
It broke his misanthropicus erectus.
And she was cute too.
She was awful hairy.
She was beautiful.
She was the hairiest woman I ever saw.
But she was big, wasn't she?
Yes, and there was something so fragrant about her feet.
Musky.
Musky, that's too old.
Get a whiff of that yeti's.
Max, Max, Max.
Oh, yes, musky's a natural.
Thanks, Alan.
I don't know what I'm just thinking about.
That makes you feel manly.
Big old yeti girls.
Yes, sir.
Okay, keep off her leg.
Are you man enough for the she yeti?
Are you man enough for one of her legs?
Are you a she yeti?
Yes, sir.
You could ride on that leg, boy.
You could grab you a tight hold on that mane she's got growing down that leg and ride.
I tried to ride her in my dreams.
I tried to ride her off into the sunset singing my Yahoo final darn year song.
But it seems to me every time I begin to mouth the love of young whatever you might
name the lady, I seem to...
She asked him her name and in a back room voice she said...
Wanda.
Wanda?
The she yeti.
Oh my god.
Wanda of the jungle!
Wanda of the Himalayas!
When I took a walk around in the park, she held my hand, she crossed my wrist.
I went out running and she caught me, just like that man!
It ain't no fun when a woman can out run, he ain't tackling me at the same time.
There I was laying on the ground in Central Park and birds twittering around and screaming
in pain.
And this huge, huge female yeti is here trying to have her way with me.
Wanda does not even think about the time when she could run.
Dallas. Deep
Wanda. Wanda does
sing. Behind
the grill. Wanda.
Behind
Wanda's dream behind.
Wanda likes schoolgirl
uniforms. Yeah, man.
Did you see the latest issue
of Yeti? Big Yeti.
I think it was Big Yeti, September
B-Y-Y-S-A.
Yeah, there was
some spread you there. I couldn't believe.
In fact, it was one of the largest magazines
I ever bought. We had to get a guy
who had, well, he had a Volvo wagon, and we
loaded up three or four of them, and it took half an hour
just to get them in the back. Oh, yeah, the fold
out in the middle is like 30 yards
long. Yeah, we was going to wallpaper that national
over on the top of the hill there with
oh, Mr. Repercussion
had lips.
Oh, those human
stroke books might show some
pink. But you won't be
seeing no pink in Big Yeti
magazine.
It is kind of
expensive. They're like $8.95.
It's specialty material. And if you've
seen the Yeti binaries
on the news,
on the internet,
you can get you some. Boy, there's some
pictures out there. It takes about
30 days to download.
They're so big.
They're such big.
Big Yeti.
Come out, Harry.
Because the
true women of the Yeti
race over the Big
Old Harry.
Oh, powerful.
And they could pick us
men up by our parts and
swing us around their heads. And we
loved it. Oh, it hurt. Yes, it
hurt, but we loved it because
they were disciplining us, you see.
We had discipline in those days.
The big women,
the bigger and hairy
women taught us discipline.
And we thanked them for it.
Yes, we got down on our knees and we
worshipped them. We were polite
to a woman in those days.
And I languished in my
dish. When we exploited a woman,
we cleaned with respect for the woman.
When we
When we dissipated a race of
gigantic Yetis,
we did it out of respect
and discipline.
We did it on time.
Not like these slackers of today.
Yes, in the first moment.
In the old days, the very
Yeti women were on time.
Always on time.
The blood runs thin.
They have fluoride in their blood.
They are not like the Yetis of yesteryear.
The yester-Yeti.
But I must interrupt with this important message, friends, on how to get to the real X-Day in western New York State.
That's Salvation and Infotation at www.subgenius.com.
Or, got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 204206, Austin, Texas 78720.
That's the Subgenius Foundation.
Or me, Ivan Stang at
Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That's Stang at subgenius.com.
If you want to email me
or e-mail me.
Friends in the background, this is D.K. Jones,
and this is the great instrumental
Kurosaki, Christ Bob.