Mr. Speaker, a message from the Senate.
The subgenius powerhouse mob.
Oh, but we are. We're all here.
We're all sitting here together right now. Remember?
Yes, and we were all sitting around at the Beachland Ballroom listening to the microphone when it came on.
Yes, and my nose was expanding and parts of my brain were disappearing.
Little pieces of my head were flying off into the atmosphere.
Oh, my goodness.
It was. It was. It was.
Oh, give me land, lots of land under starry skies above.
Don't fence me in.
Let me linger for a while in the land that I love.
I want to ride to the west, to the sun.
And gaze at the moon till I lose my senses.
And I can't stand huggers and I can't stand fences.
Don't fence me in.
Fuck you!
What's going on?
The answer is the U.S. military attacked a U.S. patrol killing four soldiers who refused to go on a convoy mission.
Convoys in Iraq frequently get ambushed on Friday.
A lot of people haven't arrived because Ralph Nader would be included.
Last month, Eagle County prosecutors dismissed Bryant after the woman accusing him of rape said that she did not want to participate in a string of break-ins targeting cars and RTD lots.
She is in a women's prison in West Virginia.
There you go.
I'm George W. Bush and I approve this message.
Oh, golly.
He's a tomato plant fellow.
Oh!
I'm John Kerry and I approve this message.
Vote for Barry Goldwater.
Mr. Speaker, our president again wants dead and decaying human flesh from the governed.
Today, medical science patches up mutilated bodies transplanting humans in.
Eyes.
Lips.
Even vital organs.
Is the next step the transplantation of the human brain?
Many scientists answer yes, but they pause and add a grim warning.
For in the ancient folk legends, tales are told of blood-sucking vampires crawling out of graves to live on the bodies of helpless victims.
Is man now doomed to produce a race of ever-living monstrosities worse than the vampires of legend?
Will ruthless men and women of great wealth and power be able to survive?
Will the power greedily buy or steal the living bodies of the young and beautiful so their brains may live on forever?
Such questions may seem fanciful, but at this very moment scientists are working on the answer to brain transplantation.
And human bodies are used.
I'm George W. Bush and I approve this message.
Vote for Barry Goldwater.
Uh, uh, Mr. Bush says...
My opponent wants dick.
It's wrong to cross against the cars.
And when I'm president, we will tell scientists that they can't lead the world against the computers.
You're on your own shot there, thanks.
I want dick.
Certainly the president's very large and very important.
Well, you know, Wally, there's a quotation from Shakespeare that kind of fits in here.
Take that gun out of your pants.
Well, I'm the president, I'm not going to give any shit.
Okay, so this is what I'm going to do.
I'm George W. Bush.
The president is going to be no more than a few years old.
And he's going to be the president.
And I approve this...
message.
Well, sort of.
Good evening.
And before I take your questions, let me speak with the American people about the situation in Iraq.
This has been tough weeks in that country.
And I'm going to talk to my friends.
If this were a dictatorship, it'd be a heck of a lot easier.
Just so long as I'm the dictator.
You said we're headed to war in Iraq. I don't know why you say that.
I hope we're not headed to war in Iraq.
I'm the person who gets to decide, not you.
Our enemies are innovative and resourceful.
And so are we.
They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and our people.
And neither do we.
I was sitting outside the classroom waiting to go in,
and I saw an airplane hit the tower.
The TV was obviously on, and I used to fly myself,
and I said, well, there's one terrible pilot.
The Iraqi regime is a threat to any American
and to threats who are friends of America.
The goals for this country are peace in the world.
And the goals for this country are peace in the world.
We are a country, or a compassionate American,
for every single citizen.
I mentioned early on that I recognize there are hurdles,
and we're going to achieve those hurdles.
We're going to achieve what we need to achieve.
Porque este país es un gran país,
with great values.
For a century and a half now,
America and Japan
have formed one of the great
and enduring alliances,
dua ger de baguias sig Feuerwerk.
From that alliance has come an era of peace
y entre tanta fuera de paz.
So that's what tells the ideas.
And my job is to think beyond the immediate.
Nobody can threaten this country.
Oh, they may be able to
bomb a building.
There are some who feel like it,
the conditions are such that they can attack us there.
The answer is bring them on.
Hay que l Stalin Colombia a само arranged?
trying to shake the will of the Iraqi citizens, and they want us to leave.
That's what they want us to do.
And I think the world would be better off if we did leave.
If we left, the world would be worse.
The world is better off with us not leaving.
I want to remind you all that in order to fight and win the war,
it requires an expenditure of money that is commiserate with keeping a promise to our troops
to make sure that they're well-paid, well-trained, well-equipped.
And the other lesson is that there are people who can't stand what America stands for
and desire to conflict great harm on the American people.
See, without the tax relief package, there would have been a deficit,
but there wouldn't have been the kick to our economy that occurred as a result of the tax relief.
You're working hard to put food on your face.
The law signed today directs new funds and new focus to the task of collecting vital intelligence
on terrorist threats and on weapons of mass production.
We cannot let terrorists and rogue nations hold this nation hostile or hold our allies hostile.
To encourage them to start a ministry which will find the children of those who are incarcerated and love them.
Coalition forces have encountered serious violence in some areas of Iraq.
Our military commanders report that this violence is being instigated by three groups.
There's a lot of countries that have got a direct stake in whether or not North Korea has nuclear weapons.
We've got a stake as to whether North Korea has a nuclear weapon.
China clearly has a stake as to whether or not North Korea has a nuclear weapon.
South Korea, of course, has a stake.
Listen, people join terrorist organizations because there's no hope and there's no chance.
To raise their families in a peaceful world where there is not freedom.
It's in the interest of long-term peace in the world that we work for a free and secure and peaceful Iraq.
A free and secure Iraq in the midst of the Middle East will have enormous historical impact.
You're free and freedom is beautiful.
And, you know, it'll take time to restore chaos and order.
But we will.
Conspiracy theories abound in American politics.
I don't think we need to be subliminal about the differences between our views on prescription drugs.
We say to seniors, we understand how important prescription drug coverage.
So prescription drugs will be an ingrained part of the Medicare plan.
The, the, frankly, mood of the world.
I would have been astounded had the United States acted unilaterally in trying to deal with Al-Qaeda in that part of the world.
You know, I think the intelligence I get is darn good intelligence.
And the speeches I have given were backed by good intelligence.
Some of the other members of the crew are here as well.
Where are they, Robby?
Where are the members of your crew?
Here.
Well, they must have couldn't pass the security check.
What do you think tribal sovereignty means in the 21st century?
And how do we resolve conflicts between tribes and the federal and state governments?
Tribal sovereignty means that, sovereignty.
You're a, you're a, you've been given sovereignty and you're viewed as a sovereign entity.
Okay.
And therefore, the relationship between the two is not good.
The relationship between the federal government and tribes is one between sovereign entities.
America stands for liberty, for the pursuit of happiness, and for the unalienable right of life.
You know, I, I was campaigning in Chicago and somebody asked me what, is there ever any time where the budget might have to go into deficit?
I said only if we were at war or had a national emergency or in recession.
Oh, so there's no budget.
Just higher, higher so the government is doing for about $700 million.
And what does that have to do with...'It' don't exist as common sense though, do you think?
I've always wanted to make poison in milk.
So they can start picking one from the end to the other.
It's up to the state and the government.
would happen then?
ARE THE GREAT LEGAL LOF WE LEGAL LEGAL, NO, THEY'RE GOING TO L你的 BROTHERその
WHO LIE WHAT REALLY MAR
want to call it speech
I asked Americans to give 4,000 years 4,000 hours over the next or the rest of
your life of service to America that's what I asked I said to 4,000 hours
there's an old saying in Tennessee I know it's in Texas probably in Tennessee
that says fool me once shame on shame on you
fool me we can't get fooled again for once at this Thursday ticket counters and
airplanes will fly out of Ronald Reagan Air Force
uh yes
dude
stop it!
dear friends
uh cut-ups there by yours truly and uh Fernanda Nende-Lemur and tonight
is uh Halloween two days before the horrible election
it's there's people disguised as monsters on the street and monsters
disguised as people in Washington and uh Rudy Schwartz project in the background
and lonesome cowboy Dave in the studio and princess we are dough and we're out
of candy yes it really is as we broadcast tonight it's it was Halloween
don't know when it was for you we have no more sugary tweets we only have little
nuggets of truth to dispense with our hearts and our minds and our minds and our
to the children and hope that they do not
vomit in their sleep and fall
into a deep coma.
I promise you they don't want that.
They don't want the
nuggets of truth. They probably would love the deep
coma. Oh, yes, of course. As the
romantic movement grew, we noticed
there were many, many more suicides
throughout the land. People
dressing up in drag and
blue shoes and
drinking tryptophan
and then...
Well, you know, when you've had everything, you start
thinking, well, I want to try death
next. We may
not have much choice after a
while. Yes, it'll be chosen for
us, I think. We all will get the
ticket at the end and we'll get
our stubs punched. Well, we
all end up on our heads, you know, Bob
said. One and all, the
greatest and the lowliest.
That's not very...
That doesn't really make me feel all that
much better when I see the
lowly suddenly become great
because of the other
lowly. The lowly
outnumber the highly, I guess.
Well, they certainly do, but we cannot
bring the highly down.
We struggle, we struggle, and yet
the highly remain on high.
I don't know, man. I'm feeling
kind of brought down.
But that's maybe because my neck
hurts. Well, it may be because of that
huge, gaping neck wound
inflicted on you by
one of your little teenage
twicker tweeters with a George
Bush pin on its thing.
That wasn't one of them. It was the anxiety
about them. It was the anxiety,
it was the worry about them that caused me
to cut myself.
I was anxious because they
burned it down
and then they tried
to resurrect it
and then I
had to vote for
the fatherland
and I had no choice.
I had no choice. I could vote
for Adol
for sickle.
I could vote for
von Hindenburg.
I used to vote for Hindenburg,
but the taxes went down,
but Hitler says
no new taxes.
The taxes...
I am dogs.
Get that thing.
As I march into Poland,
I can already feel my
feet begin to stink.
It was the same way we rolled into Baghdad
on the 4th of May
2002.
What? When was it again?
I don't know.
Somebody close the window and get these flies out of here.
Drag the corpses out.
Culturally and genetically
engineered buzzard.
Buzzing thing.
What is it?
I've got one of those
protest songs
coming up by a protestical
please fellow. Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I've heard about him.
It's a live recording.
Have you tried the ergot eye wash?
Oh, it is
very, very
sick.
Yes, I have.
The president's on the phone
talking to his mom and dad.
The president's
on the phone
talking to his mom
and dad.
The president's on TV.
Talking to you and me.
He's talking about liberty.
But you and I.
Meanwhile
outside the world is coming
down in a pile of shit.
There's war and revolution.
Suffering destitution.
The government seems proud of it.
Of the president's
on the phone.
Talking to his mom
and dad.
Saying should I
turn over evidence
or be a good old
stonewall lad.
The president's
with Karl Rove.
Talking to his White House
aides.
The president's
program control.
Making sure they don't
see the hope.
Meanwhile
outside the world is
tumbling down in a pile
of shit.
There's war and revolution.
Pain and destitution.
And the government seems proud of it.
Music
semb roller
Sir
Life
Music
Meanwhile, outside the world is tumbling down in a pile of shit.
There's war and revolution, pain and destitution.
The government seems proud of it.
The president's on the White House lawn, talking about opportunity.
Opportunity.
He's talking about opportunity.
As if there's enough for folks like you and me.
The president's on TV, telling us we're all free.
The president's in your mind, when nobody can see.
Meanwhile, outside the world is tumbling down in a pile of shit.
There's war and revolution, pain and destitution.
The government seems proud of it.
The president's in your mind.
The president's in your head.
Right.
Lonesome cowboy Dave in thine ear bones.
The who?
Of course we're doing everything we can to protect America.
It's hard work.
But by speaking clearly, it'll mean it's less likely.
And less likely we have to use force.
I wake up every day thinking about how best to protect America.
That's my job.
To, uh...
And, uh...
There's a lot of good people working hard.
And we're making progress there.
We've done a lot of good work.
We've done a lot of hard work together over the last three and a half years.
And I have, uh...
I understand what it means to be the commander-in-chief.
We're making progress.
I, uh...
Let me finish.
Of course I know Osama bin Laden attacked us.
I know that.
Of course we're after, uh...
Saddam Hussein.
I mean, uh, bin Laden.
He's, he's, he's...
Let me say, I certainly hope so.
Uh, I think that by speaking clearly...
Uh...
Let me, um...
You know, my hardest...
The hardest part of the job is to, um...
No doubt about it, it's tough.
And, uh, it is, uh...
One of the things I've learned in the White House is that...
There's enormous pressure on the president.
And you cannot wilt under that pressure.
Otherwise...
Um...
Understand that, uh...
We must...
Um...
Before I, uh...
I, I just think...
I believe that, uh...
Uh...
What you believe in your core, in your heart of hearts, is right for...
Interact.
Uh, you cannot lead...
If you send mixed, mixed messages.
And so the answer to your question is...
You know, it's hard work.
Uh, Phineas Narco from nationalcynicalradio.com.
Oh, God.
That's wonderful.
One chromosome too many.
He's my president.
Now, did you hear the story that Prescott Bush actually was the one who introduced the alien chromosome into the rest of the family's corpus habium?
And that's why he has the extra spinal attachment.
Like, he's got a little vestigial tail down there.
But it's not cute.
It looks like, you know, it's like, um...
Uh, uh...
Um...
It's got a...
It's a...
Monde-loid...
Monde-loid!
And he determined what he could see!
He was a monde-loid!
Determined that he would be...
The president of these here, you...
The restless snakes.
The restless snakes!
These uneasy sounds.
Well...
This is a cover of Monde-loid, played by Monde-loid.
Mongoloids at X-Day.
Actual mongoloids, too.
Yeah, it's the acid corpses, I believe.
So do they have three X's and two Y's?
Or besides the vestigial tail and the X-Line?
Oh, wait.
Here's the horny one.
That's the sexy, sexy one.
Anyway.
Let me make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make, make.
It's incredibly hard.
Need some wood?
It is hard.
It's incredibly hard.
It is.
It is hard.
It's incredibly hard.
It is.
Need some wood?
Understand how hard it is.
Missy understood that.
I think about Missy Johnson's fantastic body.
I told her after we came together, change positions.
Speed up.
Change positions.
Quicker.
Here, we're getting the job done.
It's incredibly hard.
I try to love her as best as I can.
We were very much involved.
It's incredibly hard.
It's a matter of using every asset at our disposal.
Just be.
It's incredibly hard.
You need some wood?
It's hard.
It's incredibly hard.
You need some wood?
Once there was a boy down south
Always had snot running across his mouth
What's that mess boy the neighbors would say?
Why is that snot on your face that way?
Snot, not riddle, snot, not riddle
Snot, not riddle, snot, not riddle all day
Mama sent him to the grocery store
Asked him to buy three eggs times four
Run back home for the grocery man say
Why is that snot on your face that way?
Snot, not riddle, snot, not riddle
Snot, not riddle, snot, not riddle all day
Soon this boy became a man
What did you know?
The master plan
So to the Lord he did say
Hey God, why is this snot on my face this way?
Huh?
Hey God, God why, why do I have this snot all over my face like this God?
Hey, hey God, why is this snot on my face like this God?
Snot, not riddle, snot, not riddle all day
Snot, not riddle all day
I love her and the Ink, she takes the kids down here before they put them in the snot mart
I hear those trains running day and night, day and night
I hear their anguished cries as they went by
Never did much don't but waves
Those were the days
Sometimes we see their little fingers
Stick, stick, stick, stick
I see their little fingers sticking out of the box
Car bar blue
It's so painful just to think about, isn't it?
Oh, not for me.
I enjoyed sometimes if little toes and fingers would fall off,
I'd come back and collect them, make soup for the family,
and everybody enjoyed it.
That's just disgusting.
And it's, you know, life is for the moment.
And it was a beautiful moment.
I guess you could think of it as sort of recycling.
The red sky, the Zyklon B in the air,
and the trains going by,
and the exciting sounds of the clicky-clack.
Sometimes they all have, all the cars would be from Korea,
and China, and Japan.
And sometimes there'd be a man with it,
like he looked like a little cartoon figure
and a big old W on his head.
I guess he was selling the hamburgers.
They didn't eat too much after the first love fest, though.
Most of the hairs, well, they were pretty well depilated.
And, of course, the mind just can't watch the watering down.
Yes.
It can't.
It can't hold it.
Yes.
It's like a sieve.
Steel sieve.
As we see from these four appropriate messages being beamed in,
it appears that we are actually literally making some sort of contact.
And I would expect the president of these here United Snakes
is going to be standing firmly out on that White House lawn.
And he's not going to be sputin' dog pootie.
No, he's going to be talking to whoever this group is,
these aliens.
These aliens.
These people with a third nostril.
These strange beings who...
Wait a minute.
I think I need to...
I...
Listen.
Time.
We need guns.
Manumission.
We need hair.
We need...
Hello.
Abu Ghraib Detention Facility.
How may I help you?
Hello, this is Amir Samir.
Amir.
I seem to have lost my children
during the last curfew roundup.
Could you tell me where they might be?
Hold on for a minute.
Your call is important to us.
Please stay on the line
until a directory assistance operator can help you.
All service operators are currently busy.
Your call is important to us.
Thank you.
Our book of red is bound to be your bread.
Better get inside before curfew.
Better not demonstrate.
Better not try to procreate.
Better get inside before curfew.
Our book of red is bound to be your resting place.
Our book of red is bound to be your final grave.
Better get inside before curfew.
Our book of red is bound to make you change your ways.
Our book of red is bound to be your final grave.
Its got tape gonna be your final grave.
Better get inside before curfew.
Better not chain your neck.
Better not do the best old hair.
Our book of red is going to be your final resting place.
Your final resting place.
The Band bulbars are on…
Two…
Four…
Five….
six…
Seven…
And Bush laughs and laughs and laughs because somebody voted for Nader.
You know, I guess some people thought, I know, I'll vote my conscience this time instead of the lesser of two evils.
Better stick with that lesser of two evils next time, friends.
Well, that was Lonesome Cowboy Dave at the Beachland Ballroom at some subgenius revival at some point in the past.
I don't know which one. I can't remember.
And before that, Rudy Schwartz Project, the great Rudy Schwartz Project, doing snot mouth tweedle, a thinly veiled allegory of current events.
Now, staying on.
I hate to interrupt you right there.
I was going to ask you the interviewer type question, but go ahead.
Oh, no, no, no.
I was going to ask.
No, you go ahead.
No, that's all right.
I'll go ahead.
All right, then.
Stan, what do you think of the thing in the back of the president's neck?
The thing hanging between his scapula and his vertebrae?
Well, you know as well as I do, that's what they used to control him.
I mean, that's the receiver.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, the receiver, the actual, one of the tentacles itself, perhaps, even, right?
Or does he get...
Is he the puppet one, or is he still one of the Bohemian Club hillbillies?
Well, you know, I've always...
You know, at this point, I have, to tell the truth, haven't been paying that close of attention.
At this point, what does it matter?
He could be one of the puppets.
He could be one of the clones.
He could be the real George Bush, somehow transformed, like in that stupid Stepford Wives movie.
The Stepford Presidents.
Well, he could really be one of the puppet presidents, not only as a puppet of the, you know, whoever controllers,
but that thing in the back.
It might be like, you know, Team America.
They might have...
Trey Parker and those guys might have, you know, I mean, they might have actually sussed on to something,
as they used to say in Popeye Island.
You know, they might have smoked something out, and it didn't feel good.
Well, now, how many puppets down the line are you talking about here?
Well, I'm talking about that apparatus on the back of his whacker that makes him talk quicker and makes him lick faster.
Right, and you better hope the right guy has the remote control.
That's right.
That's, you know, just like they blew up the world.
They built Tate Centers with a remote control, one of those little games.
Yeah, they used a Sega, I think.
Yeah, a Sega.
Just, that's how he went through the debates, as remote as you can be.
They said he had a remote look in his eyes.
Well, you know, speaking of remote, Princess Wee and I are going to be leaving the country shortly after the erection,
and do you think we'll be back?
I don't know.
Depending if the encumbrance is still encumbrating us.
Uh-oh, that's all I can think.
Yeah.
Whatever happens this election, the nutty squirrels have it right.
You might be voting for Feisthelmer von Wuchenschmapp, the schnick-schlapper for dog capture.
That's right.
Capturer.
When I was a little kid, they said in Russia, they don't give you any choice of who to vote for.
It's just, you know, you just get one vote, and it's just for this one guy.
And then we have one TV station.
Comrade X.
Yeah.
And it's all government stuff, talking about how evil us Americans are, and how great the party is.
And somewhere in between, there's that book and movie and comic book called 1984,
which is a little bit out of date by about 20 years, kind of dated.
But, you know, you put it all together, and you go...
You know, dude...
Well, who do you think, Dave?
It's true.
Dave, who do you think is going to win, Predator or Alien?
Or will we all lose?
I think we'll all lose to the Predators and Aliens running this cavuncular hospice we call UXA.
It's a gone deal, man.
You know what I mean?
What I'm saying, they've already pre-registered...
I forgot what I was talking about.
Oh, yeah.
All those implants.
Yeah, right.
That's what happens.
When you start talking...
About the subject...
What were we talking about?
See, friends, it's not...
It's not conspiracy.
It's actually difficult to brainwash somebody into talking about something,
but it's very easy to brainwash them into not talking about something.
Allow the flow to go.
It may come out in strange rivulets of otherworldly spokeages.
Some people even have taken the stuff down, all the way down,
and...
And it still comes out pretty much legitimate business for the rest of them.
That's BAU, of course, which stands for BAU.
Well, luckily, we in Ohio don't have to worry because some Ohioan guy makes the voting machines,
and he's a good friend of George Bush's.
Yes, and Taft.
And has said that he wants to help put the emperor back...
You know, keep the imp in place.
The imp.
The imp perverse, I would say.
He reminds me of the imp perverse, and I've noticed...
You know, the colloquial little drawings that have been done by each little neighborhood in the world
that show his ears sprouting into a kind of demonic thing,
and his forehead going backward into kind of like a bowling pin shape,
and he looks like Alien.
The Alien, you know?
Have you known...
Oh, I'm sorry.
She's dangerously...
I thought those were supposed to be you.
The big...
No, the big...
I thought those pictures in Mad Magazine were supposed to be you.
Those funny-looking guys acting stupid.
No, they're being...
I thought they were supposed to be you.
The big signals tonight.
Oh.
When the waves are dense, there's no...
I bet the waves are going to be so dense on historical erection day
that nobody will be able to maintain the encumbrance
unless they're wearing the wrong, you know...
Well...
Nobody will be able to maintain, period, okay?
Yeah.
Well, that's...
Yeah, that's exactly it.
I mean, you just won't be able to maintain.
No.
All right?
I think a lot of people are going to be flipping nervous
and going, yeah, yeah, right out there in front of the booths.
Do you?
I don't know.
I've seen this happen so many times before.
And everybody...
The monkeys get all upset.
I know.
They get riled up.
They rattle their cage.
Throw the food back at the keepers.
They fling their poo around.
Yeah.
And then, in the end, they're still behind bars
and everybody's still laughing at them,
going, look at those silly monkeys.
Yeah, and then they burn the Reichstag again
and then the monkeys are laughing again.
Yeah.
Hey, what happened to the October surprise?
Well, I was pretty surprised.
I was surprised that a month actually happened
and we didn't all die.
I mean, so far.
Well, no, they promised us we're going to die
every couple of days.
You're going to die tomorrow.
Yeah, you're going to die because the evildoers...
Be careful of Tuesday.
Tuesday is your walking dead day.
But one of these days, it's going to be...
It's going to happen, you know.
Well, yeah, well...
It's going to happen.
You know, Bob said it's going to be a bummer.
But will we be zombies then going to the booths?
In the same old way that we have...
His prediction came true.
It is a bummer.
I'll be a good zombie going to the booth.
My daughter called me up to make sure I was.
She said, Dad, you're not so radical
that you don't even vote, are you?
And I was like, well, yeah, I am,
but I'm going to vote anyway.
Yeah.
Just in case, you know, just because.
I don't know, just so I can get off work.
So do you have to go to a voting booth to get it off?
I do, yeah.
Can you go to a phone booth and just start screaming
and pounding on the windows?
No, this year they've made sure that you have to
dot all your I's and T's and punch your chads and everything
or they won't...
Especially if you have that one vote.
And they'll throw that one out.
Especially in a swing state full of swingers like Ohio.
Oh, yeah.
And Ohio is full of some of the ugliest swingers.
I drive by those trailer courts off the highway
and look and go, that's where that picture I saw
on the internet was taken.
Why?
Because the people in that trailer,
they're the ones I saw in the orgy shot on the internet.
Those are the ones that you...
They're the ones that are going to go and vote on Tuesday
or stay in their trailer.
Sometimes you think, man, maybe they shouldn't vote.
Maybe democracy was the worst idea that ever happened.
Maybe the king was right.
That last king was right.
You cannot trust the people because look what they do.
But that was supposed to be built into the Constitution,
you know, that magical...
That was supposed to be a document
that had some modicum of the people's will.
Because let's face it,
you can't really let the people call the shots.
I mean, if you voted by, you know, your television,
say every idiot,
okay, today we're all going to vote.
Should we go to war with Russia?
Everyone who wants to vote yes.
If they're playing the right theme music,
everybody's going to vote yes.
Do you really want to leave it up
to the people?
the Americans, the people
who elected this guy in the first place?
Do you want to leave anything up
to them for now? Or do you think
perhaps a dictatorship under
a kind and benevolent
benign dictator
like J.R. Bob Dobbs
an illuminated one.
But this is not the year
to write in J.R. Bob Dobbs
as world over.
Those of you who are dumb enough to listen, please do not be
dumb enough to write in Bob J.R. Bob Dobbs
for president.
I did that last time and look what
happened. Hey, don't blame me.
I voted for Bob.
Go ahead and blame me.
It's my fault.
No matter who wins or loses
it's always going to ultimately be
the conspiracy's fault.
And Dobbs is
always going to be the
what?
It's always the conspiracy's fault and it wasn't
really Bob's fault.
Or if it was Bob's fault
it was really
Conor's fault.
It was Connie's fault.
Because you know you don't really directly blame
the world overlord.
You always blame his wife or his underlings.
Yeah, you blame the first lady
and she's not involved in nearly enough projects
to be a suitable first lady of our land.
You know, let alone of any large
or small church.
Princess, we and I were discussing the difference
between the Democrats and the Republicans
and the way they deal with their
used up women
after these politicians.
Like in a Democratic White House
your biggest problem is going to be
blue dresses
and sweaters clogging up
the toilets, you know, as people
have tried to flush them away.
Whereas under a Republican administration
they just kill the hookers.
And so you've got, in their case, the entirety
of Chesapeake Bay backing up
with dead presidential
hookers that they've used
and wisely cast away
and made sure they weren't going to go telling
their little buddy somewhere
about, oh look, I got collected some sperm.
off the president.
Let's make a little waterhead president
clone baby.
Let's make a little lonesome
cowboy George.
President, lonesome cowboy George.
The monkey animal president.
Oh, been there, done that.
You know, if you're out of the beltway,
a lot of these...
Let's get another rich person.
Yeah, we need another rich person.
My dad, I caught my own dad going,
well at least Bush is a Texan.
He's a rich Connecticut Yankee
acting,
like a stupid Texan,
so stupid Texans won't vote for him.
At least he's a German.
You know, he could be, you know,
Swiss or Slovenian,
but thank God the Fuhrer is a German.
I will vote for him.
My family comes from
Bavaria.
And I...
You know, ironically enough, my family
actually does come from Texas
and Connecticut.
And Mexico.
Mexico.
Well, it was Mexico and then they called it Texas.
And then they called it Mexico.
Didn't you say your old Uncle Pappy
Rubric Cube or whatever?
He was a wetback.
He swam across a river,
but it was the English channel.
What have we got coming up next?
Oh, let's have some music.
How about that band,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
I suppose this isn't music.
You know, what are you...
I'm digging this music that's going on right now.
We better soak up the slack volume.
You can't, kids.
It's full of things you can't control.
It's going to all be taken away.
Of course it is my childhood.
Favorite music.
It's the Nutty Squirrels.
I'd like to see Laura Bush
scat along with the Nutty Squirrels.
Live. I'd like to see these guys live.
Maybe at Democracy Plaza, you know,
ice skating at Christmas time after they've won the election
and Iraq ceases to be even a place.
You know, geographical area.
That isn't...
It'll all be like a big shopping mall someday.
I hope so.
Where can you find finer things
than an Iraqi shopping mall
that goes all the way from the Arabian Sea
all the way up to the coast of Turkey
and then narrow borderline
that guards it from the rest of the world?
I think you could find it in any of the shopping malls,
like the one that goes from North Dallas to South Austin
or the shopping mall that goes from South Washington
to Northern Boston.
Any of those big malls.
Well, do you think anybody will ever notice
the spasm, you know, these weird spasms
in the face that Bush makes at different times?
Do you think anybody's ever going to say anything about it?
Well, you know, now, to be fair,
like where you take your pig,
I was cutting that Bush stuff up
and I thought...
I've had people cut up my speech patterns.
To be careful where you take your pig?
And...
I'm trying to...
I learned it from you, Dave!
Anyway, um...
We, uh...
What the hell was I talking about?
Let's just play that song.
You were taking your pig out for a dance.
Yeah, now, see, I can't even...
I tried to...
Pizza flag!
I was trying to be...
I learned it from you, Dave.
A pizza and a soda.
I'd like to salute the flag
to which we all swear a republic
to the United States of America.
The flag known as...
O'Gory.
Well, I'm proud to salute
And the colors for which she stands.
She stands.
Red for the blood.
Pow! Pow! Pow!
White for the guts.
Blue for the blue-bodied bag.
Zip!
And I'm proud to tell the story
The story
of the United States of oil.
Chug, chug.
They come and take
The brains gone about
Chug, chug.
Learning and living the story.
The story of oil.
Well, I'm proud to salute
O'Gory.
And the colors for which she stands.
The red for the blood.
White for the guts.
Blue for the blue-bodied bag.
And I'm proud to tell the story
The story.
Of freedom and financial gain.
Chug, chug.
Free to carol.
Free to back tail.
To the chain.
Free to haliburte.
Haliburte.
Hey, hey, hey.
Well, Mama, I'm coming back to Air Force, Andrews Air Force Base, dressed in a brand-new white suit.
They've done some work on me, but I think I'm going to be all right.
The planes keep coming in, coming in every day.
Well, Mama, I ain't got no arms or legs.
I just got stumps.
But that's good, because I got a new job at the polling alley.
I'm going to work there every day.
I'm going to sell off my car and sell off the house and the bar.
So I'm proud to salute old Dory.
Old Dory.
And the colors for which she sang.
She sang.
Red for the blood.
White for the guts.
Blue for the blue body.
Bye.
Yep.
And I'm proud to tell the story.
The story.
Of freedom and financial gain.
To the chain.
Free to head.
Free to car line.
To the chain.
Free to Halliburton.
Halliburton.
Hey, hey, hey.
Well, Mama, there's a few things I forgot to tell you.
I got part of my head blown off.
But that don't matter with the kind of job skills I got anyway.
I'm missing a few digits.
Oh.
I'm missing big chunks of my skull.
Oh, what the hell.
Oh.
No, no that's over.
Oh, we caught personalities in baby, you know.
Yeah, we obviouslyording.
I'm just going to let you guys do that the whole time.
Boy, that guy's like Bob Dylan.
He's a regular Bob Dylan of...
I should have just let you guys sing this over all that stuff.
It would have sounded a lot better.
I would have liked to sing it like this, but I just don't have the time.
I have the earwax, I have the eye color.
I have the nostril, but I don't have the time.
And the time...
He's doing the harmonica.
The answer, my friend, is blowing out your arse.
The answer is blowing out your arse.
We cannot have a president, commander-in-chief, who blows in the winds.
He must be steadfast in his steadfastness.
And never change his...
His minds.
Even though he may be of more than one mind.
His minds must all be focused.
He must... I'm sorry.
Let us all pray...
You were right about those consonants.
He will have to just work on his carry...
Character.
Impression.
Yes.
Well, I...
I have it once in a while, but I don't have it now.
It comes in flickers.
I do have AdWords.
And believe me, this...
Oh, no, that's gore.
Okay.
For good fun.
I don't...
I...
How do you tell them apart?
I'm a selfish rich guy.
You know, any young fellow or girl can grow up to be president in this country.
Any abused, young, misogynistic young child can have their foreskin and their pecker driven any way they want.
And they can grow up or grow down to be the president of this great American country that...
Oh.
Well, Bill Clinton actually was some kind of a po-bucker that became president.
Yeah.
He was...
That doesn't usually happen, though.
Usually, they're the sons of mafia leaders and big businessmen.
Yes, the great white clans of Norway, yes.
Husbands of incredibly rich, powerful monsters.
Sometimes...
Disguised as people, like on Halloween.
Right.
Sometimes, they're those guys with the big long nose tubes from Papua New Guinea, and they sneak them in there.
You know, they bleach their skin a little bit.
Make them a mason, you know, or something like that.
And then the next thing you know, they're taking the strips out of their hair.
Yeah, and then before you know it, they're pulling off almost all of their skin because they can't...
Their skin just doesn't work anymore because of GSR, the galvanic skin response.
You know, start buzzing, man.
And then the next thing you know, they're standing in front of the Republican National Committee.
And they're standing there, thousands of people are cheering.
And they...
Well, Dr. Trump, is it true that Dr. Howell, your comrade there at the show, is going to join being a Republican?
Well, we're approaching the tail end.
My eyes are bleeding.
The very butt of the show, as I said.
It's a devilish tail, isn't it?
Yes.
Forked like Popeye's nose.
My eyes are bleeding.
My eyes!
Strange happens too.
Let's just allow ourselves to be as free as we can be.
And don't forget this November 2nd.
To get out there and vote with your feet.
The way God intended you to.
Run!
Run for the nearest border!
And next week there will be a radiothon.
Yes, as if we could use one.
Yes, the station will be...
So, I'm just warning you ahead of time.
If you have any money, spend it now before then.
You know, things might be very different a month or two from now.
There might not be any money one month from now.
We don't know.
There might not be any money.
There might not be any people.
Or there might not be any...
The winner could abolish money.
Maybe the change will be that change will finally stop happening.
Right.
The changelings then will be the happening.
That, my dear, is impossible.
Well, that's the...
Change can never stop.
It could be that...
It's the only constant.
It could be a dream come true, though.
Small change.
A complete perfect piece of stasis.
Ah.
I...
Where sleep is awareness.
And love is...
Hey.
A death.
Number one is really number two.
And number two is really number one.
Well, friends, all we can do is ask you to do the responsible thing.
But, unfortunately, you're subgeniuses.
So, it doesn't do much good to even suggest such a thing.
And, uh...
But, uh, whatever you do, don't name it after Bob.
Friends, uh...
Whatever you do...
Love yourself.
Yeah.
You sure have killers out there.
You hear it now?
You listen to Princess Wee.
Don't feel bad about yourself, man.
Don't beat yourself up.
Feel bad about others.
You've got other people to beat up.
Goodbye, the powers.
Goodbye, the powers that trusted me.
I say, if I solemnly swear you are president...
Of the United States of America.
Um...
I have promised...
Many things.
I have delivered few...
Empty promises.
Some of them were big empty promises.
As big as that football field there.
There are no empty promises, only empty heads.
And some were empty premises that had actual heads.
Where are we?
Um, I think we've just, uh, passed Langley.
And we're heading for the Maryland border.
And now we're gonna have to take a little quick loop over here to get back.
If you want to get close to the White House lawn.
Gonna make the digit repair, the, uh, funnel entry.
I guess they're calling it now.
Uh, there's no, uh...
Are you, are you picking up anything on your, uh...
Are you picking up anything?
Bogey, six o'clock.
It's six o'clock already?
Christ, I was supposed to have eaten by now.
Are we gonna get some food before we get back?
Or are we just gonna...
Mmm, I understand that...
There is food aplenty on the ground a few thousand feet below us.
There are people.
There are houses.
There are little cows.
There are roses.
Flowers.
Tomatoes.
Fresh proteins and greens from the sea.
Produce from the islands of Langahans.
Uh, now there's more than one, anyway.
And large, large vessels of oats.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, why, I don't...
Ladies and gentlemen, this has been the Hour of Slack.
Thank you for listening.
And, uh, that terrible background music there was by yours truly.
Friends, this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, number 967.
Check out www.com.
Subgenius.com for all information.
Or, uh, write to Hour of Slack, Reverend Ivan Stank.
Church of the Subgenius, Subgenius Foundation at P.O. Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.