Now you've turned your record over, and you're all ready for some more sing-time sing-along songs.
Bob?
You could actually save people from death.
The dark side of the Force is a pathway to many abilities some consider to be unnatural.
You killed a fly with a fly head.
She killed a human with a human head.
If she murdered, so did you.
I know.
But I was deranged.
Yes, yes.
It could have been the subgenius power of the Force.
I know there are things about the Force that they're not telling me.
Let me help you to know the subtleties of the Force.
Even the nature of the dark side.
If one is to understand the great mystery, one must study all its aspects, not just the dogmatic, narrow view of the Jedi.
If you wish to become a complete and wise leader, you must embrace a larger view of the Force.
I'm thinking of my back.
It's either too tight or it's too slack.
That's all it is.
How much?
Ah, yes, dear friends.
That was Keith Richards with that song, 999.
A little clip of it anyway.
Because, friends, this is Hour of Slack number 9.
999.
And it's a salute to Bob show.
Because 999 is in fact the number of Bob.
Because Bob isn't the Antichrist.
Bob is the anti-Antichrist.
He's not the Christ.
He's just the one that messes up the Antichrist.
Not because he's a good guy.
Just because he's Bob.
And, friends, there's so much more to this.
Magic.
In this number of Bob 999.
Did you know that 2 times 999 equals 1998?
The date the world ends?
Uh, uh, two weeks from this recording time, in fact.
Did you know that 3 times 666 equals 1998?
But that 6 times 333 also equals 1998.
And 333 is the number of the...
anti-Bob.
So happy
X-Day, friends.
And so now let's let
Norrell Preff
take us now into
the Bob Hour.
Join us now for
the Bob Hour coming to you from the campus
of Bob. Our speaker today is Bob.
The title of his message is
According to the Flesh.
There is much potential in this room.
I am stark naked.
Naked according to the flesh.
We are equipped.
We have what we need, young person.
Think about that grace that saw you
as a spiritual corpse and blew you.
When you want to be full-time,
submission is expected.
The scope
is expansive.
It is going everywhere.
The blood and the
gore that we find ourselves in.
The sin, the stain of iniquity.
A mood or an attitude
of negativism.
I shared a story yesterday with Bob
about his father.
He came up to me and he had this wild-eyed
look in his face and he said,
Bob, we'll do a mental exercise.
Live in the context of history.
History of blood
and gore and violence and sin
dealt the
existence of
human history.
I'm going higher someday.
What are you going to do about it?
Bob had a large and wonderful head.
I did whatever he needed me to do.
I gulped and stopped breathing.
I was pregnant.
Because all of our worthless
financial resources.
I studied the essence of Bob,
which, by the way, is the official name of our Savior,
according to the flesh.
You've been listening to the Bob Hour,
coming to you from the campus of Bob.
Send a check, send a check, send a check, check, check, check, check.
Sponsored by Bob.
What's going to happen to your children?
What's going to happen to your children
when this society we've created,
this society we've created,
air-conditioned,
station wagons with wooden sides,
cautious indeed,
a retired actor,
indeed,
orange hail,
What happens when that collapses?
What happens when your diary was a damn well?
That's when the man from Planet X-9,
I'm down to save the members of the subgenius jerk.
But until that day,
the power and wisdom of Bob
can help us break their mind control
by activating that mutant gland that we all have within us.
Hey!
What's going on here?
Along with Bob,
the pursuit of slack,
and a conspiracy of pinks,
the subgenius theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
According to church doctrine,
on July 5th, 1998,
when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth.
They're going to...
They will put us...
They will put us out of our misery
unless Bob can explain to them in ways that they can understand
that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii,
the dues-paying, book-buying,
receipt-in-the-pocket,
paid in full to the church subgenii,
have the tiniest prayer of survival.
The rest of them?
It's a tough world, Jack.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one!
Yeah!
We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin.
They destroyed the world.
So, what's going on?
Already, hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain.
And civil defense authorities state that the situation is much the same across the entire country.
Martial law is now nationwide.
Our fellow countrymen are dying.
The very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble under the dread assault of that horror long feared.
Bob?
Colorado channel.
This is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Stay in your homes!
Oh, my God!
I got exactly what I wanted!
Ha ha ha ha!
Woo!
How long you been on Borg Bongo, John?
I mean, Jane.
About 15 minutes now.
Oh, James, I thought it was 15 years.
I've been on for 15,000 years.
Well, there's no real time, is there?
No, it's whatever time you want to stay or have or be on.
Oh, my God, it just never ends.
It's like a loop.
It's time to go.
I've been to theuest place in my life.
My name's James Van praise as probably the most old lutce said in the damn tv show isn't
There's nothing like the face of Bob.
about.
I'm.
There's nothing like it you'll ever see.
A face as happy as it can be.
There's nothing like the face of a...
Bob.
The great American...
If this was indeed an extraterrestrial spacecraft with living occupants,
it must have been very disconcerting for them to cross millions of miles of space
only to be hit on the head with rotten oranges.
The dramatic advent of such fascinating objects
as those which were first called flying saucers
attracted the inevitable attention of those individuals
who let their imaginations run away with their veracity.
By 1950, some of these characters were beginning to spin their stories
of fantastic conversations with alleged space people.
Some of them expanded the stories to include alleged rides in the UFOs.
Suddenly everything went black.
And I...
I realized that I'd been cut off and shut off in a little tiny room
where nobody was listening to me.
And I was talking to this hot little plush felt red rubber tip microphone
and not hearing a thing and seeing only little tiny lights
and wondering why I was strapped to this chair
and put into the studio that seemed to be rotating very rapidly
with lights flashing off rhythmically.
And it was a small man with a swollen head and hideously deformed eyes
sitting behind the console pushing the buttons
while pencils of light and energy flashed across my body.
And I wondered why I was there and what did they want of me.
And I couldn't figure out why I was sitting there.
And they didn't say anything.
They just kept flashing those lights at me
and pumping those strange chemicals into me.
And the man with the funny head, the leader,
the man with the strange grin and the pipe...
Well, I just want to know, do you want to be in the church or out of the church?
And where's your wallet?
The DC9 pushing the buttons.
Yeah.
I didn't know that I'd been snatched up,
but it wasn't really a dream until I saw these...
sacred nasal positions.
And suddenly it all came back to me.
And I realized that they'd stolen four and a half hours out of my life
when they put me in that tiny room and plugged all those wires into me
and made me talk and talk and talk and talk.
Well, it's only an hour and a half tonight, mister.
And talk because you only paid for an hour and a half.
Is it possible to learn this power?
Not from a Jedi.
It's a dream.
Bob's only got getting back home on his mind now.
Hi, Bob!
Right, Bob?
Bob?
I came as a visitor, not an invader.
I must get back to my ship, see if I can repair it.
And then I must leave.
No, wait.
What harm is there in hearing them out?
Other than being a salesman, what does Bob do for a living?
Other than being a salesman?
Bob is not on Route 80 with a bag full of brushes on his head.
Who has met Bob?
He seemed extremely paranoid. He believed in conspiracies.
He came on like a Nazi. I was afraid of him.
Your tricks don't frighten us, neither do you.
We've come a long way in 5,000 years.
But you're still of the same nature.
I could sweep you out of existence with a wave of my hand,
and bring you back again.
I can give life or death.
What else does mankind demand of its gods?
Mankind has no need for gods.
We find the one quite adequate.
We shall not debate, mortal.
No, we shall not.
For there is but one Bob, and he is Dobbs.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Friends, we've been hearing testimonials from as recently and as nearby
as Reverend Shane Smirker in Australica,
to as old and near as Dr. G. Gordon Gordon discussing his ride in the UFO
from the old, old subgenius media barrage albums of the 80s.
Friends, we heard some great preaching from Pope David and Meyer.
We heard that great background music by the Amino Acids, which continues.
We heard bits of previous X-Day Live recordings.
But now,
let's break for music.
I mean, besides this background Amino Acids music.
We'll be hearing from Norrell Preff,
and some Reverend Ed Fred,
and even Dr. Howell.
And we always hear from LeMur constantly.
But first, here is Saint Anne.
Brains on!
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get it?
The feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Give me slack or give me food or kill me.
Kill me.
And gentle friends,
let's kill him boldly, but not wrathfully.
Let's carve him as a dish fit for the gods.
Bob?
Oh, if you get it like this,
the best pair of tits,
a f***ing kiss all night.
How much?
Nine times.
Well, give it to me.
I'll make it later.
Nine times.
Got to plug and calculate.
That don't make sense.
Nine times.
Here comes the dice.
Die, die.
Yeah.
Paris Hogan.
Deep Throat.
Bob Nau.
Word, word, word.
Madonna.
Deep, Deep Throat.
Bob Nau.
Deep Throat was a criminal.
Superstar.
The 91-year-old.
Drug-idic.
Elton John will perform.
Deep Throat.
Seemingly forever.
Bob.
That was in the, in the, uh, airport.
In the hall of the pressure at the airport.
Airport in Arizona.
And what the?
Where we just went boo.
Where we just bumped up to first class simply because we were sub-gum demons.
They said, you know, Bob, man, you need to be in first class.
Here, take this wine.
Take these gifts.
Take this seat that folds all the way back.
And sleep.
Sleep, sleep.
The sleep of the dead.
Drug-induced.
Pulled on a trailer by pilot Chicken John.
They followed the marchers.
Sleep of the dead.
One day before the death of the recent pontiff.
Put on this flyer.
Jacket.
The first of April, two thousand.
Put on this, this periscope.
And so it was.
I mean the parachute, not the periscope, you idiot.
By crucifixion and taking on.
Okay, now get ready to jump.
We're gonna be, we're over the area where you will be required to.
Taking on sin in the person's tomb.
Bring back the special tools that we'll need.
And putting it off on the cross.
But on the cross.
All pity the piteous and was rough with the rough ones.
Bless the Lord.
Bless you.
Wow, what's that?
Alien beings.
Bless you.
The blessings of the gods of Greece.
Look at that face.
By the gods.
Bless you.
May Zeus bless you.
I do not bow down to gods and demons, to nameless gods.
The son of her.
Zeus the father.
Deus pater.
Pater omniscer.
You're put on the bulletproof vest.
We'll need it.
We have to automatically attack the other shows.
We got a show on before.
I'm, I'm doing the clean up here.
We left Gods all over the place here!
Chase the one that's burning in here.
There's another one, get him!
They're taking the security officer's handbook.
You're gonna need it!
That God's coming for ya, he moves!
Blow out the dark pepper spray!
Little Gods, and big Gods, and movie Gods, and book Gods...
Take the attempinator!
Stop gun!
He's...
The wizard stops time.
There's a little god crawling along the floor here, begging for mercy.
Here, take the survival armory key.
You'll have to get in there after we...
But he could be right outside your door.
Oh, I'd welcome him in.
Bob could be lurking outside your home.
Even now.
Bob could be getting closer and closer.
My God.
Suddenly you begin to feel it.
His divine subgenial radiance.
Piercing through the walls like radiation.
Piercing through my wall.
Piercing flesh and bone.
Irradiating.
I can feel the slack emanating off him right now.
Slack so powerful that it renders objects in the material world entirely permeable.
Until they boil over with an atomic crust of free neutrinos.
And cheesy.
Chocolate stuffing.
Here is the glowing blue purplish effect of Chilenkov's radiation.
Bob melts his way through the door.
You're trapped.
You can't get out the back.
Subgenius protoplasm has frozen the lock.
Ah, that's okay.
I got a trap door up to the attic.
He can't get me.
You've only got seconds before the Bob thing melts its way through the door.
The fire department is on its way, but they can't help.
It's okay.
We only get the flap.
I get the stuff in his pipe.
Ha ha ha ha.
As far as they're concerned, Bob's just another drug.
Just like heroin or codeine or marijuana.
And, um, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
You don't come down from Bob.
You aren't being, when you do a hit of Bob, you ain't gonna come down from it.
You're not gonna wake up the next morning going, oh, I feel horrible.
I better have some more Bob.
No.
I feel terrible.
I've had enough Bob.
I can't have any more Bob.
Bob's giving me too much slack.
Ha ha ha ha.
Too much slack.
Well, one of Bob's pithy phrases was, too much is always better than not enough.
Ha ha ha ha.
And like so many religious slogans, it really sounds good, doesn't it?
Think how many alcohol overdoses in college students can be blamed on Bob.
Oh, Bob said too much is always better than not enough.
Phew.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ugh.
There's a second part of that.
There's a slogan, but it's too much of a bring down, and we lopped it off the end.
The second part was, but it's almost as bad.
Ha ha ha.
And that's just like, too much is always better than not enough, but it's almost as bad.
That just doesn't do it for you, does it?
Ha ha ha.
No.
There's more like what mom would say.
Well, I found out after years and years and years that mom was right.
Three squares and enough sleep will get you higher than anything.
And, uh, I wish my mom had taken her own advice.
Ha ha ha.
Three.
Far away.
It's real big around the college.
It appears to be rapidly increasing.
What happened?
I don't know if I can get through 11, possibly.
Here, let me help you.
Ha ha ha.
Oh, goodness.
Do I have to start over now?
Yes, you do.
Ha ha ha.
Man, that steel sink really echoes that.
And with that said.
Oh.
The smell, I know.
Good lord.
I got to get to the bathroom.
Oh, that's not good.
All over my shirt.
Oh.
Yes, it is.
My new shirt.
Silly.
Gosh.
And I just put on my new shirt this morning.
Now, channel three doesn't work because it's all clogged up.
Oh, no.
No, it doesn't.
I was blowing beads, man.
Glove beads.
Barfing chunks.
It's not necessary to write this down, is it?
I hope you've been writing it down because there'll be a quiz at the end of the show.
Well, I'm sure it'll happen again.
The other DJ will ask you a subterranean question.
It'll be a quiz.
It'll be a really spooky quiz.
It's going to be the image that you don't want to see on TV.
I don't know if I want to use my mind.
Your mind is not your mind.
Your mind is my mind.
My mind is not mine.
My mind.
Its pain is really a liquid crystal display.
Forty years and we're still getting it right.
The Puzzling Evidence Show, the way the truth was meant to be heard.
Well, there's two reasons for that.
One is a secret and the other is a lie.
One.
Secret.
B.
A lie.
Big.
C.
A lie.
B.
The lie.
I can't.
My mind gets killed.
It's so confusing.
A.
Hi.
Hello.
Choice Q3.
Surveillance is a mythanthropic design flaw.
Choice Q4 and down come the pants.
See?
Move.
Stranger.
I think he's stupid.
That's why Clorox has a line of disinfecting products to get rid of kids.
Their lives are hell.
Hey little brothers and sisters.
Why don't you get around?
I've got something important to say to you.
Something I think you need to hear.
Come on now.
Are you sure you got your life together?
You think you're on top of the world.
But reality is about to rear its ugly head, my friends.
Are you ready to face the music?
You're big!
We think!
You drive that big old SUV.
Draining your wallet into used to be.
You're in a material race you just can't win.
Following society is your greatest sin.
You are destined to fail, my friend.
You're gonna be poor and alone in the end.
You got your treasures, you got your hoard.
But you're only gonna end up broken board.
Come on, friends.
It's time to turn over a new leaf.
Unleash your weakness and get some relief.
Slack is king and nothing else matters.
Don't be pink!
Pull yourself up by your latex undergarments.
Toss away all your commercial influences.
The slack within you can be born again.
Act now.
This is limited time awful.
Get yours now, while supplies last.
Awful Void in Alaska and Hawaii.
Be sure to consult your doctor about any risk.
that might be associated with slack.
Yeah, I hope you learned something today.
Now I'm going to get myself some slack.
That was Ed Fred, friends.
We also heard from Lemur,
Philo, Hal, and Puzzling,
and some of yours truly, Reverend Stang at Winterstar.
Incidentally, I'll be preaching at the 25th Anniversary Starwood
in late July.
See subgenius.com for details.
We'll do that on the escape vessels if we have to.
We're going to let Radio Synesthesia do the live parts of the show,
this show, number 999.
The line is a mammoth heart in a little place
You won't get it till it's in your face
Oh, get me out
Out of deeper red
Don't panic
I swear I want to be
Yeah
A useful member of society
I just need
A little of that old money
Yeah
Come on, come on
Oh, here we go
Yeah
Mob?
Well, frankly, I don't think that anybody should feel guilty about what their ancestors did.
You know, we don't regret the past.
We learn from it.
I'm just trying to get out of the fact that when Mom and Dad were the only ones who didn't get hurt,
They came back from Jonestown, and they had the guy on a passport.
You know, the only...
You should fart beyond that, you know.
The only regret about the acts of my ancestors that I have
is the fact that they ever conceived me in the first place.
Right, the third act, the denouement, where you come down.
You know, that's the part that gets us all.
Mom and Dad, well, they were stupid.
Grandpa and Grandma were stupider.
And then somewhere back there, there was like a person
with their brain hanging out of their head.
I hope my kids aren't thinking that very same thing right now.
They probably are, Stank.
They don't want to copulate because it'll look like you.
I've been trying to encourage my son and daughter-in-law to have a kid.
So it'll look like you.
They're the same age I was when I had a kid,
and the age my dad was when he had me,
which was a pretty freakish accident, but let's not go into that.
Well, the party feels better for each family only having one child.
What's wrong with aborting that baby?
Eating it.
If you're hungry.
You know, it's a good late-night snack.
Oh, it's a modest proposal.
It is definitely a source of many, many, many essential vitamins and minerals and whatnot.
You could put like a little bit of baby muscle on a trisket.
Oh, yeah, you know, I mean, it's also the most perfect balanced protein you can get,
you know, baby or fetus.
I just say no to kids.
How about this?
How about endovocal cords on hot dogs?
Like instead of a hot dog?
Your parents have told you no.
No, more often.
It could be just the endovocal cord in the bone.
By listening to this show, you have edified.
No mouth, no.
You have practically edified yourself.
Oh, you scroll forward.
To a state of supreme discipline.
And let us know, is it coming out there or is it just static?
I mean, we're not getting the regular feedback.
All this is possible.
If you are under the O.G.
That would let us know that the...
If I can't hear it.
If you are...
If you are not able to hear...
...then you must have slack.
Just the slack must have...
And it is all about the slack.
That's about right.
Sometimes slack is just a silent radio signal.
Or for the kids.
Or, you know...
No, we're tired of doing it for the kids now.
We're tired.
We're just doing it for the slack.
And the kids just don't get it.
That's the problem these days.
The kids don't appreciate slack.
They don't get the slack.
They don't appreciate it.
They don't understand that their forefathers...
...their fathers had to die...
on the field of battle to make sure that they get the slack.
Well, they're just kids.
They don't know anything.
But the problem is, you know, they don't teach them anything today.
Yeah, they don't teach them the kids.
Like when I was a kid, slack was part of every classroom agenda.
We would come in in the mornings and, you know, well, that's the problem.
Everybody here doesn't get that kind of training anymore.
Knock-kneed, slab-sided, social engineering, egg-sucking liberal.
You know, they used to teach us fun because it was a predecessor to slack.
That long-line listener just turned on the radio is what it was.
They couldn't get the good signal on the Internet,
so they had to turn on the full spectrum sound of the radio.
You are the loudest voice.
You have to imagine the show.
Yeah, you have to imagine what the show sounds like tonight.
Since we're not sure if we're going out over the broadcast airwaves,
the ones owned by the public, you, the public, own these airwaves right now
that we are signaling across.
It's sort of like bumping into.
Airy wave.
They respect those airwave forms.
Because we're going up one side and then simulating a downward.
They respond to attention.
So, what's the second experience that we see in the log and the radio?
We do the signal and you help us in.
Harmonizing audio is like thesus keeper.
You're in cookie stone, promise me.
Now,  vitesse is 100.
correctly.
Alljoyance, layer.
I'm so happy we have a nuclear system out seawater.
Don't do them.
Here it comes.
These headphones have moved.
They're bleeding now.
These headphones are bleeding.
Well, they are another sign of the end times when headphones show bleed.
Really?
And audio.
So do you know the people that took the baby from the Body World show?
I'm still trying to find out.
Was that Sacramento?
What about Trace?
Well, I'll trade you this shiny piece of tinfoil.
Yeah, Leandro.
Trace had one pretty good on the radio.
Okay, so I guess that if...
Now, this isn't a real caller, though.
This is just a tape.
No, this is a real caller right here.
Sure, that's what the last tape said.
We need to know if it's...
Are you a live real caller or are you a recorded?
I'm a live.
But you're a pre-recorded live real caller, right?
I think he's pre-recorded.
It's not one we know for sure.
He's actually listening to us in real time right now.
Real time.
One, two, three, four minutes.
I know that's a clever mixing technique that our operator, Puzzling Evidence,
is probably tricking the audience now into thinking that they're listening to a live show with live callers.
What'd he do?
Pseudo-religion.
There they go again with that.
Well, they're so hip.
They are sort of a pseudo-religion.
So pop.
So with it.
So wacky, crazy, judgmental.
Church of the subgenius.
Imaginary memories, too.
A lot of the newer McDonald products contain, like, synthetic memories.
Like you have a quarter pounder with cheese.
You know, you go with some old standby like that.
Half an hour later, you're thinking of maybe, like, mowing some people down in Baghdad or Fallujah.
I was there.
Damn it.
I remember.
Well, if you've got cow memories, it's usually pretty peaceful up until the very last one.
Well, as you know...
Not if you got mad.
Not...
Not if the memories are coming from the cows that went into the McDonald's burger.
Maybe if you get, like, an Amish burger, the memories would be peaceful, but...
You don't want the memories of the slaughterhouse.
You don't want the memories of the feedlot.
You don't want the memories of the...
But up until then, they're on Valium.
Not really.
They're on heavy doses of antibiotics and hormones.
I wonder which memory in the other world would be the most salient in your mind would be
all those goopy, happy things you did or the fact that you were being corralled in a place
with about 5,000 other monkeys and people were plugging you right and left.
That might leave a little stain, you know?
Bummer, man.
And that's what we're eating every time we eat a McBuser or a Harvey's or a Deluxe or
any of those things like that.
We're eating the excrement of the vegetable kingdom as well as the mineral kingdom and
the fuselage of the animal kingdom.
Hey, man.
And, uh...
Not at the stand.
We're at the ranch.
We raise cows.
Believe me.
They have a very peaceful life.
Oh, yeah.
They go out to pasture and everything, don't they?
I bet.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the way cows, you know, evolve to live.
You know, they have a nice big grassy pasture to stand around in and soak up some sun and
munch on some grass.
Yeah, we've had pure, pure capiprop.
Did they chew their cud?
Do these cows on your ranch actually chew their cud?
We don't send them to a slaughterhouse.
We strangle them ourselves.
That's the way God intended, you know?
With our own bare hands.
With our own staying strong.
Now, some of the ones, some of the more prized specimens you keep, right, the ones you want
to let die of old age, the one that you got is, you know, remember the one that's named
G. Gordon Gordon?
Right.
The one that saved my life when I was a little boy.
Yeah.
We didn't eat that one until it was like 40 years old.
Gonna talk to my attorney.
Gonna take a little journey.
Too far away.
Down in sub-genius land.
To the city that is Bobstow.
The place that's known as Bobstow.
Gonna take me down.
Down to sub-genius land.
Gonna wash my brain until my pain goes way down there.
Sell all my stuff I've got enough to stay down there.
Way down in southeast Asia.
In the jungles of Malaysia.
Come on with me.
I'll take you by the hand.
Gonna turn my brain to porridge.
When they put my soul in the storage.
When we go down.
Down to sub-genius land.
It's the place I know where the bobbies go when they milk them dry.
Those endless mobs still seeking Dobbs.
Oh, they don't know why.
They don't know why.
So if you like to gamble.
Come and take a little ramble.
Just step right up and tell me I'm your man.
Gonna be with you in Bobstow.
In the city known as Dobbstow.
Bobstow.
Yeah.
When we all go down.
Down to sub-genius land.
So hop aboard, you little campers.
Crawl into Beelzebub's belly.
And down to sub-genius land you go as the master demon chews you and masticates you.
And you slide down the demonic esophagus to Dobbstown, Malaysia.
Are you eating your arms?
We'll stay and hang.
When the trumpet.
Calls.
X-Day.
In a brother and sister band.
When they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Sub-genie of the world unite.
Alien sex every night.
Sub-genie of the world.
Sub-genie of the world unite.
weil wir aufrieren werden....
We shall have paradise.
Singteni auf dernheit.
Radiant suks.
Every night.
Pandora's lesson has panicked you.
Castratum snnai.
Digsea's demais.
The World, Santini of the World, Santini of the World, United!
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, live there, friends, at the Beachland Ballroom,
backed in part by ESO.
We're now around the middle of the show, 999.
Meanwhile, the Berkley Show has lost 10 listeners.
Before the beginning of the show, now we've got the 47 poor listeners.
Those other seven.
We don't like those other seven listeners anyway.
We're glad they're gone.
We'll be down to the true believers very shortly.
They won't jump the rocket ship as it falls back to Earth.
That's right.
They're going to ride it down in the fullness of its furious, blazing glory.
One of my favorite versions of that in an actual subgenius short story is in Captain Tomorrow.
Yeah.
And the people.
The T-47 that rules the Earth.
From PR News in Washington, I'm set for tomorrow.
General Motors said today that it will eliminate PR News.
The cuts should save about $2.5 a year and move the world's biggest automaker back toward PR News.
A senior Palestinian official complained to some of Africa's poorest countries.
Stocks 1, 10, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
President Bush and British Prime Minister Tony Blair are holding a joint at the White House.
President Bush.
Bush said that Blair has been seeking a deal he hopes to present to PR News in Washington.
Anybody got the, anybody know the scientific name for poison ivy?
Um, no.
It's also, it's also a homeopathic remedy.
A homopathic remedy.
Uva scurpus.
You know, the great thing about homeopathic remedies is you could poison an entire city water supply with just a few molecules of a poison.
No, you couldn't.
You couldn't.
Yeah, but, you know, where do you find the right homeos to do the job?
Well, you know.
I maintain that it's one of the biggest frauds ever perpetuated in the history of medical science, actually.
Well, think about it, you know, but according to the way homeopathy works, it's almost like the less of a, the greater the dilution, the more powerful the medicine.
So if you just put one or two molecules of, say, cyanide into the city, I mean.
Then everybody will be immune to cyanide poisoning.
Oh.
Uh.
No, I don't think it actually works that way.
I don't know.
Like, uh, there's quite a bit of research out there that is, uh, questionable, puzzling, um.
It was kind of invented back when they knew even less about medicine than we do now.
Associative magic.
You know, like.
See, like, okay, like homeopathic.
Homeopathy was invented 200 years ago, about.
Uh, at a time when they were still using leeches.
And they kept on finding that leeches kept on, you know, a lot of patients kept on dying when they used these leeches.
And they didn't understand, like, this is good medicine, right?
Yeah, they're not the leeches now.
But then when they figured out that if you give them a sugar pill, the sugar pill won't kill them the way the leeches might.
So suddenly they found something that worked better than leeches.
And they've been doing it ever since.
Psychotherapy.
No.
Um.
Mind control?
Yeah.
Bad medicine.
All these things and more.
Perhaps.
Come on down to Dr. Sinister's office.
Lay down on the couch.
Tell me your problems.
I'll prescribe you a homeopathic remedy.
Okay.
I'll give you some oleum serpentus.
They all have the Latin names, too, so you don't know what they really are.
Because if, like, if you found out that you were paying $5 for a jar of, uh, natrium muriaticum,
and, like, it didn't even have any natrium muriaticum in it, and you could make it yourself at home for...
Do you know what natrium muriaticum is?
Salt.
Oh, yes.
Uh, somebody called up, uh, to a store once asking for, uh,
I'm looking for a homeopathic remedy called Diplombum.
And the salesman said, oh, yes, metallic lead.
Yes, uh, we have some of that right over here.
He's like, where would I want to put lead in my body?
So these people, they take these medicines, they don't even know how they're made or how they're supposed to work.
And, uh, it's kind of ridiculous.
Like, once you tell them how it's supposed to work and how they're made, they're like, that can't work.
And yet, there are people who swear by that stuff.
Because they believe.
And if you notice, you notice a lot of, a lot of the complaints that they prescribe these things for are things that would go away on their own in an hour anyway.
Right.
The injections on all of them are like, you know, dissolve two to four tablets under the tongue once every hour for four hours until symptoms disappear.
Lay down in bed for 20 minutes and headache will go away.
Yeah.
You know, silly stuff like that.
Oleum Serpentis.
That's my favorite.
Well, the ear candling is a good example of, uh, I mean, I saw people absolutely believe in that stuff.
Well, ear candling can do some things, but not a lot of the things that people claim it can do.
It's the same thing.
The only thing is there's no ear attached to it.
Well, as far as pulling out wax goes, it won't, will not, ear candle will not pull wax out of your ear.
No.
It will put wax in your ear.
It does not care.
I've tried it before.
Exactly.
Those funnels that you have to wear.
Yeah.
They make, you know, people burn crosses on your yard and they, you know.
Right.
And it doesn't keep the saucer beams out of your head or the government beams out of your head.
It doesn't pollute.
Although, although it can have an effect on the air pressure balances between the head, you know, the ears and the sinus.
And all that stuff.
Well, the overall barometric pressure.
So you can change like the pressure maybe.
The FDA and the DEA.
But, you know, you're not going to be pulling out the wax.
It'll show up at your house later, but.
Although, I can say that it's probably, you know, if you have the evil spirits in your head that cause those voices all the time,
the ear candle can draw out the evil spirits and burn them up.
Right.
So you won't hear those voices anymore.
And you won't get an orgone ear candling.
Ooh.
Yeah.
That is especially efficacious.
Don't even get me started on the orgone.
Yep.
The Reikian.
The Reikian candles are.
They're shaped like little PP, PP, PP32s.
And they, they can take down flying saucers.
Yeah.
They can, they can cause rain.
They're like rain making machines and flying saucer repellent.
I bought one of those things to keep flying saucers and ghosts away.
And I tell you, man, it has worked fantastically.
Yeah, but you got a really good one, Stang, when you had that stroke of luck and you spent the extra money.
You know, a lot of people can't afford that kind of thing around their house.
Yeah, I was, I was lucky to get, I got a really good deal and it came along at a good time.
But, you know, it has kept supernatural beings, really every order of supernatural invasive creature away.
Well, the ones that aren't that good, you know, seep and leak.
The next thing you know, you think you're living in a good place to live and there's an alien ghost, you know, at your dinner table, you know, saying, you know, the coffee sucks.
It's a fine.
It's a fine time for the computer here to start crashing on me when I need to place.
Okay, here we go.
I'm stupid.
That's why Clorox has a line of products that can make kids sick.
Yes.
What is left of Bob's right brain?
In Bob's right brain, there's nothing left.
In his left brain, nothing works right.
So don't depend on him for cosmic wisdom.
We worship Bob only because he's luckier and better and smarter.
Well, he's not smarter.
He's actually just lucky.
That's why we call it subgenius.
We believe that intelligence has been misdefined by the conspiracy of the normals.
And they equate it now with book smarts.
Whereas what Bob is talking about is common sense, sense of humor.
And dollars and cents.
Which reminds me, I have a trunk load of CDs of our radio shows.
MP3 collections where you can get like 60 radio shows in one disc.
We've got DVDs.
And I can do marriages.
If you need just a 24-hour marriage, say you're a young couple or three, four, just you and your hand.
I don't care what.
You need to feel absolved for like 24 hours or so.
You don't want to really get hitched.
I can take care of that.
I'm ordained enough.
And if I'm not, then there's a lot of people living in sin.
And a lot of people who wasted money on divorces.
I don't have nearly as many workers around here at the church headquarters as I used to.
We had to lay.
We had to lay off.
God, you know, half of the factory staff.
Bob is a stingy, stingy master.
I've lost a lot of limousines and mansions.
Outsourced to Planet X.
I had to sell old Bessie.
Those damn exists, they work for peanuts.
How can we compete for our jobs with exists?
687-3515.
Oh, I thought we had another caller.
They don't believe in the exist aliens.
They believe in the gray aliens.
Right.
You know, sure, they're there.
But those are like, you know.
I just believe in the off-white ones.
Those are no-account, worthless bunch of...
The Manila aliens.
They're hardly any more advanced than we are.
Yes?
I'm kind of new to all this, and I was wondering what Bob's last name is.
Oh, I'm sorry.
His full name is J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Dobbs is his last name.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
The J.R. doesn't stand for anything.
And he has, quote, Bob, unquote, is on his birth certificate.
People occasionally will say, well, Bob's just made up character, isn't he?
Would you say that to a Christian?
Oh, Jesus just made up character, isn't he?
People just don't, you know, they don't have sensitivity about these things.
Is the pipe important to Bob?
Some think that the pipe is the one calling the shots.
Look at this T-shirt.
This is a really unusual one.
I didn't realize this until about...
an hour ago.
I was thinking, well, Bob's smoking this brain, right?
And his brain's on fire.
There's another way of looking at this.
This brain is sucking Bob's brain through the pipe.
The fire is up here.
Bob lit...
I mean, the brain lit Bob's head up here
and is smoking his brain through the pipe.
And you can do that, too.
The next time you see Bob,
run up there and put a...
a lip lock on that big old pipe and suck.
I know that early in your life
you took that wrong turn expecting to find the truth.
And yet, you're still looking.
You're still looking.
And somehow, stumbling through the radio dial late at night,
you come across...
Wait, you got me.
Oh, no, you lost it.
The Puzzling Evidence Show.
And finally, you said to yourself,
this is what I've been seeking my entire life.
Of course, if it's a digital tuner, you've been here all along.
Aficionados of politics find the show obsessive.
Queen Zizi of Z finds the show...
We don't know what she means by that.
We're still looking for the translation device.
But the Bible is a difficult book to interpret.
It's all Star Trek.
It contains puzzles and textual variants
that are just mind-numbing in a...
Is Hal asleep?
Yes, he's asleep.
He's disappeared.
He's completely intangible.
He's just...
He's discorporate at this point.
Incorpor-real.
And we will check and see if there's any life form left.
Oh, damn it.
I won't wait.
I can't wait.
We've driven them down to 35.
They're the 35 true core listeners.
The audience elimination experiment is a success.
This is the way.
Radio listeners,
I hear Hal's nose on the microphone.
Hal's nose.
The only thing that's left of Hal is his nose
stuck to the end of the microphone.
The rest of his body has completely disintegrated
into a jelly-like mass at the base of his chair.
And yet somehow or another,
it's still jiggling and wiggling like jello.
It is jello.
Here, try some.
This is great.
You're puzzling.
Try some of this.
It tastes like fruit.
It's good.
I don't know how.
Oh, man.
Hal's got us this great.
It's like what fruit tastes like on Jupiter.
Man, who would have known Hal had all this jello?
Who wants to go to Jupiter?
Thank God we don't have to worry about the fate of Iraq anymore.
We've got Hal's jello.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Yes.
Mmm.
This Hal jello is indeed something else.
Friends, Hal jello and Dr. Philodrum and Slime
will be at 8X Day,
as will the amino acids heard in the background,
and Reverend Susie the Floozy,
yours truly, Reverend Nikki Death Chick,
and Dr. Dark's drive-in bad film theater every night.
And you can, too,
if you find out, uh, how.
At subgenius.com, friends.
It's kind of an adults-only website,
and it's kind of an adults-only festival.
But, but, kids or adults can write to subgenius
at this number coming up.
Got that pencil ready?
That's subgenius at P.O. Box 181417,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Once again, that's Box 181417,
And, friends,
Lee Murr will now give us the rest of the information.
One, three, zero, one, three.
Bob?
Bob's a small guy, physically, I'm pretty convinced.
Uh huh.
You seen the photographs?
Are those the autopsy photographs that were rearranged
to look like choir photographs?
I never trust an autopsy photo.
Now, don't get us wrong.
God loves you.
God really does love you,
but Bob, Bob Wants You!
God loves you, Bob.
you but old Bobby, old Bobby wants you
and he's going to find you friends
you can't find yourself
you think you're going to find yourself
better than Bob can
are you that prideful
I tell you what friends
I'll find myself when they pry me
out of my cold dead fingers
so follow
that pie
follow that pie
pipe-er out of
Conditch to glorious
Dobstown friends
but you can't just talk about it
like I'm doing up here
you have to do it, you have to actually do it
you can't be a chicken shit
so build your own ship
and evacuate or vacate
the evacuation chamber
god damn it
this church of the subgenius
sure it's a joke sometimes
but why can't it also be the one true religion
this is the
divinity school of hard
knocks my friends
and it actually is
as real
as it gets
as Dr. Legume said
we will lead this damn nation
to damnation
and as
Princess We Are Doe said
we are good
but we're our own brand of good
so friends
in closing
I want to get off here and get some slack myself
I have refrained from taking any drugs
until five minutes from now
but in closing
I want to reiterate friends
when you need slack
you make your own slack
make your own slack
and build your own ship
Bob Dobbs is not the answer
and neither is anything else
you must learn
to think for yourself
only Bob can show you how
and friends
the last thing
the most important thing of all
fuck them if they can't
take a joke
and praise Bob
happy X day
Bob bless y'all
if I don't see you no more in this world
I'll meet you on the next one
and don't be late
I cut my finger on a soup can lid
I got an infection and it spread to my dick
it swelled up to the size of a human hand
and then a mouth opened on it
and this is what it said
kill the pink boys
quit your job
mocks the world
and praise Bob Dobbs
we'll build a ship
and take a trip
go on go get a pen
write the coordinates
three and a half months in my garage
tearing parts off of old used cars
my groin at this point was unusually large
and went occasionally home while smoking cigars
the project was finished
the ship would hold twenty
the power source was anything the crew would think was funny
we didn't need the slack
we just needed to get the fuck out of here
we're blacklist they're hapless
our north proved its worth in escaping the stark fist
on our way to planet X for sex direct snacks
a prairie squid and every pot of money shot a coney twang
it's an all-horse hour of bonanza
it's like a world without Tony Danza
or fans of the pink shit that hits the charts
in a world of dead art
simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
we take a moment and we pause to reflect
on the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wrecked
then we laugh like banshees and howl like comanches
do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
our fantasy is a reality
earth's tarnished to dust as planet X are bust for us
Bob's pipe is lit
space and time shift
temporal disturbance
that causes a slack rift
and the drop then a hit
a dimensional split
severs forever subgeni from pink shit
Bob walked in a circle
and steadily exhaled in the smoke
I can see why the pink boys failed
two pay-a-days has caused destruction
second hole of slackless suction
pay-per-view alien abduction
functioning on solar energy
the money should be painted black
the mate from space that stole your balls
will soon come back and take it all
return to slack return to Bob
repent slack off and quit your job
or slurp the beastly knob
concrete
lick the throbbing vein of slavery
now you're sleeping like a baby
but Bob woke me up and said
get out of dodge
there's a guy who's dick and top with a UFO in his garage
I ate some bad ham and I got really sick
and in a puddle of my puke went a
the puke was most sick
a mouth did appear
and it beckoned me near
and it whispered the following words into my ear
it said
kill the pink boys
quit your job
mock the world
and praise Bob Dobbs
you'll build a ship
and take a trip
go on go get a pen
write the coordinates
six and a half months hold up alone
circuit boards duct tape and turkey bones
the ship appeared more than disaster prone
but the vomit assured me that far weirder ships had flown
the project was finished
the ship would hold twenty
the power source would be gone
the universe was anything the crew would think was funny
we didn't need the slack list or hapless
our murk proved its worth in escaping the star fist
on our way to planet X for sex that wrecks necks
the prairie squid and every pot of money shot at Connie Twan
it's an all-horse hour of bonanza
it's like a world without Tony Danza
or fans of the pink shit that hits the charts
in a world of dead art
simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy
we take a moment and we pause to reflect
on the pinks that we killed and the planet that they wreck
then we laugh like banshees and howl like Comanches
do a victory dance in our underoos and panties
our fantasy is a reality
earth turns to dust it's planet X or bust
planet X or bust
the great classic by the great El Queso All Stars
praise Bob
god damn funky
man it's too tight
it's too tight
Bob