On July 5th, 1998, 7 a.m., when we all have hangovers, Wotan's judgment will take place in the form of what the pre-scriptures call the advent of the angelic host.
Like any other prophet, Bob preaches about the end of the world, only his predictions are just a little different.
July 5th, 1998, at 7 a.m. to be exact, the men from Planet X, as the news media will call them, will arrive to rupture the subgeniuses, the true believer subgeniuses, up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
And believe it or not, plenty of people, 4,000 of them so far and more every day, have already joined up.
Suddenly the joke has become serious and profitable.
Your standard religious rip-off, right?
But can anybody take this stuff seriously?
Dear Bob, it's time to close my eyes.
Remember now, it's no surprise, if I should be found dead someday, I'll think that you were in the way.
Oh, gimme Bob.
Confusing that face.
With my own.
Can't remember my place.
Bob's Rude.
My role on this planet is to see that the Earth is not sold on that glorious or terrible day we call X-Day in 1998.
When the men from Planet X arrive.
Yeah, now it may sound ludicrous, it may sound ridiculous to many of the believers out there.
Are you saying they're all nuts, all those people?
Maybe, yeah, maybe.
Planes fly!
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that...
Free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Give me slack or give me food or kill me!
Kill me!
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Earth.
Night, little monkeys in your cage.
Night, night.
All your great skyscrapers, your achievements, your mighty books and discoveries, your symphonies, your armies, your concentration camps.
All of it was...
Your indoor plumbing, your toiletries and your mini...
As a wink.
Delicacies that no one...
A tiny spark.
Starving.
Dying.
Flying ember in the middle of thousands and billions of light years of empty, cold space.
Glowing stinky hole in your third eye.
You are about as important as a cork in the ocean, my friend.
Think of a cockroach, if you would.
I don't know if you want to think of one for too long,
but just imagine the revulsion you feel when you swat one and brush it away from yourselves.
Think of yourself as a mere cockroach compared to these weird exes, archons, whatever the hell they are.
They don't notice you. They don't care about you.
If you happen to hitch a ride and they don't swat you off, then count yourself lucky.
But don't think you're some kind of a big deal
just because God or some aliens happen to pick you up by the scruff of your neck
and show you a thing or two.
They're in there with you. They're in the room with you.
You can't see them. You can't smell them.
You can't taste them.
But they're in the room with you.
And they blend with the walls, with the CDs, with the vinyl rack,
with the digital, with everything, with the microphone.
And with the airwaves.
It's the hiss buried in the tape that we use to carry the code, the coded signal.
But it's the only way we can stop them.
The human mind.
The human mind is capable of receiving and transmitting radio signals.
It has no way of converting this knowledge or energy into a practical use.
However, the brain has in it, in some miraculous way,
the ability to transmit and convert and receive radio signals.
We use your brain as an envelope to send our letters to the others.
They are our course.
We are our correspondents with a world you could never fathom.
It's square to your round.
It's cheesy to your musky.
It's black to your white.
It's green to your red.
It's out of focus to your sharp image.
Do the rat in the cheese.
The cheese is the universe.
Do the rat, baby.
Do it one more time.
Everybody love to watch you do the rat.
Do the rat.
The rat.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
it's the Ask Dr. Hal Show, live on radio.
Well, not really.
It's just I happen to be visiting.
I was passing through your state,
so I stopped in to pay a visit to your burgeoning community
to see how you are doing in this neck of the woods.
Yes.
See if the swirling demonic forces of the conspiracy
have managed to erode away the last vestiges of subgenius thought.
Because some outlying communities are just that,
outlying, benighted, bereft,
struggling in darkness thicker than tar.
And all we want to do is loosen it up a little,
provide a lack of obstruction so the flow can be eased,
so really,
relaxation can take place.
The true communication of letting go.
Oh, you've got to let it all go.
Everything.
This entire earth and all that it inherits.
The mountains, the trees, the animal life and plant life,
the sights and smells of earth,
all to be gone, wiped out in a single fiery convulsion.
Not of nature.
But of advanced science.
Perhaps perpetuated by a perverted and senescent will.
So old it does not even fathom its own purposes.
Yes, this is coming.
Coming, my friends.
Coming for you and for me.
None of us shall escape this rain of fire
except those who have performed one simple act.
As simple as the ablution of a baby's bombast.
All you need to do is send in your $30.
And now it's so close, I don't know if the mail can accommodate this.
I really don't know.
It may be too late.
I may be speaking to an audience of the damned.
No, you're speaking to an audience on a community station
where we would never have a call to action or a specific amount.
Well, I can surely refer to symbolic words in the book of the...
Yes, when Hal refers to...
In the Christian Bible, I can talk of 30 pieces of silver,
the tares that are thrown in the field to be cultivated for later,
or the chaff to be swept into the furnace and burned at the final day.
That great day when the dreadful judge in middle air shall spread his throne.
The seas give up their dead and monsters walk the earth.
Worse than we got now, I mean.
Yes, it's all going to happen,
and there's not one gosh darn thing you can do about it,
even right here on community radio.
Nonetheless, it's good to be able to come in, hang up my hat,
put my feet up on the end iron, light up a good cheroot.
Oh, I guess we can't do that.
And commune as gentlemen in these, our last days on a planet
which was once this whole quadrant of the universe's most promising experiment.
Yes, there were...
Great hopes for a little earth when it began.
Just a twinkling spot of light in God's beard,
nestling within the heliopause,
one of those precious little precocious inner rocky worlds,
shunning the gas giants and their gravitational and magnetic barriers,
coasting in close to the sun and mooching its life-giving warmth.
Well, those soft days are coming to an end, buddy.
Sure enough.
There's not going to be...
There's not going to be no more whales and quails and any of that stuff.
The snails or potatoes.
Snails, they're going to be gone, too.
No braille, either.
No more need for braille.
No more staying in the dark using the fondness you have.
It's going to be too high in the sky.
The sun will be blue.
Too high.
The sun will be blue indeed as it ratchets toward the far end of the spectrum.
But you blew it, my friend.
What?
How is that?
You didn't join the church of the subgenius in time.
But, Pastor Stang, I thought we weren't supposed to mention that kind of thing here on the community.
We're not telling them to join the church.
They've already blown it.
It's too late.
There's no call to action here.
That's right.
The community radio people, if they want to get on your case,
they can do that.
As they're charred cinders blowing over a field of ashes 7,000 miles wide,
they can't do much about our...
Our...
Our violation of these petty rules of radio.
Right to our commercial considerations are of little value when you're atomized.
We've got a lot of ashes to haul, friends.
And a lot of atoms are our future consumers.
Unfortunately.
I hate to dismiss the idea out of hand, but since my hands are glowing right now,
I thought I might remind us all the fact that we're being pelted, or at least pionized,
with numerous sprays already.
And I don't know if they're ready to...
To...
Spring a leak, or if things are going to happen, or...
My, them cosmic rays get you from any angle, wherever you are.
You get interpenetrated.
You don't want to bend over in front of one, that's for sure.
Well, no need.
They'll get you from that direction, too.
And there's cameras everywhere that'll film it.
Yes, that's true.
But there's not beings everywhere that are interested enough to watch it, you know.
Thank goodness.
That's the problem.
Other machines are watching our misdoings as we give it the finger.
Well, that's their job.
They've been programmed to take a peek at the unsanitary side of humanity.
And to them, it's just another epiphenomenon to record in their infinitely expanding memory banks.
It is a sad thought, boy, and there are plenty that you just erudited right there.
Well, I know that's true, but, you know...
They're all true.
The old rules are coming to an end, and the new ones will begin presently.
The end of the term will have come,
and school will be let out.
We will rush out into the glorious recess of the afterworld.
They're coming to take us away!
Ha-ha!
Hee-hee!
Yes, they are, and they will take us away.
I have my stateroom reserved, and I think we are all down with the new luggage rules.
The lack of a bag fee, I think, is quite progressive for these UFOs.
Well, for some of the people who need too much oxygen,
I don't know if it's a very considerate idea,
but it'll probably still have to go into the memo book in the files.
Oh, yes, some drone in the central offices will put it there.
I just handed Hal the very first filled-out subgenius membership card.
Number one.
You know, even Hitler's party membership was number eight.
But this is number one, man, and I just touched it with my sweating fingers.
It's filled out with a manual typewriter.
It has...
It has my human name.
I didn't even...
I hadn't even become...
I hadn't gotten my free name of Ivan Stang.
I had my simple old name of Mr. Smith.
Read the obverse.
Of Dallas, Texas.
Yes, Dallas, Texas.
Oh, well, here's what I have.
Not at all of a similar vintage.
Dr. Hal here has...
Be it known that Dr. Hal is a genuine pope.
Oh, this is an original...
This is an original Discordian pope card, isn't it?
Yes.
Wow.
Not a, you know, not a subgenius one or anything classy like that.
Do you have a miter and a hat and everything, or...?
Well, I brought them, but they're not here at the radio station.
I was...
Have you absconded with the wealth of all the parishes yet?
That's to happen at the moment, the special, specific moment.
7 o'clock a.m., July 5th, 1998.
Will this be 1998, my friend?
At last.
Is this month, is today June?
Or whenever you hear this...
The leafy month of June.
Is it the day you think it is?
Is this even the planet that you thought it was?
We can't be sure of anything.
Well, you must be familiar with Scientific American's new research on the substitution of Mars and Earth,
which is a hot thing in science.
I heard a little bit about that.
But why would you want to...
And we were ahead of them.
Dr. Onan Kanabite wrote his first essay on that in 2005.
2005.
They're worried that it may destabilize the whole system, the solar system, this switching,
because they do have effects on the other planets in the disk.
It won't be the first time it's been done.
Just over periods of eons and so forth.
But why do we want to substitute anything for...
You know, it's like being in a Chinese restaurant.
And there are no substitutions.
I think we've failed on a way out of there.
Well, then they're just not going to get your business from then on.
Mars is...
If they won't accommodate you in your Chinese menu,
then the Martians will have to go home.
Oh.
It's just like...
We are the Martians.
...90 million miles to Earth.
What is the basic premise?
Was there a migration or the actual orbit shift?
The conspiracy used up the planet we were on last
and switched orbits and took over this one that we're on,
which used to be called Mars.
And now everyone complains that the resources are so meager
and everything seems to be used up.
Well, it's quite easy to see that now that we're on this old rusty Rust Belt planet,
we no longer have the lush opportunities we once did
when life was green and growing
and the devil could take the hot most,
the sweet, salty zest of life.
I think I heard that devil coming now.
Is that him?
Or is it Bob?
Oh, no!
Or is it the men from Planet X?
Or the men from Planet X?
I have a moment here.
I explain satanic bacon
and how it grills so easy
and goes down so fresh and moist
you'd wish it was Tuesday all over again.
Ah.
Ah, Scrapple.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, long pick.
Are you Philly bound or are you just a big cheese?
Uh, Doc, uh, Mr. Sister.
Reverend Dr. I.D.
Dr. Mr. Sister picked up some Scrapple for the X-Day event.
Boo-coo Scrapple, as I hear it.
At the store we call Giant Bagel.
Well, what the Eastern folks really love,
well, it's later on in the summer and stuff,
is to grill your Scrapple and make toasts.
And have big, slopping, huge, homegrown tomatoes
on top of it and mayo.
It's delightful.
To mix healthy food with Scrapple?
I've never heard of such a thing.
We'll have to try that sometime.
It might fool the body into accommodating more.
For those listeners who, in other realms,
who don't know what Scrapple is,
you know what they make hot dogs out of?
Hot dogs.
And you don't even want to think about it?
Well, Scrapple is made from what they won't even use
in hot dogs.
It's time to stretch and fetch
and visit our snack bar.
Hot dogs.
Visit our snacks.
Hot dog, it's a wiener.
Soft drinks, all colors.
You're saying that the average wiener
accommodates all sorts of colors
in its spectrum of light?
A coruscating rainbow of iridescent evil.
Oh, well, that's the least of our worries right now.
Ha ha ha!
Yes, I...
Impugning overwhelming good is going to sucker us all.
Well, we're just going to have to have a new...
a new scale of aesthetic values.
The poisonous lime greens
and head-ache-inducing vibrating oranges
will become the daily color of the fabric of our lives
in the new unthinkable existence
we all are now rocketing toward.
Oh, what a dire thought in your prescription.
Oh, you'll like it. It'll be fun.
Just like these so-called sex goddesses,
if you saw them in any other...
context, you might recoil, blanch, shriek,
or attempt to claw out your eyes
to cut out the hideous sight
of their undulating chitinous mandibles,
et cetera, et cetera.
But on the board, the saucers,
you will frenziedly copulate with these babes
because it's all chemical.
It's a chemical signal that you can't escape.
One calibrated to you
and your personal needs in this new world
all the way to planetary...
X.
And then in the waiting room
at the Port Authority building...
I beg your pardon?
I said, that's right, little shapers.
No genitalia necessary.
Act now while offer lasts.
It's like the Matrix inside the Matrix.
Yeah.
In the real world, you have to eat recycled roach crap.
In the Matrix, you can have the finest lobster
in a restaurant.
In the Matrix of the Matrix,
you can be on the escape vessels of the sex goddesses
with J.R.R. Martin.
Or Bob Dobbs himself.
Oh, yes, that makes it all worthwhile, doesn't it?
Sitting at the right hand of Bob,
each single one of us will be sitting right next to Bob.
Yes, that's right.
Farewell, Earth geometry.
...quality of the place where we are going.
If we think the wrong thoughts,
perhaps the wrong sex goddess will appear
and devour our needless genitalia.
You'll enjoy it just the same.
Enjoyment is the name of the game.
You'll enjoy it whether you want to or not.
You will.
It's chemical.
It's locked into you so that you are bound to enjoy it.
And it's so much better than what's happening to everybody else.
It's lump smoking good.
That's right.
You may be a smoking lump by the end of the voyage,
but you will be an enlightened lump
ready to participate up through the various sub-universes
in future heavens.
The polycosmos.
I didn't know a polycosmos was promised.
I'm sorry I'm so lax in my...
It just is.
Just take a gander at the...
It already is.
...afterlife diagram in Revelation X,
which shows clearly the pathway that one will follow
after reaching the port authority building on Planet X.
That diagram happened to have been drawn by Dr. Howell.
Yes, I drew it, and I was intending to produce a color version,
but then Philo came over to my house
and without even asking my permission,
rolled it up and said,
oh, I'll just take this away and make a copy of it.
Then he lost it.
You're kidding.
I can easily believe that.
And I couldn't tell the tale one more sorry time
of what he did to my computer desktop.
He decided he could improve on my desktop arrangement one day.
I will never let him forget that.
What did he do to your desktop?
He cleaned it up.
Oh, well.
By his standards.
Cleaned all those annoying images out of it.
His idea of cleaning it up.
As if I didn't know that there was an autopilot,
clean-up thing.
This was back in the days before desktops reached out
and cleaned you up.
Oh, it says,
you have unused items on your desktop.
Okay, I don't care.
Click.
Pop.
You have unused light.
Hey, I just...
It's actually telling you to take care of the detritus
through your coffee and your cigarette machine.
Oh, so blame it on the vending machines.
Well, you can blame them around here.
I went with $1.25.
I tried to get some diet soda.
All they had was diet Pepsi.
Then they didn't have it.
Oh, no.
Then they didn't have water.
They don't have anything,
and they won't give me my money back.
It sticks inside the machine.
So you can see...
I wondered why you came back empty-handed.
The conspiracy fights to the end,
to the very last end.
It will wriggle and thrash
like a snake whose head has been removed.
There's still life in its sinuous coiling fold.
But life is flowing out of it,
and it will soon be as stiff
as its prehistoric ancestors.
Yes.
Look at Hitler's feet.
It's a rock.
Yes.
Now, Doctor, how did you do like in the movies
where you slam into the machine and kick it?
But this is not my radio station.
I could do a full-blown Homer Simpson on it,
but I just arrived at this place,
and I give a good account of myself
and not immediately start by trashing.
The lighting is nice there, too,
and it's pretty.
The walls are pink so that you don't argue
The money's still in there.
I can go hit it later
and try to get $1.25 back.
Try to get something back from the organization.
We should all try to do that.
Don't let them get away with murder.
But wouldn't you agree that the machines
are actually reading our minds,
taking our very thoughts
and using them as data to reconvert reality
and change our minds
and to make life miserable for us?
Pound away.
You guys, it's all yours.
Wow.
Ivan Stang's going to go and do battle
with that device right now
and strapped into the back of that mechanical mother.
There is a special solenoid
that'll keep him punching
until he's drunk with power,
as we classically say.
He's strapped in right now at this moment.
He left his post,
and he went there to start punching that machine.
But still, you know,
the only victory would be getting the money back
since they have no drinking water
or diet soda or anything else,
only heavily sugared death pop.
Well, remember,
remember in Dr. Strangelove
when Kenan Wynn went insane at the very end there
and shot the machine.
Colonel Batguano.
He was asked to...
He took all the money because the damned...
I'm not supposed to mention the name
on a non-commercial station.
Soda Pop Company was, you know,
did the wrong thing, and so he deserved...
Well, he said that Colonel Mandrake
would have to answer to that company
because he...
That's right, that's right.
Mandrake asked him to shoot the machine
to get the change out
so he could complete his mission.
He could complete his telephone call
to the White House in Washington, D.C.
That was correct after he had learned
about purity of essence.
So what, it just snickered and leered
and buzzed at you?
You're going to have to answer for this.
I was going to say,
you're going to have to answer
to the Coca-Cola Company.
That's right.
Yeah, I guess only in this case
the Pepsi-Cola Company.
It said...
It actually said,
do not rock or tilt.
Well, Mr. High-Voluntan, High-Minded.
Here goes a whole cultural movement
starting in the late 90s.
Yeah.
In the 1940s and going up to today.
You can't rock or tilt.
When I tried to...
I started pushing buttons on it.
That's what it said.
It said warning, eh?
My sensors indicate
an intruder is present.
This machine is too high-tech, you know.
I think we should take
a Phillips screwdriver
and take it down to the side.
Danger, danger.
Not too late.
You got it coming to you.
So a bend-over, a bend-over machine.
Well, on the other hand, once again...
Danger, danger, Will Robinson.
This is hurting my...
Now he's got my name wrong.
The thing is...
My power cells are extremely low.
Oh, that was the problem.
It did say it was out.
Yes, it said that to me.
It's out of everything that it's selling.
Then why does it keep the money?
Exactly.
Well, I know why.
Same reason we do.
Now, did you notice
there was a tunnel in the basement?
It just doesn't seem fair somehow.
But when you walked away from the machine,
did you or did you not notice
a strange sensation,
a feeling that it was already...
It was only June 15th.
Yesterday was the 27th.
And today was...
And that you had to get the papers done
before Dr. Mesmer came back.
And then you realized
that the machine had probably been...
How could a machine lie to you?
They don't lie.
They don't really...
They can't fabricate
because they don't create.
It's an instrument of the con.
They are designed by humans
and they interact with humans.
And this can include...
I think that...
I think that cut machine is coming down the hall.
It's a Pepsi machine.
The Pepsi...
It's...
It's rolling forward.
It's rocking back and forth,
rolling towards us.
Well, we're safe here.
I thought it was just a gun
that was there most of the time.
No.
It seems to have a built-in
flamethrower.
Shoot it with a laser.
Or a lighter.
I told you that thing
was too high-tech.
Why couldn't they just have
a cooler with a refrigerator coil
and you put 25 cents in it?
Oh, well.
Look at the vibrations in my water.
Look at that.
It's feeling the glass
with its little extended palps there.
It's trying to figure out
how to get in.
Somebody put a flower
in the gun barrel.
It was only...
It's only a dollar 25.
Look at this thing.
Well, and you see,
I thought I had better quit
while I was not too far behind.
This whole thing is similar
to what's happening.
I've broken my glasses.
I've had various disasters.
And it's just because
the conspiracy is gearing up
for the final struggle.
And now they've sent
this ridiculous rolling refrigerator.
I think we're fairly safe in here
and we can give it the old raspberry.
Although we're going to have to
get out of here
when the show starts.
The show is over.
Food is not allowed in the studio.
Yes, it should know that.
Have you ever heard of
Purity of Essence, Mandrake?
Why?
Have you ever heard of
Purity of Mandrake, Hemlock?
Mandrake, Hemlock?
Heimlich?
Unheimlich Maneuver.
Heimlich Maneuver.
He was one of the first
in the movement.
That was the very first
card carrier.
And do you remember
the Fuhrer was number eight?
Unheimlich, yes.
He was in a Fuhrer
about that.
He liquidated
that later date
Heimlich Maneuver.
On the other hand,
that's part of the whole deal
with those natty Nazis
and their uniforms.
The idea was that
the main guy
would appear to be
not really main
but slightly standing
off to the side.
So everyone got
a super spiffy Nazi uniform
except for Hitler
who was rather plain,
you know,
as if he didn't need one.
And he wasn't
party member number one.
He was party member number two.
He was party member number eight.
Yeah, sure he was.
Well, I wonder
who else in this room
would have a little bit
in common with
good old Reverend Adolf.
I'm not sure
I understand your meaning.
They saved Hitler's mustache.
An Allied Artists production.
I'm a mere reverend,
not a doctor nor a pope.
I just serve under Bob.
That's very good.
When you sit next to me
at the X-Day stage
during the live hours of Slack,
you're usually dressed
in a,
you know,
a,
sort of a,
a gentleman's
suit,
a uniform,
whereas I'm sitting there
with some
threadbare Bob t-shirt.
Well, this year,
unless it's too hot,
we may have
Papa Joe Mama
sitting there
in a full uniformed
splendid...
That's right.
Papa Joe Mama,
we have just learned
this week,
will be
at X-Day 14.
to bring his
Schutzstaffel special
with the,
the shiny boots
and high-crowned hat,
you know,
that'll really shock
the Bobbies.
I love the music as well.
Yes.
It makes me weep.
They have complained.
We've gotten complaints
when Papa Joe showed up
in his full authentic
SS uniform.
Yes, but that was
at Brushwood.
Wisteria hasn't been
exposed to this side
of the Church of the Subgenius.
There's no hysteria
at Wisteria.
We're going to show them
the strange range
of subgeniuses.
You know,
they're not all
peaceful,
cud-chewing hippies
by a long shot.
The Reverend
Sturmund Drang.
Yes.
No, that was
Stang and Drummond.
Well, it still
sounds like
they're pure police.
They copied
that original
Two Cool Guys Club.
They were two salesmen
ranging the country,
drummers,
as they were called.
And there were
some brain clones
thrown into the mix
down in Peru
or somewhere
in South America
as far as anyone knows.
Look, I'll get back
to you in half an hour.
I've got to remove
my bus.
Ayahuasca
all over the place.
Well,
I guess
we all need
to get in shape,
you know,
do your exercises,
get prepped
because it'll be
strenuous to slide
over the spillway
into the new world
that's coming.
Sure will.
We'll be like
those tiny little
hyundais
in the great tsunami.
Yes,
tossed away
like some kids
wound up a car.
The raw power
of nature
against the
pitiable power
of man
or woman.
Yep.
It's,
uh,
nothing I would
like to be
in front of.
The powerful
hyundais.
I don't remember
you in front
of this place
before.
What are you doing
there standing
with that weird
fez with the
one eyeball in it?
Well,
you got something
you want to say
to me?
Hey,
look,
listen,
see,
now watch.
Get that hand
away from your
pocket.
You holding
a heater?
No,
I was just
easing myself
there.
Listen,
I wanted to say
this whole thing
is an opportunity
for us to
redeem the
entire mass
of mankind
in one,
final,
convulsive
moment.
Uh,
like the
inarticulomortis
doctrine,
where at the
end of a life
of sin,
you get to
go to heaven
anyway.
This is our
chance to
make it right
in the last
moments before
the entire
thing is
crushed and
blown away.
Unless,
of course,
someone does
go back in
time and
indeed kills
Bob and
conquers the
singular paradox
theory we've
encountered since
this last
week.
Oh,
we've tried
that,
Duff.
A thousand
times.
And it puts
wear and tear
on the
continuum,
and those
wormholes
look tatty
and not
fashionable.
Strings keep
popping up
everywhere and
popping down.
The gears
get loose
and the
mainsprings
sproings out.
Ever wonder
why things
look so
tacky these
days?
Half the
businesses are
closed,
except for
the churches,
liquor stores,
and hair salons
and subgenius
churches.
And the
Ask Dr.
Howell show.
Coming to you
in San Francisco
and on Radio
Valencia FM.
See Ask
Dr.
Howell dot com.
See the
giant flying
bat at a
time when
centaurs
walked the
earth.
Hercules at
the center of
the earth
versus
Goliath and
the dragon
Magog.
Starring
Luciana
Paluzzi,
riveting beauty
of the city,
and Carl
Teeters as
the son of
Zeus.
Hercules.
I told you
before,
this was the
will of
Thera,
and also
of Artemis,
and the
Welians.
And remember,
if we step
back one foot
from this
shore,
Greece will
never retain
its glory.
What are you
saying?
Surely we
cannot go
against Hercules.
Hmm,
yes.
I do not
mock the
Persians.
I mock their
breasts and
their unusual
haircuts.
In the first
place,
what do they
do thinking
they are
crossing the
Aegean Sea
the way they
do think
they are
doing?
Pardon me,
my lord,
a message
from the
octopus.
This helmet
makes me
talk funny.
Take off
your helm
in the
presence of
your lord.
His head!
I stand
before you,
sire,
hoping that
I can
conquer
Macedonia
on my
own.
With this
fragile foot
and my
lack of
wings,
I still
I shall
perform the
task you
ask of
me.
Give him
wine and
garum paste
to eat,
and let him
recline upon
this couch
surrounded with
soft Lydian
airs.
For he has
done well.
The luscious
Lucian de
Pazzarati
is the
queen of
Herpiman.
Hello,
big boy.
Stop!
Do not
touch that
false
enchantress.
She is
evil
and corrupt.
Look,
sire,
it is gold.
Hermites is
right.
It's all
gold.
We're rich,
sire.
But I can't
even eat a
bean,
you fool,
before it
turns into
gold as it
strikes me
in the lips.
This is the
longest trailer
I've ever
heard.
See,
Hercules versus
the moon man,
or whatever it
is,
in this
theater.
In Censoround,
Cinemascope,
Regiscope,
Fantomation,
and Dynaflow.
Also in
Ridiculous Comet,
issue 14 to
45.
It's in
8D.
No one
will be
admitted during
the first
72 minutes
of this
motion picture.
The last
century has
been scoped
and kept
for your
cultural
disbelief.
With exciting
co-hit,
Mommy and
the Ogre.
Mommy,
who's
that funny
man?
Why,
it's
someone who
owes your
father an
awful lot
of money,
honey.
Pay up.
I'd like
to talk
to you about
Miss Wellesley.
Since her
release from
the institution
last month,
we've had
numerous
complaints.
I was wondering
if you would
speak to her
at least about
these outbursts.
The poor
girl lives in
a blinded
world of her
own making.
No one can
crack that
shell and get
to the runny
meat inside.
She's been
ironing
the wrinkled
ascot and it
just won't
come straight.
But how can
we know she's
not having us
all on?
Maybe she's
having the
last laugh.
It's true.
It could be.
Damn you,
Mrs. Finzer.
This is not
an ascot.
I prescribe
lobotomy.
I'm for
thrallbots
didn't it?
Please,
death.
Wait a minute,
did you say
thrallbots?
Yes,
thrallbots,
who do
my bidding
as I command
in thrall.
The new
enemies of
the Transformers
and the
gobots.
And the
Decepticons
and the
Johnsons
Smiths.
Yeah,
right.
The Martins
and the
Coys.
We've
expended
them all
and rightfully
so because
they did
not deserve
to die
for it.
The Grangerfords
and the
Shepherdsons.
The Kulots
and the
Hamburgers.
I mean,
it was the
Kulots
and the
Georgian
seafaring
people,
the ones
with no
eyes.
You remember
them all,
don't you?
Yes,
I remember
those who
used to be
here.
Who could
forget?
Now only
these effigies
remain.
The Heelots.
A lot
of heels.
Spear carriers.
Sandal wearers.
And people
with no
foreskins.
Yes,
or aftskins.
Strangely
exposed
to fate
and its
vagaries.
It's a
change not
only in
this dimension
but all
the dimensions
around it.
Don't you
understand what
you're messing
with?
Can't you
understand you
might be
destroying not
only this
world but
every possible
world to
come?
We have to
take that
chance.
Especially
while the
mighty
army
of Lars
Porsena of
Clusium is
in the
field and
advancing upon
us.
So we have
to break a
few rules.
Let loose
a few
outmoded
laws and
ordinances.
This is
full-scale
war against
a ruthless
enemy.
Listen guys,
I know a lot
of you don't
like the idea
of not only
training so
hard and so
long but
wearing the
new orifices
we're forcing
you to wear.
I know
they're
cumbersome
and they
don't feel
right.
Sometimes
they hit
you in the
wrong places
but I'm
telling you
they're just
like your
buddy system
and knowing
your weapon.
They're there
to save your
life.
Because where
we're going
no one
wants to
go.
And that's
why we
got to
go.
Because we
don't want
to go.
If you
want to
go somewhere
then you
can't go
there.
But somehow
I don't
know how
this works
out.
If you
don't want
to go
there then
you got to
go there.
But then
of course
if you
could somehow
fix it in
your mind
where you
both didn't
want to
go there
and go
there and
go there
and didn't
at the
same time
then the
problem
might be
never mind
dismissed.
Just don't
fling me
into that
briar patch
officer.
Just don't
throw me
into subgenius
hell lord.
That's right
I sure don't
want to go
there.
I'd rather
be in
Christian
heaven
wouldn't
you?
Did you
not
praise Bob
during your
life and
serve his
church
when you
could just
as well
have served
the lord
here in
heaven?
Well yes
lord it's
true.
I'd like to
play back
the tapes
of this
show right
now.
It's true
lord just
don't throw
me into
subgenius
hell.
Don't
throw me
into where
all those
people are
partying
all those
young
attractive
folks
all grappling
with each
other.
His name
does not
appear lord.
Then I
say unto
you
depart from
me ye
unclean
spirit into
the eternal
hideous fire
prepared for
Satan
and his
fallen angel
buddies right
through that
suspicious
looking tunnel
with the smoke
coming out of
it forever
and forever
for I
thy god
am a jealous
god.
Although I
am so
senile I've
forgotten what
I'm even
jealous of.
It doesn't
matter.
You have to
walk that
lonesome road
into the
flaming pit
which my
boy
Yeshua
cooked up
for you.
This thing
God's got
himself into
a whole
peck of
peckerel
trouble
as Miss
Annie and
Jumberline
trying to
figure out
the order
of the
saints.
They search
out an old
obscure volume
called
Lives of the
Saints
but they
can't seem
to figure
out the
bibliography.
Well we
join them
now as
the fun
begins.
Honey
how am I
going to
tithe by
Saint
Swithin's
Day?
I'm all
out.
He's
schizophrenic?
Me?
No.
Who?
Why don't
you calm
down and
say your
beads and
I'll look
up in the
eschatological
calendar if
it's alright
to use
the back
shed today.
What's
the beads?
Am I
a bead?
Who's
the
scotch
a
lot
in
New
England?
It's the
eschatology
that's
what we're
talking about
the end
times and
scatology
refers to
what goes
on in the
back shed.
Damn you
I told you
I'm getting
a little bit
up there
in aeons
and so
forth and
so forth.
What else
was I
telling you?
I'm
jealous.
That
twice battered
god of
Palestine
Lord
deal as
you did
with him.
Remember
when Dagon
was sassy
to you
and you
knocked over
the statue
of Dagon
and then
they set
it up again
and then
you knocked
it over
and broke
it into
two parts?
That showed
the Midianites
a thing or
two.
Yeah Midianites
whatever
did we
batter dip
and deep
fry them?
Yeah they're
gone.
They're
all gone.
With
Nineveh
and Tyre.
trying to get
there and
made a
flood and
so forth?
Now you
are getting
on in
years but
you did
say you
wouldn't
send another
flood since
you did
that the
last time.
You said
that next
time it
would be
the fire.
Oh that's
right.
Fire.
I like
fire.
It's
really hot.
hotter every
day.
I think
all but
the most
blinkered
blinders
wearers
can see
the
grizzly
frizzling
shape
of the
inflamed
future.
Oh boy.
I can
we're
talking
about
again.
Exists
they're
going to
pour on
the heat.
The
subgeniuses
are going
to be
down there
barbecuing
and then
the
exists
are going
to begin
the grand
barbecue
in which
all will
fly up
to heaven
in flame
and smoke.
I get
the credit
though.
Remember
I'm
jealous
right?
Yeah
sure
Jehovah
we can
just fly
away and
watch you
manage
your
burned up
compost
pile
and say
thanks
for the
memories.
You know
I never
thought we'd
have Jehovah
One on
the show
and I
thought he'd
be taller.
Well you
know he
was once.
Let's give
him credit
where credit
due.
Maybe he
didn't even
shrink.
Maybe man
just got a
little more
bloated and
large.
Well if we
believe the
teachings of
the Vedas
that means
he is the
substance of
memory itself.
He is beyond
all memory.
How could he
lose his
memory and
act like a
feeble-minded
duttering fool
like that?
That's under
Hindus and
don'ts.
I cannot
find it here.
Well be
under the
altar.
of the
many-armed
statue of
the deathless
eater of
Saul.
I wish
you well
but I
can't see
what you're
talking about.
Better bring
me around
somewhere.
Oh my.
Well I
guess I'm
a little bit
behind in
my churchly
duties but
there'll be
a nice long
interval where
I can do
all my
devotions and
get right
with the
pantheon.
Nothing like
it.
Getting right
with the
pantheon.
I remember
it was,
I think it
was the
day of the
great snake.
We're all
hunkered down
for a barbecue
afternoon and
one of the
bigger children
began slaughtering
all of the
smaller children.
Now Mammy and
Pappy didn't
exactly go for
that.
They'd had
plenty of
children before.
They called
them the
beast with
a thousand
breasts,
so to speak.
That means
a thousand
generation upon
generation
intermixing and
kind of making
themselves a little
bit genetically
impaired but
that's another
story.
I guess that's
the fighting
spirit in
them.
But I'll
return my
vigor someday
and when I
find it I'm
going to
shoot it down
the drain and
cry.
Well it's
good to have
aspirations and
hopes of
however
inadequate their
chance of
being realized
for without
that we are
truly stopped,
defeated and
blinded.
We have to
compartmentalize
is what we
have to do
especially if we
realize some
things that we've
always wanted are
never going to
happen.
We have to
find out new
reasons to go
on.
New shapes we
still may weave.
New laws,
new gods
receive.
Smooth ascots.
Janet.
New popes.
Janet,
you've got my
ascot and my
aspirations for a
new world.
What's wrong
with you?
Has father been
lying to you
again?
What's wrong
with your
pants?
You're supposed
to be dressed
like a man
again.
I forgot to
bring those
special pants.
I just
remembered.
Oh, now I
am.
What has
happened to
your nose?
I've just
returned from
Rome.
There was a
nose there
once.
Yes, this
was once a
nose that all
the world
could behold.
But now his
nose is thin
and it rests
upon his chin
like a staff
and a crick
is in his
back and a
melancholy
crack in his
laugh.
The mossy
marbles rest
on the lips
that he had
pressed in
their bloom
and the
names he
loved to
hear have
been carved
for many
a year
on the
tomb.
So now
he walks
the streets
and he
looks at
all he
meets
all for
long and
he shakes
his weary
head so
it seems
as if he
said they
are gone.
Blasted
with antiquity
super
annuated
with extreme
age and
eld
palsied
shaking
feeble
piping
with his
lisping
voice
and faltering
shaking
roomy
eyesight.
Now
Puck Black
isn't that
bad.
No I
guess not.
He's in
bad shape.
He's actually
only 22
years old
but he's
done a lot
of hard
living.
Yeah
Governor
can you
spare me
23 more?
Get away
from me
you uncouth
being.
Please
please
some
cutter
for me
brother.
Where
are you?
Are the
police
at times
like this?
Really
I can't
be bothered
by these
street
urchins.
Constable?
What seems
to be
going on
here?
What's
all this
about
Vinay?
Well
the street
Arab
was sassing
me
officer
I think.
I wasn't
doing
nothing.
Oh another
sassy Arab
eh?
That's right.
Blank
why did
you go
back
where you
came from?
Innocent
I'm telling
you I'm
innocent.
And who
are you
Vinay?
Can I
see some
identification
here please?
I'm
totally
innocent
nothing.
I don't
see that
on your
driver's
license.
Wow.
it looks
like a
mandrill
head.
Who
took this
picture?
It's
the sign
of the
rabid
baboon.
Ah
a sign
we've been
waiting for
for so long.
The sign
of the
rabid
baboon.
Yes
it's time.
Ranging
in the
east
pounding
the earth
creating
a cacophony
of
mistrials
and
misguided
efforts.
Nobody
knows the
trouble I
seen.
Nobody
knows.
Did you
hit him
hard son?
Did you
get mean
mad?
Well I
came out
swinging and
I landed
a few
good punches
but on
the whole
I was
steamrollered.
I haven't
been holding
my own
lately.
I have
been swept
backward by
the overwhelming
current but
as I was
saying earlier
or trying to
say we
should all
expect a
little of
this.
The
resistance.
demonic
resistance
trying to
keep us
from
getting to
the
assembly
point to
the
nexus
of
X-Day.
You
have to
walk
forward
against
that
wind.
What's
that
bruise
above
your
third
eye
son?
You
look like
you've
been in
a hell
of a
fight.
Well I'm
sorry you
noticed that.
That was
I ran
into the
end of a
door actually.
I thought it
was Ash
Wednesday.
Well maybe
it was.
I can't
even
I have
to consult
my notes
to figure
out
exactly.
I'm
somewhat
confused
as to
the
calendar.
Well there
was something
in the
ashes
son.
That's
the only
problem.
Oh yeah?
You came
in and
got your
dust in
all right
but it
might dust
you off
if you
know what
I mean.
I thought
it was a
little
leaden
heart
that
wouldn't
melt
even
in the
middle
of the
fire.
Everything
else
ashes
but
this
little
coal
black
heart
was all
that
remained.
You know
the burning
of the
subgenius
icon
at X-Day
this year
we're
not
going to
you know
we're
rebooting
the
franchise.
This is
like X-Day
2.
It's
like the
new
Star Trek.
It's
not just
Ginebrum's
directed.
It's
not going
to be
one of
those
Bob
icons
made of
plywood
that burns
up just
like that.
We're
actually
I believe
that
Reverend
Wilhelm
Stahlhelm
yes I
don't know
why
it makes
me
three
dimensional
flammable
Bob
designed in
such a way
that first
his clothes
burn then
his flesh
burns off
his eyes
will literally
roll out
of his
head.
He's
been designed
to have
eyes that
will roll
out of his
head and
a skeleton
that will
be left
behind.
And if
you say
the tiny
little
lead or
in this
case plutonium
heart.
I ain't
scared of
no
skillet.
And
Stan will
be doing
the familiar
pyrotechnic
displays from
his
dairy
or
ice
bone.
No
that's
chicken
John
stuff.
Banjo
Bob.
No we're
not going
to do
anything
familiar.
Nothing
will be
familiar
this time.
All that
old stuff
goes by
the boards.
It's
going out
the window.
Yeah with
the baby
and the
bath water
all of
it.
Yes don't
stand below
and we're
going to
be washed
clean and
able to
start our
new complete
reboot of
the church
of the
subgenius.
Once upon
the time
at a
next day
past
Magdalene
led the
ritual of
actually
burning the
church
itself.
Really?
And
resurrecting
it as a
zombie.
That must
have been
like five
or six
years ago.
Well it was
like one of
those little
birdhouse
churches.
That explains
a lot.
It does.
That's what
happened.
And he
crudely took
a poor
young robin
and dressed
it up like
a vicar
and burned
it alive.
There's a
couple of
robins in
here.
Who
does
that?
Who did
such a
thing?
I think
therefore I
think.
There's two
robs in here.
Hello goodbye
therefore I
think.
Well yes.
I already
explained that
if your name
is Rob
then you
are very
close to
being a
Bob.
And I
explained the
derivation of
how I
actually also
can be
Bob.
A
gnomon
designation.
Very quickly
I'll say it
again.
Nixon.
The White
House.
Watergate.
The 70s.
H.R.
Haldeman.
Nixon's
chief hatchet
man.
His name
was Harry
Robbins
Haldeman.
My name
is Harry
Robbins.
They called
him Bob
Haldeman.
Bob short
for the
Rob.
Rob in
Robbins.
Therefore if
he is
Bob I
also with
the identical
name am
Bob.
So put
that in
your pipe
and smoke
it.
What about
that?
Ain't enough
room in
this town
for both
of us
Bobs.
I think
two of
them
Bobs are
going to
have to
go.
Say.
Hey who's
been snorting
on my
whiskey
bottle?
Is it
a you
short fat
acne
bespeckled
Bob or
the tall
handsome
Bob with
straight teeth?
Does it
matter if
one is
handsome or
the other
is unappealing
as long as
they're taking
your whiskey
away?
I don't know
where to trade
a bottle of
whiskey.
That's what
I'm trying to
say Snooki.
Both of
them Bobs
have got
to go.
And who
will replace
them?
Reverend
Hyde.
Dr.
Dobbs and
Reverend Hyde.
Reverend
Jacqueline Hyde?
Yeah.
Reverend
Jacqueline Hyde
will be at
the judgment.
Well alright
then.
That's good.
We'll be in
good hands.
I think it's
going to be a
little bit
difficult for
judgment day
for a lot
of people
who have
shown
remarkably
poor skills
in judgment.
Or maybe
that's their
common
that's what
it's all
about you
know.
Forgiveness.
Atonement.
Atonement with
nothing
absolutely.
Absolutely
nothing.
Perhaps a
peculiar feeling
in the groin
area.
Hopefully for
some.
But that's
our universe.
It's mostly
composed of
absolutely
nothing.
And then in
one small
area there's
a little bit
of feeling.
An area
soon to be
made much
smaller.
But with
an increase
of feeling.
That
I can
see it
now.
A big
beautiful
world of
the afterlife
spread out
before me.
Infinite
possibilities.
Eternally
young
and vigorous.
All possibilities
open.
My knuckles
are clean.
Enough time
to learn
Portuguese
and do
everything else.
The baby
of my aunt
is on the
table
of my uncle.
I did it.
I'm a success.
Yes.
No.
How much
does it cost
to use the
lavatory?
On the
Ask Dr.
Hal show.
Yes.
The Ask Dr.
Hal show.
A special
visitor program
from Radio
Valencia FM.
Hello friends.
This is Dr.
Hal and
I.
Joining us
tonight.
On the
radio.
Doing a
special link.
Link.
Yes.
That's right.
Link with
our sister
radio station
here.
I've been
telling all of
you.
Fool followers
about the
the end of
the world
the
conflagration
that's coming
up.
Well we're
going to have
one and
this time
it's not
going to be
a dud.
Yes the
world really
is going to
end and
I'm going
to tell you
I've been
camping on
that for
some years
and it
irritates me
when these
false prophets
from their
citadels
are
proclaiming
their fake
apocalypse
when the
world really
is ending
and
why is
everyone
fooling around
to such
unacceptable
unagreeable
levels of
falderal
with some
hillbilly
radio preacher
instead of
using their
eyes to
look around
and see
the
despoiling
of our
world
which is
after all
all that
we stand
on
to keep
us from
being
tumbling
through
space
forever.
The shifting
despoils.
Well it's
something
people should
think about
it.
Instead they
have to
couch it
in quaint
and curious
rites of
primitive
savagery.
Oh a whole
bunch of
them think
they have
until 2012.
Well many
more believe
October 21st
but that's
several months
more than
they actually
get as you
know.
That's right.
Well that was
that one
interpretation.
Well they
said they
were pulling
their legs.
We just
said F
myth they
can't take
a joke
but they
said they
were pulling
their legs
and that's
what happened
as they
approached
the speed
of light.
Their legs
got a lot
longer.
But they
didn't get
any taller.
That's right.
I'd like to
remind everyone
aboard this
vessel that
the following
rules are to
be either
obeyed
vigorously
or not
obeyed at
all.
Furthermore I
would like to
remind the
passengers that
you may or
may not be
passengers upon
my own
personal women
within the
next five
seconds I
may all
have you
killed.
Where's the
holodeck buddy?
John Mayle?
That is a
mean
diamond
deed.
You're confusing
your Star Trek
generations.
Those are
first generation
background
noises.
There was
no holodeck.
I thought it
was a
holo show.
Oh well.
These are
not holograms.
Warning.
All employees
of the
subgenius
government
must present
identification
to registrar
before entering
these holodeck
grounds.
What is
acceptable
identification?
must be
presented
for
extinction.
How about
a good old
California
driver's
license?
Does that
cut the
mustard?
It's
holo X
day.
Only
those who
bear the
mark upon
the hand
and the
forehead
and that
one other
place.
You've
got to
tamp down
the reaction.
I can't
change the
laws of
physics.
Well,
the Catholics
got rid of
purgatory in
a snap of
the papal
fingers.
So that
same thing
happened to
physics
apparently.
With a
more
frothy
reaction.
We can't
make it,
Captain.
There is
that.
It's made
us.
Can't you
see?
Look at
your feet
now.
Oh,
they're rooted
to the
spot.
I always
thought that
was just
an expression.
You don't
need to
walk anymore.
No,
I've walked
too far
in somebody
else's
shoes.
Put out
branches
and acorns.
Wise
acre.
That's what
they called
you in
school.
You never
listened.
Now you
listen and
put back
all this
nonsense.
I had
to travel
my own
way in
my dad's
cast-off
Galagaskins.
Now I'm
going to
walk about
no more.
I love
the bees
around here
and the
trees and
flowers.
Bees,
trees,
flowers.
I look
often in
the distance.
There's all
my departed
relatives.
Well,
I'm not
going to
give them
anything.
Clean up
Armenia.
Get a
hair lip.
You can
help the
Armenian
Republic
continue to
exist.
I must
do is send
all your
money from
the United
States back
home to
me.
Shorban
Arzanian.
That's
Shorban
Arzanian.
The
hewn
Armenian.
He's
rough hewn
from
solid
matter.
He's a
good fella.
Kind of
chunky.
Regular
looking.
features.
What's
regular?
Well,
he's a
regular
dealer.
Has bowel
movements at
the same
time every
day.
Exactly.
There is
that.
That can
be understood.
And what
other ways
are he is
regular?
Well,
he's,
he follows
the regs.
That's for
sure.
And he
has even
features of
his face.
Yes,
that is
true.
Such a
pleasant
evenness.
Almost as
if sculpted
by some
divine
phidias.
So perfectly
symmetrical,
his heart
is directly
at the
center of
his chest
between his
lungs.
And
unfortunately,
this makes
him prone
to heart
disease.
Well,
that is
unfortunate.
But,
you know,
you give
a little,
you get
a little.
He would
have no
more
problem.
Simply
remove the
heart,
place within
the use
of the
parts of
the brain
to
reconclude
or
capitulate
a new
form of
heart and
perhaps just
pour gasoline
on him and
set him
on fire.
It's
neither left-handed
nor right-handed,
but begins
each line
of text
on the
opposite ends
of the page,
writing with
both hands.
And that
brings us
to the
end of
this
particular
first
hour of
Slack.
What?
Yes,
we've been
recording for
exactly one
hour.
Friends,
if you
have to
have more
information
about the
Church of
the
Subgenius,
the Ask
Dr.
Howell
Show,
or the
Lonesome
Cowboy
Dave
Purgatory,
feel free
to
investigate
www.subgenius.com.
Stay tuned
for the
next show,
which follows
at some
point.
In some
way,
shape,
or form.