From PR News in Washington, I'm happening at this hour.
The White House is reimposing multiple PR news on Iran after a powerful earthquake struck Indonesia last night.
The newly reimposed PR news will affect Iran's automotive sector as well as Washington.
The city of Charlottesville, Virginia, left one person dead.
The doubt was 39-25-5-2-47-10.
The White House reports you're listening to PR News and you're listening in Washington.
The New World Order, as it marches down to the final battle,
where Satan and his communist anti-Christ forces are gathered in power and might and wisdom and knowledge and wealth
to attack the subgenius power of Satan.
The New World Order, as it marches down to the final battle,
where Satan and his communist anti-Christ forces are gathered in power and might and wisdom and knowledge and wealth
to attack the subgenius power of Satan.
I'm gonna Google you.
You'd be surprised to know just what you can find
about a person if you have enough time.
A little number unlocks a lot.
And I found it. Hooray, I found it.
Now that I know just what you want in a man,
I'll go remake myself the best as I can.
I'll be complete.
So when we meet you can't resist me,
but you can't resist me.
Change up wardrobe and my music.
Don't like goatees, I can lose it.
Learn to play the blues if I have time.
Fill my iPod up with Lenny Kravitz.
Get my head on up like rapid.
Never gonna quit until you're mine.
I'm reading all that I can.
I soak up all that I read.
I'll become all that you need.
A million.
Why don't you take a chance?
Come on, give me a try.
I'll be your perfect guy.
One in a million.
You've got no secrets.
At least none you need to hide from me.
Ooh, I don't believe it.
Your mother lives right down the street.
I can't wait to get to know you.
Hope you take the best of things I wanna show you.
Open that computer room.
By the light of the Gatot ray tube.
And I bet that you'd be flattered too.
You know I could own you.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
And I thought you'd give it up.
But I'm just gonna leave it.
I can't move to the room.
Oh, ooh, oh.
I deliberate.
And I've had to take this one.
Oh, ooh.
The gaping number of chili pepper plants keeps on growing and erasing me.
I've had so much the joy of getting them.
I missдуct for that popcorn.
ooh, ooh, ooh.
Daddy,
it's so much fun to have the baby home.
though the things you're doing to me
I know some things will come and go.
...
Too much fun at X Day.
You guys had the overload where you're like,
I'm not sure I can have any more fun or I might die.
It's a psychedelic endurance test.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Endurance is not the word.
Ken Kesey has nothing on us.
No, not at all.
Part of X Day is hanging around and trying to prove that you can be on more stuff
and act less like you're on any stuff at all than all of your friends can
because you've got to be number one dope fiend.
Yeah, but this is not a required practice.
It actually takes a membership in the church that is at a doctored level.
Once you get $35, once you pay your $35 to Bob,
your tolerance to every chemical-nosed man is increased by 50%.
Triples.
Quadruples.
Your consumption levels are just amazing.
Sugar tastes sweeter.
One thing that our listeners who are stupid and don't come to X Day
might not realize is how clean subgeniuses actually are, apart from the smell.
When I first came to X Day, I thought that by the end of my experience with Steary
it would be just a Mad Max-like wasteland of cigarette butts and beer cans
and Susie's armpit hair.
We do have all of those things.
In far less numbers than one would expect.
Goddamn garden of delight.
Cigarette can... cigarette tree...
The beer trees are growing, but they're just little cans.
They're not full yet.
They're right over there by the spam trees.
Can't pluck them yet.
There's cans of beer right next to the spam trees.
There are many cans of beer here at X Day.
We could... with what... the consumption levels here are amazing.
Most people don't know that three weeks before X Day starts,
we come and we...
We plant two beers.
When X Day starts, you have all the plethora of beer that you see
because it's a quick-yielding fruit.
You can see one growing out of the ground right there.
We didn't get that when we picked it.
And you'll see them sprouting throughout the camp
and that's all of the hard work of your pre-X Day people
who come out and plant those beers.
Right, look, there's two right now.
They're like tribbles, actually.
They'll have a safety team come in after the fact
and eradicate the beer plants.
Just little guys.
Couple little guys.
Couple beer guys.
Couple more beer guys.
Just hanging out.
They're not full yet.
They may have been once, but there is a belief at X Day
that if you leave your beer cans sitting on the table at Caffeina's overnight,
they will refill themselves and be cold in the morning.
This belief is, of course, entirely fictitious,
but it appears that many, many subgeniuses believe it.
I absolutely believe it.
It's absolutely true.
I have engaged in the practice and found...
But, you know, I just can't...
I can't give up trying.
You, sir, are a known deceiver.
The beer fairy is among us.
Man, look at her eat that.
I didn't know you could do Disney voices so well, Danny.
Yeah, I can do all kinds of voices for you.
That's crazy.
You ever heard your mom's voice come out of my mouth?
Well, now...
She doesn't like to share those tapes with me,
so I've only seen it once.
The thing is, I don't know if I can properly emulate the way you hear it,
because I hear it in such a different context,
than you do, P's.
I'm muffled by her thighs.
Yeah, your mom sounds like...
I hope you're listening, Mom.
I'm so proud.
This is your son.
This is what you made.
I finally made the big time.
And this is his friend, talking about him.
I can't hear you, Susie.
I have headphones on.
Don't talk to me.
Top of the world.
Just sorry.
X-Day is like the Titanic.
It has a robot stang.
Now, here's the robot stang moving the table.
Who's ever seen stang move anything before?
Speaking of the Titanic, you know, with how good it looks,
I bet that robot stang was built by Jimmy Cameron.
Little Jimmy Cameron himself.
I wonder if Princess Wee had any insight or input
into the designs of the robot stang.
I heard once that there was an attempt made
to create a subgenius X-Day documentary in 3D,
and that there were actually...
It was a film crew here with 3D cameras,
and perhaps it was...
That wasn't...
That...
The documentary was a front for...
Bobo's easy.
James Cameron's attempts to create a false stang.
Under the orders, the directives of the notorious,
hyper-genius,
Fid Chooley.
Fid Chooley is the mastermind behind everything that's gone wrong.
If Fid Chooley was the mastermind behind this,
there would be more circus music.
No.
We know that Fid Chooley has spared no expense
to have a complex built in the woods
where he now controls everything that's going wrong with X-Day,
in order to befuddle and bemuse Argus Fox.
This battle of wills between Fid Chooley and Argus Fox
has carried on for many years,
but we're not sure what's going to happen.
He seems to have outspent Argus this year.
I'll tell you one thing about Fid Chooley.
He's a terrible dancer and a terrible singer.
Yes.
But he was so well disguised that no one knew
that it was Fid Chooley in disguise.
One man knew.
One brave soul stood against the rest and said,
No, that person is Fid Chooley in disguise.
And the person who enlightened us and opened our eyes,
that was one Argus Fox.
Sound man and general wizard of the Church of the Subgenius
and proprietor of Hypercube Laboratories and Dobbslayer.
Bob Killer.
That man there.
And they're in the anals of Bob.
Just like...
But we all have a chance to kill Bob every day.
Every day.
You may see a Bob.
I can't hear you, Argus Fox.
I'm wearing headphones.
Don't talk to me.
Don't talk to me, Susie.
I told you once.
Jesus.
Subgeniuses.
They can't hear you when you're yelling at them
through a PA system.
Eight feet away.
Well, technically, we should have a mic that's pointing towards the audience.
I'm not going to repeat that on the air because it was self-deprecating
and I wouldn't want to say anything bad about Susie the Flusie on the air
because she has the second best subgenius radio show
right after the Thor's Eater and Podcrest,
but above the hour of slack.
We could point the microphone towards the crowd
to get these important questions asked and yet answered.
Shut up, peace.
It would be something getting some questions answered.
Here comes Robot Sand.
Shut up, peace.
Everybody play.
Isn't it cool?
Shut up, peace.
Hi, Stang.
Yeah.
Is that hot?
Robot Stang.
Robot Stang, yeah.
Yeah, look at him.
He's doing the thing.
He acts like he has human affection.
There's nothing wrong.
We're making the numbers.
See, he's a robot.
He wants to know if his machine is making numbers.
All he wants to know is his machine making numbers.
Beep, boop, beep, boop.
Beep the hamburger.
Hell out of there.
Hamburger not found.
That's pretty much all life is.
Counting numbers, right?
Yeah.
They teach you to count and you never stop counting.
Robot Stang, he's fooled us all.
Not me.
Robot Stang, Chicago.
Not Argus Fox.
The weird thing about robots is they think they're so smart,
but they really can only count zeros and ones.
Right.
How smart is that?
They only know two numbers, but everybody thinks they're so smart.
It's because they can do it whapping fast.
Shhh.
Stupid.
Idiots.
Dumb machines.
Who needs them?
Why are they good for you?
You tell them what to do.
They're not dumb.
It's the humans.
When you're at X Day, you realize how little you need machines in your life
because you sure ain't going to be using your phone if it uses cell towers,
which a funny thing about phones.
You'd be better off.
And Dr. Cosmack, the Hypercube Laboratories lead technician,
can tell you that cell phones use cell towers.
It's an interesting thing.
You learn a lot at X Day.
Do you?
Do you really?
I have actually learned nothing,
and I will continue to do so.
I have learned so much about nothing
that I don't think I could have any more knowledge of nothing put into my brain.
My learning capabilities have been overtaxed.
That happened 30 years ago, Eggplant.
Don't laugh at that, Pease, unless it's a knowing laugh of,
ah, yes, I also can't remember shit.
I sailed that ship with you too, Captain.
There's dark waters ahead.
See, the trick with father figures I've learned
is you've got to make them feel,
that you're disappointed in them.
You've got to beat them to the punch.
You've got to gaslight your dad, people.
That's what life's all about.
It's about getting that old man
and turning the tables on him.
Step by step, you can say that.
How'd you get that bear?
A bear did just run by,
but we chased it away through our prayers and hopes and dreams.
I clearly saw someone bring you a frosty cold beer.
I need a beer garden.
I'd like a beer garden right here.
Well, we've been,
Subgenius has been attempting to plant a beer garden here
at Wisteria for years.
And this was the first harvest that we had,
so we're very excited.
A bear hasn't sprouted in front of me,
and I'm growing rather sad.
Argus Fox, Bob Killer.
. . .
前 ever speed
I'm the king of rock
There's none higher
All the rads on fire
Tough as hell
Ur routes are work,
I'm the king of the world
Exhaust the 겁
No more
EBO
This is life
Why are you just crying?
I can't smoke
Just here're playing
But It's an Therweise
We're a band
Thank you with love
Back in 1955
Stay the Big Shanks!
And the beginning
Back in 1955
Man didn't know about a rock and roll show
No, that's right
Black men had the smokes
Black men had the booze
No one knew what they was gonna do
But Tchaikovsky had the blues
Oh, let me be rocked
What do you want?
You just don't know what I want
I want rock and roll
I love rock and roll
Come here, rock and roll
Put a lot of time in a jukebox, baby
Rockin' ages
Spill it out
Keep on rollin'
Rockin' ages
Realize you're living in the golden years
You can't beat me, I'm a rock star
I'm riding on the top of a car car
When the revel in my full foam pops far
It's almost over now
And it came to pass
That rock and roll was born
Rocked Pops and Land, every rock and land
The throwing up the stone
And the guitar man got famous
The guitar man got rich
And everybody was a superstar
Oh, let me be rocked
What do you want?
You just don't know what I want
I want rock and roll
I love rock and roll
Come here, rock and roll
Put a lot of time in a jukebox, baby
Rockin' ages
Rock and roll, yeah!
Still rollin'
Keep on rollin'
Rockin' ages
Realize you're living in the golden years
We will, we will rock you
No sling tail
Riders on the storm
Into this house we're born
Into this world we're thrown
Like a dog without a bone
An actor out on loan
Riders on the storm
And the music was good
And the music was loud
So let's rock
Get it back
To the wall
What is this
Fuck off to the wall
Hiss-hiss
Nothing is the answer
Too late
Dance
Yes, yes
Force to the wall
Oh lord, yeah
Rock of Ages
Still rolling
Keep on rolling
Rock of Ages
Realize you're living in the golden years
Still rolling
Keep on rolling
Rock of Ages
Still rolling
Keep on rolling
Rock of Ages
Yeah
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Pretty amazing, huh?
That was something by, I think, an entity called Dido or Dedo.
It's a mashup of Led Zeppelin versus Rolling Stones versus Run DMC versus Chemical Brothers versus Def Leppard and a whole bunch of other stuff.
Man, move over, girl talk, holy cow.
Yeah, rock of ages.
Again, I think the mashup artist is named Dido.
Dido, something I pulled off of YouTube as a result of a link suggestion by Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Goodness.
Who had scooped up a whole bunch of those mashup type things.
Amazing.
Yeah.
Before that, we heard a little bit of some pod crust from X Day 20 a couple of years ago.
Some unheard.
But really subgeniously, X Day live radio by Reverend Shawgoth, Reverend Pease, and Reverend Eggplant.
And the song at the beginning was Chameleon by Liberty Tubes.
That's the one that goes, I'm going to Google you.
That's St. Andrew the Impaled.
First time we've heard it.
Studio version.
That was great.
I loved it.
And as almost always, the titles, PR news, and any collages are by the great Fernanda Nandy Lee Murr.
And yes, yes, yes, friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1744.
The way we're numbering these for release to the other stations and the internet.
The music in the background, incidentally, I left all my stuff at home.
But I found something at the station called Amsterdam Bach Soloists Live in Concert.
And they're doing a sonata.
A D minor by Johann Fosch right now.
Oh, they never do any Bach on this.
They do Locatelli, Haydn, and Mozart, but no Bach.
And yet they're called the Amsterdam Bach Soloists.
Humph.
Street band in Amsterdam.
Princess, we and I have enjoyed string quartets.
We've been performing on the streets of ancient European cities.
Yes, thanks to Tonya and Bucky.
Reverend Bucky and Reverend Tonya.
We're really, really, really lucky.
The best.
Oh, and I was going to say, another thing that makes us lucky is all the other stations that play this show.
I don't usually have the list in front of me, although I realize tonight that it's on the internet.
It's on subgenius.com in the radio section.
But thank you so much, these other stations that we mail CDs to.
Because, well, yeah, we could use MP3s and do it all by downloading, but the quality isn't there.
We insist on full CD quality.
And that would include WLSL in Dade City, Florida.
WCNI in New London, Connecticut.
Of course, WREK in Atlanta, Georgia.
Of course, WORT in Madison.
And WOZO in Knoxville.
And there may even be a WMPG in Portland still playing.
I don't know.
But now we have a Dave, I think.
You nearly think staying.
You just reflect openly.
And so be it.
I wished for a Dave, and so it appears.
It's the real Dave.
I can tell.
I can hear it in his voice.
It's Dave.
Can you smell my turban, too?
You have a turban, Dave?
Of course I'm wearing a turban.
Don't I always?
I didn't know.
With kind of like a phallus-shaped forehead and a ring-a-lario.
Hee-haw.
Dave, we don't really actively smell your turban all the way from Ashtabula, D.C.
to Cleveland, but the memory of it is so very, very real and vivid.
It is as if we smell your turban night and day all the time.
It is a medal.
Thank you so much for saying that.
Because if I could give people medals of honor for smelling my turban at a distance
through their memory, I mean, using their memory.
I know what you mean.
I know what you mean, buddy.
Scent memory is the strongest of all memories.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Scent memory is the strongest of all the sensory memories, isn't it?
No wonder that pimple got so fast.
Well, it's why whenever I walk by an elementary school and whiff those industrial hamburgers
in the cafeteria.
Oh.
Or I used to.
God, it would take me back.
I could remember every math lesson, which I can't possibly remember now.
And all those friends of mine.
Yes.
Diagramming sentences.
Well, I'm mainly thinking about all the girls I had crushes on, which was...
Every one of them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sooner or later.
Every single one.
Then one of them finally agrees to go somewhere with you and you screw it up because you can't
talk and you get real scared and nervous.
Yeah, and that didn't happen until I was 18.
And then I still got married.
That's a high number, but you still qualify.
Well, I'm afraid I'm like most other nerd fellas, if they'd really admit it.
Lucky.
Lucky indeed.
Yes, lucky.
As lucky as a pork chop on a spindle, I might say.
Oh, a lot luckier than the pork chop or the pig it came from, although we all end up on
the spindle sooner or later in the barrel.
I'm going to race to avoid being coming part pig.
Rotating.
Sometimes.
Rotating on the spit in the barrel like one of those logo pigs that's slicing his own
meat off of himself and eating a pork wrap with a big smile on his face.
Yeah, wearing it like children, you know, laughing and smiling in the park and listening
to the birds hum.
Pigs don't really...
Can't stand when they do that.
Pigs don't really want us to slice.
They don't want us to slice them up and eat them.
But schmoos do.
But of course, you know, the conspiracy outlawed schmoos as soon as they knew what they were,
so nobody knows what they are.
My parents used to call me schmoo when I was like a toddler.
Oh, Dr. Sinister came in here.
Yeah, but you weren't fat, Dr. Sinister.
The original schmoos had a belly on them.
Well, I have a belly on me now.
Schmoos are just like a blob.
They could take on any form that they want.
But they were primarily pear-shaped.
Yes, they were pear-shaped like a ham, kind of.
A ready-to-go ham.
And they would happily smile through their big mustache while they sliced off pieces
of their own bellies for you to eat like spam.
Yeah, serving up your own cartilage and stuff like that to your friend.
Yeah.
Right.
But again, that's illegal now.
But never on a first date.
Right.
And then...
No, well, in China, I guess they put it on your social credit card if you don't.
You got to put out cartilage on the first date?
You know, we're going to...
You got to put out some cartilage, if not all of it, a small degree of it.
The social credit cartilage of China could spread to here.
You know, they grade you now.
In China, on how decent and patriotic or not your social media and social activities are.
Goodness.
And you can be...
It's worse than social media now.
Denied a job or fined for not being literally PC.
Holy schmoo!
Yeah, well, that's...
There's this huge, huge, huge nation on the planet that takes a lot of money to build a house.
Except about three-fifths of the nation's.
It's just entirely screwing large.
And it's...
Half of them are rat finks on their neighbors and stuff.
Oh, the United States?
Yeah.
No kidding.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, the USA.
It's like...
Yeah.
I guess.
It's a nation of finks nowadays.
Rat finks.
To quote William Burroughs.
How did the word fink become an insult?
Or a term like ratting on someone like...
Well...
You ever met somebody named Fink?
Yeah.
There was Santa Claus imitated.
He also did the Elvis Presley routine at the ice cream parlor.
Or at the custard shop, whatever you could call it.
Why would you not change your name if your name were Fink?
Well, because...
Because you're proud, man.
Yeah.
But respected command.
Well, you know what it means in German?
It means farm.
There's some Vietnamese names that can't be said on the radio because...
Because the pronunciation sounds like something else.
I mean, how would you like to go through life with the name Smucker?
Right.
Like that.
Well, if you live in Orville, then everybody knows what your family does.
I guess.
Orville and Analville, they're all the same, you know, too.
I mean, they were the same at least the last time the census came out.
And believe me, that document was too heavy to transpire in one afternoon.
Well, friends.
The important thing is, this is the last show that Princess Wee and I are going to
be able to do here at WCSB.
I think.
Probably.
I mean, we might be back for funerals.
Princess Wee will be back in town more than me, but...
But I don't engineer radio shows.
And I can always call in to WCSB.
But you always have Dr. Sinister on your side.
Right.
And on one side, and African Abstract on the other side.
And I'm...
I'm going to miss my old bracketing DJs and this nice microphone and these huge headphones.
Nice couch.
Yeah.
And the air conditioning that's not real loud.
The music that you can choose background music from.
Yeah.
Like I did tonight.
At a moment's notice.
We're going to miss all that, but there's a reason, you see, for us to leave lovely
Cleveland Heights.
And it actually is relatively lovely where we are.
And going to rural Texas full of Trumpensteins and so forth.
But see, for once, we're going to miss that.
And the one thing, we get to see my little sister again.
That's real important.
And my son and daughter.
And we've got a new grandson.
I have a grandson that a great...
A grandson I have not seen yet.
Yeah, he's already walking, sort of.
My mother has a great-grandson she's not yet seen.
And my brother.
And the nephews and nieces and in-laws.
And the sunsets and all our stuff.
The goats!
All those books I brought.
The thousands of books and the thousands of goats.
And the house there is paid for because my parents were smart and I'm lucky.
And we were going to leave this next Friday, but we shan't because I broke my neck.
Yeah.
Sort of.
Actually, I think it's just a pinched nerve, but I'm doing this show, friends, with a big neck brace or cervical collar on my neck.
Boy, does she look stupid, too.
Looks ridiculous, like a robot movie.
Oh, I couldn't fit it.
From 1957 or something.
I couldn't even find my cervix.
But yet, here is that collar.
Once you start trying to locate your cervix, it seems to be almost there.
It's a never-ending task.
If you don't succeed in the first few times, now your bohina, as they call it in Norway, is much easier to find, especially if you're looking through a loopage in the back door.
What about your Princess Whee?
Have you had trouble with finding your...
Bohina?
Cervix?
Uh, no.
Never have had any problem with that.
How about your platitudes or your erectile cabbage?
No.
Well, those are right up front.
Yeah, they're in easy sight.
You know, there's no way to get around them.
You just grab them.
You just walk up and grab them.
You know, if you're a celebrity, you can do anything you want.
You just grab them by the country.
Yep.
Mm-hmm.
I think if you speak in platitudes, you should get stung by a platypus.
Or at least sharply bitten.
Yeah.
Because that would be even more egregious.
Yes, a pinchy nip.
Well, that's actually a good thing.
You know, you live in a country where there's a mass shooting every week.
I just think there was another one this week.
And two weeks ago, or three weeks ago, was,
Stang thought it was not such a good idea to highlight the most recent slaying of numerous people.
Then that next week, there was more.
Well, that was really too much to even mention.
You know what I mean?
Because it would be too seasonal and occupational, like a hazard or something like that.
Mm-hmm.
And so I thought it would be just a good idea to do it someday, because now I realize it's never going to stop.
How did The Onion put it?
There's no way to stop this, says only country where this happens.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, well.
Well, we're going back to Texas, and we'll have looser-than-ever laws.
And I can be the good guy with the gun if I ever actually get a gun, which I probably should do.
I think you need one of those little New Year's Eve horns.
You know, wah, wah.
Right.
That thing comes out of the air.
Yeah, a noise maker.
And if you were a, yeah, a noise maker.
Yeah.
A little, a little.
They wrote various orchestral pieces for that, with the noise makers.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
And some of them get 15 feet long, and they tickle the person in front of them's ears.
Is that true, Dave?
Well, I-
Are you joshing me?
A little.
Well, just think if you were like-
That's why the ranks are staggered.
Yeah.
Like, if you were like in a great hall, and you're with your symphony buddies, you know, and stuff, you're tickling the ears of maybe a viola player going right past the tubas and the other French horns.
You can hear that sexy stuff going on in the background.
Slurp, slurp, slurp.
Mm-hmm.
Well.
It's gone.
Princess Wee, this'll be our last Sunday night in the freezing cold studio.
It's a lot colder where she's sitting than it is where I'm sitting.
It's more temperate tonight.
It was able to take my feet off.
I'm in front of this giant electronic board that's probably a bit warm.
And soon we'll be doing-
Well, nowadays, you know, you said it was a giant headboard, but I believe that over the past few years it has become a thyroid pygmy of boards.
Oh, we're gonna have to make room in a U-box for that headboard and all those toys.
Which I knew I could.
Yeah, I said in the video, you know, I showed Alice fishing a few times, and what happened was, I finally could get 100 hours.
Well, I figured I should, too, included a ten minute clip I says, have a ceilings sign, like we should.
I'm saying, we could do 20 or 30 in a day, probably, but I'm like, a little bit overly weird and Europa.
younger Hercules types to do everything,
including drive all that junk to Texas, what's left.
Hercules.
It's only two U-boxes worth, but that's still...
It's still too much money.
I hate having to pay someone to do a thing
that I could easily do 20 or 30 years ago.
And I hate even worse being reminded
that that's the way it's going to have to be.
God darn it, heck, fire it.
Consarn it?
Consarn it to carnation.
Just think of it as a relief
that you don't have to do that anymore.
Instead of, man, I used to do this in five minutes
and it was fun.
Just think of it as a relief
Well, if you're not going to be able to hang on to it,
you might as well completely kick it right in the poop.
Just soak in involuntary slack.
That's what I'm going to do.
Yeah, I'm going to wallow in involuntary slack.
Unfortunately, there's also involuntary expenses involved
in having someone else function as your backbone,
but I'm just lucky I still...
sort of can.
Well, you still have your Republican Party card?
Oh, I've got...
Actually, instead, what I have is a bumper sticker
that says,
Dobbs Cthulhu 2020.
Well, that's some pretty good eyesight, if you ask me.
Yeah.
Well, actually, it says Cthulhu Dobbs.
Next year is officially the year of hindsight.
Oh, yeah?
Yep.
Yeah.
So...
2020, don't you get it?
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
Loosen up those sphincter muscles.
I haven't heard that...
Breathe deeply as if you were at a yoga convention.
2020 at an optometrist's office in a long time.
That Cthulhu Dobbs image is great
on that bumper sticker, by the way.
It's just great.
I heard it was real scary.
I haven't seen it, but I heard it was real scary.
Did Bob make calamari out of Cthulhu or what?
Well...
Bob needs dinner sometimes,
and there's always some pasta,
and, of course, Cthulhu needs souls.
Bob doesn't have one of his own,
but he's got everybody else's
in the Church of the Subgenius in little canisters
in case President Cthulhu needs to be paid.
Of course, it's really...
Then we've got President Furman Supreme,
who already is...
He is president, but they just...
Nobody knows it yet.
Did he slap his mammy ten times or more than that?
Oh, at least.
At least.
You know, and he's got this whole free energy system
involving zombie power.
Because the living dead are kind of...
They seem to just keep going and going and going.
Whether they eat a brain or not,
they never stop.
They are perpetual motion machines.
So, yeah, they're perpetual motion machines,
and President Furman Supreme has advanced
pretty serious technical specs about how to do that.
Oh, we just can't...
You can't have that.
It's just a terminal illness by anybody's degree.
It's just like the American bald eagle
winging its way soaring through the wilderness.
Somebody's going to try and shoot it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, if there's a national park,
somebody's going to drill it, frack it,
knock over all the beautiful old rock sculptures
that took a million years to...
Be formed by wind.
Because, you know, it ticks off the libtards.
That's what's important.
It makes me wonder what kind of greasy gray underbags
they smoke every morning.
You know?
What kind of underpants they're living in
to have such a soulful rendition,
a dislike for their own atmospheres.
Once again, back again to smelling turbines,
which is kind of silly, really think about it.
Righteous anger is the marijuana of the 2020s.
How's that?
That's great.
Well, it's kind of swiped from a thousand different people.
Oh, it sucks, then.
Yeah.
No, it's still great.
Even greater because it's the collective work of the people.
Righteous anger.
Everybody's got it.
Everybody's got some.
Where will the slack of the masses come from?
I sure have some...
I have some righteous anger, but not like I used to.
Man, I just don't feel that righteous anymore.
I could be wrong.
That doesn't...
You could be wrong.
You know, having that...
That kind of self-doubt,
questioning,
trying to learn more,
those don't really fit in well
in this modern political dialogue, you know?
Yeah.
It's all or nothing.
Kill them all, let Bob sort them out.
Unfortunately, it's the dictum from the, you know,
the leader himself or herself,
whichever it happens to be at the moment.
Dictum over.
Yeah.
What a way of feeling it, too.
Trying to talk about bad remorse for things you didn't even do.
I can't even remember all the terrible things I did,
but I know I did something really bad.
So I feel all that remorse.
I only have tiny little remorsals.
Oh, why does that go crazy?
You can eat those with a little chopstick.
Oh.
Yeah.
A little tiny bit at a time.
Vietnamese foo-foo.
Yeah, it's like the Dalai Lama eating like a bird.
A Lama.
You don't need many morsels of pain or anger and agony
when you're a holy man.
Only a little bit.
And many morsels are even better.
In my former job,
they just did another story on this person from Ashtabula County
who was named for a Nobel Peace Prize,
shaking hands with the Dalai Lama.
This is the third time he's been...
He'll never get it.
He's just somebody.
Somebody.
Everybody likes it.
When he likes there, you know,
because he's real, you know, he's the regular Joe.
But there he is, shaking hands with the Dalai Lama,
and you can tell the Dalai Lama's just eating a very spicy Momo,
you know what I mean?
He's got that kind of half-grimace look going.
Dave, did you just say spicy Momo?
Uh-huh.
I was wondering about that.
I noticed that.
I know he said that.
I heard him say it.
Spicy Momo.
What exactly?
What exactly do you mean by that, Dave?
Tibetan dumplings that are kind of fiery.
Or, you know, hot pepper.
It's a spicy Momo.
Really?
There's a food called Momo?
Yes.
Okay.
Hmm.
There's also an Avatar character emoji that's killing everybody or something.
I don't know.
Isn't it?
Oh, no, that's not Momo.
I know what you mean.
That's that scary child scaring...
Yeah, that's, man, that's old.
That meme, that meme's long gone.
That was last year's scary clown.
Last year's killer clown.
That's what I heard them described as, scary killer clowns.
Yeah.
But they haven't been using that routine since the days of the posse.
And the Invictus wheels and speaker edges.
You know, when they say orange is the new orange,
and the kind of cleavage is not allowed, except for certain times of the year.
Hmm.
Emoji Momo?
Emoji Momo.
Hi-ya, hi-ya, hi-ya.
You, you, that's when you were supposed to come in with the bass part.
Ha ha.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
Ba da da da da da da da da da da da da da.
No.
It's a scatological kind of review, to say the very least.
I remember, again, I had to bring my own box of kitty litter along.
No.
Really?
Then I had to wear old gear, you know, like a World War II Army guy.
Helmet and everything, and knapsack, and leggings, and football shoes, and ironclad iron.
You know, all of those were the days that I can barely envision.
There's a lot of days that we Daves can barely remember or delve into.
The Daves of our lives.
Yeah.
I've known quite a few Daves.
These the Daves I know?
These the Daves I know.
None.
Not one was truly what I could call normal, strangely enough.
I hear you.
A lot of them are bald, I've noticed.
I don't know that anything really is truly normal, you know?
That's kind of a statistical fiction.
That's why my sister-in-law could never say the word normal.
She only said nor-ball.
Yeah, because she was abnormal.
Yeah.
Repent, quit your job, slack off.
Well, there is some very, very ancient dialectal homologies where M's and B's get confused.
No, but seriously, Dave, this is like the last ten minutes of this microphone and these
headphones for me.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be back on my home microphones.
Tarzan!
The Tarzan's mix board.
And, you know, it's a little limited.
Philo and Bleepo and I figured out a way that we could get three of us on the phone, on the recording, pretty well at the same time.
But we all have to have iPhones, you see.
I think that's going to happen again.
Oh, there's other ways to do it, but they're not as high quality.
And, yes, it will happen again.
And with Dave, too.
But, you know, the last five minutes.
Which comes up in four minutes.
I'm going to play the tearjerker song.
Or track or recording.
That's where you're going to play the tearjerker.
Yeah.
There's a lot of tearjerkoff artists out there.
There are old listeners that we've never heard from.
They've heard a thousand episodes of this show.
They've never donated a penny to any of this.
And we're not the stations that run it, nor the PayPal link on subgenius.com.
Keep, keep, keep, keep the skates.
And if ever there was a time when we could actually, no, I'm not supposed to do that.
No, of course not.
If ever there was a time, this would be it.
And this is the hour of slack.
And that's a big if.
From the Church of the Subgenius, found at subgenius.com.
I am personally the owner of the trademark that is the image of J.R. Bob Dobbs' face.
So don't you mess with me.
I don't think anybody was thinking of that.
Yes.
And I'm paranoid.
Well, you certainly told them.
And Dr. Sinister will still be tuning in.
Even though it's an hour later from Texas than it is here.
I thought you'd like that better, you know, that it's an hour earlier for you.
It's got a big...
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It is an hour earlier.
It's a traditional thing.
It is a little easier.
You get the early bird special for synesthesia.
Yeah.
Such is your privilege.
Oh, everything's all central time and a hundred degrees.
Yes.
Well, only for half the year.
That's right.
If they had any kind of degrees at all, those are the ones you'd want, too.
You know, it's better than MBA, at least as far as skullduggery and tomfoolishness.
Friends, Princess, we and I have been walking into this station.
Actually, it was in another building before it was this one for about 20 years.
Mm-hmm.
People used to fall asleep in the lounge in the early hours.
Yeah.
And they'd say, where's my beer and stuff like that.
Oh, you used to be able to smoke in here.
Yep.
Oh, and drink beer.
Oh, you could.
They'd have bottles of whiskey in the student radio station.
Leave the window open on the 29th floor, you know.
Those days are long gone here and every other station.
But, friends, you're lucky to have a station even remotely like this in your city.
In fact, you have two in this unusual city in Clinton Road, Texas.
Oh, yeah.
You're lucky to have a station.
Well, if you have internet, you can always hear the Hour of Slack.
But friends, we're going to sign off.
Again, this isn't like the last show or anything.
It's just...
I don't know that we're going to be back in this nice...
Are you getting old?
No, I'm not.
But this song I'm about to play will make everybody that way.
Remember that old...
Old show, ESO Swamp Radio, that you and me and Chaz and Psycho Pathfinder and Princess
Wee and Michelle George and them were on for years and years and years and years?
That's what I'm going to end with.
It's actually a recording from...
From years and years ago.
X Day 99 or something like that.
One of those things.
I'll leave you potted up, Dave, so that you can hear it.
How's that?
Pot me up, man.
Yeah.
That's what they all said.
I may jump ship in the middle part if I get too verklempt.
If I get too...
Oh, you won't.
You won't...
It's a little too hard to hear.
But for those of us who remember it, thanks for the memories, dear friends.
And I...
I...
prays bad.
I dream of
pleasure ships
from high above
until I fit
next year.
Go
to sleep
and dream of
flying high
on lullabies
and dreams that Bob
has now.
Sex goddesses
and squid
shall
guide
your way.
The smiling face
of Bob will keep
you safe till
your second
sex goddess
is gone.
I missed it.
Now it's the other part.
By counting
sheeples
follow bulls
to the
hell they build.
Follow
blob
blindfolded.
Go
to sleep
and dream
of times
when we
will meet
to sing
and praise
the name
of Bob.
Sex goddesses
and squid
shall
guide
your way.
The smiling
face
of Bob
will keep
you safe
till
dose
again.
Sex goddesses
and squid
shall
guide
your way.
The smiling
face
of Bob
will keep
you safe
until
next
day.
David
talked about
inside he
had you
know
Hot
hot
these
think
From PR News in Washington, I'm being held in four states today.
In Kansas, I'm being treated as one.
In Michigan, Missouri, and Washington again earlier today.
PR's report the day began as two reports 20 years ago today in Nairobi.
In Nairobi, because the point of the attack was to pull PR News apart.
We have suffered. We are beaten. We will never defeat us.
On Wall Street, 26 to 34, 875, 36, 24, 36.9.
President Trump says this is PR News.
In Nairobi.
And they used a third-party lawyer to make PR News.
President Trump did not endorse PR News.
So their names wouldn't be involved.
The stock soared more than 7%.
But it will be profitable in the second half of PR News.
Now the largest in California's history as workers continue to search through the PR News from Washington.