The Power of Slack!
Oh baby!
The Swingin' Love Corps is there,
a live version of The Fog and The Dew,
originally a Rudy Schwartz project,
tuned by Joe Newman, the swinging love corpses, dear friend.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Let me try to explore a little cock in layperson's terms.
As I understand it, cock is really accurate.
Yes.
Is that correct?
That's correct.
And, I mean, I was thinking about my cock opening where he said,
A gentle lady from Colorado is recognized for ten minutes.
A little collage by Fernanda Nandeli-Mur.
And now, Brother Cleve Duncan.
Yes, dear friends, Brother Cleve Duncan himself will recite the legendary brag of the subgenius.
I picked the goddamn terror of the fucking gods out of my nose.
I'm implying my language, but...
Let the sons of God and man be a witness.
Even in the...
In the belly of the Thunderbird, I've been casting out the false prophets.
I'm busting a gut and blowing my O-ring, and I'm right to throw a loaf.
For I speak only the fucking truth, and never in my days have I spoke other than.
For my every utterance is a lie, including this very one you hear.
I say, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
By God, anything for a laugh.
I say, I am the last remaining homo correctus.
I am the goddamn man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so not just to walk a foot.
I am the human being of the first goddamn water.
Yes, I am the javelina.
I am the humping junkie that jumped the men from Mars.
I drank the devil under seven tables.
I am too intense to die.
I am shielded by acts of God and Satan.
I was shagged by bodiless fiends and alien Jews from a corporate galaxy.
And got away with their hubcaps.
I cannot be tracked on radar.
I swear nothing uniform.
I wear God no, God no, no goddamn uniform.
I tell you right now, I was suckled by a triceratopsis.
I gave the anti-virgin a high protein tonsil wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon.
I'm armed and I'm loaded.
I'm a fission reactor.
I fight plutonium.
Power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow.
When they plug me in, the lights go out and hong fucking kong.
I weigh 666 pounds and zero gravity.
Come and get me, motherfucker.
I sign retired space baby bastards across the cosmos.
I cook and eat my dead.
Yahoo!
I am the unshaven Thor.
The poetry of the Atlanta Zoo.
I pay no motherfucking taxes goddamn.
Shit, piss, pee your own damn ass.
The devil's hands are my ideal playground.
I hold the seven bladed windbreaker.
The wheels that turn are behind me.
I think backwards.
I do it for fun, motherfucker.
I do it for motherfucking fun.
My imagination is a fucking canter.
And I'll poke it before it pokes me goddamn.
They say a godzillion is the highest number there is.
Well, by god, do I do count to godzillion and one?
Yes, I'm the purple flower of hell county.
Give me wide berth when I drop my droll mother nature swoons.
I use a python for a prophylactic.
I'm thicker, harder, and meaner than the Alaskan pipeline.
And I carry more spew.
Yes, I'll freeze your seed before it hits the bathroom floor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I kidnap the future and ransom it for the past.
I made breath wilt the tree of life.
I left my spore on the rock of ages.
Who'll tell me flesh with me?
Who'll split their juice?
Who'll guard with me?
Whose candy will I fight out?
Whoo!
I'm ready!
I'm ready, daddy!
Take the job, daddy!
I'm ready!
Step aside, all you butt-limb, neurotic, insecure, bespectacled slabs of wimp meat.
I'm a crime-fighting master criminal.
I am not insane!
You hear me, motherfuckers?
Not insane!
I'm a screamer and a laugher.
I make a spectacle of myself.
I am a sight!
Goddamn, my physical type cannot be classified by science.
My familiar is a picture of exactly life.
I feed him dipshits.
I communicate without wires or strings.
I am a thuggy.
I ain't feeding the tongs.
I have the evil eye.
I carry the mojo bag.
I swam the Bermuda Triangle and didn't get wet.
I circumcised dinosaurs with my tips and make them leave a tip.
I change tires with my tongue and my tool.
Every night I hook up a lunger and extinguish the sun.
The sun goes right out of the atmosphere, you queer.
I'm the Bigfooted Devil at level 14.
Who will come shoot me?
Where's the robot child who tried to blow me down?
I package the brownies of the gods.
I leak the plague from my nether pods.
Opiates are the mass of my religion.
I take drugs!
Yes!
I'm a ripstone.
I grab coca leaves right into the arm veins before they pick up the tree.
Space monsters cringe at my tread.
I wipe the pyramids off my shoes before I enter my house.
I'm fuel-injected.
I live forever.
And remember, afterwards, I'm immune.
I'm radioactive.
Come on!
Give me cancer!
I'll spit up the tumor and butter my bread with the juice.
I'm supernatural!
I've been crow-viled with my meat, axe, and thumb.
My eye droppings bolt through the earth and erupt because I'm China.
Yes!
I can drink more wine and stay sober than all the heathen Hindus in Asia.
Yee-hoo!
God bless you!
I am the world!
I am a moray eel!
I am a Komodo dragon!
I am a killer whale befitting of its pup!
I have a triple-track bone!
I was scythed by the wolfmen!
Give me all, all, all your slack!
I told Jesus I wouldn't go to church and he shook my hand.
I have my own personal savings.
I change them every hour.
I don't give a fuck if there's life after death.
I want to know if there's any fucking slack after death!
I am a god-damn visionary!
I see the future and I know there's a future.
past in comic books and wine bottles. I eat black holes for breakfast. I bend my jeans and whittle
in my DNA with the sheer force of my mighty will. I steal my own goddamn evolution. I ran out of
heaven and sold it to hell for a private goddamn praise bob. Praise bob. I am enlightened. I
achieved Nevada and took it home with me. I am so ugly the speed of light can't slow me down.
The gravity won't tug at my cuffs. When the rapture comes, I'll make them wait. They'll never clean my cage.
That was Brother Cleve Duncan doing my brag, my brag. And now, well, here's me bragging on
the great Reverend Saint Dr. Cleve Duncan. A mean son of a bitch. A crib fisherman if ever there was.
Yeah, you heard me right. A crib fisherman. Damn crib fisherman. And a skull farmer. A skull farmer
if ever I seen one. I've seen that goddamn Cleve farm over 80 skulls out there on the 840.
He was killing them and farming them down. Spreading that. He'd squirt that seed
all over the damn pasture. I don't know how he did it. He must have a damn seed bag the size of a
fucking watermelon or somethin'. He'd break for a goddamn beer every now and then.
Sucked down one of them damn malt things, shaking that damn hair of his all over the place.
And he'd go back to farming them dun skulls. He'd pull his pants down, you see. They'd he'd, uh,
he'd jump down into one of them furras. They'd plow this field first.
He never ran around to plow. Somebody else did.
The only one who ever ran around to plow was this three folks. That was the only one that wanted to do it, man. Such was the real marshmallow. My brother Bob Molto said to me that he would you know the best. Maybe in your own help he helped me get it. Sometimes be
jump down into this furrow, and then he'd start fucking it.
Just a dirt, you know, just a row of dirt,
and it'd be stretching out in front of him, oh, maybe like 300 yards,
you know, big old, big old, about an acre field,
and he'd start fucking that dirt.
He'd be humping on it and fucking on it,
and just, you know, he'd be getting all muddy and filthy and shit,
but, man, he'd see them damn furrows, and he'd be scooting along, you know.
It'd take him only about like five minutes to get all the way down to one of them furrows.
He'd be at the end of that furrow, he'd drink him a damn beer,
and he'd get back on that other furrow next to it,
going the other way, back the same way,
and start a fucking, and a fucking,
and behind him you'd see this furrow be filled up with the goddamn seed,
and then out of that they'd grow the children of the hydra's teeth, you know,
and then these skull farmers come popping up with their damn little hats on
and their pieces strung.
They'd be all hanging off their grin and teeth,
and then he'd fuck them, you know, after the end of the harvest.
Ah, yes, the harvest.
The Mess from Bad Doctors 1982.
In 1982, oh, the years, the years,
and now Einstein's Stardust Outlaws Radio.
From 20 years later.
You can donate to us and get a gift certificate for chain link addiction
and go have your penis pierced.
Wow, I want to be cool too.
Where can I get a mail through my pecker?
I want to show how smart I am.
How can I get a mail through my pecker?
Nah, you're smart.
Do I get a special gift certificate if I donate to the station?
You might be a smelt.
Get a shop.
Six was a brain.
And now it's time once again for meditations with non-contributional types.
When I was a kid, you know, to be cool, you had to grow your hair long.
That took a long time.
It took commitment.
But if the man was about to get you, you could cut it off real quick.
Nowadays, oh, to be cool, you stick a nail through your pecker.
That doesn't take long.
So it doesn't require that sort of commitment.
Not my problem.
You can get your...
Open your mouth.
And we're going to pierce your uvula.
Press like that.
And then we will attach it to your nipple clamps.
The only real way to be cool is to give up a chunk of your flesh.
The most important part of your body, which is your money.
Give it up.
That's right.
Give till it hurts.
What matters to you more?
What matters to you more than your children?
What matters to you more than your spouse or your job?
I'll tell you what, your money.
That's what matters to us, too.
I get a little horny and I'm on a little funky.
Give me something back, I won't make fun of it.
Roll around without a mind, I try to pretend it won't make any difference.
Make it fun.
The pleasure face makes the kissy lips look so real, no one can tell that you're still thinking.
And when it's all over you, I can roll around in the slip.
Hunch butter, hunch butter.
Rub it in my back, rub it in my back.
Well, you look like you're clean and you smell like you're shaving.
Climb up on the cigarette and make it like a monkey, you pump your funky.
Yeah.
Hips until 100.
Starts.
Jumping and lapping up like a dog.
It's all over your chin and everything.
I can tell you like it.
I like it too.
I like it on my neck and chest.
Hunch butter, a hunch butter.
Rub it in my back, rub it in my back.
Whoa.
You're on your own.
Youек.
On its mom table.
It's all done.
Awesome yourselves.
Have fun on your own.
Thank you.
That's a nice sentiment.
It is.
Just if everybody, I think, would take those words to heart
and do as that person says in that song with all their heart and soul,
I think this country would be turned right around the other way
and we'd be looking,
and it's backside right quickly.
Hey, what kind of shit is this?
It's the best, man.
I got it from a Negro.
You're probably so high already you don't even know it.
Really?
We're at the Death's Grip in waiting for the class to fall.
And it's the first contestants from All Life and Chilliwets,
Henry Kiss and Troy on the Pinochet Five.
I'd like to start this song with a
brief explanation.
Oh, this is one of the philosophical songs.
They're talking about what is reality.
We can come in all our own way.
I hate you, Sherman Rice.
I hate you.
I actually hate you.
Ha ha ha, that is reality.
I hate you.
It's a fucking mess.
Thanks for the hate.
Everything's a fucking mess.
I hate you.
Ah, if lizards could think like men.
Iит's a punk Thanksgiving like customer for Perkinspies right?
We're all put together to provide entertainment for all people.
There's a packer, feed the army, and can go into the
A pah video of aresponisby.
It's a punk Thanksgiving.
This is for our horror campaign!
Dear neighbors and crazy quella guys ,
the time when we danced in awritten Rifteapshot,
coffee from the iHerb Hub and who keeps 훈 and 10
in full Android with us amazing Eunni Beckler on turn
the bar, holy damn, no more karate's, mafioso,
so much write and you keepgon rain outside,
I really laughing poaaa port altitude with po やerne,
I don't think he's funny.
Fucking mess.
I think he's funny.
He is the beast of the apocalypse.
Thanks God for a damn industrial nightmare.
And no jobs for the worthy.
I think he's mean and nasty.
Thanks Lord for coming.
Maybe this one will lighten the mood a little.
Thanks for college radio.
It's chaotic discord with a song called
Fuck religion, fuck politics, fuck the lot of you.
Thanks.
Thanks to Roy, lady, fucking Lord.
Fucking hell, fucking, fucking money.
And for some of those people out there who have given up the goat.
Poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking, poking.
You're on my foot.
You got some kind of punk collection.
Is that what happened here, Chaz?
20 years of greatest punk golden oldies.
Yeah, it's down to 43.
Remember these amazing hits.
The Sex Pistols, The Crabs, The Clears, The Fuck You, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks,
Doctors for Wotan, The Sarcomas from Greece,
Teeny and the Poopoos.
They're slaughtered.
Slaughter and the Dogs does a version of White Light, White Heat.
Let's hear this.
Oh, yeah, Slaughter and the Dogs did a good version.
Poo, Water, Towel.
Now, that was a...
They were the ultimate nihilistic punk band.
They hated everything so much that they would just destroy all their equipment.
Before they even did the start of the show, like in the truck out back.
That's how nihilistic.
So the audience couldn't even see them destroy their equipment.
Then they'd come on stage and just sit there.
That's punk.
They were totally punk.
They were so punk that they looked kind of like Bob, just real normal.
They didn't have tattoos or...
Because they didn't have time for that shit.
Yeah, because they didn't have time for that shit.
Yeah, because it was like a...
Fuck it!
Fuck the punk scene!
I remember those guys.
I remember them real well.
But the problem is, they don't remember us now.
Then everything got kinder and gentler with New Wave.
That was the Bush era.
That was the era of the hairy man, in fact.
It's hip to be square.
It is.
It's hip to be square, especially if...
Yeah, spazzy short hairs were in for a short time.
And I actually had girls come on to me during that brief period
when Elvis Costello, Devo, and David Byrne were the sexiest things in the world.
You know, those...
Like blue corn diapers or something.
You know, guys with goofy looking glasses and uncool haircuts and little suits.
The nerd look.
Yeah.
I just happened to...
Tiny pussies.
A lot of us happened to look that way for that six month period.
And we're cool.
I remember those days.
That was it.
Back then, it was something else.
Then it was long hair again or bald heads or little goatees or spike in the nose or a
broomstick in the butt.
That's the current fad, I noticed.
Have you ever taken a safety pin and shoved it through your cheek?
Oh, that's...
That was...
That's so 80s.
Yeah!
I'm going to make you come tonight.
Come, come, come tonight.
You can...
Girl, you'll make me come tonight.
Come, come, come tonight.
Caller?
Hi, dear.
How are you?
Good afternoon.
Is there a gentleman in your life?
Yes.
Is he incarcerated?
Of course.
Do you suck nicks?
Yes.
Are you a Peter Puppet?
Of course.
I want you to answer my question.
Did you have a question?
My question is, what kind of work do you do?
Oh, my goodness.
I love you.
Good.
A collage by Fernanda Nandeli-Mir and Al David Allen Coe.
Who are you teaching.
Serve the deck.
Yep.
I'm MITCH ALLENwert.
Rever fingers again.
Any pineapples and sure, it'll be Mm.
I guess you are gay or whoever said dijug Да ЕS.
I knownis AAc.
I'm all gay.
Please little?.
you leave home
to go out on
your own. I
just like to
fuck you one more
time.
One more time.
I'd like to slip my
pecker in
your
avon. It's just
a quickie. I
won't mind.
No, I
won't get your
new white dress
dirty. Baby,
I just
like to fuck you
one more time.
There is no
need to cry.
Cause you're leaving.
Your
mother and me,
we ain't blind.
We both
knew someday
you'd go
on your way.
And I just
like to fuck you one more
time.
One more time.
I'd like to slip
my pecker in.
Your
avon. It's just
a quickie. I
won't mind.
No, I
won't get your
new white dress
dirty. Baby,
I just
like to fuck you
one more time.
Heaven
knows that you've
been a good
daughter.
Baby, and I
just like to fuck
you one more time.
I just like to fuck
Lord, I love it
when you call me daddy.
And I just like to fuck
you one more time.
Come back when I've had
some sleep.
Baby.
Was it you
did the pushin'
Left your stains upon the
cushion
Left footprints on the dashboard
upside down
Was it you
you made these peckers
Who stole my
throwbackers
Or was I thinking
better leave this town
Well it was me
who did the pushin'
Left my stains upon the
cushion
Left my footprints on the dashboard
upside down
But ever since I
screwed your daughter
I've been trouble passing
water
So I guess we're even
all day around
There you go, you learned a song.
That's a song you go,
What'd you learn at Starwood?
Take that home and teach it to your kid.
Best Starwood for me yet?
No doubt.
So don't fuck it up for me.
Chaz Smith.
Professor Chaz Smith at Starwood.
2002, I think.
And now,
The Swingin' Love Corpses.
I need weed!
I need some blowjob!
I need some weed and some blowjob!
I live from weed and blowjobs!
Life begins with blowjobs!
How does the tune go?
Like this!
I need some weed and some blowjob!
I need some weed and a blowjob!
I got a little song.
We had a blowjob.
Maybe a little cocaine too.
Sixteen year old.
I need a sixteen year old car.
And some Colombian gold.
I need a ten dollar more.
To get me a big old nasty blowjob.
A big old nasty blowjob.
Big old nasty blowjob.
Blowjob.
Fuck that car.
Fuck my car.
Blowjob, blowjob, blowjob, blowjob.
Blowjob, blowjob.
Blowjob.
Ahhhhhhhhh.
Wooo.
Oh.
That was positively the most exciting display
we've seen.
So far here tonight at the Home and Garden Show.
The Royal Home and Garden Show.
And those were some quite enormous tulips we just saw.
Look at those gardeners drumming.
Those gardeners are going like that.
Well they come from a very specific part of Norway.
And most of them are caribou hunters in the winter.
And in the summertime they sprout their tulips.
Their pants jockeys as we like to call them there.
I wonder what those big Norwegian girls look like
without those furs.
Oh I've heard that they're clicking devices on.
It's a cool dance they're doing.
Some of them.
Oh look at the feet.
The poor children.
How can they dance with feet like that?
Oh look here comes out the funeral.
This is a Norwegian funeral.
Oh my goodness.
I would have mistaken it for a celebratory ride of some kind.
It's a funeral, eh?
And all the hair on their feet helps them dance.
It's bouncy.
What's that in the coffin?
Why it's a herring.
A pickled herring.
These are the people who died of...
These people died of the holy disease.
The sacred disease.
The priest disperses to the believers.
Dispenses.
Yes.
It hurries them along to heaven they believe.
Ah.
Then what exactly...
Much like our modern day cocaine.
These primitive people are so fascinating.
What's the meaning of the pickled herring in the coffin?
That represents the disease to be...
It's the grandfather who goes with him and will guide him through the afterlife.
The grandfather...
The Norwegians see as a great vat of urine, yak urine.
Ah.
Which goes on forever.
Well this is quite fascinating.
You know the people of Sumatra have a similar belief and it's amazing they're so many miles
away, well at least not as far as the new mall is concerned.
But that same tradition of the yak urine is...
Yeah they think the yaks eat these...
Some sort of mushrooms that grow in the snow.
No.
On the yeti droppings.
Well we've heard that religious cults also enjoy these droppings.
The church of...
You better believe it Dave.
The subgenius and some other...
Yes.
Yes that's right.
The subgenius cult...
It's funny it's...
As part of the survival expansion and advancement of the subgenius race does grow these yaks
and mushrooms and...
He's a big boy.
He knows what he said.
What did you say?
I said I drink the urine man.
Go...
It's okay.
It's what we do.
It's just our thing.
Just...
You're funny.
You mean...
So let me understand this cause I don't...
Maybe it's me I'm a little fucked up maybe.
But I'm funny how?
I mean funny like I'm a clown?
I amuse you?
I make you laugh?
I'm here to fucking amuse you?
What do you mean funny?
Funny how?
How am I funny?
That was Joe's finest hour.
And from then on it was all downhill.
He played a...
There it went.
I tried to be good but all I was was bad.
I tried to be joyful and it made me far more stoned.
I tried to be fair but I knew I should be loud.
I tried to use my reason and it showed me that I'm f Mun!!
I tried to be smart, but I didn't want to think
I tried to be clean, but I was prepared to sneak
I wanted to soar, but can't do that thing that's neat
I tried to be in control, and it drove me to the plane
I tried to be warm, but I despise all others
I tried to be strong, but I hid under the covers
I tried philanthropy, but I couldn't think of others
I tried to be eloquent, and got reduced to six
Just a little
Fuck it, who cares, what good is it?
Little Theodore, the sexiest of the uber nerds.
In fact, that is from, I think it's from Beneath the Uber Putts, one of his oldest albums.
You can learn more from littletheodoreatyahoo.com.
That's an email address.
Little Theodore, Theodore spelled F-Y-O-D-O-R.
One word, littletheodoreatyahoo.com.
Who's driving you home tonight?
Is the devil driving you home tonight?
Or is Bob your co-pilot, my friend?
Who's blowing you?
The wheel as you go 90 miles an hour.
Satan or Bob?
I know who you'd rather have.
Of course, we'd all rather have.
At 80 miles an hour on a wet...
Cecil the Sea Serpent.
...that you really want because there's plenty of room inside there.
I'm coming, Beanie Boy.
Have you ever seen the end of Cecil the Sea Serpent?
You can stick it all the way in forever.
Once you start going into Cecil, if you can keep going,
he'll keep going.
Because there's no end.
He never came all the way out of the water.
Cecil the Sea Serpent.
You couldn't see the tail.
I'm coming, Beanie Boy.
On a toy.
The toy Cecil.
Sure, it had a tail.
They have a show.
Doctor, for your friends, listen to this.
Doctor Philodrumon has one of those porno shows
downloaded from the internet
that shows Cecil the Sea Serpent
all the way.
The end.
What?
Are you really...
Huh?
You could...
A puppet, you say?
Cecil was a puppet?
If Cecil the Sea Serpent was a puppet,
then...
How can you believe anything is real?
For all we know, Bob could be some made-up character.
For all we know.
Bob could be Beanie himself.
Do we really know anything?
No.
Cultural relativity stripped us of all solid knowledge?
You cannot know anything.
Are we now on a shifting, sandy beach of hypocrisy,
even in science?
Minneapolis International Airport information, Mike.
0053 Zulu.
Wind, 230 at 34 gusting to 65.
Visibility 2, heavy thunderstorm.
Holy fucking shit.
We are getting our asses kicked here.
Do not try to laugh.
Are you a dumb shit?
Save yourself.
Caution.
Pieces of mobile homes and dead cows on all runways.
Advise you have Mike.
Oh, Mr. Sister did that.
And before that, KPFA, subgenius business retreat,
sponsored by Don Joyce and Puzzling Evidence,
over the edge.
And now, from bad doctors,
Philodrummond.
Here's the tape of the tape.
Here's the tape of the tape of the tape.
The sound of it, the basic sound of the Earth's prize itself,
you couldn't see the explosion.
Initial accounts indicate they were shielded from the explosion.
Inside, what NASA claims to be an alien spacecraft.
As yet, there has been no official statement from the White House.
It was magnificent.
It's embarrassing.
It's moist.
It drips.
It squirts.
It's liquid warmth emitting from your body.
It's...
It dribbles.
It spits.
It's nasty.
But yet, it's beautiful in its own wet, slimy, squirting and embarrassing way.
It's beautiful.
It's... It's... It's... It is... It is... Just listen to this.
She leaks...
She leaks all over everywhere.
I'd like to pin her over like a 12-inch shack and put her over a couple of...
Yes, sir?
I think he should have an 8-inch shack.
And that is what we did.
We inundated her inner cavities with our own thicknesses of tissue.
Which was buried up her chute and rammed inwards and yanked outwards.
And one does have to yank these long tools because the head, the knob on the end is most
powerfully built and is kind of a barb almost, which it is easy to push it in because of
the flexible nature of the head.
And yet, the ridge around the edge of the head makes it very difficult to withdraw this
intruder, which we call the Avenger.
And here it is now.
Yes, you can hear it going in and out, squirting and farting.
Yes, air and liquid both emit from this new type of tool, which we have now begun to provide
to the ministers.
And those who would spread the seed of Bob.
The seed, my friend, of Bob.
For we find that the nuns, snakes, the young women who, and men, who wish to, they wish
to be boogered by Bob, and yet Bob is too busy.
So they come to the...
Hello, Bob.
And believe it or not...
Wait a minute.
Maybe Bob is here.
We may be able to get Bob in just a second.
I'm going to drop in on this.
I sure hope not.
I saw a little plant there, I know.
Goethe, Goethe, take off your knickers.
Goethe, slip the brassiere off of your pendulous sagging old breasts.
Goethe, Goethe, let me clean your teeth with my tongue.
Goethe, let me clean your armpits with my tongue.
Goethe, Goethe, let me clean your toes with my mouth.
Where's the bathroom?
Ask the woman where the children are.
The big daughter comes often, not the little daughter.
Ask, where is your daughter, where is the bathroom?
room. The big daughter does not come much. The big daughter comes often. Not the little daughter.
Yes, we have a big boy. The big daughter comes often. The husband is also coming. His wife is
coming also. Yes, not the little daughter. The big daughter or the little daughter. Yes, yes, we have a big boy.
The big daughter comes often. Not the little daughter. Where's the bathroom? The toilet is
there. I don't have much time. Come, family, by heart ignition. Step into the hazy, hazy phase.
Okay, I'm stepping out onto the ride.
Lift it up. I'm stepping out to get a surface over there.
Yes, an actual reenactment for your listered pleasure.
The walking of the moon. And now he's fucking Christ on the moon.
That's the part NASA covered up. Yes, the cover-up of the discoveries made on the moon.
Things you never wanted to hear.
Vast crystal towers and tunnels filled with burrowing, monstrous, grub-like lunar ticks.
Pools of chocolate pie and people who mispronounce their
identity.
No names. Yes, tick men of the moon.
Coming soon in Technicolor and Odoran.
Can you prove it won't happen?
Oh, they love to swim in the chocolate pond.
We love to not only swim in the chocolate pond, but this is where we place the newborn children.
We don't let them get past six and a half years around here. Once they get too big, they're too old for money.
And so we have to change the direction. Notice how we refuse the synapses on this little boy.
These people-sickles are yummy.
Ah, they're more than yummy. They're nutritious and help you to psychically enhance your luck.
Kids will enjoy their silent greens with people-sickles.
People-sickles.
Friends, you're listening to the X-rated version of the Hour of Slack.
And more is available.
From www.subgenius.com.
Or you can send your tapes and contributions in to me, Reverend Ivan Stanion.
Post office box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118, baby.
Bye-bye.
It was very hard to understand.
Why don't you just drop them pants?
That's right. Why don't you just drop those pants, Johnny and Tina, and come on over to the table.
Dave!
We've got some things that we want to show you.
And maybe you can ask your mom and dad what some of these things are.
They're like little tools.
See this thing here? It looks very, very harmless.
I went to confession today, and Father Riley showed me something.
Well, he's good at showing things.
He wants to show children his thing.
He's got a thing to show.
He sprayed me with his hose.
Well, he's trying to mark his territory like your little kitty Tom-Tom.
Don't you understand, Johnny?
Mommy, the father put white pee in my front butt.
Well, he's trying to communicate with the spirits through the top.
Are you ready?
Here, wait. No, I didn't play this last week.
But let me play it this week.
This is a cutoff of a Howard Stern show.
And here is some actual quotes from Mr. Rogers.
Howard Stern's having a little fun with it.
Take some of the actual quotes.
You know what Mr. Rogers always says?
I don't watch Mr. Rogers.
Here's what he always says.
I get all soapy.
You know, soap suds all over me.
And my grandfather would...
Take this hose.
It would go like this with me.
It would squirt all over me until this soap.
So you were playing.
Yeah, my grandfather and I did a lot of playing together.
Children, watch that show.
I got cool Mr. Rogers clips.
Want to hear some more?
Yeah.
Here's some great ones.
Here's some cool Mr. Rogers clips for you.
People probably download these and put them on their computer
because guys are always doing that.
That's a guy thing.
Downloading stuff and sticking it on your computer.
I know.
Guys are into weird stuff.
I don't even know who they play these things for.
I guess when they hit a button...
On their computer, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They make some sounds.
Here's a good one.
Okay, I can go on now.
Here's a good one for you to download.
Mr. McFeely came over here last night
and asked if he could do something fun for me.
A kind of secret, he said.
I think that's a dangerous program.
That show's weird, man.
You know how religious groups are always going after me
and taking things I said out of context?
If you start taking some stuff Mr. Rogers said,
you get that show thrown off the air, too.
Absolutely.
I'm ready.
Here you go.
Do you have a special something that you take to bed with you?
Does it help you to go to sleep when you hold your special something?
Okay, isn't that wrong?
That is wrong.
I have to agree with Howard there.
I'll show you what's going to fit in that hole.
It's in my pocket here.
Well, that hole, it's going to fit in that hole.
Come on.
My favorite, though, is his grandfather's soapy holes.
He's got a good point.
They sell this stuff to kids in the daytime
when no one's paying.
Paying attention.
Soapy.
You're going to have soap sites all over me.
And my grandfather would take this hose
and go like this with me.
It'd squirt all over me until the soap...
So you were playing.
Yeah, my grandfather and I did a lot of playing together.
What kind of man is he?
I mean, doesn't he know what kind of message
he sends out to kids?
He's a voyeur of such perversions.
You've got your hose squirting all over you.
Right.
Howard's having a fantasy about it here.
I mean, don't you know that that's kind of sexual?
Well, I'm sitting there saying to myself,
why is he telling this story?
He's Mr. Howard.
He says that he didn't get hosed by grandpa.
I'm the last one to criticize.
Oh, there's no more.
I thought he was going to play one more.
My grandfather actually let gasoline go up the hose.
You know what I mean?
And then sometimes he would light it.
Really?
Like Le Petit Mane would light his own orphanage.
Did he suck gasoline up his, quote, hose?
No, he would blow it up my blowhole.
My grandpa, no, no, boy.
He'd take a huge...
Wouldn't it, like,
explode?
Would I explode?
Of course I exploded.
Numerous times.
Yep, there it goes.
My only hope is that the big Lebowski kills me
before the Germans can cut my dick off.
Now, that is just ridiculous, dude.
No one's going to cut your dick off.
Thank you, Walter.
It's not a five, anything to say about it.
That makes me feel very secure.
That makes me feel very warm inside.
Oh, dude.
This whole fucking thing.
I could be sitting here with just pee stains
on my rug.
Yeah.
But no, man, I gotta, you know.
Fucking Germans.
Nothing changes.
Fucking Nazis.
Say what Nazis do?
Oh, come on, Donnie.
They were threatening castration.
Uh-huh.
Are we going to split hairs here?
No.
Am I wrong?
Well, he...
Man, they were nihilists, man.
Huh?
They kept saying they believed in nothing.
Nihilists.
Fuck me.
I mean, say what you want about the tenants.
They're in charge of national socialism, dude.
At least it's an ethos.
No.
And also, let's not forget...
Let's not forget, dude,
that keeping wildlife,
an amphibious rodent for,
you know, domestic
within the city,
that ain't legal either.
What are you, a fucking park ranger now?
No, I'm just trying to offer...
Who thinks a shit about the fucking Marmok?
We are sympathizing here, dude.
Fuck sympathy.
I don't need your fucking sympathy, man.
I need my fucking job.
What do you need that for, dude?
You have got to buck up, man.
You cannot drag this negative energy into the tournament.
Fuck the tournament. Fuck you, Walter.
Fuck the tournament?
Okay, dude, I can see you don't want to be cheered up here.
Come on, Donnie, let's go get us a lane.
Another Caucasian, Gary.
Right, dude.
Friends like these, huh, Gary?
That's right, dude.