You're listening to a free audio sample from the top 10 proofs that Bob is the only true religion.
After listening to this sample, we hope you'll consider purchasing this CD to hear the rest of the evidence showing Bob is the only true religion.
Thank you, and enjoy your free sample.
The Self-Genius Hour of Religion!
Bob?
From PR News in Washington, I'm down half a percent and also down more than half a percent.
President Donald Trump is commending PR News.
It is great and successful.
Within hours of publicly scolding them.
Trump singled out NATO.
NATO.
The Senate voted 97-2 on Tuesday in favor of PR News.
The Dow is 98-8, 24-24, 720, 1858, 61-32.
21st Century Fox says this is PR News.
I pledge allegiance to my slack and against the conspiracy in Pink Nation.
And to my escape vessel stocked with froth.
One nation under Bob.
Unexplainable.
With guilty pleasures for me and fuck the rest of them if they can't take a joke.
Joe.
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
The Mixolydian Illiterati experience with that slack pledge of allegiance.
Friends, you'll hear more original works by subgeniuses for subgeniuses on this show,
The Hour of Slack, than on any other subgenius radio show.
And there actually are four or five others, including one that predates Hour of Slack by three years,
The Puzzling Evidence Show.
And thanks to Lee Murr for the whole opening, the mouth at the front end of the show monster.
Speaking of which, I've been trying to find ways to keep that monster from devouring what's left of my time.
You know, ways to streamline show production.
Not caring would be the easiest, but I've tried that and it just doesn't, well, it just doesn't even happen.
We have plenty more X-Day recordings from the last three years of drills,
but those all take editing and editing takes time and time takes time.
And heck, just lift it.
Everything okay there, dogs?
Okay.
Everything.
That's fine.
Just listening to a rerun and removing the obsolete blather subjects, that takes a long time.
Anyway, I recently stumbled upon an old mixtape, well, actually a mixed CD,
that I'd made at some point of my favorite 1970s classic rock bulldada hits,
which aren't the same as ordinary classic rock hits by any means,
but they are by famous bands, which I've mostly declined to play on this show for about 20 years,
since there's so much new stuff that gets heard nowhere else, practically.
But I was surprised at how some of these hoary old rock and proto-Prog rock songs hold up
in terms of relevance to today's shameful world.
A 1970, 2020, 50 years later, we're right back at the same time.
The same place.
Only much, much worse.
So I thought, what if I just throw together a show that's nothing but my favorite music
from when I was in high school and my early college dropout years?
It'll be just like the radio show I did in my high school on closed circuit.
And it'll be easy.
All I have to do is play records, like almost every other radio show DJ in the whole universe.
Besides, these...
old-timey songs of yore, which are from like 1968, maybe, through 1975 or so, I guess.
They're not hits that you've heard a million times.
Half of our listeners will have never heard these particular songs before.
And the older half will be going,
My God, I haven't heard that song in years!
I forgot how great that was!
And we'll start with the great Captain Beefheart,
and then we'll be moving.
And through Alice Cooper, Jethro Tull, Neil Young, Jefferson Airplane, King Crimson,
Bob Dylan, and the Hee Haw Gospel Band.
And some surprises.
And strangely, they're all on the subject of religion.
All of these songs.
But first, from his album, Clear Spot, the great Captain Beefheart and his magic band.
Clear Spot.
Distant cousins, there's a limited supply.
And we're down to the dozens, and this is why.
Big-eyed beans from Venus, oh my, oh my.
Boys and girls, earth people around the circle, mixtures of man alike.
Big-eyed beans from Venus.
Don't leave me alone.
Let anything get in between us.
Beam in on me, baby, and we'll beam together.
I know we always been together, but there's more.
Mr. Zuthorn Rollo, hit that long lunar note and let it float.
Man, let your wallets flop out, and women open your purses.
Cause a man or a woman without a big-eyed bean from Venus
Is suffering with the waste of the cases.
Yeah!
Now you're suffering with the wisest of cases
Put them out in the sun
And when the night comes
You don't have to go out and get them
They'll glow with you
They'll show with you
Ain't no losers
Cause they're on the right track
You can be on the right track together
Of course, of course
Ain't no snafu
No folly or wrong
Check these out
Big-eyed beans from Venus
I'll let a few out
Let them pass in between us
Just a cousin's
There's a limited supply
And we're down to the dozens
And this is why
Don't let anything get in between us
Big-eyed beans from Venus
Big-eyed bees from Venus
And I don't need to swing an egg
No,釁
I couldn't tell
Well, if the bells are getting louder The songs they ring I finally recognize
I only know hell is getting hotter The devil's getting smarter all the time
And it would be nice to walk upon the water To talk again to angels on my side
Time is getting closer I read it on a poster
And it would expose us If owners brought the sign
It would be nice to walk upon the water To talk again to angels at my side
I just come back to show you All my words are golden
So have no doubt to pull me out the line
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm the one who's the darkest Of all the stars
And it would be nice to walk upon the water To talk again to angels all the time
Time is getting closer I only know hell is getting hotter
Thank you.
And oh, it's cracking
How long, how long
Ah
guitar solo
Southern man better keep your head
Don't forget what your good book says
Southern change
from the comet
past
Now your crosses
are burning
fast
Southern man
guitar solo
Lily bell
your hair is
burning brown
guitar solo
I've seen your black man
coming round
swear by God
I'm gonna
cut him down
I heard
screaming
and bullets cracking
How long, how long
Ah
guitar solo
bass solo
guitar brief
drums solo
bass solo
guitar solo
è una viola
Thank you.
And you've got no place to go
Soon you'll obtain the stability you strive for
In the only way that it's granted
In a place among the fossils of our time
guitar solo
Loyalty to the kind
They cannot tolerate our minds
In loyalty to our kind
We cannot tolerate their obstruction
In the only way that it's granted
Life is change
How it differs from the rocks
guitar solo
I've seen the world
In their ways
Too often
For my liking
New worlds again
My life is to survive
And be alive
For you
guitar solo
I
, shapes of tomorrow
I, shapes of tomorrow
Text, certain, and fairy language
Stream, Millennial's
Your foreabît
And 20 to the right
They call that a week
The powerhouse, rise and go
20% case gets a man
I'm a black, I'm water
I'm a talent, I'm spirit, I'm fire
Innocent snakes with no teeth
21st century gets a man
I'm a black, I'm water
Black seed, woman's seed
Let's go in to believe
Money is gold, in many leaves
20% case gets a man
guitar solo
solo
I don't have to tell anyone as old as me
that we just heard King Crimson
doing 21st Century Schizoid Man,
Jefferson Airplane doing
Crown of the Red Cross,
Crown of Creation,
Southern Man by Neil Young,
and by the way, I am a Southern man
and he's welcome around anytime, anyhow,
Jethro Tull's
My God,
and Second Coming
by Alice Cooper.
And now,
Buffalo Springfield
with the corniest and
unfortunately most
prescient of the songs
so far.
There's something
happening here
What it is
ain't exactly clear
There's a man
with a gun over there
Telling me
I've got to beware
I think it's time
we stop, children
What's that sound?
Everybody look what's going down
There's battle lines being drawn
Nobody's right
if everybody's wrong
Young people speak in their minds
Are getting so much resistance
Falling down the line
behind
Time we stop
Hey, what's that sound?
Everybody look what's going down
What a field day for the heat
A thousand people in the street
Singing songs
and carrying signs
Mostly say
hooray for our side
It's time we stop
Hey, what's that sound?
Everybody look what's going down
Paranoia strikes deep
Into your life it will creep
Into your balls
As the sky slides
The war begins
Get right via a giant
One time ago a crazy dream came to me
I dreamt I was walking in World War III
I went to the doctor the very next day
To see what kind of words he could say
He said it was a bad dream
I wouldn't worry about it none, no
Them old dreams are only in your head
I said, holy doc, a World War passed through my brain
He said, nurse, get your pie at the boys
He said, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I said, that's insane
He grabbed my arm, I said, ouch
I landed on the psychiatric couch
He said, tell me about it
Well, the whole thing started at three o'clock fast
It was all over by a quarter past
I was down in the sewer with some little lover
When I peeked out from a manhole cover
Wondering who'd be there
He turned the lights on us
Well, I got up and I walked around
Up and down the lonesome town
I stood wondering which way to go
I lit a cigarette on a parking meter
And walked on down the road
It was a normal day
Well, I rang me a fall-out shelter bell
And I leaned my head and I give a yell
Give me a string bean, I'm a hungry man
Shotgun fired my way around
I don't blame him too much
Though he didn't know me
Down the corner by the hot dog stand I seen a man
I said howdy friend I guess it's just us two
He screamed a bit and away he flew
Thought I was a communist
Well they spotted me a girl before she could leave
I said let's go play Adam and Eve
I took her by the hand and my heart was thumping
She said hey man you crazy or something
You seen what happened last time they started
Well I seen me a Cadillac window uptown
There was nobody around
I got into the driver's seat
And I drove down 42nd Street in my Cadillac
Good car to drive after a war
Well I remember seeing some ads
So I turned on my car to ride
But I didn't pay the car net bill
So the radio didn't work so well
Turned on my record player
It was rock of day Johnny singing
Tell your ma, tell your pa
Our loves are gonna grow
Wah wah
I was feeling kind of lonesome and blue
I needed somebody to talk to
So I called up the operator of time
Just to hear a voice of some kind
When you hear the beep
It will be three o'clock
She said that for over an hour
And I hung up
Well the doctor interrupted me just about then
Saying hey I've been having the same old dreams
But mine was a little different you see
I dreamt the only person left after the war was me
I didn't see you around
Well now time passed and now it seems
Everybody's having them dreams
Everybody sees itself walking around
There's no one else
Half the people can be part right all of the time
And some of the people can be alright
But some of the people can be alright
part of the time, but all the people can't be alright all of the time. I think Abraham Lincoln
said that. I'll let you be in my dream if I can be in yours. I said that.
I'll fly away.
To a land on God's celestial shore.
I'll fly away, oh glory.
I'll fly away.
I'll fly away in the morning when I die.
Hallelujah, fly, fly.
I'll fly away, fly away.
Just a
just a kid
ran away.
Bullshit little kitty went to a
little place and told the story of a child on a
I'll fly away.
I'll fly away, oh glory.
I'll fly away in the morning when I die.
Hallelujah, fly, fly.
I'll fly away
No, that makes me cry.
That was from a hee-haw TV show from 1973
with Tennessee Ernie Ford, Grandpa Jones,
Stringbean, and Roy Clark.
Clark, an extremely moving song,
obviously about X-Day.
And before that, Bob Dylan's World War III Blues.
And now, okay, friends,
talk about your classic rock royalty.
Here's the ultimate, the greatest,
the king, Dewey Cox.
guitar solo
Mailboxes drip like lampposts
In the twisted birth canal of the Coliseum
Rimjob fairy teapots mask the temper tantrum
Oh, say, can you see them?
Stuffed cabbage is the darling of the laundromat
And the summer's a-bottomin' up the window
Rarity mascot sat with the lumberjack
Pressin', passin', stingin'
Half-synthetic fabrications of his time
The mouse with the overbite
Explained how the rabbits were ensnared
In the skinny, skinny self-thrash
The apothecary diplomat
Inside the three-eyed monkey
Within inches of his toast
A roaster of an life
In my mind
I'm half-blind
My inner wrath
Is mostly death
I'm smell-impaired
If you cared
My sense of taste is wasted
On the phosphorescent orange peels
Of San Francisco axe-encrusted frenzy
So let me touch you
Let me touch you
Where the royal jelly gets made
Chimes in لوpo
Where the royal Kommo
And A-m처럼
Will go ap셈
T dummy
Bringing weeds and social clingers
Hangers on and fancy flingers
To the dress ball
Mushrooms and bowling pins
Stovepipe hats and other things
I can't recall from juvenile hall
We're so unlucky and stuff
Woodrow Wilson never had it so tough
Dairy Queen and Vaseline
And Maybelline, Paul Bunyan and James Dean
Allegory agencies of pre-Raphaelite paganry
And Shenandoah tapestries
Compared with good mahogany
Collapsing the undying postcard romance
The feline perspicacity
By the universe
That night I held a paucity
Which you deemed common courtesy
I wasn't what you thought I'd be
I shouldn't have invited you to dance
In my tree
I'm halfway free
And in my chair
One quarter there
In my dream
One sixteenth cream
And in my chair
In the coffee of the courtier
Of the sycophantic assistant to the king
So let me touch you
Let me touch you
With a roar
You're a Construction
Let me touch you
Over here
Sensink
At that moment
I've got to go
Before you think
That you had a bad time
What if you don't have the right
Besth
To think
You can't make these who know you
with a meltdown of the classic Jefferson Airplane song, White Rabbit,
which has been covered by every drugged-out weirdo in recording Christendom,
many of which recordings were mashed together by our friend, Reverend Dr. Phineas Narco
of that other subgenius-affiliated show called National Cynical Radio,
linked, like all the subgenius shows, on the radio page of subgenius.com,
which also shows you how to receive eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Praise Bob.
¶¶
Thank you.
One pill makes you larger
And one pill makes you small
And the ones that mother gives you
Don't do anything at all
Go at her
When she's ten feet tall
And if you go
Chasing rabbits
And you know you're going to fall
Tell them a hooker
Smoking caterpillar
Has given you the call
Call her
When she was just small
When the men on the chessboard
Get up and tell you
Where to go
And you just had
Some kind of mushroom
And your mind is moving
Oh
Go ask Alice
I think she'll know
When logic
And proportion
Have fallen
Stopping dead
And the white knight
Is talking backwards
And the red queen's
Off with her head
Remember
What the dumb mouse said
Feed your head
.
And thank you
National Cynical Radio
No, that's actually
National Cynical Network
Why do I keep saying that wrong?
Did that white rabbit
Megamix
Dr. Phineas Narco presiding
Friends, you're listening to the hourglass of the day.
This is episode number 1764
Called You Should Frop
For this one
And there's more information
From subgenius.com
Ha
Praise Bob