As much as we thought it was going to be a live show tonight from a darn opium den,
well, not opium den, it's an alcohol den, but what's the difference as far as I'm concerned?
We couldn't do it. We were going to do a live show at RC,
but we were like opening for a Grateful Dead show, see?
And we don't know how to do a Grateful Dead show.
Well, some of us probably do, but Dave Moynihan was sick.
He was sick. He was the guy that was going to do it.
We were just opening for him. He couldn't do it.
And so there's some people sitting down there at RC Bar going, what's going on, man?
And I'm sorry, friends.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Numero...
Pneumonia or whatever, you know, I mean, serious colds and so forth.
So once again, it's just another hour of slack.
And yet, and yet, well, this way you'll get to hear the professional version
of what we were going to do in a very rinky-dink way over there at RC Bar on Henderson.
Yeah, we're going to do pretty much the same thing.
And then next...
Next week, or maybe a week later, sometime in the next two or three weeks, we will do it live.
But for now, you have to hear the...
I'm sorry, you have to hear the recorded studio version, so to speak.
Of course, it's just as chaotic as it would have been over there, practically,
because we don't know what's going on, and you don't know what's going on,
and that's what's so wonderful about it, isn't it?
Isn't that what you love about it?
I'm just waiting to see what kind of a horrible goof-up...
your radio announcer will make.
Oh, you can count them up?
Just listen, count...
Let's start a new contest.
Count my mistakes.
Go ahead.
Don't make no difference to me.
Don't make no...
Never mind at all, because instead of actually being able to do the Grateful Dead show,
which we would not really have been that good at, but we will next week,
instead we...
Well...
Well, we're...
We're doing what we know a little better than the Grateful Dead,
which is the 60s in general,
and the effluvia, the fallout from the 60s,
as it exists today.
Only 30 years later.
Hehehe.
Yeah, I remember that time way back then when I did that Mahoody,
and then we ran down to the Mahoody,
and we...
Oh, man.
That was one big co-hern-key...
Cool...
Like, groppin' groove-go thing, man, baby.
And, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
I sure got the blues this morning, baby.
Yeah, and I'm here to tell you about it.
So you might as well pick up on it.
Welcome, dear friends, to the subgenius hour of slack.
That's right.
because we're
y
pump
train
pum
let's
Let it be
Clutch your hands
Oh, the world's left to live
And I ain't gonna copy you
Principal?
Oh yes, dear friend.
This is Li Liqing, a Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the Hour of Slack on KNON in Dallas, Texas.
Remember, Bob is a comrade of all people.
Here in China, just like in America,
the people need Slack.
In Chinese, we call Slack 乐天台
But it must be true Slack, not the bad Slack of the conspiracy.
Please, Bob, help me somebody.
Bob!
I don't care
This
Cause I've taught my own words to live the will
And I ain't gonna copy you
She said, cutting her own legs off
in what was to be the foment of a startlingly trend
among the so-called punk de-tele-hantia.
Problem.
That's the problem with the punk de-tele-hantia, dear friends.
I just don't have any sense of history.
So, uh, we're gonna try to fill you in on the worst of the 60s tonight.
I'm afraid.
I don't want to walk and talk about Bob.
I just want to see his face.
This is the first time I've called, and I really love your show.
Thanks for calling in.
You're welcome.
And, um, I'm calling.
Thank you.
Okay, um, I'm a born-again Christian, and Jesus Christ is my Lord.
And about three years ago, he delivered me of drugs.
And one of the drugs that I was on was acid.
And I remember, um, I didn't like it.
I wanted to get off of it, and I didn't have no control over my mind.
And I said, well, I'll just go sleep it off.
So I went to sleep, and I remember the devil, the devil and Jesus.
Like, it was a, I felt the warfare, the battle.
Mm-hmm.
And, um, I remember I cried out to God.
I said, God, you know, I'm really sorry, and this is really scaring me.
And I remember I went to sleep, and I woke up the next morning, and there was this big burn on my knee.
And, um, and I told my husband about it, and he said, no, you must have just, you know, burnt yourself with a cigarette, because I smoked at the time.
And I was wondering, um, is that possible?
Okay.
That...
Yeah, well, uh, I don't know exactly the significance of it.
But most anything is possible.
But what you're telling me, I mean, I have verified in my research around the world.
For example, you could have been in a room with a half a dozen other people who had dropped acid.
And you would have all been seeing the same landscape, going through the same adventure, encountering the same entities.
Now, that's, uh, I mean, I've talked to too many people who've had that experience.
So you know that you are all being manipulated by a common deceiver.
And, uh, but I've also talked to people who have...
who have literally come to Christ on an LSD trip.
Satan overdid himself and freaked them out.
And they got so scared, they cried out to God.
And, uh, the Lord did rescue them.
And I'm not recommending drugs to lead somebody to Christ by any means.
But God is very gracious.
So something really is going on.
Your brain is being manipulated.
Yeah, and we'd like to manipulate it a little bit more, dear friends.
In the meantime, friends, as I said before,
this was supposed to be a, uh,
a live, dead show from the, uh, the RC bar.
Uh, technical and health problems caused that not to happen.
So instead, we're gonna sit here in the studio and do what we were gonna do,
which is talk about the 60s and actually the early 70s.
Kind of both, uh, but it's interesting to find out
because it's interesting to find out
where the 60s segued into the 70s
and went from sort of a political, cultural thing
to kind of a, uh, drug thing.
Too bad, wasn't it?
How many of y'all were hippies?
Had long hair, listened to rock music,
believed in free love, which was neither?
I don't know. It's kind of a shame.
Free love never bled over into the church of the subgenius,
probably because we had too much respect for the women.
How many of y'all dropped acid?
How many took part in demonstrations?
How many, above all, served for our country in Vietnam?
If you did, I salute you.
Not the war, but those who served.
Now, me, I was, uh, of the 60s, but not in it.
I was a little too young.
I was more like part of the 70s drug brother generation,
you know, the kind that could have gone to Woodstock but didn't.
Never got into the Grateful Dead, but, uh,
Hendrix, yeah, Zappa, mm-hmm,
Quicksilver Messenger Service, Poco,
Firesign Theater, Zap Comics, ee!
But I was a suburban kid, friends.
I had it easy.
In 1968, I had, I hate to admit it, but it's true,
in 1968, I carried a Nixon sticker on my briefcase.
And yet, by 1969, I'd seen Easy Rider,
and so I realized the hippies were up to something.
Unfortunately, by 1972, what they were up to mostly was dope,
but I clung to the, well, not the political part,
but the cultural hippie thing.
Yeah, just the cultural part.
And that's more than I can say for most of my contemporaries.
I mean, hey, man, I've got the most complete underground comics collection in Dallas.
The guy that draws most of the sub, well, the main subgenius,
uh, heavy-duty activist artist is also the guy who now draws the furry Freak Brothers,
believe it or not.
Yeah, all that old underground comic stuff.
The rip-off press that published that stuff, they're, they're publishing Bob now.
The circle is unbroken.
Not to brag, but we are bragging.
Yeah, the 60s was a fun, scary time.
I did some 60s-type things, hitchhiked across Europe
with a hippie chick, and then I married her.
That wasn't a very hippie-like thing to do.
Lived on a Sioux Indian reservation in South Dakota.
Worked on, worked there, actually.
I wore braids and buckskin like an idiot.
Smoked hash in Morocco just like everybody else.
And as my dad said,
son, if everybody jumped off a cliff with you,
no, no, but I did.
Only, I had a parachute, dear friends.
Because I had...
buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, yeah.
How about I stayed a mutant?
I really did.
I got married when that was the least cool thing you could do.
Cut my hair short just when long hair got acceptable.
Made underground films, man.
But punk style.
And finally, went to work for Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius
and told everyone who was cool to buck off.
So call me old-fashioned, friends,
but I believe that you can maintain the spirit of the 60s
by blowing off the external trappings of them.
Of course, some of these ideas have to get modified.
I used to think, heck, if somebody wants their country to be communist,
let them.
But then I went to China.
And I compared China and Japan,
and I thought to myself, well, who's kept their heritage?
The country that was subjugated and occupied by the United States?
Or the one that just went Marxist?
And friends, the one that was subjugated and occupied by the US
kept far more of its traditional values and prospered.
Whereas the Marxist commie countries became hell on earth.
But to get back to the subject, I mean,
I guess it all started when Bob Dobbs met Ken Kesey
and sold him some LSD.
Had quite a markup, I might add.
I don't know, maybe it began when Dobbs bumped into Dr. Albert Hoffman
and made his hand slide across that wet table of fungus spore effluvia.
And maybe it started when the two-year-old Bob Dobbs
was accidentally dosed with belladonna instead of aspirin
by a drunken druggist, his own father, as a matter of fact.
Well, I don't know.
We're going to look into what delineated the 60s
and why it's irrelevant in the 90s,
as will be heard once again on this show, dear friends.
It's a nasty and tricky, tricky, tricky question.
It concerns me because a lot of our psychiatrists here today
is administering drugs that in fact do manipulate your brain as well
and can lead to hallucinations and so forth.
So you probably had a real experience.
Where the burn came from and what the significance is,
I don't know, but it is definitely possible
to have these physical intrusions into your body
from the spirit dimension.
Sure.
If you can just get your mind
together, then come on across to me.
We'll hold hands and then we'll watch the sun rise
from the bottom of the sea.
But first, are you experienced?
Have you ever been experienced?
Well,
I have.
And that eliminates some of the arguments that have come before
that these are physiological or pharmacological manifestations
because if it was pharmacological,
then an LSD would generate different kinds of disjointed hallucinations.
The common element there suggests a common deception.
And we're really back into 2 Corinthians
and we're talking about deceivers, angels of light and the like.
And I think that's a logical explanation.
The Bible calls it sorcery.
Sure.
The New Testament indicates it would be revived in the last days.
The world would refuse to repent when God's judgment would come.
And one of the Greek words for sorcery is pharmakia, pharmakos.
Sorcerer takes consciousness-altering drugs to contact spirit entities
to gain supernatural powers.
And my alma mater, UCLA, believe it or not,
gave Carlos Castaneda his PhD in anthropology for Journey to Ixalan.
I know, I know
You probably scream and cry
That your little world won't let you go
But who in your measly little world
Are you trying to prove that
You're made out of gold and
Can't be sold?
Hey!
If you could just get your minds together
And come along with me
Hold hands and watch the sun rise
From the bottom of the sea
What good is it to be a man?
If this is a privileged crowd here tonight,
because the Pope of all New York is going to do his 60s nostalgia rants
for the last time.
So, Joseph, I need you to not only listen carefully,
you must respond to me.
And let me now at this point introduce my perky spokesman, Otto Kapp.
Can we have a lovely hand for my perky spokesmodel?
Kapp is going to help you, help me tell you
what delineated the 60s and why it's irrelevant in the sub-90s.
Tell the truth!
Now, Jonah, help me now.
We're going to talk about the first thing that delineated the 60s.
Can I get a P?
Can I get an O?
Can I get an L?
Can I get an I?
What's that spell?
That's right, children.
Politics.
Is everybody done laughing?
Politics in the sub-90s, children?
The last political thought you've had in the last six months is,
who's Von Hall?
Politics is a dead issue, and let me explain to you why.
Why?
You can go to Poland and vote, children, if you want to vote.
You can go to Chile and vote if you want to vote, children.
And the people that live there know what they're voting for.
And do you know what they see as democratic freedom, children?
I'll tell you.
Do you know what they want in Russia, children?
What do they want?
They want Led Zeppelin albums and 501 Blues, children.
Led Zeppelin!
The products of a free society are now mistaken
for the society which had the freedom to produce them.
So nobody around the country, around the world,
is looking for politics, children.
They want ghetto blasters as big as El Dorado.
Me!
More slack!
When you invest in pop culture,
which is what you've been given as a substitute for politics, children,
you get bored in a hurry.
And you get bored in a hurry so that you'll go out and buy more pop culture.
More pop culture!
You're so convinced that your taste in rock and roll,
or art, or movies,
is what defines you, children,
that you buy and buy and buy to shore up that definition.
And you're playing right into the conspirators' hands, children.
Right! Right!
But as it turns out, children,
you're also playing into our hands, children,
because Bob is a savior designed for a consumer society.
Bob is...
A short-duration personal savior!
That's right, children.
Bob wants you, Bob wants you
to take him into your heart,
to take him into your mind,
to take him into your wight,
and then cast him out, children,
and make your own church.
And children, when you look around at the shambles
that the modern world has become, children,
don't blame Bob.
He doesn't make history.
He just exploits it.
And if children, if you look at these subgeniuses,
and you see how deep their devotion is,
and how truly they believe,
and how much Bob means to them,
and you say,
a joke is all that's left children,
yes, that's true, children,
but it's a joke you can believe in.
Joke!
Now, children,
let's talk about the next thing that delineated the 60s.
You're going to help me.
Give me a B.
B!
Give me an R.
R!
Give me an A.
A!
Give me an I.
I!
Give me an N.
N!
Give me an S.
What's that spell?
Brain!
That's right, children, brains.
Children, you're going to find this hard to believe.
You're going to say to me,
no, Dave, no.
No, Dave, no.
But in fact, children, at one time,
it was hip to be smart.
No!
Hip to be smart, children.
Now, that's nostalgia, children.
Think back on the days when it was hip to have brains.
Children, nowadays,
if you're in a conversation with someone,
and you imply that anything underlies anything,
if you show the slightest spark of intelligence,
people look at you like you're crazy.
Crazy!
And that's why in the church we say,
if you act like a dumb ,
they'll treat you like an equal.
That's right, children.
You know what Bob says, children?
What does Bob say?
You know how dumb the average guy is?
Well, by definition,
half of them are dumber than that!
I mean, children,
do you really want to think about your job?
Do you really want to think about your future?
Do you really want to think about that check you take home?
Do you want to think about the environment?
Do you really want to think about the government?
Hell no, children!
So, children,
I think it's safe to say that brains are a dead issue
in the sub-90s.
The next thing that delineated the 60s,
help me, children,
give me a D.
Give me an R.
R!
Give me a U.
U!
Give me a G.
G!
Give me an S.
S!
What's that spell?
R!
Drugs, children.
Drugs?
Well, let's run down the drugs
that delineated the 60s, shall we?
Let's start with marijuana, children.
I don't know about you,
I don't know the last time I saw any marijuana.
And when I,
in the 60s, children,
marijuana was $12 an ounce,
not $220!
Yeah!
Now,
I don't know if you've ever seen
but it's $220!
Yeah!
Nowadays, children,
life being what it is,
when people say to me,
day!
Day!
When they say to me,
red day!
Red day!
New York City day!
Do you want some marijuana?
I say,
no thank you, children.
I can get depressed and paranoid
for free.
All right, now,
let's talk about cocaine, children.
I know cocaine is popular now,
but the only one thing to say about that,
and that was said by the great subgenius,
Saint Hunter Alexander,
S. Thompson,
when he said,
Yeah!
Drug culture?
What drug culture?
It's just a big dirty business.
Now, children,
psychedelics,
psychedelics in the sub-90s, children,
the Pope of all New York doesn't think so, children.
The Pope of all New York thinks in real life
it's sufficiently hallucinatory
in the sub-90s.
If I could quote another,
another great subgenius,
Saint Paul Krasner,
when he said,
when you're watching TV
and you see something
you absolutely cannot believe,
just flap your arms like a bird, children,
and if you float up to the ceiling,
you're on LSD.
And if you stay in your chair,
you're in the sub-90s.
All right, children,
the last thing that delineated the 60s,
give it up!
You can see!
Sorry, we can't say sex on the radio.
Let's cast our mind back,
all of those of you who are the same age
as the Pope of all New York,
those of you who are in college
and the early and mid-70s children,
do you perchance remember
all the crazed weasel-like running
you were doing with everybody
who came along in the early 70s, children?
Would you do that now, children?
I don't think so.
But maybe, maybe, children,
you'll be smart enough to do it.
Maybe you won't listen to me,
but you'll listen to the conspiracy children.
Remember, children,
the prisoners are happiest
with the prisons they built for themselves,
and the anti-sex league of 1984
is taking shape, children.
It's taking shape.
But I know you won't let the conspiracy
kick your away.
Now, Tony, I don't think you all know
what happened on July 5, 1998.
I think you all know that that's the day
the X-Men come down.
And you know, Tony, the X-Men,
they're businessmen.
They're simple businessmen,
just like Bob is a businessman.
And all they want, children,
is real estate.
They want real estate, children.
And they have a contract for the planet Earth,
the X-Men,
and they have the means to repossess it.
Do you know who stands in their way?
Say Bob, children.
Who is it that stands in their way?
Who stands in their way?
Bob!
Bob only stands in their way
with your help, children.
when you buy the MacGyver,
the subgenius 995!
You better watch the stores everywhere.
Hold on.
You go to the table where my will-o-law is.
I buy T-shirts, former stickers,
buttons, badges,
and the new Arise video tape.
Now, children, a long time ago,
when the church and the subgenius began,
1998 seemed as far away as your day.
But now, children, it's only 10 years in.
10 years in.
10, children.
10 little years.
And you may, those of you who like to read Nostradamus,
think that plagues are going to be visiting us in those 10 years, children.
Drought, fire, war.
But, children, the plagues of the next 10 years
will not be externally derived, children.
They will be internally derived.
They'll be the plague of sitting at home
and watching your tape
when you should be making Bob art,
when you should be corresponding with other subgeniuses,
when you should be buying the MacGyver,
when you should be buying from Bob
and tying to the sacred P.O. box.
The conspiracy, children, wants to break us apart,
make us function as that all-important consumer unit individual
and get rid of us.
But there's a man, children,
a man with a pipe.
And he's waiting, children.
He's waiting to save you.
But it's up to you, children, to open your heart to Bob.
It's up to you, children, to let Bob come in.
It's up to you to see the value in Bob.
And now, children, in closing,
I'm going to quote from the great subgenius saint Lester Bayes.
I'm going to read you something, children.
This was written upon Elvis' death, children.
So be patient with me and listen to this.
If love is truly going out of fashion forever,
then along with our nurtured indifference to each other
will be a more even contemptuous indifference
to each other as objects of worship, like Bob.
We will continue to fragment in this matter
because solipsism holds all the cards at present.
It is a king whose domain engulfs even Elvis.
But I can guarantee you one thing, children.
We will never agree on anything as we agreed on Elvis.
But, children, the fact is that just as this church
has an infallible pope, it has a fallible saint.
And in that regard, Lester Bayes was mistaken.
Because there is one thing, one man, one entity
we will agree on as we agreed on Elvis.
And who is that man?
Who is that man?
Children, that man is Bob.
And Bob is there for you.
Bob loves you.
Bob needs you.
Bob wants to help you.
Bob wants to fight the conspiracy.
Bob wants to bring you joy.
Bob wants to grant you slack.
Naturally.
With the help of the Reverend Island Stand.
With the help of Court Holland.
I'm forward, Court.
With the help of the Reverend Sterno Docs.
You're going to help me help the Calumet's Christmas City First Climbers
only for Bob Corral sing about Bob.
Are you ready?
Now, children, you're going to sing back to the Pope of all New York.
Say yes.
Yes.
Are you ready to take Bob into your heart?
Are you ready to take Bob into your mind?
Yes.
Are you ready to take Bob into your what?
All right, children, here we go.
You ready?
Yes.
There once was a man.
And when the Herbert жестed a bit,
Well, image number one,
forum for the fellow 내려ued by alisted
and140
c hein monda lo贈
He while he was of old
was who he named
Mel Lofthgrove.
And it's coming again
I know, I know
Don't want to scream and cry
This little world won't let you go
But who in your world
Are you trying to prove
That you're made out of gold
And can't be sold
But first
Are you
Experienced
White collar conservative
Flashing down the street
Pointing their plastic finger at me
Don't pursue my kind
Of drop and dive
I'm gonna win my free flag
High
Wow
l
Boy ikara
No
Boy ink
Shining
just like agen
Just a game
Long
You
Would KShour
Do it here, huh?
¶¶
Now imagine a world where heroin was legal,
but...
possession of coffee was punishable
by up to 50 years in jail.
In other words, friends,
think of a world where you could run down
to the nearest convenience store
just about any time of day or night
and purchase any amount of liquid heroin you wanted.
A whole bottle of heroin would be about three bucks.
Or you could go down to a heroin den
and sit and shoot up with all your shooting buddies
until about 2 a.m.
Then you'd get on the expressway
and drive home.
Or, for that matter, folks,
in the heroin world,
where imagine that the authorities
making heroin so much a part of their business world
that nobody closed a big business deal
without having a few shots of smack with the client.
Wouldn't there be billboards all over the roads
for the coolest brands of heroin
showing beautiful models,
skin popping next to a wall,
a waterfall?
And on TV, well,
not only would there be all these ads
showing your favorite sports heroes
shooting their favorite brand of heroin,
but in any party scene,
any scene of any TV show
where people were shown relaxing
or having a good time,
well, they're always taking just a few little
sniffs of smack.
Now, the leaders of a world like that
would have to be pretty insane, right?
I mean, it'd be obvious
that the leaders themselves
were not only heroin users,
but stood the game quite a bit
from the whole population,
aside from a few anti-heroin fanatics
leaning on this substance to relax.
But let's take it a step further, friends.
Imagine if these people made coffee illegal,
because they said it was addictive
and it led to harder stuff like espresso.
But yet, untold millions of people
had been drinking coffee for thousands of years
and no one had ever tried it.
No one had ever OD'd.
You drink it, and it sharpens you up a bit,
and then later you crash a bit.
But it's so illegal
that the smugglers are getting fantastically rich
having contraband coffee beans
flown up from South America.
And there'd be this whole subculture
of bean heads,
people that were into coffee
partly as a rebellion against the establishment.
And the whole reason that coffee
led to harder stuff like
espresso or NyQuil,
was because to buy coffee,
you had to go to a coffee dealer's house,
a pusher's house,
where you'd encounter people who were espresso users.
And on top of that,
a one-ounce bag of coffee beans
would cost like a hundred bucks
just for an ordinary Maxwell house grade.
And people'd be arrested
and spend their whole lives in jail,
maybe even be executed for using coffee,
which is relatively harmless,
while this whole planet of junkies
was going skyrocketing
and the world was going to be shot free.
And President Reagan would be up,
you'd see him in the news at,
you know, partying with world leaders,
all of them snorting a bit of smack
and shooting up.
Imagine what a horrible, topsy-turvy world
that would be, friends,
where they made a powerful,
central nervous system depressant
not only legal,
but glamorous.
While an organically grown,
harmless bean off of a bush
could wreck your life,
only because of the laws against it.
But, but,
but that could never happen here.
No, not in this world, friends.
Nah, nay, nay.
Couldn't happen.
No way, baby.
We're an enlightened people here.
So just forget that little allegory.
You know, let's not get depressing about it, friends.
Let's,
let's just lean back with a good stiff drink
and forget it.
It sure is quiet around here tonight
with the TV on the blink.
I know if I go to bed this early
I won't sleep a confounded wink.
Think I'll just mosey off uptown
to see who all I can see.
Sure as hell, I'll be up in the morning,
and, sweetie, you can go ahead and hit the hay.
No need waiting up for me.
I'll just stand here outside the old bar.
I can't go in,
cause I'm on the wagon.
No more of that beer, wine, and gin.
I'll just sneak up here and take a little look
through this window.
Oh, what do you know?
There's old Joe.
He's still on a bender.
Uh-oh.
I think he's seen me.
Yeah, he has.
And just look at that smile.
Oh, well, I can't see what it'd hurt
to stay just a little while.
No, Joe, I can't have one with you.
You know I'm on the wagon.
Well, make it a small one.
No use to keep on begging.
Hey, Joey, wonder what wife is gonna think.
You think she'll let me in?
What the heck, if she won't,
I'll just have to stay over at your house again.
But if I'm not, I'll stay.
If I go home like this,
I'm gonna be in a mess of trouble.
Here I am, done winning back on my word of honor,
feeling single and seeing double.
Hey, wait a minute, Joe.
Now, this is on me.
One more won't do no harm.
Hmm, that do feel good going down.
Sun nice and warm.
Hey, Joe, dig them crazy twins over there.
They're dressed up just alike.
Boy, wouldn't a little woman have a little
bit of a fit if I brought one of them home tonight.
I'm just sitting here kidding myself.
I wouldn't trade her for all the world.
Though she did put me on the wagon,
she's still a good old girl.
Hey, bartender, you got any coffee?
I bet I look a fright.
I've done gone and set your talking, Joe,
and got myself hiring a kite.
Hey, where'd old Joe go?
Do what?
You say you left.
You mean I've been sitting here all this time
mumbling and jabbering to myself?
Well, if I just knew for sure that my old tomcat
wouldn't mistake me for a mouse and that I could
get by the dog, I'd go sneak back in the house.
I'll sleep off this, too, I'm in,
and I'm gonna quit getting on these sprees.
I'm going back on the wagon.
I'm going back on the wagon,
because this drinking's killing me.
I'm sorry, I'm on a soapbox at this point,
and I'm gonna...
I'm in a bad mood.
So I'm gonna flip back over.
I'm gonna let Jane or Hyperclete just spell it out for you, eh?
This song is dedicated to Jesse Presley,
the aborted fetus twin brother of Elvis.
You can't arrest me, officer. I'm not drunk.
I might be half-ass drunk, though.
Whee!
Just a half-ass drunk.
Half-ass drunk.
Well, you know who you are
when you got a hangover and it's all hung over back
straight in your girlfriend's car.
Half-ass drunk.
Just you and me.
Sergeant Carter, haircut, gunner, piled, hooked up,
living off of LSD.
Have a ass drunk
and I'm feeling blue.
Well a flood come in and it washed away my den
and my water bill's still past due.
Have a ass drunk
Called my boss
I ain't feeling quite right.
Well it can't be Monday cause I don't remember Sunday
and my hands are sitting Saturday night.
Sweet love song.
Have a ass drunk
and I'm drunk as
Well I used to have a job but I'm sick of getting robbed
so I finally just up and quit.
Mama had a fit.
Have a ass drunk
and all my head feels odd.
Well baby needs food but his daddy's
got a need to lose.
Well the baby better find himself a job.
Have a ass drunk
and I'm having fun.
Stopped on a hill cause I had to take a pill
but I couldn't quite find my tongue.
Have a ass drunk
Hell I can see.
Well they said the light was red.
Now a couple of folks
Well there was 22 mangled
and there was one guy that was gimped up pretty good
he had to sort of walk like this for the rest of his life
and there was one guy
who was pretty neat
and he was a little bit of a jerk
but they had, he was hurt pretty good I guess
they had like this machine that was like
hooked up where he had this tube running up
through his nose you know
and that was the only way he could breathe
and well there was this one dude
it was like a blade he chopped straight down
on his toes and last I heard he still
couldn't walk. There was one guy
well this is what's weird
they found parts of him on the front of the car
and other parts of him on the back
of the same car
I mean it sort of defies the mind
doesn't it how you could find pieces
of the same person on the front
and back of the same car
I mean it, I just don't understand
they ought to run some kind of scientific test
I don't even see how that could even happen
And a couple folks dead
well it
well it sure looked green to me
half ass drunk
hell I wish I was
turned a brand new trans
amethyst to an old tin can
trying to outrun the fuzz
half ass drunk
I'm a victim of lies
well there's
nothing wrong with me your honor
I can say hell I got too damn deep of your eyes
half ass drunk
oh woe is
me
well it don't really pay
but it's steady every day breaking rocks
till they're broke as me
half ass drunk
well I'm half ass drunk
lord I'm half ass drunk
just sorry
oh half ass drunk
I already made it
I tried so we couldn't
oh that's right friends
that was uh
Chaynor Hyperkleets and Doctors4Bob
Doctors4Bob
uh
the most grateful of the
dead you might say
uh
from the uh
subgenius album
uh
Doctors4Bob
uh the title of the album
I think is Dick
comma a girl
and
of course if you want
information on just what
we're doing here on the church
uh just write to
Bob for free information
hold Bob
at
Bobox
one four oh
three oh
six Dallas
Texas seven
five two one
four
here's some old timers
to wish you a happy evening
music
Dangling dynasty
Think it felt alright
If that woman that you meet
Could I think
Of how you
Feel
Sweetie
You took love
And shined a light on you
You can never be gone
You better be chill
You need a drink, Lord
And shined a light on you
Like the evening sun
When you're drunk
In the hall of the evil
Which flows on
And you're late
Not a friend to leave you
In the cold, gray dawn
Oh, just ain't too many
Flies on you
I just can't
Crush them all
Angels beating
All their wings in time
Smiles on their faces
And a thing right in their eye
Oh, Lord, I heard one
Say
Say, something is
Come on off now
With that question
Hold it close
See the appeal
You bring desire
On your face
Oh, come on
sewn up
Felt as your
무엇
Wordly
Thank me please
to captain
Maid sleep
Yeah!
Like the evening sun
After relaxing on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time entertaining his friends.
Right Bob?
Bob?
This is the church that's gonna kick ass on the normals!
The mediocrities, the pit boys, the hippies, the Trekkies and the Admin!
I wonder...
What?
If God were to come to Earth, would they find him so strange?
That they would be afraid?
And would they shoot him?
Did not his son come once, Pedro?
And they kneel him to a cross?
And then spent two thousand years learning to believe in him?
All things take time, Pedro.
We will certainly come out on top again if we succeed in being defeated.
You talk like a madman!
But I live like a sane one.
I was a fascist when Mussolini was on top.
Now that he has been deposed, I am anti-fascist.
When the Germans were here, I was fanatically pro-German.
Now I'm fanatically pro-American.
You'll find no more loyal parties in all of Italy than myself.
You're a shameful opportunist!
What you don't understand is that it's better to die on your feet than to live on your own.
You have it backwards.
It's better to live on your feet than to die on your knees.
Enjoy life like Bob.
The End
I dressed up to do you harm.
And I'm here to make you go.
Give a kiss to Vladimir, for he's in the bottom of the tomb.
I hate you.
You love more than I do, don't you?
I never thought it was a legal term.
Some things work, I hate you.
I hate you.
More than, more than a black or blue.
I've seen you live a royal crime.
I hate you.
I can do everything to power you alive.
I can do everything.
I am a fine flame.
I'll give you a shine, bottomless issue.
So I won't do the same.
Peace and love will always be here, and I love you.
I've got a clear, clear case in my hands.
literature.
Thank you.
Thank you for your wine, California.
Thank you for your sweet little friend.
Yes, I've got the desert in my journey.
Uh-huh.
And I hit the speed.
I'm not sure.
Come on.
Come on down.
Swing a genie.
Come on.
Come on down.
Hey, you.
Come on.
Come on down.
You got it in you.
Come on.
Come on down.
Swing a genie.
Some jigs do do all your tricks.
Swing a genie do all your tricks.
Swing a men looking like me.
Swing a nice genie.
einzel opposing the south of shore
some Outside for Lebens wanna meet
Da talking about raiding a festival
I want you to come on, come on down, sweet Virginia.
Come on now, baby, yeah