Nay, nay, I'm afraid not.
Wish it was.
Thanks, Robert.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang.
Robert, on the way over here, I was scanning the radio dials,
and I must say that, as far as I'm concerned, you had the best hour in Dallas.
Thank you very much.
For the next hour, sit quietly, and we will control all that you see and hear.
Turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
Wake up, puppet boy!
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation to provide programs
which will be enjoyable, entertaining, and tasteful.
There is...
There is absolutely no other possibility.
Copyright 1986 by the Subgenius Foundation and the participants.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius Hour of Sight.
What?
Welcome, potential initiates.
And remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Gosh.
The practice of hallucinatory drugs was big back in then,
and they were hearing these messages that the Beatles were placing backwards.
What?
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is the Church of the Subgenius.
Hour of Slack number 51.
The long-awaited Subgenius anti-drug special.
Part one.
Take one.
This one's for Dr. X.
May he rest in peace.
Now, you're saying,
now, Reverend Stang, what is this?
The Subgenius anti-drug special?
What is it?
The Church of the Subgenius joining with the conspiracy
on its big fad of anti-drug mega-hype
and holier-than-thou witch-burning?
And I answer, nay, nay.
This is the anti-mega-hype we're hyping.
Not that we've ever condoned drug addiction.
Of course not, friends.
This is a church.
The only drug you need is Bob, my friend.
Bob will get you high and keep you there.
No, we're just anti-certain drugs,
just like the conspiracy is.
They only hate the drugs that they're not on.
Death to pushers.
That's what Ronald and Nancy, if that really is her name,
Reagan, say.
Death to pushers.
Oh, yeah.
And yet, dear friends,
they continue to use the United States government
to support the tobacco industry
and the alcohol industry.
Oh, oh, but we're only against drugs, they say.
There's nothing wrong with being able to have
a little drinky-winky now and then, is there?
And one cigarette never killed anybody
unless it's lit right next to a leaky tank full of church air.
That's what we're doing.
That's what Ronald Reagan says.
Oh, death to marijuana pushers,
but subsidize the tobacco industry
and the liquor industry.
Oh, friends,
you know, lips that have touched the bottle
will never touch mine,
though I do partake occasionally
of the holy frop admixture
prescribed by my personal physician,
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But like Bob himself said,
I frop that others may live.
And, friends, frop ain't one of those conspiracy street drugs.
Uh-uh, but we'll be talking about frop later,
maybe even next week.
I know, I know y'all want to know what frop really is
and how to get you some,
but we're just going to have to listen.
You're going to have to listen real, real close
in stereo headphones tonight, friends,
if you even want to gain butt.
An inkling.
Drugs have become an escape
for a nation of ignored youth.
Many parents too busy to stop,
listen,
and love.
Yes.
Hi there, Mrs. Darvon.
Okay.
And so she found the answer to her question by herself.
Bye.
Here comes Mrs. Darvon again in her nice soft dress.
Hi, Mr. Belliam.
Hi.
Well, today we're going to make sure that everybody feels okay.
That's right.
Yes.
They're eating Kool-Aid and pills.
Yeah, well, Mrs. Belliam, how well I'm sad today.
Pills.
Pills for the bad and pills for the good.
Pills for the young and misunderstood.
Pills.
I'm talking about pills now.
Well, pills in my hamper, pills in my socks.
Pills in my woods and pills on the rocks.
Yeah, pills.
Pills.
I'm talking about pills.
Pills now.
Pills.
Pills always tell me things to do.
Pills are better friends than you.
Yeah, pills.
Pills.
I'm talking about pills now.
My friends, the pills.
Oh, just give me some of them pills.
Oh, give me those pills, Bob.
Pills.
Here, have some pills.
And take some more of these pills in the morning.
More pills.
And that's just the sort of thing I was talking about exactly, gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, hello to you in Dallas, Texas.
This is the secret Reverend Bleepo Abernathy speaking to you over the airwaves of your local radio station there,
courtesy of Stang and the Reverend Bucknaked, for which I'm glad to present this opportunity to myself to speak at this time.
First of all, I want to say that none of the pills are ever good enough, as you all know.
And as you're out there, you know, you cannot feel anything without some sort of pill.
Now, that pill could be, of course, you know, your average, you know, vitamin or dexatrim or something like that.
Or it can be Jesus.
It's any kind of pill that you mention at all.
We don't want to get too specific here.
But let's just face it, friends.
You're all looking for a pill.
And I don't know.
I don't know.
We're not talking a quart of pills.
We're talking a bucket of pills.
Some people relate to half an old-fashioned bathtub full of pills.
Like, sometimes, I don't know how much quarts of pills go for in Dallas right now.
I think in New York, you can get about a half a handful of pills for what, like, a pint of pills might cost you in Austin or Chicago.
But we're in Dallas now, so we're talking quarts of pills.
But this is just...
Heliopters full of pills.
These are all legal.
They're not drugs.
These are herbs.
They've been smuggled in by Tibetan llamas, which have been working for Bob for centuries.
I heard they put them on the bellies of sea turtles at one point.
They'd fit them in the Atlantic.
They put them on...
A seven-year voyage.
They put them on your tongue.
They put them on...
They might put them on...
...mongooses.
They put them on your nose.
You can put them in your shoes.
And Bob makes the best pills ever once made.
Yeah!
You get them pills!
And you feel...
You feel wise.
Your heart feels wise.
You're buying.
And you know that you're the only one, and the rest of them are wrong, and you're the
only one that's right.
And that's how you're supposed to feel, because you got the pills of Bob in you.
That's right.
Possess these children with the fire of thy holy way.
Fill them with the blood of your passion.
That will enable their weak spirits to move in pursuit of your holy work.
Our children are faced with the peer pressure of taking drugs and drinking alcohol.
It is readily available.
The effects are devastating.
And I walked into the family room, and the family was watching the TV set with their
back to me.
And then I started firing a rifle.
And I was like, I'm going to die.
And I was standing behind my dad.
And I shot him.
Through the head?
Yes.
And then right away?
Almost instantly, my mother.
This would sharpen you up and make you ready for a bit of the old ultra-violence.
Can you spare some cutter, me brothers?
Go on!
Do me in your bed!
I'm a bastard, cowards!
We don't want to live anyway.
Not in a stinking world like this!
Oh?
And what's so stinking about it?
It's a stinking world because there's no law nor there anymore.
It's a stinking world because it lets the young get onto the old.
Look at you, darling.
Oh, it's no world for an old man any longer.
What's talked about water is it at all?
Men on the moon and men spinning around the earth.
And there's not no attention paid to earthly law nor there no more.
Oh, oh, dear little lad.
I fought for thee and more.
In the U.S. today, one of every ten,
high school seniors uses marijuana daily.
Thirty-five percent of all students use drugs at least once a month.
It isn't all the illicit, illegitimate market that's the problem.
We have a panacea in America that is a pill to solve every problem.
The farmer, he got wild.
The bricklayer got plastered.
The mechanic, he got tanked.
And the construction worker got blasted.
And daddy beat up mommy and broke her collarbone for good luck.
And everybody's drunk.
And everybody's wasted.
And everybody's drinking on the job.
The garbage man got trashed.
The janitor got messy.
The taxi driver got smashed.
And the waitress, she got tipsy.
In Kansas City, New York City,
the great big city,
the itty bitty city now,
everybody's drunk.
And everybody's wasted.
And everybody's drinking on the job.
Well, there's a whole lot of places that I ain't been.
A whole lot of things that I ain't seen.
A whole lot of things I'll never be.
The generation that would change the world is still looking for its car keys.
Whoo!
The terrorists got bombed!
The president got hit!
Security was tight
Yeah, the Secret Service got lit
The FBI, CIA, DWI, USA
Everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's stoned
And there's nothing that's gonna change it
Cause everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking on the job
Me, I'm just frothing on the job
And lucky to be doing that, friends
Yeah
Cause since they've had this crackdown on crack
They have succeeded in true conspiracy fashion
In making it so you can't get anything but crack
I wonder why that is
Actually, you can't even get crack in Dallas
You get plenty of cocaine
Oh yeah, cheaper never
Cause coke, like most of these other drugs
Lights up that little spot in your brain
That would normally be lit up by sand
I won't do it here
Cause your American business is still up there
Would you have figured it out with this mouthpiece?
The bébé moi
And Cap einige kuci
No, sorry, will you please transmitted?
that a mighty undiluted, unneagified squirt will flood that spot with,
with just the right juices from just the right glands.
But, but, since to read that good book takes days,
you've got to be in the right place at the right time for that song to have the effect.
If you're going to get it through sex, well, that takes at least five minutes,
and often you have to take them out to dinner.
But, my God, you can just go out and spend some money,
and in no time at all you can light up that little spot,
just as soon as you can get back in your car, baby.
Just as soon as you can get you a sample.
Fire that booger up, boy.
What else do you need?
Why would there be any need for noble feelings for all mankind,
or even any sense of human decency whatsoever?
Why would?
Why would there be any need for anything but to light up that spot in that brain?
And when you get those headsets,
where you just tape a little pad to either side of your temple,
one in the front and one in the back on a shaved place on your head,
and you have that little control in your pocket with a battery in it,
as long as you've got you a $1.98 9-volt battery in that thing,
you can crank it up to 5, to the 5 marker on the dial,
and feel mighty damn good.
Turn it up to 10, and you'll never turn it off.
There'd better be somebody standing by.
It's anywhere past 6 on the infinite control with knob,
and you're not going to turn it off.
You're not going to, friend.
You might turn it off for a second, but it would hurt.
It would hurt to turn it down, even to turn it down.
And once you've felt that 10 setting,
you're not going to want to live with anything else.
You're going to be crying a year later,
for the 11 setting.
You're going to be begging.
Oh, you'll be reading all the catalogs,
waiting for that breakthrough that'll give you an 11 on that control.
Oh, yes siree.
You think they got a drug problem now?
You think there's a drug problem in the United States,
in the whole world now?
Oh, mark my words, ye sinners.
Wait until you get some electronics involved, baby.
You think those computer whizzes got rich quick.
Wait until they invade.
They're going to invent the head zapper.
Oh, it's my head, you'll say.
It's my head.
That's all you'll be able to say.
Every song will be the song,
It's my head.
That'll be the only awareness you need.
It's just between you, your head, and your control.
Your pleasure center stimulator control.
Oh, yeah.
You'll be like a monkey in a cage,
sitting in a pool of his own saliva.
That's right.
Because once you feel number 10,
you ain't going to,
you can kiss what you now know as reality.
Goodbye, baby.
Yes, and after a while, even the 10 starts to feel like pain.
But you can't go looking for the 11 button,
because you can't get up.
You've been there too long, because you're dead.
You're a ghost that died while it was high.
Yep, yep.
If you die when you're high, my friend,
your spirit becomes a wandering shade.
Wandering, trying to score for eternity.
Or at least until a subgenius priest comes along
and sends it spanking back to where it originally came from.
My God, and here I am, running out of gas.
You're always going to run out sooner or later.
That's what you got to remember.
Too much, oh, yeah.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Till you run out.
And you will, friend.
You'll run out of that church air right when you least expect it.
Right when you thought you had all the church air in the world.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I had all the church air in the world.
But, but, but, Negi has it now.
Oh, you'll scream, you'll cry, you'll wail and gnash your teeth,
and you'll wish you could die.
You'll wish you could die, but you can't.
You can't die, because your terror keeps you alive
and manufactures just enough church air for you not to die,
but just to keep needing more.
You're going to be ready for the finals in 1998, my friend.
Let there be slack.
You know I've seen a lot of people walking around
with tombstones in their eyes.
But the pussy don't care.
Oh, if you live or if you die.
God damn.
Mm-mm, the pussy.
Oh, my boy, if it's drugs you want, the old doctor can help you out.
Right this way.
Get your hands off me.
I don't want to leave.
Then roll up your arm and bend over.
Do you want regular or premium?
Oh, this is ridiculous.
You guys are nothing but a pack of cards.
Drink me.
Drink to me only.
Must be some way out of this.
I'll change the air.
That's what I'll do.
Let's see.
What have I got left on the climate control?
Uh, dust storm?
No.
Tibetan wilderness?
Land of the pharaohs.
That sounds great.
It's so very lonely.
You're 600 light years from home.
Before age extra.
Today they must trust you.
But they wouldn't.
Thanks, big boy.
My Southern Ocean, with my度에 .
And the water, and the water, and its meaning.
Mama! Papa!
Open up! Here's the police!
The madness is a journey to hell,
where the brain is ill and weak.
In ever-changing dimensions,
where the evil nights live.
Goddamn!
On the pusher!
...the world bank, and you still find the time to make the nicest peccary pie in all of Longbox.
Oh, Darlene, I remember when the least little problem used to put you right to sleep.
Oh, not anymore. Today's modern narrow-gogo women just pops these simple little...
...anger dreams.
Swell demonstration, eh Sarge?
It's routine.
Maybe. But if the chief ever caught me taking these pills, he'd snap my head off.
Here, try one of mine.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, the chief himself's been on these for a week, and he's a change.
And welcome, dear friends, to the...
...hour of slack on K-N-O-N. Praise Bob!
Good. Open your mouth, Chef.
No, I don't like pills.
It really does help take the trouble out of falling asleep.
The haunting reality is that any one of these addicts, prostitutes, or runaways could be your child.
There was me. That is Alex, and my three droogs.
And their enemy is the God-centered family.
An 18-year-old teenager named Diane, living here in Hollywood, took her life.
She was under the influence of LSD.
She had experimented with it as a result of peer pressure from her friends.
This young lady had everything in the world to live for.
She had just won a Grammy award.
She was signed for a television series.
Today, drugs and alcohol have replaced baseball and football as the national pastimes.
We are producing a country without a future.
Any punk will tell you there is no future.
They don't think about it.
They wallow in just now operating. They only have the present.
I can't hold my breath...
...any longer.
In front of the policeman?
The policeman has no choice but to go with him.
See what he has to say. I'll minister to him.
I've tasted the dew on the lips of sweet death herself.
You were right, Paul, when you said that someday we'd all live in the treetops.
Like apes.
Like monkeys.
Like rodents.
Like...
Vermin.
Like the squirrel that has found itself electrocuted.
On my electric fence, the one I use to keep Zandy inside and the dogs.
The squirrels can't take the voltage.
They fry. They...
They die convulsing.
They suffocate.
Because their lungs can't take it anymore.
They need another breath.
But yet, their brains are aware of the terror.
My little boy walked out one morning and he said,
Daddy, is the squirrel sleeping?
Is the squirrel sick?
I said, no!
My child, the squirrel's not sleeping. The squirrel's not sick.
The squirrel is dead.
The squirrel will not come back. The squirrel can't be fixed.
It turned into a skeleton.
A squirrel skeleton.
My son said,
Father, I want to be like that squirrel.
I, too, want to be a skeleton.
You can't arrest me, officer. I'm not drunk.
I might be half-ass drunk, though.
Eee!
абсолют
Half-ass drunk
Hell, you know who you are
when you're got a hangover
And it's all hungover back home?
Say to your girlfriend's car, have a ass drunk.
Just you and me.
Sergeant Carter haircut, Gomer Pyle hookup, living off a LSD.
Have a ass drunk.
And I'm feeling blue.
Well, a flood come in and it washed away my den.
And my water bill's still past due.
Have a ass drunk.
Called my boss.
I ain't feeling quite right.
Well, it can't be Monday cause I don't remember Sunday.
And my hands are sitting Saturday night.
Sweet love songs.
Have a ass drunk.
Hell, I'm drunk as shit.
Well, I used to have a job, but I'm sick of getting robbed.
So I finally just up and quit.
Mama had a fit.
Have a ass drunk.
You know, my head feels odd.
Well, baby needs food, but his daddy needs a lewd.
Well, the baby better find himself a job.
Have a ass drunk.
And I'm having fun.
Stopped on a hill cause I had to take a pill.
But I couldn't quite find my tongue.
Have a ass drunk.
Hell, I can't see.
Well, they said the light was red.
Now a couple of folks.
Well, there was 22 mangled.
And there was one guy that was gimped up pretty good.
He had to sort of walk like this for the rest of his life.
And there was one guy.
It was pretty neat.
They had.
He was hurt pretty good, I guess.
They had like this machine that was like hooked up where he had this tube running up through his nose, you know.
And that was the only way he could breathe.
And well, there's this one dude.
It was like a blade.
It chopped straight down on his toe.
And last I heard, he still couldn't walk.
There's one guy.
Well, this is what's weird.
They found parts of him on front of the car and other parts of him on the back of the same car.
I mean, it sort of defies the mind, doesn't it?
How you could find pieces of the same person on the front and back of the same car.
I mean, I just don't understand.
They ought to run some kind of scientific test.
I don't even see how that could even happen.
And a couple folks dead.
Well, it sure looked green to me.
Half-ass drunk.
Hell, I wish I was.
Turned a brand new Trans Am into an old tin can.
Trying to outrun the fuzz.
Half-ass drunk.
I'm a victim of lies.
Well, there's nothing wrong with me.
Your honor, I can see.
Hell, I got you damned.
You dug your eyes.
Half-ass drunk.
Oh, woe is me.
He's been gone for so long.
He can never come home.
He is gone for one more fifteen days.
I could have been a sinner for my Culker.
I've been gone for more
Held up in an intensive care ward
Lying on the floor
I was gone for all those days
But I was not all alone
I made friends with a lot of people
In the danger zone
See my lonely life I'm for
I see it every day
I'm for
Now imagine a world where heroin was legal
But possession of coffee was punishable by up to 50 years in jail
In other words friends think of a world where you could run down to the nearest convenience store
Just about any time of day or night and purchase any amount of liquid heroin you wanted
A whole bottle of heroin would be about three bucks.
Or you could go down to a heroin den and sit and shoot up with all your shooting buddies until about 2 a.m.
Then you'd get on the expressway and drive home.
Or, for that matter, folks, in the heroin world,
where imagine that the authority is making heroin so much a part of their business world
that nobody closed a big business deal without having a few shots of smack with the client.
When there'd be billboards all over the roads for the coolest brands of heroin
showing beautiful models, skin popping next to a waterfall.
And on TV, well, not only would there be all these ads showing your favorite sports heroes
shooting their favorite brand of heroin,
but in any party scene, any scene of any TV show,
where people were shown relaxing or having a good time,
well, they're always taking just a few little sniffs of smack.
Now, the leaders of a world like that would have to be pretty insane, right?
I mean, it'd be obvious that the leaders themselves were not only heroin users,
but stood to gain quite a bit from the whole population,
aside from a few anti-heroin fanatics leaning on this substance to relax.
But let's take it a step further, friends.
Imagine if these people made coffee illegal.
Because they said it was addicting, and it led to harder stuff like espresso.
But yet untold, millions of people had been drinking coffee for thousands of years
and no one had ever OD'd.
You drink it, and it sharpens you up a bit, and then later you crash a bit.
But it was so illegal that the smugglers are getting fantastically rich,
having contraband coffee beans flown up from South America.
And there'd be this whole subculture of bean heads,
people that were into coffee, partly as a rebellion against the establishment.
And the whole reason that coffee led to harder stuff like espresso or NyQuil
was because to buy coffee, you had to go to a coffee dealer's house,
a pusher's house, where you'd encounter people who were espresso users.
And on top of that, a one-ounce bag of coffee beans would cost like a hundred bucks
just for an ordinary Maxwell House grade.
And people would be arrested and spend their whole lives in jail,
maybe even be executed for using coffee, which is relatively harmless,
while this whole planet of junkies was going scot-free.
And President Reagan would be up there, you'd see him in the news at, you know,
partying with world leaders.
All of them snorting a bit of smack and shooting up.
Imagine what a horrible, topsy-turvy world that would be, friends,
where they made a powerful, central nervous system depressant
not only legal, but glamorous.
While an organically grown, harmless bean off of a bush
could wreck your life only because of the laws against it.
But...
But that could never happen here.
No, not in this world, friends.
Nah.
Nay, nay.
Couldn't happen.
No way, baby.
We're an enlightened people here.
So just forget that little allegory, you know.
Let's not get depressing about it, friends.
Let's...
Let's just lean back with a good, stiff...
Drink...
And forget it.
Praise God.
The best thing you can do
Doctor Smokey
Nurse Smokey
Just a little bit of smokey
Judge is smokey
Even the lawyer too
So you've got to live a life, you say
Is that prop?
This is habit for opposite-y-lops, too.
You can smell it.
It doesn't smell like marijuana at all.
If you can hold it to the microphone,
it's got a very pungent odor.
I don't like this stuff.
It is free.
We have to smoke it.
It's one of the rules.
We're talking about a barrel of Havifrottem.
We're talking about a void,
a limitless void of Havifrottem.
We're talking about several alternate realities.
We're talking about your basic...
We're talking about putting it in your pipe and smoking it.
And another thing I want to tell you about tonight,
we've had some calamitous times in Malaysia.
You might have heard about all the rains we had.
Yes, dear friends, it was flooding over here,
but, oh, Bob, oh, good old Bob knew
that when it flooded in Malaysia,
you better build your houses on stilts.
So all our houses are built on stilts over here, dear friends.
Ha-ha.
We knew a long time ago that when those floodwaters came,
we'd better be sitting pretty, sitting high,
so nobody could come by.
And speaking of sitting high,
we need something over here in Malaysia.
Yes, our whole drug cabinet was washed away.
And after a flood, you know, we need some drugs.
We need some drugs that can help the people out here.
So what else...
Something really, really scary.
It was Mike Hills.
I wonder if that guy Bob took them.
I guess I better go down this dark river.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, okay, what?
Oh, okay.
Where are we going?
That guy took all my pills.
Okay, well, I still got my tape recorder and my camera.
You don't need those anymore.
You can give them to me.
Ha-ha.
Come on.
Whoa, look out!
Whoa!
Charlie's in Mama's mouth
Well, it's all right
The girl's got a very large mouth
But it's all right
Her teeth look okay
She must be crushing them quite a bit
Of course, her mouth is empty
She's got lips all around the hole
And there's the large
And we can only assume
As to how she's been using it
Charlie's in Mama's mouth
Well, it's all right
The girl's got a very large mouth
But it's all right
She's got lips all around the hole
Where she puts her food in
They call it the mouth
Which is as good a place as any
For the tongue to include in
That's why they call it the mouth
They call it the mouth
La-la-la, la-la-la-la
Kind of young, kind of wild
Charlie's enormous nose
Well, it's all right
The girl's got a very large nose
But it's all right
She once was okay
But she's been blowing it quite a bit
Of course, her twins are extra large
And we can only assume
As to how she's been choosing it
Charlie's enormous nose
Well, it's all right
The girl's got a very large nose
But it's all right
She's got stuff all around the hole
Where she puts her food in
They call it the mouth
And when it finally locks away
I guess you'll probably try the drug again
They used to call it the mouth
They call it the mouth
La-la-la, la-la-la-la
Kind of young, kind of dead
Charlie's disgusting brain
Well, it's all right
They call it the mouth
The girl's got a very dead brain
It won't come back
She used to convey
But then she took an extra hit
Of course, her friends are extra dumb
And they were terribly excited
While they watched her do it
Charlie's disgusting brain
Well, it's all right
The girl's got a very dead brain
It won't come back
She's got dirt all around the hole
Where they dump their boxes
They call it the grave
Which is as good a place as any
For a chump to repose in
That's why they call it the grave
They call it the grave
And all around
At the side of the grave
Stood Charlie's friends
Who could not save
This stupid girl
From the way she behaved
Hey!
But among the mourners
And the frowners
They cry away
Hey!
In the donors
No, I ain't dying anymore
Although it doesn't exist
And they are shooting each other
Because of a new prize
Billions of dollars
In American money
the hard-earned or hard-stolen dollars of America's heroin addicts.
Hey, if you want any of this junk, go to it, boys.
But this young girl, 14 years of age, in the eighth grade,
recently took 50 pills to take her life.
She has slit her wrist and she's been into heavy drugs.
I've got super dynamic overdrive.
I'm operating in 10,000 revolutions.
My motor is being preserved because I'm operating in supernatural overdrive.
Are you certain you know what reality is?
No matter what I do to change it, normal I remain.
Normal can be just as bad as riding in a wheelchair.
Today, serious heresy.
This is a deviant state of consciousness.
Not so much deviant opinions as having a kind of experience
which is different from regular experience.
We are taught what experiences are permissible.
And therefore, if a person has so-called strange experiences
and endeavors to communicate,
he has to communicate these experiences to other people.
He is looked at in a very odd way and asked,
are you feeling all right?
Because people feel distinctly uncomfortable
when they realize that they're in the presence of someone
who's experiencing the world in a rather different way from themselves.
They call in question as to whether this person is indeed human.
They look like a human being, but because the state of experience is so different,
you wonder whether they really are.
And in rather the same way, in a very everyday kind of circumstance,
when you're sitting in a bar drinking, and you find you have a drunk next to you,
and he turns to you and says,
I say,
and you sort of move your stool a little way away from this man.
Because he's become in some way what we mean by non-human.
And you expect a high of about 65 degrees tomorrow,
increasingly cloudy skies once again, with some rain in the forecast.
All right, boys.
Bob's got you hooked.
Bob's got a monkey on your back.
Hey, you know that...
Bob's doing something spooky again, ain't he?
That's what you're listening to.
Yeah.
That's the kind of Bob that comes up out of the shadows.
That's the kind of Bob that follows you home.
That's the kind of Bob that calls you up in the middle of the night and hangs up and suites you.
Hey, Doug, let's kill Bob, you know.
Would you like some cappuccino?
Yeah, hell yeah.
I have an espresso machine in there.
Espresso.
I feel the need to express myself into a cup,
and then pour it back into the spot in which I once stood.
Pour it into my shoe,
and I will be reborn.
I'm born again.
A man of caffeine.
Y'all get your own whiskey,
get your little snort,
get your little reefer,
get your little...
Are you serious?
Plain people that's fixing to kill you
puts the drugs out here for you.
How many of y'all know that?
Let me see your hands.
Some of y'all got your hand up,
got reefer in your pocket.
And we sat in the Carova Milk Bar,
trying to make up our razzoo docs
what to do with the evening.
The Carova Milk Bar sold Milk Plus.
Milk Plus,
Vellaset,
or Synthemesk,
or Drencrum,
which is what we were drinking.
This would sharpen you up
and make you ready for a bit of the old ultraviolence.
And they got your head so messed up,
everybody got their hide,
and don't like nobody else's.
Yeah, the whiskey drinkers have always looked down on the wine owners.
Reefer smokers now got a attitude about whiskey drinkers.
All at once the cocaine snarters think they're more sophisticated
than the reefer smokers.
And the coffee drinkers hate them all.
And yet there is more stomach cancer caused in America every day
from drinking coffee than lung cancer from smoking cigarette.
And after enough of us been riding it long enough,
Harvard University, where they old tricky self had finally come out now
and said,
cancer of the colon is caused more from drinking coffee than anything else.
And to show you how insignificant nothing they got you,
ain't nothing you can do about it but keep on drinking coffee.
It's my impression.
I'm not talking about manslaughter.
I'm not talking about
Milk Plus,
Vellaset,
or Synthemesk.
A lot of evangelical leaders seem to have forgotten that.
Now we understand the drunk.
We know what's the matter with him and it'll wear off.
But when quite unaccountably a person gives a representation
that he's suddenly got the feeling
that he's living in backwards time,
or that everybody seems to be separated from him by a huge sheet of glass,
or that
he's suddenly seeing everything in unbelievably vivid detail.
Moving colors.
You say,
well that's not normal.
Therefore there must be something wrong with you.
We like you and should ignore you,
but instead.
Makes,
oh god it hurts,
my headaches come back.
Ah,
ah,
ah.
If these headaches keep up,
I'm gonna have to go to bed.
Fuck.
I'll go down in the medicine fish hole.
I'll go in the medicine fish hole if I have to.
Thanks for the kiss.
Oh.
Do you have any aspirin?
Probably.
Getting stoned on sunshine
Getting high on air
Getting to it naturally
Really getting there
Getting such a high on
Loving what I do
I'm so full of happiness
Hooked on something new
Life is such a trippy thing
Hello birdies, hello spring
Each day on earth is a day that's worth remembering
And I mean just what I sing
Life is such a groovy thing
Don't pity me
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling
My pot is filled with flowers
My grass is bright and green
My tea is brewing in my cup
And still I make the scene
So just don't try to change me
I love the world I've found
I've got to fly my own sweet way
Don't you shoot me down
Ha ha ha
Life is such a trippy thing
Hello birdies, hello spring
Each day on earth is a day that's worth remembering
And I mean just what I sing
Life is such a groovy thing
Don't pity me
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling
A ding-a-ling
Don't pity me
I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling
A ding-a-ling
Ding-a-ling
O drink of that
A ding-a-ling
Or condescending
It's just silly
Ding-a-ling
A ding-a-ling
Schefff
Haha
Friends, that was definitely one of the stupidest songs ever created.
That was Frank and Nancy Sinatra, believe it or not.
And well, friends, this is the end of your hour of slack.
Ron Lindsey is here with the Soul Oldies show.
And for those of you who want to know what I was playing tonight,
it was all on tape, so I wasn't cutting in and telling you.
You're just going to have to write for information from the Church of the Subgenius.
That's right.
You, friend, are going to have to dare having your address on our mailing list.
Do you know what sort of government agencies get hold of our mailing list,
whether we know it or not?
Eh?
I don't either.
But anyway, you need to write to Bob, friends.
Write to Bob at the Church of the Subgenius,
and here comes that P.O. Box number.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
This is KNON 90.9, the voice of the people and other things.
In Dallas, Fort Worth, Texas.
Huh!
There can be no such thing as a safe pleasure drug.
Even if it had no harmful physical side effects,
it still would have, it would still be overused
by some people who cannot get pleasure in other ways.
That's what's so sad.
Oh, I know smoking cigarettes causes cancer, but I can't stop.
But if them same folks told you smoking cigarettes in your automobile
would corrode your engine, it would be no more smoking in the car.
Now that's kind of sad.
Because they've manipulated us to the extent that these educational
institutions ain't nothing but tricks.
Why?
Well, I didn't tell you this before, but he's an egg salad addict.
You mean he's hooked on drugs?
He's hooked.
He's got a chicken on his back.
Yeah, well, too bad for him.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
As far back as educated men have recorded their history,
veils have been lowered to disclose a vast new reality,
rinse in the fabric of man's awareness.
And somewhere in the endless search of the curious mind
lies the next vision, the next key to his infinite capacity.
There's reason to believe that incessant stimulation of the reward
or pleasure centers of the brain will lead to a resetting of the pleasure threshold
so that ordinary enjoyable things no longer stimulate that area,
or if they do, they aren't effective, and one can't enjoy ordinary life
so that all one has left are the chemicals.
If we keep using drugs, we're going to die.
If we keep using drugs the way we are, we're going to go down the chemical dumper.
Well, you look puzzled, Peter.
Oh, then you're still plain Peter Wayne.
But don't worry.
You'll all be crystal clear as soon as you cross over.
Consciousness expanding.
Properly induced CE will give a subject full awareness of capabilities never known before.
What?
The doses have been somewhat...
...sort of for me the last time or two.
If you can hear me now, you'd better listen to my warning.
Warning, warning...
Well, I went on down to my girlfriend's shack to see how they did hang.
When I got there, her cupboard was bare.
I couldn't ignite a thing.
There was no shard, no bone, no twig.
I brought my comic book collection.
Was about this big, yeah.
Well, from...