Well, I've been around him a long time. That's the first time I ever heard him praise anything but himself. I can't believe it.
Now listen carefully.
Hello. Hello, Bob.
I'm beginning to smell a big, fat, crummy rat.
Take off your pants.
Me?
Take off your trousers.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
You got more on me than any guy in this town, and I'll lay you out that the minute you get out of here, you're going straight to the cops and spill everything you know.
Me?
Yes.
Yeah.
Is that correct?
No.
Yes, it is.
Thank you.
That will be all.
Oh, thanks, Bob.
Excellent.
Yes.
Very interesting.
That's beside the point.
I walked down the long corridor, heading back to my hometown cell and the same dangerous double life.
I wondered for an instant how it would be to have a wife and kids to go home to.
And then I killed the thought.
I can't afford to have thoughts like that.
I'm a communist for the...
Self-genius.
Power of...
What?
I walk alone.
Dana Andrews will return in just a moment.
This is Dana Andrews.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it's Hour of Slack, number 1063,
the all-commy episode, thanks to Comrade Lemur,
also heavy on the Norell Prefaganda,
and the resurrected ancient subgenius album, Media Barrage No. 4,
and Puzzling Evidence, and Dr. Howell, and Radio Synesthesia,
and Cuff Links, and wait, what, what, what, what's that?
Oh, look, it's Dr. Bad Idea.
There goes my spleen.
You haven't even sucked the tip of that conspiracy.
Uncover the truth.
Did he hit you? Did he hurt you?
Vascular embolization. Bullet got into his arterial system.
You ever been to a swingers party?
I don't know.
Right-handed, a Libra, circumcised, rich.
Smelled funny.
Diazepam.
Pinzos, pinzos.
When you're home alone, you lock the bathroom door.
I don't even know you.
Sure you do. We all do.
It's human nature to avoid being vulnerable, isn't it?
Wait, so you're saying the guy has B.O.?
Hotty odor, bad breath.
Later.
Exactly as Noah getting into the ark triggered the deluge that destroyed the earth in his day,
and that it's very highly possible that when this all takes place,
that a great cataclysmic judgment will do that very thing.
And we do not know that it wouldn't happen in 1982,
but we don't know what day it'll happen.
This article was referring, as I said, to the nine planets in our solar system,
Mercury, Earth, Mars, Uranus, Pluto, Jupiter, Venus, Saturn, and Neptune,
when these are scheduled to be perfectly aligned in 1982,
that these things perhaps can happen.
Many scientists with varying ideas of what could happen
have expressed their views that huge solar flares will take place,
resulting that could be disruptions in the television and radio communication,
and a great deal more.
I see that I'm not going to have...
much time to go into this anymore today,
and so I'm going to carry it through tomorrow
and try to bring it to a more clear climax.
But may I tell you that all of these are warnings to us
to repent of our sins and to get ready for the coming of the Lord,
for we can see great and drastic things that are going to take place on the earth
when Jesus comes and the judgments of God are being poured out upon a Christ-rejecting world.
Parasite intelligence,
parasite intelligence,
the parasite mind can control the actions of its host.
Symbiosis.
Symbiosis?
Yes, exactly.
Why can't we combine with the other intelligences and wipe out the parasite?
Oh, no, you don't understand.
A disease of the mind.
Yes, it's made only with the very whitest pigment.
White, white, white, white.
Parasite intelligence,
parasite intelligence,
why can't we combine with the other intelligences and wipe out the parasite?
Oh, no, you don't understand.
You've obviously never heard of Gabaltorium.
No, what about it?
Gabaltorium-G has a radioactive half-life of 93 years.
If you take, say, 50 H-bombs in a 100-megaton range and jacket them with Gabaltorium-G,
when they are exploded, they will produce a doomsday shroud, a lethal cloud of radioactivity
which will encircle the earth for 93 years.
Oh, what a load of cum.
No question.
We have a problem.
We all know that.
But that doesn't mean that we ought to change the whole system we have, find out where the problems are,
the character of the problems, and address them.
All I want is some help.
I don't want to be sitting out here and forgotten with poison water.
That's all I ask is for some help.
The state of Michigan said there's nothing wrong with it.
The EPA came out and said there is something wrong.
The Health Department of Michigan later sends me a letter saying it's all right.
There's nothing wrong with it.
There's nothing wrong with your water.
You can drink it.
And if you don't think that doesn't scare a mother to find out that a boy is urinating
to your blood when you know he's only got one kidney, believe me, I've had it.
I cried all the way to the doctor's office.
Joe, come here a minute.
I got a red hot tip for you, Joe.
See that guy with the red suspenders driving that car with the bright red fenders.
I'm not a red hot tip for you, Joe.
I know he's one of those heavy spenders.
Get that communist Joe.
He's filling my gal with propaganda.
And I'm scared she will meander.
Don't want to take the chance that he'll land her.
Get that communist Joe.
He's the most revolting character.
And the fellas hate him so.
But with the girls, this character is a good one.
I'm a comrade Romeo.
Since my love he's sabotaging.
And the law he has been dodging.
Give him what he deserves, jailhouse lodging.
Get that communist Joe.
Get that small Joe.
He's the most revolting character.
And the fellas hate him so.
But with the girls, this character is a comrade Romeo.
Since my love he's sabotaging.
And the law he has been dodging.
Give him what he deserves, jailhouse lodging.
Get that communist Joe.
The Cavaliers, dear friends.
And before that, Media Barrage Number 4.
I am going to cover the results of the
And, first of all, some short talk.
In order to understand, you'll need to send in an email from Nixon.
America, we're throwing you away.
There are two ways to get to Tehran, sooner or later.
To get there sooner, fly Iran Air.
Only Iran Air flies from New York to Tehran non-stop.
You arrive in the afternoon in time for dinner and a good night's sleep.
You wake up refreshed.
On other airlines, you arrive after dark, often much later.
Fly to Tehran the fastest way on Iran Air.
Try the urgent way to fly.
Fly, the best way to stay.
Serving you in many more ways.
Iran Air is rolling your way.
Remember, you're only one stop from London, Paris, or Tehran on Iran Air.
Ah!
Ay-yi-yi!
Killings, carnage, bombings, suicide.
Many Americans see little hope.
Terrible wars are time of joy.
Joyous times.
You know, we're not leaving.
Sick.
Disaster.
Excitement and opportunity.
Renewed violence and terror.
Joyous times.
Huge mistake.
You know, unbelievably huge mistake.
You know, war is a time of joy.
Hostility is in place, intact.
If you want to join the Marines, you have to have sex with me.
You know, so she had sex with them.
Joyous times.
To join the Marines, you have to have sex with me.
Tantalizing abuse of power.
We're not leaving, we're not leaving.
Devastating lapse in judgment.
Memorialpref.com has more of where that came from.
And now, Lean Murr.
I'm a good boy now.
I have two cufflinks where there was only one before.
Are you?
Cufflink.
Give it to me, give it to me, give it to me.
Why?
I can't help it.
Cufflink.
I can't do it.
Yes.
He couldn't afford a cufflink.
But I know that nothing will save me if the cufflinks find out what I've engineered.
Comes the showdown.
I'm a cufflink for the great cufflink.
I walk with their help.
Dana Andrews will return.
This is Dana Andrews stepping out of the cufflink to remind you that our story was pure fiction.
We've changed names and modified incidents to protect the cufflinks.
And that's what counts.
Because you were the wrong cufflink.
Yeah.
I'm a cufflink.
The person I'm looking for is, should be very interesting and, you know, not plastic
or anything like that.
And someone who enjoys going out and having a good time and a good conversation with.
And I guess that's about it.
Okay.
Your code number one more time?
239.
Thanks for calling.
Good luck.
Thank you.
So long.
See you then.
More proof that a cork really works.
Marvin L. Kosnowski, president of Kosnowski Corks, is proud of his corks.
I am proud of my corks.
I ask your friendly cork dealer for a file for today.
If you itch, you need soft and soothe.
It's swimming, you know?
High temperature today, 100 degrees even.
That makes it the 63rd day this summer that we've been there.
Well, actually, the city has been there for a while now.
year because almost the entire and if weather conditions had been different the toxic cloud
released might have blown over manhattan and it's scary it's damn scary especially the fact that i
got two kids i normally die with these chemicals irid double x helps keep you extra extra dry
let your fears well up
you have them now don't deny them their chance to claim your soul
know that within every man is a monster and this monster may create a monster
a frankenstein monster to bring your realistic world crashing down around you you say it can't
be true
you
al qaeda is calling
i uh fear the rise of democracy
good morning i i fear the future i made my position clear
help help this week i met with my dead
to keep this momentum going we're pursuing a strategy
you
just wanna tell you now report we will defeat the world we will defeat our next
control
it's 여러분
broemente
lie
non as is
unrestraint
same
the com
world strong
and leave behind a violent terrorist nation.
The American people expect terrorist attacks.
We, uh, I, uh, and by the way, the enemy, me,
that's why I instructed the Justice Department to give Al-Qaeda to the United States
and stop the United States.
And I believe we're all in terror.
And we must bring an end to the Justice Department who are the terrorists.
And therefore, this country of ours is why they're calling.
Al-Qaeda is calling, but America's weak.
And, uh, is it war? Clear, clear, clear, clear.
Clear, clear, clear, clear.
This is an absolute, this is, now, now, now, thank you all very much.
I just can't believe.
Uh, thanks to Norrell Preff.
It's a privilege.
Uh, asteroid comes down, kills all the dinosaurs,
and yet life still goes on.
Right.
It's hard to, it's hard to wipe life out.
It was many times more powerful than all the nukes we have today.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's, it's very hard to wipe out life.
It's, it's just hubris if we think we, we could.
Now, that doesn't mean that we should, that we should be careful.
Well, maybe we should try.
I'll take you up on that challenge.
I think we should wait for the saucers to come before we try that.
Because we all know, as we all know,
that this, this program has already stated its nuclear ambition, uh, before.
I, I, we have already announced our intentions, uh, here at, uh, CSB
to get our own nuclear arsenal.
Because, you know, we don't feel safe.
Well, the Church of the Subgenius already has three nuclear,
nuclear weapons.
Nuclear, that's all?
Yeah.
That's the best you can get.
The conspiracy has thousands of nuclear weapons.
The Church of the Subgenius, we've only got three.
But yet we dare to use them.
See, I, I can't believe the, the Church of the Subgenius
is stuck with, like, you know, primitive 20th century weapons technology like that.
I can't believe the saucers haven't, uh, you know, left anything better behind.
No anti-matter bomb?
No, no, no.
These were, these were, uh, trinkets that, uh,
that, they were, uh,
meant to be offerings to the Exists,
in other words, for, for certain alien technologies,
but the Exists refused to trade.
Yeah, I, I can't blame them.
Yeah, and somehow they ended up in the hands of the group
that was dealing with the Exists back in the 40s
when they had made contact in Roswell, New Mexico.
Hey, listen, this is a long-distance call,
so I'm gonna get off now.
All right, well, it's been fun.
All right, later.
Thank you.
So, what do you do, uh, you know, if,
if you're, uh, you know, a,
this is something that has occurred to me, actually,
the, uh, the, uh, the ban on liquids on planes now.
Well, it's...
I think that's gonna be, like, completely reversed in a few years
because eventually they allowed,
eventually they allowed, uh, nail clippers back on again.
I can't believe they went so far as to ban nail clippers for a while.
Well, they're gonna, they're, they're working on explosives detectors.
You see, what's really funny is,
is the terrorists come up with some really ingenious little plot
that can only work once, you know,
and then after they bust that plot,
or after that plot is already carried out,
then, then they implicate, uh, they, they, uh,
they implement some really horrible draconian security measures
that everybody gripes about, and, I mean...
Well, if the...
Who's the shoe bomber?
I mean, come on, like, who,
who the hell is gonna try and use a shoe bomb
after, uh, Richard Reed's trial run, you know,
was less than successful?
You never know.
I've never even heard of such thing.
Shoes have been used for smuggling before.
Right, I've never heard of the shoe bomb before that.
I wonder if it was detonated with, like, a shoe phone.
Like, Maxwell Smart.
No, he was, no, it required him, uh...
I'm, I'm joking.
Beverages, shampoo, lotion, toothpaste, and hair gel.
I don't know where you boys are getting all your fa-
But, uh, I know something's wrong here...
First of all, first of all...
Second! Second!
There is no evidence, there is no evidence!
Beverage? Shampoo? Lotion? Toothpaste? Hair gel?
I've never seen anything like this in my entire life.
And so I think they decided to have some fun.
A terrorist, a terrorist, a terrorist.
Mass murder on an unimaginable scale.
Major threat.
This major threat.
This is a well-orchestrated plan.
Major terror plot, United States.
Major terror plot.
Beverages, shampoo, lotion, toothpaste, and hair gel.
Somebody's abusing my rights, that I'm sure.
Erase Norrell Kraft for that one.
Don't do this, please.
Careful.
Hey, don't do this.
You don't need anyone.
That's not true, I need you guys.
If nothing matters, how can I matter?
I don't know if nothingness matters or somethingness matters.
I'm trying to figure that out and I want you to help me.
You know what?
It's somethingness, nothingness.
I can't.
Just you figure it out.
Let go, let go of me.
Okay, uh, hold on now.
Tell me what happened, okay?
She won't stay and share this with me.
Tell me what that is.
It's important.
I mean, I see it so clearly.
Yeah.
You use petroleum, you're a murderer.
That's a fact.
A murderer.
I know you say it clearly.
Killing the ozone and all the creatures that it's hurting.
Calm down.
Two, killing Arabs and oil-producing dictatorships
where everybody is poor.
Yes.
That is cruelty and it's inhumane.
I know you've talked to me about this.
All right, so if this world is temporary,
Yeah.
Identity is an illusion.
Then everything is meaningless
and it doesn't matter if you use petroleum.
No, no.
That's got me very confused.
No, it matters.
It matters.
Look, look, Tommy.
See, this is a universe
and that's our galaxy over here.
What universe?
This.
Tommy, come on.
Come on.
There's dust and gas there.
Yeah.
There's us over here
and good and bad luck in the middle.
That's chaos.
That's my B.
You know, this doesn't sound like you.
No, Bubon talks about space.
Where'd you get that book?
You sent it to me.
No, no.
We would never give you this book.
This is a pretty good book.
You should read this.
What?
She says nothing's connected.
It doesn't matter what you do.
You can drive a car.
You can burn up gas,
which would explain the way things actually are
where people do destructive things
like it doesn't even matter.
Tommy, Tommy, everything is connected
and everything matters.
There is not an atom in our bodies
that has not been forged in the furnace of the sun.
Now, isn't that cool, huh?
Yes.
That's a cool thing, isn't it?
But.
But what?
You tell me where she contradicts that.
Right here.
Where?
There.
Less than 5% of the cosmos
is composed of the same elements
that compose human life.
You know.
There you go.
That means we're all alone
and we're miserable and isolated.
Molly, if you, listen,
if you, if you, if you leave me
before he gets done dismantling,
we, he will never make it to the other side, okay?
You know what?
I'm done with the dismantling.
You don't want to ask these questions?
No.
I, I want to live my life.
What is that life, baby?
What are we part of?
Who are we?
Look at this.
Do you know where these come from?
Yeah.
My closet.
Indonesia.
Baby, this is the truth, okay?
Little girls like you,
they have to work in dark factories
where they go blind for $1.60 a month
just to make mommy her pretty shoes.
Can you even imagine that, Caitlin?
I don't want the children to work in factories.
Don't listen to him.
Daddy, daddy.
Daddy is crazy.
Daddy's not crazy, baby.
The world is crazy.
Shut up!
A clip, friends, from I Heart Huckabees
and before that, much more Elpref.
And as before, so below.
Yeah!
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition.
This week, America received a stark reminder
that box cutters kill our people.
Death on a massive scale.
The terrorist threat is being used for partisan political advantage.
The inconveniences you will face are mass murder.
I'm grateful for the terrorists' plight.
We've been fighting attacks.
We've raised a threat.
And we will win the war on freedom.
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition.
There are some 50,000 nuclear weapons in the world today.
I think we really need nuclear weapons
because Russia and everybody else has got them.
Jesus began to give to them.
The signs of his coming and the end of the age.
And one of the signs he referred to
was the abomination of desolation
that was spoken of by Daniel the prophet.
This hasn't taken place yet.
Just don't buy your doomsday theories.
Well, you better buy them.
We are in worse shape from the point of view
of our military preparedness
than we were on the 8th of December 1941,
the day after the Pearl Harbor attack.
The Russians got the definite advantage on us right now.
But we need to show more strength.
We've got to catch up or get ahead of them
or we're dead meat.
Well, after we come through here
and we purify through this plant here,
it takes out some of the chemicals in the mud out of it.
But you can't drink.
We can't drink it.
Nowhere in the world you can drink it
unless you hold your nose.
The ice is coming.
The sun's divining.
Meltdown expected.
The wheat is torny.
Engines stop coming.
But I have no fear
because London is drowning.
I
live by the rules.
I live by the rules.
It'll also tell you about the prelude to Armageddon
and also some of the strange events
that have been forecast for 1982.
Some of the things that are coming
in these last days.
Do people say you're slipping
that you can't take it anymore?
Extreme irritation.
However, there has been more fighting overnight.
Bloodthirsty war.
They were bound for a cult.
I always was a barbarian.
Human vivacity.
Hum Kämp.
비싹신 This is the blow.
Se purposes of the recht.
The Snigger van定 MURGHEN
You are everything
They will Lind back
The Russian national
A long spent
Trust the bread
Not thirsty wars
Legendary savages
Complete sell-out
Cancer, you call it
I can achieve a sort of intellectual understanding of what that means
Never an emotional one
I always was a barbarian
I feel a desire for a little disconnection
Quiet, angels
I'm gonna pass one more miracle
And you gotta help me
In case it's a new kind of miracle
In my own image
Let there be man
Sure, we gave second thoughts to paving over the earth, but...
Well, like, cement's not very biodegradable.
And we had enough of it down already.
We figured we may as well go ahead and pave over the rest.
It's a lot easier than tearing all this up.
We could air-condition and it got rid of the bugs.
I don't know, it's just a lot easier to keep things clean.
I mean, we got air-conditioning,
toilet training for all our children.
We've got all the rest of the world.
We could tear down the rocks, we could chew them.
But you don't need nature for beauty.
The buildings here are inspiring monuments to our adaptable workers,
such as the enchanting shopping metroplexes.
During Let's Go Shopping,
a 20-minute break and a 20-hour workday,
humans compete to consume as much as possible.
And all it costs is time.
What husband could resist letting his wife have us free for free?
And there's sure no trouble deciding what you want.
Oh, don't mind me.
Nobody wants me.
I used to be popular, but not no more.
Hey, man, you want to buy me?
All of that's been bought by all of you.
Besides, he only costs five minutes.
And when shopping time is up,
all the products you've just bought
are flushed away down to the factories
to be recycled and back on the shelves by tomorrow.
From Let's Visit the World of the Future,
a film done 33 years ago
by your...
truly Reverend Ivan Stang.
That soundtrack was on Media Brach 4.
In the background, I believe we hear
uh, uh, three...
five-fisted tales of Connie at 9X Day.
And now more Norell and Macaca.
Macaca, Macaca, Macaca, Macaca
Macaca
Welcome to America
and the real world
but Macaca
The enemy.
That's what we're saying.
Macaca
Who was, uh, uh...
pulling it out.
corpses
But I also talked about the human suffering agenda.
And I also had relations with Macaca
because, uh, well, uh,
the idea is to try to help create, uh,
you know, a
a more dangerous world.
Uh, to kill innocent life.
I didn't...
Part of the reason we went into Iraq, uh, was, uh,
the main reason we went into Iraq at the time was we thought he had weapons of mass destruction.
Turns out he didn't, he didn't, he didn't, he didn't
send the wrong message.
You had suiciders leaving Iraq.
You know, everything was just fine until we arrived.
They were gonna stir up the hornet's nest.
What did Iraq have to do with what?
The attack on the World Trade Center.
Nothing!
The capacity to make...
The attacks of September the 11th, uh, were ordered by...
Macaca, or whatever his name is.
Uh, who would, uh, power.
Nothing!
Positive, constructive ideas.
Stirring up even more trouble in a part of the world
that, uh, the Middle East.
Now look, I didn't...
And so, my question, my answer to your question is, is that
imagine what the world would be like...
This is just, this is just, this is just, this is just...
The, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the...
that, uh, had so much resentment and so much hatred...
The mission is complete as far as I'm concerned.
Except for it's part of take threats before they fully materialize.
Nobody's ever suggested that the...
Probably will never come.
So welcome, let's give a welcome to Macaca here.
Welcome to America and the real world.
Paying suiciders.
And I believe if we ever cease to pray,
and cease to seek God,
God will destroy this country!
And I believe I'm gonna live to see cities in America,
cities in this nation, literally, instantly destroyed!
I believe I'll see it soon.
You can keep your eyes on some West Coast cities.
And you watch.
I'll guarantee you when the majority of our population
begins to turn their back on God,
and begins to try to tell us that
a perverted lifestyle is a normal lifestyle,
and they have no time or tolerance for God,
focus your attention, and you watch,
because I promise you, God will not continue
to leave that city, that people, without judgment.
The victims of FEMA is...
Here at Renaissance Village,
Trailer Park...
Trina, Trina, Trina, Trina...
Living in government provided trailer homes.
Prosecutors in Michigan, however, say they are standing by
terrorism charges against Walmart in Central Michigan.
One of the most violent areas...
Wait, wait...
And now there's another hassle.
Because of the work being done here by
some really fine Americans from different agencies in our government,
America is not yet safe.
And we gotta be right one time.
Proud to report that in this building,
we've got some good ass working hard,
and energy, and effort.
Difficult job.
We're willing to kill innocent life to achieve political objectives.
The United States of America is a extremist group of folks,
bound together by an ideal,
ideology,
willing to use terror to achieve their objectives.
And, uh...
And we've got some good ass,
and the best ass that we have is...
Trina, Trina, Trina, Trina...
More at norellpref.com
Each human shares his spacious total living unit
with a different female each night,
since they are circulated to provide variety and companionship.
The unit contains two single beds,
and a large variety of luxuries,
including the Eye of Taxis,
a crime prevention device,
and of course, a normal machine,
constantly supplying everyone with the TV shows of your dreams.
Everyone watches the normal machine.
TV, TV, TV, TV...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha...
Ha!
Oh...
O!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
Ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha...
TV variety show has been declared an endangered species...
of any waste material.
TV Variety Show
Also sold separately...
Nerf hook...
Nerf ball...
and super nerd.
And I have chosen
you,
Mr. Beale,
to preach this evangel.
But why me?
Because you're on television, dummy.
He's a blank.
Waiting for the final finished face
to be stamped onto it.
But whose face?
Albert.
Forget Brad.
Albert, come back to me.
Where are you?
Albert, picture a tree in a field.
Good.
Now put someone you respect in the tree.
Hey!
Still Brad's dad.
Add someone else.
Like who?
You know, someone who can understand things.
Someone who can help you.
Who's your guide?
Well, I use Magritte,
the Belgian surrealist.
I got someone.
Who is it?
Mrs. Shermer.
She was my high school English teacher.
She helped me.
All right, good.
Look, he pushed her out of the tree.
Okay, Mrs. Shermer has a vacuum cleaner, Albert,
that sucks up fear.
Now she's going to send you rays of security
and complete acceptance.
Okay.
Oh, he chopped her head off.
Yeah!
Hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
You're doing well.
Now, you can't...
Now, don't give up now.
Didn't she vacuum the lawn?
Yeah, but then he vacuumed her.
I had to chop him up with a machete.
Okay, Albert, Albert, I'm going to let you in on a couple of secrets.
One, your mind is always occupied on something,
so it may as well be something helpful, like Mrs. Shermer in her vacuum cleaner.
Two, there's a lot of things you can do about it.
There is no such thing as you and me.
So then there's just nothing?
Three, there's no such thing as nothing.
There is no remainder in the mathematics of infinity.
There's only the blanket.
I thought I understood the blanket.
Now I'm not sure.
In my little 11-year-old child,
I think his mentality is much more alert than his 16-year-old boy.
The point is, stupidity is all around us,
and it's not worth getting upset about.
It is not a thing a sane man would do.
The doomsday machine is designed to trigger itself automatically.
But surely you can disarm it somehow?
No, it is designed to explode
if any attempt is ever made to untrigger it automatically.
It's an obvious coming trick, Mr. President.
We're wasting valuable time.
Let's make war.
We're getting ready to claw at us.
Well, we've done it.
We've let loose the dogs of war.
I wonder how they'll destroy us.
Lombardy, bring the blood, leave us all.
History shows I'm getting up, yeah.
I'll get your points up.
The folly of man.
Godzilla!
You two act like it was the end of the world.
Well, it could be.
But we will return to enjoy your final moment.
Commentator Jonathan Mathias with another bulletin.
And now, as the Sino-Russian border war continues to rapidly escalate,
U.S. authorities are beginning to question
to what degree we will become involved
in what could...
...quickly grow into global conflict.
Abort firings. Abort firings.
Interception will fragment the Sili-carrying missiles.
Tonight's presentation on the beach was of course fiction.
All Americans share the common desire that a nuclear holocaust will never happen.
And certainly an alert, prepared America
is our greatest hope.
To safeguard in a nuclear age.
I really don't know, because I don't know the situation neither does the American people.
Our current policy is that we do not launch until we are under attack.
Now the danger of that policy today is the Soviets can deliver their missiles with such accuracy
that they'll be able to knock out in a matter of relatively few seconds
all of our ability to retaliate against the rest of the Soviet missiles.
Range two miles. Missile still deflecting.
Range one mile. Missile detonated.
All operators.
If a true alarm sounded most of our defenses would be alerted and within ten minutes many of our jets would be in flight headed for their targets.
Yet under enlisting law only the President could give the final order to fire our nuclear warheads.
... airborne at the time as part of a special exercise we were holding called Operation Dropkick.
Now it appears that...
that the order called for the planes to attack their targets inside Russia
with an average load of 40 megatons each.
General Turgidson, I find this very difficult to understand.
I was under the impression that I was the only one in authority
to order the use of nuclear weapons.
That's right, sir.
You are the only person authorized to do so.
And although I hate to judge before all the facts are in,
it's beginning to look like General Ripper exceeded his authority.
Candy fam for Mongo!
Mongo, Mongo, Mongo, Mongo!
Mongo like candy!
Candy fam for Mongo!
Mongo too intoxicated!
Mongo like candy!
Candy fam for Mongo!
Erase your own craft for that one.
Is money more important than people's lives?
And in their pursuit for private interests,
a lot of chemical companies will not accept legal,
moral responsibility for the results of chemical waste pollution
until absolute proof shows that a specific chemical
from a specific plant caused a specific disease.
The treatment you receive when you do business with these industry giants,
it's frequently frustrating,
and to make matters worse, they don't seem to care.
You won't find this attitude at Bill King's Breko.
Well, I'll tell you what, everything I figure is a hazard.
It progresses as the years go on,
and eventually we'll never be able to control it.
If you take a look,
those maps that show concentrations of various forms of cancer,
you can pick out the industrialized areas of America.
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
There are changes
Lying ahead in every road
There are new thoughts
Ready and waiting to explode
When tomorrow is the day
The bells may toll for a song
But nothing can change the shape of things to come
Certain changes have been taking place here,
such as the increase in the beatnik crowd
and the increase of the drugs that's used
and distributed by the beatniks.
There's only one thing for it.
We can save America, and that's change every person one at a time
by the power of Almighty God working in that corrupt heart.
The gates of hell was governed.
Because in Bible times, government sat at the gates of the city.
Yes.
The Bible says the gates of hell shall not prevail against them.
There's no question about it.
We are going to see the most tremendous turn of events.
Not only in this nation, it's going to affect the whole world.
Peace, did Hitler say.
Next move, Czechoslovakia.
There are a few beatniks in Berkeley.
I'm sure from what you folks hear,
you would think that the population in Berkeley
is really becoming beatnik-like all the time.
Well, the...
percentage of them is increasing a bit.
But with this movie actor getting into the governor's chair,
Ronald Regan from Hollywood,
I think that he's going to tame them down a little bit.
May I close on a personal note?
I was asked once in a press interview what book I would choose
if I were shipwrecked on an island and could have only one book
for the rest of my life. I replied that I knew of only one book that could be read
and reread and continue to be a challenge. The Bible, the Old and New
Testaments. I can only add to that my friends that I continue to look to the
scriptures today for fulfillment and for guidance. Indeed it is an incontrovertible
fact that all the complex and horrendous questions confronting us at home and
worldwide have their answer in that single book.
L-O-L
L-M-E-O
The Frotter Sody
and before that
some old
puzzles
and media
barrage
for
Mongo
was from
Norell
Craft
and now more
Norell.
She's a virgin?
What are we talking about?
An immaculate conception?
More like the immaculate perception.
Pseudo-psiesis.
Imagine pregnancy.
It's all in her head.
Well, that would explain what she was doing in Dad's bed.
Panicizing.
Wow, wow.
Hormone levels can change, setting off all the biological signs of pregnancy.
Kind of makes sense.
Hormones travel the same channels as adrenaline.
Swollen abdomen.
Lack of menstruation and sometimes bilateral galacteria.
Milk production in both breasts.
Leaking can be brought on by stress.
Emotion.
Additional or physical stimuli cause prolactin to shoot through the endocrine system, ending
in the mammary glands and triggering the cells to lactate.
Father was clueless.
About all the women in his life.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Check out these photos.
Two stains on the inside of the shirt we found at the dump.
In an electric kind of way.
And then you put your mother in the freezer and you waited until trash day.
It's not my fault.
Believe in sanity.
Good defense.
People throw things away every day.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
8.12 p.m.
We found nothing.
12.15.
Stone.
For about an hour.
1.30 p.m.
We was able to talk.
4.10 p.m.
Little brat.
Big boy.
I beg your pardon?
Didn't do too well, did ya?
Ya?
Hmm?
Did ya?
Oh, no ma'am.
10.46 p.m.
Ma'am?
That's me.
What?
I said me.
Yes, ma'am.
No, ma'am.
Yes, yes.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah.
No.
No?
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
And at 6.10 p.m.
What?
Huh?
Poor boy.
A thanks to Lee Murr, and now a scene from I Heart Huckabees, in which two seekers learn
how to gain enlightenment by slapping themselves in the face with a hard rubber ball.
Now.
Not so hard.
Sorry.
Now.
Did you get it?
Yeah, you stopped thinking.
Yes.
It's fantastic.
It's like I'm here, but I'm not.
So I'm not here.
It's just...
I don't...
I don't know.
Do it one more time.
It's like I'm a rock or a dish of mold.
I'm whatever else is around, so I'm free to just exist.
This is the answer.
We just have to be this all day, every day.
It's the answer.
Do it again.
Now.
Not all over.
No.
All covered with
But I still love them collection for now.
Where time will not last.
I never know why.
Can only ask Christ because it is what He has taken away from me.
Come to what he is from another world
Never know why.
Not a word of life for the desire on our shoulders,
an only love to have you fuller then God will not endure,
The Murr did that, and now let's go back to KPFA's Puzzling Evidence Show
shortly after the subgenius event called 9X Day.
Yeah, you don't need that anymore.
It's the end of the world.
There's nothing left now.
Besides, who has a pager anymore?
That's so three days ago.
Pagers are so early in our day.
But rather deserve an alarm system to ensure democratic progress.
This, however, does not matter to Satan,
who constantly spreads his spiderweb-like snare.
And boy, did we see a weird moth at X Day.
A strange moth with wings like crumpled paper bags
and an abdomen like that of a giant wasp,
only flattened like that of a giant katytid.
What was it?
Could it have been a wasp?
Discolored like the fingernail of a giant giant.
Could it have been a wasp, you say?
It isn't? I mean...
No, it was a moth.
A moth, I tell you, a moth.
And not only that, do you know what else we had at that campground,
that accursed place?
What? What did you have?
Sugar!
That is...
I knew this to be a statistical fact because...
Sugar!
I hope you don't...
What's wrong with sugar?
Are you something wrong with them?
Well, they get you.
Aside from that, I have no particular...
Sugars have a right to exist.
Yes, that makes you wonder why I know I put them on the ark.
But, you see, outside our meeting...
Outside our little shack, our Lincoln Log...
A girl! A girl!
Yeah, there was a girl outside the shack, but...
Let's have some girls.
More importantly...
Yeah.
Somebody left a cup of coffee out in the rain.
You mean the girl has to be a producer and the girl is a...
And the next day...
One girl has to be on...
Is that next to the cake that you left out in the rain?
A girl show?
That was unfortunate.
I had nothing to do with it.
Let's talk about hair and pink stuff.
I'd like to have a piece of cake right now.
The point I was trying to make was that...
You're wearing skirts.
What point? What's the point point?
What's the point of a point?
Inside this cup of coffee that was left out overnight,
I looked in it and it was...
What?
Full of dead insects, which had fallen into it during the night.
I had to be quiet for that.
Is this the cup you drank?
I took a spoon and started spooning out waterlogged,
or rather, coffee-logged moths and things.
And you still drank it, right?
And then I uncovered about three or four...
Yes!
Or five.
All right, call...
Maybe even six or seven...
Jiggers!
Ah!
But then you drank the coffee anyway, right?
I certainly did not, but the point I was trying to make was that the...
Because the flash is going to reflect off the window.
The jiggers really bring out the flavor of that mocha.
Insects.
I don't care where it comes from.
It was the jiggers.
Jiggers!
But don't let it fool you.
He did still drink the coffee, and that's what was the real point in this story.
The real point is that he'll do anything.
With coffee.
And I'll do anything with this collar.
Look, I'm just trying to...
We're going to cheat on each other.
I just wanted to...
What?
If I could just...
You just said, why don't we cheat on each other?
Why don't we have jiggers on each other?
What kind of sort of soap opera is this?
I've got that covered.
I'm involved in doing that right now.
Yes, on the show.
I am cheating.
So, anyway, the X's did not come and rupture us all up,
although they've been taking bits and pieces of us.
I think this time they've been working on hardware.
A lot of us arrived home to find that our computers didn't work right anymore.
That happened to me, actually.
It did.
It took a day for my computer to start working right again.
I was going to try and do some serious work on it,
and then suddenly it got better, so I didn't have to fix it.
I lost a hard drive, and Rev Lon, one of the Kentucky boys, lost a hard drive.
And he said because of that he hasn't been able to masturbate.
Oh, yeah.
A week and a half.
Well, let that be a lesson in becoming a...
In order to get off.
Well, maybe he needs to improve...
The pictures in his head.
Yeah, exactly.
You just need a fertile imagination.
Right.
You should be able to remember the pictures on your hard drive well enough in a pinch, so to speak.
Well, the best part about using your imagination is you're not confined to people who've actually been photographed in the nude.
You can...
I don't know.
Anyway, people use your imaginations.
Don't let the media rob you of your creativity.
Well, you know, I'm too polite to masturbate to somebody I know.
Yeah.
It's like you feel like you should ask them first.
Ha!
There's a certain protocol, you know, and if you're looking through your pornography and suddenly there's your friend or your teacher or your mom,
it's just not the same.
It can kind of spoil it.
It's like doing that while you're watching Soul Train and suddenly the host comes on.
Just as you're getting her.
So, I mean, like I say, it's a delicate thing.
Okay, yeah.
I'm not going to comment on that.
It's a delicate thing.
Well, Ernie earlier in the calling seemed to be concerned that you had admitted to all kinds of fun having.
Oh, yeah.
You know, believe it or not, people actually do these things.
I don't know.
He thought they were going to come after you because you admitted that.
Yeah.
In public.
Oh, yeah.
And Johann Sebastian Bach never did before a concert.
That was the point he was trying to make.
I'm going to...
How does he know?
Well, you know what?
Actually, I would bet that Bach probably didn't masturbate because when you consider that he had 20 children,
he was clearly getting his fill with his wife, I would think.
Next year I want to go to Axe Day.
Yeah, well, you know, it's not too...
Well, why don't you just go to Starwood in a couple of weeks?
I mean, Stang will be there, too.
Yeah, Johnson, you might actually have better luck there.
Yeah, you'd actually...
Getting into the kind of trouble you want to get into.
What's so big about Starwood?
More people.
More women.
Yeah, and...
Lots more.
And more normals disguised as weirdos, so you'd have a lot more luck.
Yeah, you'd fit right in.
Yeah.
Now, we need to bring more women into the church and everybody...
Actually, as I was gazing about at Axe Day...
And I was doing counts, and so I was also security and registration.
And I ascertained that we've just about hit the equal point.
During the Chili...
The Subgenius International Chili Cook-Off,
it was absolutely one gal for every guy.
They were not necessarily attached to each other.
Right, but...
And none of them were what you would call untouchables, either.
It was mostly...
In fact, I was thrilled.
I mean, even I found a woman at Axe Day.
I'm going to have to go off the phone.
I'm pretty soon.
I'm getting so thrilled.
Thinking of the babes of Axe Day.
Yeah.
Also, they're promised to be even more because there were a lot of little baby girls.
So, yeah.
In about 20 years, you know, we'll have...
Another crop.
Yeah.
That's the wonderful thing about beautiful girls is they're a renewable resource, you know?
Just when one crop starts to wear out, the new one is ready to go.
It's not the sausage fest that our jealous rivals like to say it is at all.
Well...
What do you think of Chris?
It just seems that way to the single guys because...
Well, it seems that way to the single gay guys.
All the women there are taken.
He was really complaining.
Oh.
We only have one really gay, entirely gay subgenius that was at Axe Day this year that I know of.
He was happy about how many nice-looking young men they were, but he said they rejected his advances in all cases.
I didn't even know.
Now, see, if he would be...
If he would try the bi thing, he'd probably score easily because he's a nice-looking fella.
You know, gay guys always have an easier time getting close to the ladies.
Of course, I think it's specifically because the women don't feel like they're being pursued, so it's easier for them to...
Being married helps.
And then this guy represents the giant sandwich.
Or does he represent a mattress?
Mattress.
I'm sorry, he represents a mattress.
He's a mattress bag.
And...
That ancient breed of animal...
The mattress bag.
I took a bath every morning with his baby.
I took a bath.
You took a bath with her.
I took a bath with her.
It was part of my routine this year.
Yes.
And here we see...
Sweet child.
The strange rites and rituals...
Sweet child of the stars.
Among the subgenius tribe.
You know, folks, this isn't just something we're making up.
We're trying to bring you esoteric news that they keep off all the other channels.
You can't find me.
I'm not doing this stuff in the regular...
Sinister block.
Sexy plans.
We've got it all.
In other news, don't play with fire and don't put the cigarette out in your eye.
You.
It's a bad thing to do and a bad idea, so don't get that out of your head right now.
And thanks to the Puzzling Evidence Show on KPFA in Berkeley with Dr. Howell and Dr. Philo Drummond.
This that you're listening to is Hour of Slack number 1063 from the Church of the...
Subgenius.
For more information, check out subgenius.com.
And now, just for sick fun...
We will tie a long rope to Manu, the monkey, fleeing from our arrows.
And if you hit the monkey, Tarzan will go into the jungle and bring you back a prize.
Perhaps a cruel and ugly civilization that spawned you.
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Yes, I guess so.
I have a new game, Torgo.
If you aren't too old for games.
Rest assured, my stupid friend.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack.
Torgo, don't feel good.
It was horrible.
What was it all for?
Your beauty is only of the outside.
But he ran into the path of the elephants.
The
Federal Government的人
Subtitles by
present-day- Investment vor HAIO