Ah, yes.
Dear friends, welcome to Hour of Slack number 874,
which, because I'm trying to upgrade my system,
will actually be a rerun of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse number 449,
which itself was a rerun of Suzy the Floozy's B-Girl War-O-Rama,
Bob's Slacktime Funhouse number 271 from 1999,
and yet it seems as if it was recorded yesterday.
So enjoy the work of Reverend Suzy the Floozy
with this show originally broadcast on beautiful WREK Atlanta.
To praise Bob.
Now let's see, what is our next move?
May I suggest something, dear?
Is it something, Powell?
Exquisitely vile.
Bud.
Hello?
Your party's calling.
Yeah? Who?
Your party's there.
Oh, put them on.
One moment.
Hello, Adolf. How are you?
Oh, that's too bad.
Yes, I know.
Huh?
You have a production.
Oh, that is serious.
There I am.
America, you say?
America has a production.
Oh, American production.
Well, I...
Oh, Adolf.
Wait.
I've got the very thing.
Guaranteed to keep the stars and stripes waving forever.
Is that right?
At half-mast.
What is it?
Yeah.
Am I applied?
No, it's nothing new.
Been tried and proved.
Good thing.
Oh, you remember?
In your own country.
When you first got your start.
It must be something you planned like the Stalin's.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the proletariat must be a little bit more confident.
Now relax, Adolf.
And watch history repeat itself.
Be more clear.
In a word, my dear.
War.
Hello, everybody, and welcome to the Wide World War.
I'm Sonny Todd.
And I'm Bertie Swan.
And we're here to bring you all the blood.
All the carnage.
All the raw excitement of mankind's favorite spectator sport.
The thrill of victory and the agony of defeat.
Broadcast right in your living room from hotspots around the world.
Today, we're going to take a look at a territorial dispute in the Far East.
A coup d'etat and an unstable military dictatorship.
And a possible comeback attempt by one of the third world's most popular tyrants.
But first, let's go down to the jungles of Central America where several teams are battling to the wire for a playoff berth in the upcoming 20th Century World Conflict Championship.
Hello again, everybody.
Chuck Gazoo here with Danny Don Stegma on a steamy wet afternoon in the tropics.
Trying to keep up with all the action down here in the Western Hemisphere playoffs.
And the race here in the Banana Division is as tight as anyone could walk.
And a tough one to keep track of.
Right, Danny Don?
That's right, Chuck.
You know, half the time, I'm not even sure which side is the home team.
One minute, it's the military regime.
The next, it's the rebels up in the mountains.
Gosh, if I didn't have a program, I'd never be able to keep up.
Well, one thing's for certain, Danny Don.
And that is the right-wingers are intent on bringing a winner here to the tiny developing nation of Buenos Noches.
They've made some important trades in the off-season with the U.S. team and beat up their offensive till now it's ranked second here in the Banana Division.
Right, Chuck.
And at the same time, we've got to keep in mind that Soviet training and hardware give the leftist guerrilla team a very...
...very solid look this year, too.
So my bet is we're in for a really interesting conflict this season.
As we get closer to game time, we can see both sides taking up their positions in the jungle, waiting for the starting gun.
The American coaches are waving from the home team bunkers, trying to get the game started.
And a representative from the military government is working with the ushers in the Buenos Noches cheering section,
trying to round up some last-minute additions to his team.
The U.S. ambassador is just giving the all-clear signal, so it looks like we're about to get some action in as much a way to play off series.
You know, Chuck, back in 65, when I was a military advisor, I remember we used to go...
We've got a timeout called.
Apparently, the right-wing team has called timeout to change governments.
And unanticipated, but not entirely unprecedented action.
The U.S. coaches are rushing in to confer with the new dictator.
And the old dictator gets a big hand from the fans as he's escorted off the playing field to be shot.
Very well. Now listen to me carefully.
The base is being put on condition red.
I want this flashed to all sections immediately.
Condition red, say. That's a very good idea. I'll get some men on their toes.
Look, Captain, I'm afraid this is not...
This is a very important exercise.
I want you to transmit plan R, R for Robert, to the wing.
Plan R for Robert.
Isn't that bad, sir?
Looks like it's pretty hairy.
Yes, sir.
Plan R for Robert.
Now last, and possibly most important, I want all privately owned radios to be immediately impounded.
Yes, sir.
They might be used to issue instructions for saboteurs.
As I've previously arranged, Air Police will have lists of all owners,
and I want every single one of them collected.
Without any...
Exceptional.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen, and welcome to a Saturday night at your Clark Officers Club.
You are now listening to the theme of your studio, Pacifico Young and his orchestra,
playing pure youth dancing and listening in fashion,
with the vocal stylings of Sil Castro and Daniel Lopez.
We sincerely hope that you will have a very pleasant evening,
and it's our pleasure to play for you.
Oh, hi there, G.I. Joe.
Gee, Joe, you look real lonely.
I'll be good girl for you.
You buy girl drink, Joe?
Hey, hey, Joe, buy drink?
Buy drink?
Joe?
Wake...
Wake up, Joe.
Hey, I'll be good girl for you, G.I. Joe.
Oh, nice soosie floosie.
Number one boom boom here, Clark Officers Club.
We go upstairs now?
Joe?
Hey, Joe, maybe a little oink oink oink oink will wake you up, eh?
Hey?
Thank you.
Oh, it's you.
Well, I'm certainly glad
to meet you face to face
because I'm going to put you
you on to a good thing.
You know, we have much to offer here.
Parades, guns, racial superiority,
heel clicking, hile calling, and the joy and glory of slaving
and dying for a Fira.
Would you like to join up with us?
I've been intrigued by what you told me.
I think there's going to be a war.
If there is, you'll have to return to America,
and we may not meet again.
The ladders statement proved to be prophetic.
I went to his office.
All right, you trout-scented, glue-sniffing piles
of fecal matter.
We're looking for some new store managers,
and I'm told that I have to consider some of you
goat-bred flam factories for the position.
Sir, yes, sir!
What has this sewage stent platoon come to?
Who do they think we are?
Quick trip?
Sir, no, sir!
They think I'm just going to belly up and respect
my employee that hired and promoted me.
The inside, like some kind of freaking Namby Pamby nursemaid!
I mean, that's no way to run a whale oil machine.
You've got to push your people down.
Never give them an opportunity.
Hire the first person you see, and if they do not live up
to your half-an-odd projections, give them the ODX your seat.
Am I right?
Sir, yes, sir!
Need something else.
This thing turns out to be half as important as I figure
it just might be.
I'd say that you're all in line for some important,
important promotions and personal citations when this thing's over with.
You bet your three-day-old multicolored underpants I'm right!
We promote people the old-fashioned way, and that is when, and only when, it will come down
to what, gentlemen?
The lawsuit, sir!
That's right, you doe-eyed heap of cute baby lamb crap.
I may be your mama, but I'm not here to wipe your nose.
So you will remain private until I say that you can be replaced.
Is that clear?
Good!
I got those up two, three, four occupations.
I blew.
From my GI to the heels of my GI shoes.
And if I don't go face-side soon, I'm gonna blow my shoes.
I was home on Sky Hill Drive.
Was electronically alive.
But now I'm living in Vandenberg.
I'm home on Sky Hill Drive.
So militarily absurd when things are slow down on the base.
We can shoot tear gas in the dummy's face.
We can stick our balance in the ground.
When the president comes, we'll stand around.
He'll give a dollar for his main line, two dollars for your eyes.
To pay the price of freedom, oh, it's so real-ized.
These are the voices of infantrymen, medics, mechanics, and MPs.
Fighting men armed with rifles and tanks, airplanes, motorized vehicles and missiles.
But soldiers and airmen unlike any others at any time or any place.
McCormick.
Here.
Hamilton.
Wigley.
Here.
Nanos.
These are people trained to a fine edge, ever on the ready and able to move into action
at a moment's notice.
But these are people who think of themselves as much more than PFC or tech sergeant or
captain.
They're not just soldiers.
They're men.
Or colonels.
Curlin.
Cedar.
Williams.
Foreman.
DiLorenzo.
Supplyman counselor.
Jackson.
CPA.
Mallory.
Dunning.
Switchman.
Men and women in uniform, in arms, but a unique fighting force, one that marches to a different
limit.
I spoke pot in college.
My grade point average is in the low twos.
My father pulled the strings and gave me international cards.
I'm a man.
Where do you start with the men of the national guard?
We'd like to be heroes, but all that we do here is march.
March!
And they don't give a perp a heart for a full-fledged march.
Where have you been?
Don't you know the difference between a standard and a low?
It's the same thing.
Our people have always had flags to symbolize the tribes as we marched, and they didn't
worship it.
And the eagle, that's symbolic also.
My name happens to be Arnold, and that means eagle.
I collect eagles.
I don't worship them.
I love eagles, so when I go out into the deserts and watch them fly and put on some of the best
aerial shows that any pilot would have ever seen, I'll keep them in my hand.
that could ever warrant witness.
They're fantastic.
Just, um, you're, um,
you're thinking as just off-center
about that far-fetched.
We're still trying to figure out
the meaning of that last letter.
There's nothing to figure out, General Turgeon.
This man is obviously a psychotic.
He's not going to hold off
driving on a thing like that
until all the facts are out.
I got the hook, the loop, the tree,
the hook, the passion, G.I. Blues.
G.I. Blues.
From my G.I. to the heels of my G.I. shoes.
G.I. shoes.
G.I. Blues.
And if I don't go straight side,
son, I'm going to give up you.
Who has seen the face of war?
Alabama, Arizona, Arkansas.
Who has carried the banners there?
Florida, Georgia, and Delaware.
Who made the links that formed the chain?
South Dakota, Indiana, Maine,
where brave men made their stand.
Kentucky, North Dakota, Maryland.
Who shouted loud?
Gun.
Explosions.
I'm at World War II in Germany
watching everybody fight.
A rocket just exploded my brother Doug
and that sound you heard
was the sound of phlegm in his throat
leaving his mouth
after he was blown away.
It was like a rocket that was blown up.
There's the machine gun.
Oh, a minefield.
Give me another sound hose, Hed.
Okay.
Make the sound of an F-4
doing a belly flip at 30,000 feet.
Okay.
And don't forget the Doppler effect.
You see it before you hear it.
That's right.
Here it comes with a victory roll.
Got it?
Okay.
Okay, here it comes.
Okay, for those of you
who closed your eyes during that,
you missed seeing the F-4
before you heard it.
And also,
Hosehead over there
did the victory roll with his hand.
Who's supposed to see that on an album,
you dim twit?
You can't fight in here.
This is a war room.
Yes?
Yes.
Oh, take it easy, Adol.
Take it easy.
I did all right for you in your own country, didn't I?
Fascism wasn't built in a day.
These Americans are stubborn people.
They like what they've got
and they're going to hold on to it.
There are always a few weak ones.
Stupid, greedy, half-pint souls.
Those are the ones I'm going to work on.
Cheer up, my friend.
You know, it takes only one bad apple
to spoil the whole barrel.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
G.I. Joe.
G.I. Joe, wake up, Joe.
Joe.
You see the wallet?
Joe, wake up.
Joe.
Uh, Carminia, how are you?
Nice to see you boys here.
Nice to see you.
Got all those nice people.
I'm just fine, thank you.
How are you?
These girls are with the Carminian ship.
Is the ship here?
Maybe here some day.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
You know, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, I left the Navy, honey.
My girlfriend was in the Navy.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
But she was disappointed.
She found out a 17-inch Admiral's a two-piece there.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, you'd be a welcome change of pace
from the rest of these crude and uncouth sailors.
Arr! Arr! Arr! Arr! Arr! Arr!
We selected a typical sailor
to interview this lady.
Your name, sir?
My name's Jose Jimenez, a typical sailor.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And, uh, you, you are an apprentice seaman?
Well, yes, I'm an apprentice seaman now.
But someday I hope to go to Minneapolis
and become something better.
What do you think, Spithys?
I think women and seamen don't mix.
We know what you think.
I love the Navy!
I was in the Army.
I was a wick.
That's a whack.
What up?
Ooh!
I will never forget my first day at the Army camp.
They told me I was supposed to mess with the men.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I love that.
Five days later, I found I was supposed to eat with them.
Have you seen the captain's mess?
Yes, I saw her.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, yes.
Oh, come on, Jose.
That's a very old joke.
That's the captain's problem.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Let's continue.
I understand that after this,
after an extended cruise,
a crew can get pretty rowdy.
Oh, yes.
You know, one time,
we went on a cruise for a whole year, you know,
and you should have seen them.
The whole crew got drunk,
and they run around kissing ladies and everything.
Well, that's...
I think that's understandable.
The second day out?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
You don't mean to tell me
that they had women and liquor aboard a ship.
No, I didn't mean to tell you that.
Oh, boy, am I in trouble with the boys now.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Once we got into slavery,
beazoos.
When I say that,
you guys don't think they would say,
they wouldn't say,
I don't think the wind got into my boat.
I saw anything like that.
It was Ukrainian-American,
Oh, this was before the war begins.
Oh, look at the
Now we're going to try to
And it's been a while,
young women in women.
You want a short- crucifix?
A short crucifix.
Un famili blockchain,
the system needs to be
Now, classification in the Navy is where they let you pick out what they want you to be.
I say, I want to be a cook.
And the guy goes, oh man, you don't want to be a cook.
I go, oh, you know, I was still pretty much at the hip again.
I'm like, oh, what do I want to be?
He said, well, he said, you don't want to be a cook.
What you want to be is a hospital corpsman.
I went, oh, well, I mean, what do they do, you know?
He says, they hand out drugs and hang around nurses.
And I went, oh, man.
Oh, sign me up, man.
I mean, I was right down my alley, you know, doping women for pay.
Far out, you know.
I always did like a man in a uniform.
That one fits you grand.
Us clubs are bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm home every evening.
Yeah, but I'm busy every evening.
Busy?
What are you trying to do, insulting?
Why, no, no, not at all.
I'm just busy, that's all.
Come up, I'll tell your fortune.
Give him a hair of the log that fits him.
Burl high in the morning.
That's what we do with a drunken sailor.
Hey, baby, what did you sign up for?
I said, oh, man, I got a deal, man.
I'm going to be a high school corpsman.
And this guy went, you dummy.
Your commie has no regard for human life, not even his own.
And for this reason, men, I want to impress upon you the need for extreme watchfulness.
The enemy may come individually, or he may come in strength.
He may even come in the uniform of our own troops.
But however he comes, we must stop him.
We must not allow him to gain entrance to this base.
This is your attack profile.
Ensure that the enemy cannot monitor voice transmission or plant false transmission.
The CRM114 is to be switched into all the receiver circuits.
The emergency is to be called in.
The base code prefix is to be set on the dials of the CRM.
This will block any transmission other than those preceded by code prefix.
Stand by to set code prefix.
Roger. Ready to set code prefix.
Set code prefix.
They will not reach their targets for at least another hour.
I am... I am positive, Dimitri.
Listen, I've been all over this with your ambassador. It is not a trick.
Josh, the only difference between peace and war is where we place our bombs.
Flash.
The entire staff of the Pentagon was slipped LSD early this afternoon.
They took off all their clothes and marched to Florida to surrender to the Seminoles.
Let's do it. Now. Today.
What do you say?
All right!
Invasion!
This is good.
It's so good.
Oh, God, it's good.
Ooh! Helicopters!
Ooh! Air strikes!
Ooh! Do it! Do it!
It's good.
It's so good.
Oh, God.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Can we do it to someone else? Huh? Huh?
Oh, please, God, can we do it to someone else? Huh? Can we, please?
What do you say?
All right!
Invasion!
Thank you.
Let me be proud.
I shut down the street.
Hey! Everybody!
Let's spread good freedom!
Let's spread it thick.
What do you say? What do you say? Hey, dummies, wake up! Wake up!
Joe? G.I. Joe, you wake up now!
Oh, hi, Joe. G.I., you don't look so good.
Hey, maybe a little insect surf is what you need, yeah?
A song like me, Gally? Oh, that's a trick, Joe.
Just don't make a career out of it.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
That's a group of Marines and British Marines and Air Force and Navy and Army personnel
that were entrapped, so-called, at the Choson Reservoir
when 120,000 Chinese were turned loose on us
and we were a number of about 14,000 and we had to fight our way out.
Get your hands off me.
Out of here.
Who was there?
Here, take this 9mm to that boy.
This man is obviously at site cutting.
My boys, we've got three engines out.
We've got more holes in us than a horse trader's mule.
The radio is gone and we're leaking fuel.
We're flying in lower while we need sleigh bells on this thing.
But we've got one little budge on here, Bruce.
This height, why, they might harpoon us,
but they dang sure ain't gonna spot us on no radar screen.
We're gonna have to tell the police.
He said war was too important to be left to the generals.
When he said that 50 years ago, he might have been right.
But today, war is too important to be left to politicians.
They have neither the time, the training,
nor the inclination for strategic thought.
I can no longer sit back and allow
communist infiltration,
communist indoctrination,
communist subversion,
and the international communist conspiracy
to sap and impurify
all of our precious bodily fluids.
And the first thing they look for,
this is the most important,
is his urination pattern,
says your little Tommy.
What do you mean?
If he is given the opportunity
to urinate on a pole or a fence,
but he still squats,
it shows immaturity
and is therefore unacceptable.
So, you know, if they get a squatter,
they just wash him right out.
If they lift that leg up there
and let fly, he's a born killer.
Oh, wow.
What else do they look for?
I don't know.
I don't care.
Imagine the poor soldier, though,
who gets that kind of duty.
Weird, strange place.
We had a guy that got ate by a tiger.
That is not something
that I am conditioned
through going through public high school
in the United States to handle.
Hey, Charlie got ate by a tiger.
Oh, man.
What am I doing here?
Where are the broads and dope?
I need them now, you know?
I got the one, two, three, four
Occupation G.I. Blue
G.I. Blue
From the G.I. head
To the heels of my G.I. shoe
G.I. shoe
G.I. Blue
And if a dog goes down the road
I'm gonna blow my fuse
Occupation G.I. Blue
Oh, buddy.
Oh!
On the fire, just kneeling,
I'm as lying very still
As I'm to never hold a child
Because a bullet running wild
Has struck him down
And now he cries,
Dear God, oh, why, oh, why?
But who will answer?
An unofficial study
Which we undertook of this eventuality
Indicated that we would destroy
Ninety percent of their nuclear capabilities
We would therefore prevail
And suffer only modest
And acceptable civilian casualties
From the remaining force
Which would be badly damaged
And uncoordinated
the Operation
The second Lieutenant,
Fresh from the point
he didn't know
A closed cigarette from a joint
He said,
Hey, man, let's take the hit
They put a bullet in his back
They didn't wanna die
Step up and take a look
At his eyes
And it wasn't
Bad day for the good guys.
Sergeant Major from World War II said,
Hey, boys, I'll witness for you.
Turn off that music and shine them boots.
They threw a grenade in his tent.
It didn't explode.
Step up close, take a look in his eyes.
It wasn't.
Bad day for the good guys.
Chopper pilot said, we're going to stitch some Kong.
They flew up the delta.
They were gone too long.
They saw some black pajamas that were running from the noise.
The chopper exploded.
It was a curse for the boys.
Step up close, take a look in their eyes.
It wasn't.
Bad day for the good guys.
He got back to the States, fell in love too fast.
Got married, got angry, it just didn't last.
She said, sorry, John, I just can't stay.
He got a gun and room.
So she's doing today.
Step up close, take a look in their eyes.
It was a bad day for the good guys.
Bad day for the good guys.
Blake, get up
gentlemen, get up
get your dead ass out of the rack
I want every last
swinging weenie out of the parade ground
in cold, hot, red hours
do you understand me
gentlemen, your hand
is the wire and I
am the Lord
Lord
but it is necessary now to make a choice
to choose between two
admittedly regrettable but nevertheless
distinguishable post-war
environments, one where you got 20 million
people killed and the other where you got 150
million people killed
we're talking about mass murder general, not war
I'm not
saying we wouldn't get our hair mustered
but I do say no more
than 10 to 20 million killed
Tom
on a poster announcing his forthcoming speech
this was written across the photograph of Robert McNamara
stop me before I kill again
laughs
bobs of students surrounded
state college today
they explained that they were anti-semantic
the tactile unit of the local police mob
forced the students to surrender by late this afternoon
laughs
I have fans cast rusty coming to you
live from the strategic air command headquarters
in Omaha, here's the nerve center for the
U.S. special defense team, I'm Terry Dunn
I
am
a
privileged
soldier
for out
privilege
to
experience
such
warm
Why
And see, it's even got a built-in scoreboard,
so I know what all the other teams in the league are doing at all times.
We never miss a play.
Well, it's readily apparent that the owners of this particular team
have spared no expense in putting together a winning combination for the next war.
That's right.
Survival kit contents check.
In them you will find
one .45 caliber automatic,
two boxes of ammunition,
four days concentrated emergency ration,
one drug issue containing antibiotics,
morphine,
vitamin pills,
pep pills,
sleeping pills,
tranquilizer pills,
one miniature combination Russian phrasebook and Bible,
$100 in rubles,
$100 in gold,
nine packs of chewing gum,
one issue of prophylactics,
three lipsticks,
three pair of knives,
and a pair of long stockings.
Shoot, a fella could have a pretty good weekend in Vegas with all that stuff.
This is TFC Helen Miller of the United States Army Recruiting Corps.
The United States Army is known throughout the world
for the care, training, and handling of its privates.
First Battalion, Fourth Marines Alpha Company
operating three miles south of the DMZ
in the jungle, in the yucky jungle,
in the hot, with a gun that I, with people,
and I'm shooting, and I don't know anybody out there,
and no, I'm not mad at anybody,
I don't know what's going on.
There's some dude in Hanoi, and some dude in Washington go,
go get them boys, you know?
You know?
And some guy going, my fellow Americans,
and you are, I'm not, I'm over here.
I'm in the jungle, I ain't your fellow American, you know?
And, and, and some guy in, in, in, you know, Hanoi go,
my fellow Vietnamese, you know, and, uh.
All this stuff you heard about America not wanting to fight,
wanting to stay out of the war,
we've a lot of horse down.
Americans traditionally love to fight.
All real Americans love the sting of battle.
Commandos, baby, now, one, two, three, four.
.
Oh, my God, I'm actually a pity,
of those poor bastards we're going up against.
I got, I do.
We're not just going to shoot the bastards.
We're going to cut out their living guts,
and use them to grease the treads of our tanks.
We're going to murder those lousy, hung bastards,
by the bushels.
My boys will give you the best kind of stud,
1400 megatons worth.
And you sure as hell won't stop them now.
So let's get going.
There's no other choice.
God willing, we will prevail.
in peace and freedom from fear and in true health through the purity and essence of our natural fluid.
Here we are in a nuclear pseudo-semi-partially nuclear war, right?
Now, the thing is, it gets to be a pseudo-semi-private-precious sort of semi-nuclear war
when they use everything they got except the big boom.
They used everything. They had mechanical marvels.
Men put their brains to work and they come up with so many fantastic things,
like things that you step on and bounce up in the air and blow your head off.
Men have these great, fantastic minds, you know?
And they had all of these bombs and stuff.
And one time we got into a firefight.
Well, we got into a firefight several times.
As a matter of fact, I got wounded.
I'll tell you how lucky I am. I got wounded five times.
Here we are. We got into this firefight.
Now, they call it a firefight because that's when everybody's shooting at each other
and they haven't figured out a way that you can calmly say that in newsprint other than firefight.
There are a lot of words that we used and they were not firefight,
but we're down there and everybody's shooting at each other.
You know?
And they called in artillery support.
So, over the...
You hear this...
These shells coming in, you know?
They sound like a train.
Then somebody called airplanes and they had these phantom jets.
And they dropped this napalm.
You know?
So, the whole general thing is...
I got hit with an arrow.
No kidding.
No kidding, man. I got the scar. It went in right there and it came out right there.
I got pinned to the ground with an arrow, man.
I haven't even got enough class to get hurt, modern.
I'm crawling up this side of this hill on my belly, you know?
Everybody else is shooting. I'm down under the grass going,
Hey, me, babe, you know?
I'm crawling around, I was like,
Eww, funk, you know?
And I look over and my arm is pinned to the ground with an arrow.
And I look over at this cat next to me, this other Marine Corps sergeant,
and he goes,
Only you, man.
Only you.
The hell with heroes.
For some people, the whole world is a jungle and the only law is survival at any cost.
People like Rod Taylor, who'd already won his wings and his medals and now was out for the cash.
People like Claudia Cardinale, who did what she had to do to stay alive in luxury.
People like Harry Gardino, the corruptors, the fixers.
Who were out for the loot, no matter what the price, in other people's lives.
The hell with heroes.
An explosive story about explosive people.
It's today's story, told in today's language.
The hell with heroes.
What's going on, relationships, you ain't never früh.
Hey!
Stop it, got to focus.
now people start going nuts,registrash aisjezike dial 끝났
Remember that, little already saw it in the warglobe?
The love get 하 pilin in da smoked chatting room,
Of all the ones to choose
The way my luck is going
I always seem to lose
Sailing me to the fighting line
I hope the army don't leave me dead in my grave
Hey, give me a pen
I'll do the paperwork
I'm the top rider king
I'd make a damned clerk
Don't put me on the fighting line
Cause I won't
Give you my life
Just to throw away
They've given me the law
Till they take me away
But there's not enough time
When you want to stay
I'll do the paperwork
Soon it's up to the fighting line
And I'll be waiting and riding
On every day
It's a little too long
To live on borrowed time
Well, having met these talks
The killing friends of the world
They may come back to mind
But today 시청er
Arizonaway
Where I can see
Well, we're never done
And we will stay
All through another city
The light will be very heavy
But I don't care
No matter what
Havin' new compromises
Just to feel it
In the faces of people
But the police
But who'd know
If our firts
Are forever
Only justice
¶¶
Target distance, three miles.
Roger, three miles.
Target in sight.
Oh, wow, look at the fun house here.
And this looks more like Bob's slack-time bunker with all of these sandbags.
Oh, gee.
I guess this means we're at war.
Yes, Reverend Susie the floozy reporting for duty.
Ow.
Oh, judging from my blistered editing finger, one of the Susies has turned in a show.
Oh, man, I hope she didn't do any embarrassing racial impersonations while I was out.
Oh, hey, okay, a credits list.
I guess this is all I have to do tonight.
Cool.
Yeah, I could use...
Okay, tonight we were treated to, in no particular order, damn it,
the wide world of war was by the Holy Ghost Players, a Christian comedy group.
Oh, there's a lot of Dr. Strange love, the best war movie ever made,
and one of the worst sound jobs ever in media, second only to my show here.
And that was P.I. and his orchestra at the Clark Air Force Base Officers Club.
Oh.
A little oingo boingo.
A quick trip training video with a weird boot camp thing.
G.I. Blues with Elvis.
Oh, poor Elvis.
Oh, then there's a National Guard promo album with David Jansen,
Bonnie Anderson, the poor man's Rusty Warren.
Oh, the Merchant Marine Glee Club did the Drunken Sailor song.
And then we had hippie Satanist junkie Christian comedy star Mike Warren,
and he on looking for dope and tail and knob.
Oh, and then we had Ruby 3's Invasion.
Ooh.
And then the insect surfers at Mig Alley from a limited rough mix tape I've had for years.
Oh, and Arnold Murray raving as per usual.
The Pajama Slave Dancers, excellent take on who will answer.
Bad Day for the Good Guys was by Mr. Gasoline.
And peppered in there were some comedy bits from Congress of Wonders,
and...
some Doug and Bob McKenzie was in there too.
And then George C. Scott's bits from Patton were collecting with his bits from Dr. Strangelove for a moment,
kind of colliding into each other.
And then they veered off to take in Commando, a live version by the angry Samoans.
And then we heard the fighting line by John Mayall and Ballad for a Soldier by Leon Russell.
Oh, where am I?
Oh, yes.
War.
Somehow I always heard that the W was silent.
Yeah, but I'm kind of familiar with it.
I don't know much from the politics of this particular fight,
but to a weird little girl growing up in the out-of-touch Midwest,
the televised Vietnam War made for some totally surreal psychic wallpaper.
But all I got out of it was that it seemed to be a horrifically romantic,
raw deal for everybody concerned.
Except, of course, for the fat cats in the military-industrial complex.
Oh, as big-time hawk Barry Goldwater gushed,
Thank God for the military-industrial complex.
Yeah, it seems like the sort of totally screwed business venture the conspiracy's God would get into all right.
Some motto.
Oh, yeah.
I do like the Navy slogan better, whatever it was.
Yeah, there's a fort in every girl.
Oh, but that was back in the golden final days of armed conflict,
the glorious Vietnam War era.
Yes, the war that cost us some of our most beloved stars,
like the beaver Jerry Mathers and Eddie Haskell,
and we all know how Elvis died at Da Nang.
And who can forget the fiery mishap with Joey Heatherton and Bob Hope
on the overloaded Huey during the fall of Saigon?
Oh, but whatever the toll-seekers,
back then there was still an attainable sense of honor
that went along with surviving the whole bloody imperilio,
because the Vietnam War was the last full-contact war.
Oh, Robert E. Howard's character Conan had a point of view a lot like mine.
Yes, he thought that fighting technology should end with a sword,
because it was intrinsically noble to face your opponent within arm's reach.
He considered the bow and arrow to be a colossal leap forward for cowardice.
And I can only imagine Conan's contempt
for the high-tech hands-off methods of murder that we have now.
Oh, but for some nagging reason,
I just can't get into this new level of...
warfare either.
Yeah, like that Twilight of the Gods going on in Yugoslavia right now.
Oh, yeah, I mean, hey,
it looks good on paper.
There are compellingly high body counts,
and hey, genocide's always good for a plus,
but somehow the fact that it's a putty-colored electronic war
and all the new designer colors just leaves me cold.
Again.
Hell, this malaise started kicking in back
during the putty-colored video game Gulf War miniseries.
I'm really getting bored with it all.
Hey, I brag myself enough right here every day, Bubba,
without being shipped out somewhere.
Oh, and look at all the crappy music we've had
since the Good War stopped in the 60s.
When the threat of death is apparently what it takes
to get those creative juices flowing.
How else can you justify that?
Why, the crap we lived through in the 70s and 80s
and the 90s now.
There's no glory in living through a war
when it's become something more like
the equivalent of a bad McJob.
Besides, who can take war seriously anymore?
Dodging Spuz missiles is just so...
so paintball.
Yeah, like laser tag, but lethal.
If you're lucky.
Yeah, otherwise, you're just gonna wind up
dragging ass through a life wrestling
with some bothersome service-related condition.
Ranging from winding up with less
than the requisite number of limbs
to getting some sort of flesh-eating
radioactive psoriasis.
Mmm, radioactive psoriasis.
But in the final consensus, Seekers,
what's the point?
What's gonna happen?
I mean, it's a sucker's bet, kids.
It's either all gonna blow over
or it'll all blow up.
Neither way, it blows.
Oh, but enough about me.
And although this has been
Suzy the Floozy's Bob's Slack Time Funhouse
number 271 rerun is 449 rerun is
hour of slack 874.
874.
That's what you're listening to.
And more information is to be had from
www.subgenius.com
Pre-A-Z-B-E-N-G-H-O-B.
Subtitles by Subtitle Workshop