Yes, sir. Yes, I understand. Goodbye.
He says he's pretty sure this isn't sabotage.
That he thinks there's something far more terrible than that in back of it.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
But why did they come here?
Well, they're not friendly, we're sure of that.
No matter what the cost, it must be destroyed.
Oh, this is my kind of time of life.
This is my way of living.
Little shack in wisteria, Ohio, surrounded by...
What's that about?
And welcome back.
Well, we're here and continuing this exalted special post-X-Day broadcast.
Is Dr. Drummond still there?
He had to go and...
Oh, likely story. What a pathetic excuse.
Hal was wondering about a formula that was written at the bottom of my X-Day schedule.
I was just wondering what that was all about.
It's a way of measuring a certain type of quality of X-Day.
For instance, in the old days when we had a swimming pool to work with,
and more people...
In there.
You would have more exposed female breasts than at other X-Days.
And say there were 15 ladies who got in without a shirt.
This is all very...
Okay, this is crude and dumb and sexist, all right?
But it is a formula.
Say if there were 15 topless ladies, that would be a 30T X-Day.
If one of them was an Amazon, it might be a 20T.
29T X-Day.
This year's X-Day was only a 6T X-Day.
Because that was the number of nipples visible in the baptism.
Yes, it's the number of nipples visible in the baptism of girls.
I didn't realize you kept score about that.
We didn't until about two hours ago,
when Philo and I...
Philo invented that formula.
You think I would come up with that kind of juvenile,
J. June, sophomoric nonsense?
Furthermore, you realize this is...
But I will report on it.
Furthermore, you realize this is not good advertising for it.
You're telling all the people out there that,
hey, you know what?
You don't get to see as many titties as you used to.
That's because...
What you should be telling them is that you're going to see more than ever
each year that goes by.
Well, there were more this year than last year, that's for sure.
Well, if Bob says it, it must be true.
I don't think that's right either, Stan.
My memory for these things is fairly good.
I think last year would have trumped this year.
To tell the truth...
There were far more than six.
That is the silliest thing I have ever heard.
I was there.
I took photos.
I can prove it.
Now, Princess Mia's...
So how many nipples were there then, actually?
Oh, there were far, far more than just...
Right, but they weren't all visible.
This is the number of visible...
And they didn't all belong to females.
Invisible nipples don't count, I suppose.
Right, exactly.
They're not real nipples because they're invisible.
That would be a strange thing.
You have six nipples.
Oh, it's just because the woman had a shirt on that was wet
and revealed every contour.
That doesn't count.
Why bother?
I kind of wonder.
That doesn't count.
She won the wet t-shirt contest.
Yeah, she ended up covered with...
We call it walnut oil.
Yeah, whatever it really is.
Everyone does.
Does anybody really believe that for a second, that that is walnut oil?
Has anybody thought to get that stuff tested?
I don't...
No, I took some samples from the pond this time,
and our host, Charlene, said,
well, those aren't walnuts.
Uh-oh.
What were they?
They're baby candier tadpoles.
Did you really identify what they were?
Little tiny candier tadpoles.
Nobody really seems to be interested in the question,
but I am passionately interested
because I have been telling everybody for years,
oh, it's just walnut oil,
and now I've found out that apparently
there are no walnut trees even near there,
but there's...
And furthermore, walnut oil is contained inside the nuts,
and that would have to imply that the nuts are all falling,
not just falling into the water,
but also breaking open and getting crushed as well.
It could be that there's a huge...
There is incredible scum on the surface of the pond.
Maybe there are walnut trees in the area,
but the walnut oil is actually coming from the feces
of all the animals who eat the walnuts.
Yes, and then there was some wiseacre who said,
was that scum there before?
The subgeniuses got in for the bobtism?
I thought that was another good one.
It's very hard to get out of the pond
without getting that stuff all over you
because it tends to cling.
I can't imagine how you would.
Well, I'll tell you.
Nobody ever listens to me.
No one would listen.
No one would obey.
I tried to tell them.
They just don't...
They blow me off.
I know how to do it.
It's like a dead skin follicle that resembles a walnut tree.
That's what they're saying.
They're saying,
they resemble little tiny hairs
and it looks as if you're coated with yeti-like hair
when you get out of the pond.
Some of them link together
and it's like a large beard of Spanish moss hanging off you.
The only way to get out without that on you
is to break the surface and splash around
so it won't adhere
and then keep splashing until the last second you get out.
Then you only get some on your feet-like.
We had a little debate over a photograph
of somebody taking a close-up
of that hair-like stuff.
Yes.
And one person said,
yeah, remember the picture from last X-Day
of Baby Bear's fanny
with those hair-like things all over it?
And I said, no, I thought that was Suzy the Fluzy's cleavage.
Would you like me...
And somebody else said, no,
that was two bald-headed guys leaning their heads together.
If you would like,
I'll send you the picture from my private collection
which will show you once and for all
that there was no exaggeration
in this claim.
Wisteria, cilia, cilia, cilia, cilia.
They are almost like cilia.
They're these little short, nubbly nubs.
And that's what happens to anybody who gets in the pond.
That's one of the things that happens.
But if you listen to Dr. Howell,
you can wash them off of yourself.
Exactly.
Just as no one wants to read the schedule
I work so hard on with Pisces,
just so people refuse to listen to Dr. Howell.
Exactly.
They ask, but then they don't listen.
Well, they think that it'll never happen to them.
Just like in Psalm number 10,
they say,
I shall never be in adversity.
If only they knew
how important it is to be prepared
as the Boy Scouts do.
Yeah.
I think every legitimate arm of the government
is fully aware of how prepared we have to be,
especially with these kind of miscreants
in our vacation lands
and places where we go to have...
...fun over our day of independence
from the royal rule.
It is very unfortunate that people forget
that the purpose of all this stuff
is just to have fun.
Why all this angst and bitterness
and rivalry and fussing
and heartbreak of psoriasis
and...
You're making fun of me.
No, the idea is we're just trying to have fun.
...over a campsite, you know.
Well, yeah, they set a guy on fire.
You heard about that, I guess.
Well, I was wondering about it.
I actually was hoping somebody would expand a little bit on it.
It was a flamethrower.
The guy had a flamethrower.
And it didn't work.
It did work.
Those are surprisingly easy to build a home.
That guy that was standing in for Bob
was a cinder
faster than any other sacrifice
we've ever burned up out there.
Awesome.
So guess what?
Now we're going to do your favorite other thing with fire.
Head over that way.
And let's set Bob on fire!
Fire!
Burn more shit!
Take your way to the usual place
where we set Bob on fire.
Those who have been before,
God,
newbies to the usual place
we set Bob on fire.
Also, while you're walking over there,
you probably shouldn't stand too close to Bob
because I think flamethrowers
are going to be involved.
So please don't get caught on fire.
Would you tell me if my face was on fire?
Fire!
No!
The rise will be your deepest joy.
The rise, the radio shows command.
It's time that we elect our boss.
The choice of a person shall stand.
Seriously, I don't know.
A child to pass on Jesus
shall rise for the world.
Fire and stand.
I'm a little taken by surprise.
We're going to burn Bob
and we don't really...
We don't really have a reason to burn him yet.
He hasn't let us down yet this time.
I am observing a Bob effigy
tied to a stake.
It's almost like he looks like
he's riding a little motorcycle
only the motorcycle is made of wood
that is going to incinerate him.
He has to be burned.
He has a face
of a color-printed
Dobbs head
stuck on a wig head, I think.
And this should burn well.
It should burn well.
But why...
Why are we even...
Bernie, he hasn't done anything to us.
Not yet.
No, he's...
He's pretty good, man.
He doesn't intend harm.
It just kind of happens
if you're in the wrong place,
wrong time.
If you haven't been killing
your own personal Dobbs,
here's a chance to...
Yeah.
But it's not like...
Last time,
we got up at 7 a.m.,
the saucers didn't arrive,
so we burned Bob.
And Bob had killed
all these people, too,
on top of that.
So we burned him.
Great.
Or an effigy, of course, obviously.
It's a clever simulacrum,
but it's not the real Bob.
Just so anybody knows,
this is not the real J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I don't know who is under
that little mask
wearing the suit,
and I'm sorry about whatever,
but that's not Bob.
Somebody else.
I've heard it smells like bacon.
I do hear muffled...
Shh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is he white?
He's not supposed to...
He's supposed to be
completely in us at times.
We wouldn't do that
to a conscious person.
Set him on fire?
We're just from right over our heads
from the flaming arrow.
I'd see it in white.
At this particular time,
I'm as puzzled as the pagans usually are.
Why do they burn their guru,
the guy they love?
Are you waiting for fire technology professionals?
They always say that.
Move back quite a bit.
Because fire technology professionals...
Oh, yeah, I know.
Right, right.
Of course.
No, by the fire technology professionals.
We are human flesh.
We can be unpredictable.
Can ignite.
Really, yeah.
Not unlike the searing flash
that announced the beginning
of the atomic age.
Yeah, they have...
There's gas in the human body
and it can explode.
That's right.
Again, this is not J.R. Bob Dobbs,
but someone in a Bob mask.
Actually, if anybody here
wants to step in and, you know...
I mean, this guy didn't know.
And if anybody...
If anybody wants to take his place,
you'd probably be a little closer
to the saucers tomorrow.
Nah, fuck it.
Maybe get a little better seat.
Let me...
More of a front row.
I don't know.
Can't promise you anything.
Where's sex point if you can?
I'll triple my money.
We would...
It would have to be somebody
who would fit in that suit, though.
Flammable, if you get to what I mean.
I thought you were a ghost out like me.
Now, since subgeniuses have never been able to prod
Yeah.
to satisfy the secret of fire
from our friends, the pagans...
Oh, please don't flick my arrow on my head.
We are dependent upon the...
the pagan experts who actually know
how to ignite a flame.
This is the one secret.
professionals, because they are the keepers
of the Vestal Fire,
the sacred fire on the hearth,
right over there in that little circle.
Yeah, where is that guy with the match
and the flamethrower and the howitzer?
Somebody ought to wake him up.
Oh, there! Oh, Jason!
Christ, Bob. Oh, my God.
He's adjacent.
You want him lit up?
Yeah, yeah.
Let's hide time.
Let's get this barbecue on the road.
Everybody's hungry, right?
Set him on fire.
Yeah.
He's hungry to see the old Bob burn.
Jason is now stalking the...
Well, he's tied up.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit!
Long live the new Bob.
But it is an actual flamethrower.
Bob has been ignited instantly.
Whoo!
Listen to the crowd and smell that bacon.
Oh, I'm so hungry now.
What's the problem?
I ain't trying.
I, I, I...
Hail Jason.
Jason, the bringer of fire,
the Prometheus of the subgeniuses.
Oh, shit!
Who is he out of space?
Between pagans and subgeniuses.
Are we still burning our conspiracy paper chains?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, do you have a conspiracy form?
I have a conspiracy form.
Is that your old business card from your old job?
No, this is my new business card from my new job that they gave me for free.
Wow.
And it has my slave name upon it.
Oh, cool.
And it shall burn.
Oh, yes.
He knew that.
Baby Bear is burning.
Burning a symbol of her human life.
Yay!
The sad human life that we have to pretend to live.
That's a good idea.
If anyone has anything like their driver's license or their credit...
Well, maybe...
You know, the people that...
This is the Bob that we fill with money.
Last year we had people barbecuing hot dogs on his face, lighting cigarettes off his shoes.
This is the, yeah.
This is one of those...
This is the one that was supposed to be buried with money.
That we were going to retrieve.
Right.
And...
What?
After the end times.
That was the one with the money in it?
Yes.
Oh, great!
It was supposed to be buried, not burned.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Oh, now you tell us.
It was on the schedule.
We were going to burn it.
You put the money on him?
Okay, we're going to need everybody to go up and pee on the fire.
Who was that guy?
Or blow on it.
Oh, it's too late.
It's gone now.
Oh, look.
I can see little dollar bills flying up into the sky.
I can see the blood here, just shreds of them.
Oh, but that was real smooth, guys.
Put the church savings in the sacrificial dead guy.
I didn't have anything to do with it.
So, yeah, the church needs everyone to re-register tomorrow, or actually today, because all of
the registration has gone into the sacrificial Bob.
How cute!
Oh, thank you.
What was that?
Was that great?
Was that granny panties or what?
That was my con uniform.
Dr. Drummond, don't you need to burn some representation of your job that you just retired?
No more arm sales?
I mean, how?
You sold arms?
Whoa.
Like mannequin arms?
Must have some.
Right arms.
Do you have any strong, like testicles you could throw in there?
Sure.
I have the last one, the last two extra ones removed recently.
Of cosmetic?
Yeah.
The extras.
Yeah, everybody wants to be cool.
Bob instantly burned.
And then there was a Nazi-like moment where they put a book in the flames, a book called
Unburnable.
And it almost was.
It took a long time for that book to finally start cramming.
We were starting to lose faith.
Oh, here's somebody with the, what is this, Reverend Fox?
I see.
Unburnable.
A book called Unburnable.
Oh my God.
This is a test.
It's mocking you.
Reverend Fox actually has a book called, with the title printed on it, a hardcover book,
Unburnable.
Yes, let's get a good photograph of this.
Oh, I see it.
It's Unburnable.
Because, is it truth in advertising?
Can you really judge a book by the cover?
I guess that would be the experiment we're learning tonight.
What is this?
He wants to know the publisher.
Who is the publisher?
HarperCollins.
They turned down the book of the subgenius.
They offered a smaller bid than Simon & Schuster.
HarperCollins, the publishers of this so-called book.
It's called Unburnable Book.
We'll see.
And if this book burns, it means any book can be burned.
The book of the subgenius.
I'm not sure what that's good for.
The book of the subgenius burns really fast.
Well, we know that from many X-days and many disappointing X-day drills.
All right, here it goes.
Here we go.
Oh, the author is looking out at us.
That means we'll get to see.
Wait, it's not burning.
It's a Ouija board.
It's still not burning.
It's melting.
Well, maybe we ought to change religions.
Maybe, oh, wait.
There it goes.
I like this.
There's a photo of the author on the back and she's going all Freddy Krueger.
I believe.
I fucking believe.
Yeah, we all believe something.
He's smoking now.
He's smoking hot.
How does, how did that Bob replacement dude taste?
Does anybody use it?
If you inhale the smoke, not only will you get the smoke, but you'll get the smoke.
You'll die, but you'll know the book.
If you inhale the smoke of the book, book burning is, is not a disruption of book dissemination.
Book burning is a vehicle through which people can ingest books faster.
All these douches are vaping books now.
Have you seen this shit?
Fucking douchebags vaping books.
Are you telling me?
It's taking a long time to burn.
It is taking a long time to burn.
Oh my God.
The, the, his shoulder.
The shoulder and the scapula fell off the body into the side of the fire.
Bob's in sad shape.
God, it smells like bacon.
Like hold it up.
Really?
It's really making me hungry.
You can see his shin bones through the pants now.
No, no, I'm taking it out.
Maybe it is unburnable.
It's still sitting there.
Still sitting there.
I don't know.
I'm starting to change my mind about this whole Bob thing now.
I'm changing my mind about everything.
Wait, wait, wait.
Well, this is a strange situation, Billy.
Have you fucked up?
Yes.
Oh my God.
My mouth is just watering.
I want to pull some of that meat out of there.
I love the fact that we've really got some Bob.
We've got some bread back in the car.
And we're fascinated by the blood.
And we're fascinated with the book.
It's called evolution.
Kill book.
What if you guys are just because it, just because it claimed to be unburnable.
And apparently it is because it's still sitting there.
Bob's gone.
The stupid pink book is still there.
What is this telling us?
Again, the conspiracy wins?
Or are we reading too much into it?
I think we're just impatient.
Oh, yeah.
Naturally.
Naturally, after 18 years of waiting for the fucking saucers, we can be allowed some impatience.
I guess we can.
Yeah.
We can.
It was all a lie.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Alphina was right.
How is that?
Something's been taken off my shoulder.
Was that a great thing?
Oh, my gosh.
You need to make an announcement about this.
Here you go.
Well, we have here a CD by the band or thing called Pink.
Pink.
I've been seeing these t-shirts that say, I love pink everywhere.
They disgruntled me.
So I would love to see this.
You are so not gruntled.
No shit.
It's terrifying.
So I would love to see this.
See, I wonder what they would do.
I've microwaved a lot of these CD things.
Pink.
Okay, eat your heart out, Harper Collins.
Mother fuckers.
There we go.
It's on page 42.
Oh, too late.
Pink inside.
Pink!
Pink.
Boy, what a .
What is that secret video you took of your wife, and you promised her you't get rid of
You got married? Is that what you're burning?
There's not going to be any meat left.
Fuck a clown!
Dad, what the fuck am I going to tell mom?
But Baby Bear mourned and said, now we're like Nazis and so forth.
No, because we only burn unburnables.
Well, I think any book that has a picture of the author on the cover can't really be a good book.
The last year that I remember seeing Magdalene there, there were quite a few books burned that year.
Well, those don't count. Those were mostly Bibles and Korans.
Yeah, those and the subgenius Hitler youth.
Jack Chick tracts.
Jack Chick tracts were burned?
No, I just said that to get you upset.
Oh, no.
Nobody burned the precious comic.
Who tells me that goose-stepping morons such as yourselves should try reading books instead of burning them?
Well, okay, sure, I'll sit down and read some right now.
Sure, I'm kidding.
No, the idea behind those...
Was there a hairy person that got in there?
Independent Jones and the Temple of Literacy.
The place was like a steam bath and no one could get in.
Or get clean.
You'd have to go up to the shower house for that.
Climb up a long, muddy trail and then...
By the time you get to the bottom of the hill, you need another...
Another shower.
Right.
They get a lot of exercise that way.
There were plenty of showers falling from the sky.
And I did go up and down that thing more times than I could count.
And I got plenty of exercise.
Hard, physical exercise.
What was that thing?
What thing?
You just said you got a lot of exercise going up and down that thing.
The trail.
The trail that goes up the side of the mountain to the bath house.
Sorry.
Where the baths are taken and the house has the odds.
And that is just the beginning of my journey.
Because I'd walk past that and all the way down the road a piece
until I came to the Hierarchite's cabin in the woods.
Is there one?
All around.
A beautiful little idyllic looking place.
And there were also RVs inhabited by Mr. Sistar and by Dr. Dark.
And...
And a golf cart driven by Princess Wee, which in the middle of the night made a metallic squee.
Oh, oh, oh.
I heard that.
And then Pastor Pressure had a ghost meter on his cell phone, an app for that.
And he was metering the squeal.
I have it happen again.
So you heard the squeal I referred to.
Now, what is in these advanced surveillance techniques?
The haunted golf cart.
A ghost...
A ghost-busting app.
In DC Comics.
It was a ghost-busting app?
And it was shown a very high number.
Very high number.
Somebody who was high on it.
It is a haunted.
It is measurably haunted.
Yes, according to his app on his cell.
Yeah, the golf course would make that noise when it was off.
No key in it.
The golf curse.
Yes.
That's what was happening.
Indeed.
It's one of the mysteries.
My theory was that it was Doc Savage trying to solve a crossword puzzle under the golf cart.
For hours?
Yeah.
Well, it was a really tough puzzle.
He makes that noise when he's concentrating.
It was making that noise when I went away.
And it was making that noise when I came back hours later.
Check the tires.
Yeah, check the tires.
Check the hood.
Maybe the engine's missing.
One of these crazy kids out on the street might have stolen it.
Ha ha.
There are two.
There's the other direction.
All down below.
All talking at once.
Oh, he's back from the correction.
Maybe that's your mom.
Even when the car's turned, when it's off.
Yeah.
Oh.
Sometimes a thousand twangling instruments about my ears.
And sometimes voices.
I turned two of them off yesterday.
You killed a moth?
I turned two of them off yesterday because...
Oh, turned two of them off.
This sounds like those conversations between deaf people.
Right.
Right. Telegraph.
No, I thought he said he killed a moth.
But no, he turned two of them off.
Dr. Drummond knows the secret of the mysterious squeal.
And it is that when you're putting it into a reverse gear,
if you don't take it off, even when the vehicle is turned off,
it squeals until it's all...
Well, that was quite a squeal.
And how much power does it use up while it's shrilling away in the dark?
I have no...
No idea.
But you'll find out...
When the battery gives out as you're attempting to navigate an exceptionally steep and troublesome hill.
When suddenly you roll backward at a frightening pace
and crash into the small animal administration.
Don't forget to send a triplicate, too.
And you have to have a hard copy of something.
Thank you.
You get your paperwork done and then give us another call.
This email will get you nowhere.
You need a personal touch.
You need to call up somebody once in a while and know their first name.
Well, you can't make prank calls anymore with the new technology.
There are ways.
People spoof phone numbers all the time.
They spoof phone numbers?
They spoof them.
How much did they buy them then, Matt?
What did you say?
Now, let's not have the speaking in tongues thing.
I was getting excited.
I can't help it.
I would say...
But you'd know what I was talking about.
Right.
And Kabasenka also.
Two or another great thing they used to have.
That southern thing, Kabasenka.
I'll see your Shalikandala and raise you one Vandarian.
One Debasoya.
Oh.
Got to stop drawing.
I'm getting ink all over the desk.
Maybe we should ration our speech so we can go one, two, three,
instead of all at the same time, and then a gap of silence.
Over.
Oh.
Just say over after each sentence.
Roger that.
Okay.
Let's try this new method.
Over.
Well, the first transmission is going fairly well.
It looks like almost everybody has decided to opt out of the observation,
but it looks like somebody...
I heard you say over.
Over.
Roger that.
I'm still hearing those rogers and overs.
Over.
Hearing them over and over.
Looks like we have a new caller calling in here.
Over and out.
Okay.
6-2 and even.
6-8-7-3-5-1-5.
6-2-1-half-a-dozen-of-another.
Talk about snouts, whistle, aerodinies.
Pork snouts and ham jowls.
Hey, you guys already forgot to say over, over.
Over.
No, you say it after you say something.
You don't just say over, over and over again.
I'm taking my radio etiquette from a radar-activated robot known as Roger.
Over.
Roger.
Roger that.
My God.
Is this going to go on all night?
Look, this is not ham radio.
See, this is kosher radio.
Tell Rover to roll over.
Roll over and over and ten times over.
He has that kind of picky-oon atmosphere in the background where it sounds like people
are street singing and playing with their toes and everything.
Yeah, sure.
There's plenty of chimpanzees, I'm sure.
I had a little dog and his name was Rover.
When he died, he died all over.
All but his tail and it turned over.
Over and over and ten times over.
Hello.
New caller, you're on the air.
Yes, I was reading about the Russian Museum of Erotica the other day in St. Petersburg.
He said Petersburg.
Rasputin display.
Wait, so you're saying Vladimir Putin started smoking ganja and listening to reggae and he's now Rasputin?
He said Putin.
No, no, no.
I don't know.
I'm from St. Petersburg.
I don't know if he has anything to do with the museum.
I think there's...
There's something there.
... something in Erotica.
But...
It's too much of a coincidence to be a, you know...
Are you saying that...
A coincidence?
... communistical Ruskies are ahead of America in Erotica?
Yeah, I'm just saying...
Well, friends, we've got to get busy.
There used to be...
I have an article...
We can't allow a porno gap.
That's right, Mr. President.
... of Putin is in Rasputin.
Wow.
And they know they have Rasputin.
They have to breed more prodigiously than the commies.
They purportedly have Rasputin's penis on display.
That's John Dillard.
I would call that a holy relic, all right.
No, I've seen it.
How many ways did they try to kill him?
It just means you can't kill him.
It had little I's on the end, right?
You know, I could give such a great historical lecture right now.
I'd like to hear it.
I'd like to know.
Why can't you?
Go ahead.
Barge in.
Suspended in formaldehyde.
Listen.
It's behind a curtain.
And you have to...
You have to do this.
Now, what I want to know, what I want to know is...
Has it...
Hold on, hold on.
What I want to know, hey, professor, what I want to know is, is it...
Safe?
Is it...
What kind of state is it in, shall I say?
Is it in a discernibly turgid state?
I mean...
No, no.
It's not Iraq, but it's 13 inches.
It's quite large.
He was 13 inches flaccid?
Yes.
It's quite large.
No wonder he was a mad monk.
You know, if I had equipment like that and I was stuck as a monk, you can't even use it.
... as Alexander.
No, we liked him so much.
But, you know, listen, all you guys...
He was quite promiscuous, you know.
Ivan Stang has the straight poop on this.
I knew Rasputin.
Rasputin was a madman.
I was there when those boyars killed him.
They strangled him.
They beat him.
They cut his weenie off.
They shot him.
They knifed him.
And he still...
He died.
The title of this article was...
Drowning.
The title of this article is...
I quit.
Rasputin was poisoned, shot, beaten, and drowned.
Oh, okay.
Sorry I brought it up.
Yes, he drowned in...
What was the idea of cutting his weenie off?
That's not normally a fatal...
Well, you know...
Hey, you've gone that far already.
You know, you might as well throw that in just for good measure.
They were bored Russian aristocrats.
So why would you say then it would be the reason for the secret police to remove his penis?
So they could put it in the freaking museum.
Yeah.
I think we should have a Cleveland Museum of Erotica.
And maybe we could get like Ralph Perks penis.
You mean Cleveland Little Museum?
Ralph Perks?
No, no, Cleveland Erotica Museum.
In Cleveland?
Yes.
Okay, well, let's put that before the next city council meeting.
Maybe we could put Dr. Sinister's penis up for play.
And move on to new business.
You're going to give it up.
Seriously, you know, it would probably get more use in a museum than it would detach my own body, so...
Well, now, that's a sad thing.
Now, put your pants back on, Dr. Sinister.
That's all right.
I believe you.
We believe you.
Sorry, I forgot.
Pull them up.
I believe you.
We believe you.
Well, I think you should go to the leather stallion then tonight, maybe.
We are on duty doing a radio show.
Do you have any idea?
Have you any conception of...
You can't just drop things and go off to the leather stallion.
The social responsibility is so great.
Many of them crack half of the time.
Oh, well, if you're offering crack, then that's a different matter.
The schedule of over-consumption is large.
Are you guys on drugs tonight?
Sometimes 300 miles long.
Are you, Professor?
No, no, I don't do any drugs at all.
Although I've been running a lot of...
I get the feeling you are high on something else.
Would I, Tom?
I've been running into a lot of people who do a lot of drugs lately.
It's very strange.
Yes, you and Mr. and Sister.
Very large percentages of the population.
They consume various substances on a regular basis.
Us people are on drugs.
I've had someone say this something about these drug cases.
I can shake any man on this lip.
It's a recording of staying at S-Day 2.
I mean, I'm a guy who does a lot of DMT.
You know a guy who does a lot of DMT?
Yeah.
At the DMV?
So does it become like...
Does it get easy?
Is that one of those things that gets easier every time?
Because I've never heard a...
I've never heard a description of DMT usage as being all that pleasant.
It all depends if you use the venom of the Colorado River Toad.
You know what that means.
There's ayahuasca.
You've got to keep trying it one time more.
Just one more time.
Damn, man.
I mean, Tammy.
Yeah.
Well, there's a good description of Daniel Pinchbeck's book called Breaking Open the
Stories about Modern High-Tech Shamanism in Contemporary America.
He has a good description of...
I know it exists.
I've been...
I've been to those ceremonies in Hollywood.
They had a private one.
They had the shamans flown in for it.
And I was there.
Participated.
It's designed to brainwash all of us into accepting a new world order.
Too late.
We've already accepted it.
Hey, hey.
Wake up, sleepo.
You're all asleep.
You don't know nothing.
Oh, my God.
I've got to warn people by calling this college radio show.
It's going to take him a long time.
It's going to take a long time to figure out that I hung up on him.
Because I don't think he was even listening before he called it.
Hey, jet fuel don't meet melt steel.
And I'm not used to him calling this early.
Usually, he only calls me after midnight.
I think he was on drugs.
In the case of that previous caller, if he had a hallucination that he was being swarmed,
they wouldn't be ants.
They'd be little tiny Jews.
He's a notorious anti-Semite conspiracy theorist, actually.
I got the impression that that guy was rather tactful.
Taking himself a bit seriously.
What is it about mental illness and anti-Semitism that there's such a strong correlation between that?
They're jealous because the Jewish chicks are so hot.
He wanted to get some pots and pans together and start slamming some chili on the stove.
Oh, someone's making a call.
Oh, this guy wants to call in again.
Let's have it.
You again?
Go away.
Ted, listen.
Ted, just go away.
Okay?
Don't go away angry.
Just go away.
Okay.
So now that guy's like an SS guy or something.
He calls up every weekend.
He's just a really, really obnoxious person.
And sometimes it's fun to talk to him, but eventually, as soon as he says words like
Illuminati or whatever, you know that you've pretty much gone into the realm of stuff.
But I thought he was talking about ancient Romans.
And half the stuff he says is Sonny the Great.
All right.
You know what?
Since we let one non-subgenius caller on before.
I guess we should let one more on.
Yeah.
One more.
One more on.
Let's get a good one this time.
One more person on.
And that is this guest here.
Hello, you're on the air.
This is the subgenius caller.
Guess who's there?
Who is there?
Subgenius.
Yes.
Speak up.
Subgenius.
Me, subgenius.
You.
Subgenius.
Church of the rub penis.
The subgenius.
The planet Venus?
The planet Venus.
Let's try this again.
I'm not a man.
You're on the air.
WCS 3 FM.
Subgeniuses are being eaten by mosquitoes.
Let's let the new caller speak for a second.
Hello, no money mark.
Welcome to the program.
Subgenius?
Good to talk to everybody.
Well, so much for no money mark.
Okay.
Let's just let him talk for a second, okay?
He's a good guy.
He's been loyal to the program.
Let him talk already.
Let him talk.
Let him speak for a second.
Put him on.
I'm going to hang up on every single one of you and kick you all out.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh.
Is Dave still there?
They hung up.
Yeah, they got too many hangups.
Oh, we lost Dave.
Oh, look.
We lost everybody.
Do your own thing, man.
You mean nobody is on now?
They're all gone?
They're all gone.
Hello, you're on the air.
I'm back.
You're back.
All right.
And you're beautiful.
And hey, I think the other people are back too.
They're all beautiful.
I'm back.
Hello.
Oh, you hate me so much, Dr. Sinister.
Why is that?
Because you're really annoying.
Okay, Mark, you're on the air.
That was quick.
Okay, well, I would just like to warn you guys that whatever you do, stay away from
New Zealand because it's about to be taken over.
Really?
By giant carnivorous crickets.
No, by subredditors.
Subredditors?
Okay, you've heard of the Reddit site, right?
I read it every day.
I did a Reddit interview.
You did?
Yes, I did.
How about that?
Mm-hmm.
Have you heard of a group that's on Reddit called the Red Pill?
Yes, I have.
They're horrible people.
They are, from everything I've heard.
They're like an anti-feminist group.
We hate them.
They're basically pro-rape advocates.
Mm-hmm.
Well, also, they call themselves the Red Pill because of the Matrix, because they're the
only ones who see the world as it really is.
There's no Red Pill in the Matrix.
Mm-hmm.
But anyway, this is why I read recently, thanks to a pro-feminist site that mocks the anti-feminist
sites called We Hunted the Mammoths.
Okay, so there is...
Mammoths?
We hunted the mammoths.
Princess We did indeed hunt mammoths in her years.
Yes, she was a hunter.
She was a hunter.
She was a hunter from the start.
Yeah, so...
Anyway, enough backstory.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, so there's an anti-troll law in New Zealand that just got passed, and these guys
are afraid that their site is going to be banned there because of it, so here is their
plan for dealing with it, thanks to a poster called, I kid you not, Gay Lube Oil.
Okay.
Quote, the Red Pill is 120,000 fit, college-educated.
Middle-class men.
If we really wanted to, we could invade New Zealand and install a new government.
We definitely have the manpower.
There are plenty of veterans here.
Plus, everyone here knows where the magazine releases on an M-16 from years of playing
Call of Duty.
Do they even use M-16s anymore?
I thought they used the M-4 nowadays instead.
Well, I mean, the point is, apparently this guy believes that the...
The last Starfighter principle works in real life.
Right.
If you're good enough at video games, you'll be recruited.
Isn't that what the U.S. Defense Department does?
You know, I've been contacted by the Monster Attack team because I got so good at Monster
Hunter, that game.
Now, I can't...
I don't even know how to load the shotgun that I used to have, and yet, I can sure
mow them down.
I can't mow them down in that video game.
Okay, so...
Well, those manly men are very oppressed these days by the limp-wristed sissies, the
high-voiced women, and just about every kind of weak, outnumbered minority somehow is able
to bully these manly men to such an extent that they're just crying and weeping and complaining
and...
What's the matter with these huge...
The girls picked on us manly men.
Brawny, broad-shouldered...
Those homosexuals picked on me.
Flannel shirt-wearing, stubble-chinned, watch-cat-wearing...
They made fun of my neckbeard.
I'm going to hate women forever and start a website.
I can't believe that neckbeards became a thing.
I actually had a neckbeard once when I was a teenager, just to be ridiculous.
I'm like, I've never seen one of these before, ha ha ha.
And then fast forward many, many years later, suddenly it's a thing now.
A gross thing?
And you gotta pair it with a fedora.
I don't like it, but I'm hard-wired not to like it.
By the way, there is a little bit left of this comment here that is almost as funny
as what you've heard.
Realistically, red pill reaction force would be far more effective than half the world's
militaries.
The Afghan military is fucked up on opium.
The Iraqi army can't even do jumping jacks.
Plus, New Zealand has only 8,000 military personnel.
The majority of whom are useless paper pushers.
I don't actually support the violent overthrow of New Zealand.
I just think it's kind of a fun idea conceptually.
But they make all those movies there about hobbits and things.
I don't know why that has to be overthrown.
They've got King Kong and a whole bunch of giant orcs and stuff.
How are you going to fight them?
And, as I said earlier, they have giant crickets.
Not to mention all the sheep.
Seriously, the sheep will put up a fight.
Right.
And Ruthie Lawless could take out all these guys and win.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
We're starting to get some of our callers back here.
There.
Actually, I think this is a new caller.
One more try.
Oh, hey.
What's going on?
Not much.
We're just sitting around chewing the fat.
You're supposed to know.
I was curious why the ancient tradition of throwing stang in the pond was not adhered
to during X-Day.
We weren't anywhere near the pond.
I walked into the pond myself.
Followed by a...
A number of delightful young ladies and young men.
That's true.
And then I dunked them in the pond over and over again.
That's been the tradition ever since the year the conspiracy calls 1998.
Yeah.
Because I turned it around.
How about them apples?
Now I do the dunking and they do the kerplunking.
He does the dunking and they're the donuts.
All right.
As a newcomer, you know, Reverend Peace feels very strongly we should go back to the traditional
way of throwing.
I haven't...
I haven't thrown stang into the pond.
And I think...
Oh, okay.
Well, why don't you do that?
...and leave on side of that.
I guess you better do that.
Reverend Pease can't even spell his own title.
Well, that's true, but that's part of the love and...
He can't even.
...in terms of that is Reverend Pease.
All right.
So, anyway, now I'm worried that...
Hello?
We're in the town.
I'm told you to go away, okay, Ted?
We're not letting you on anymore this week.
I'm told you to go away.
Outside agitators.
Agitators, witches, hippies, and Jews.
And, by the way, I don't know, if somebody could, like, send a text to Princess Wee to
tell her that I didn't mean to hang up on her, could someone tell, like, we and Philo
and Dave that I did not mean to hang up on them?
Yeah, I'll let them know.
We have heard that kind of thing happen before.
They've all done radio or been callers.
It was going to be intentional that you were going to hang up on her.
I said I was going to, but that was just an idle threat.
It's kind of like back in the Cold War.
We had that mutually assured destruction thing going on.
Well, that's true.
It was a challenging time.
Nobody really intended to launch all the nukes.
I was confident in the ability of my laminate desk to protect me from any nuclear fallout
that was about to happen.
Nuclear.
You know.
Grammar Nazi.
Ach du lieber, ein Stoller.
It sounds like Andy Kaufman's on the phone.
Well, look, we appreciate the contribution you've made.
It seems to be voguing up the air a little bit, though, so we're going to...
Okay, well, it was a pleasure myself.
It was wonderful talking to all of you, and have a pleasant night.
Oh, slacker.
There was a guy who threw up, and we could do an update on him.
Have a little patience, my God.
Bob put it in Ayn Rand.
We messed up.
Oh, superstitious, eh?
They don't deserve to know what's going on.
Next time!
Easy.
So is this a...
Stang, remember your blood pressure.
Do you have to actually log into Facebook to view it?
I'm afraid so.
But I think Facebook is the most insidious tool the conspiracy ever came up with,
and I will not touch it with a ten-foot pole.
Then you're plum out of luck, and you're going to miss all them titty pictures from the Bob test.
That's all there is to it.
I'm not going to put it on subgenius.com only because that guy wanted me to.
So much for that idea.
Let's move on now.
You see, he needed to...
I see those pictures, and that's what makes it...
Because he can't come to X-Day because he's too much of a wimp to come to X-Day.
No offense, Dr. Simpson.
If anything...
If anything, the Facebook page should just link to the sub-site where the real information is stored.
Yes, it should be completely reorganized.
I can't agree more.
That's just my opinion.
We've got to start all over again.
How about your opinion?
You know, yours opinions is interesting to us.
We need to know...
I bet that was one of those people that...
Are you mocking me, Hal?
No, I'm just adding on that we...
We welcome a great diversity of opinions here.
The people who hate me for not working hard enough are usually the people who can't even spell Bob's name right.
I hate Ivan Stang for not working hard enough.
Right.
I got your message, buddy.
I'm going to remember your name is on a list now.
Uh-oh.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Don't have to take steps, huh?
Bob sees all, Bob knows all.
And he tells his duly called ministers.
The dirty laundry behind those little sad bobbies.
Picking on hard-working old saintly Reverend Stang.
The kindly, humble Reverend Stang.
I have to take your laundry into Pomeroy.
Who could care absolutely very much, could not care less...
Thank you.
...about what some subgenius wants to see on his subgenius internet.
Or find underneath his subgenius Christmas tree.
We have news.
You can call her here.
Hi, this is Reverend Andrew Genis.
Reverend Andrew, did you get my Facebook message?
I did, and I responded to it.
It was a transposed area code.
Well, I'll eagerly attend to that when I manage to get away from the world of radio.
If she can tell us simply the correct area code, that won't reveal anything.
Yes, tell that, and I'll add it.
Okay.
You can go ahead and put it in my memorandum book.
Yes, it would be 856, and that would be correct.
So, there was a slight transcription error on my part?
Was that the start of the card?
Yeah, when you call 865, you get Satan and Hell, and they put your name on a book.
Yeah, so it's 856.
Okay, I thought that guy sounded very grumpy and unpleasant.
I kept calling him.
Now we know that you live somewhere in New Jersey, and we are going to start stalking you,
because we know you live somewhere in New Jersey.
Oh, my God.
The Garden State.
Only one of the most populated states.
It's beautiful.
It's a beautiful place.
Reverend Andrew Genis, by the way, so the listeners and Dr. Sinister know,
Reverend Andrew Genis is one of the mutant mountain boys, among other things.
Yes.
She did a great show at X Day of her spoken word stuff and her songs and her subgenius hit song,
May Your Records Be Unbroken.
So I was hearing intermittently some of the reports of X Day,
and I really, really, really regret not being there for the whole time.
You were there for the best part.
Okay.
No, it was cool.
In my view.
So there's always the next time, and it's a large target to hit.
There's the next drill, yeah.
I mean, you know what?
It never works out.
Like Bob, I don't know what his deal is, but, you know, I was there.
I was waiting in mid-Pennsylvania.
I went out in the field.
I waited at 7 a.m.
Oh.
Nothing happened.
We were out there, too, but I hope you had a good time at X Day.
I did.
Absolutely.
Yeah, me too.
Definitely.
So, you see, it's a, what is it, an ill wind that blows nobody any good.
Even if the saucers didn't actually descend, you know, they probably got all messed up.
They are fallible.
They're beings like anybody else.
It could happen any second.
It could happen this second.
Or this.
Oh, I already did that.
Stop trying to scare.
False alarm.
You know, now that it all has happened or hasn't happened,
I kind of like a breathing space before we all pony up for the next inflatable miracle that refuses to inflate.
That's right.
Let's get some breathing room here, and then we'll be able to face the future more steadfastly.
Yes, yes.
Absolutely.
Reverend Andrew, you should know that when, was that really this very morning?
Yes.
Dr. Hal and the other doctors and I drove down to the stone circle to meet the gathered subgeniuses.
They'd already been ruptured.
Their empty clothes were scattered all around the stone circle.
It's true.
And we were feeling pretty left behind until we heard them giggling behind the trees.
They were hiding.
They played a trick on us.
Hiding over in the poison ivy, snickering and giggling at us.
Uh-oh.
So.
That's dessert for me.
I don't know.
No.
But it was a good attempt to create variety instead of monotony.
That's cool.
I'm sorry I missed it.
It was real where I was, you know.
It was a drill.
You cooperated.
You went out.
I did the best I could.
And you know the saucers will come to get you wherever you are.
They'll just get you first if you're at the landing site.
And I'll be seeing you again at the devotional, which I think is August 15th.
Yes.
In Cleveland?
Yes, you will.
15th and 16th.
And I might be a mountain boy that day.
That would be good.
We hope you can.
I think so.
We hope you can be a mountain.
Wait a minute.
That sounds funny.
A mountain boy.
Now you're getting it at last.
Right.
Well, you know.
There's all those possibilities, you know.
Absolutely.
Why not both?
That's what we say.
That's our motto.
Why not both?
Wait.
You might be a mountain boy.
Was that the joke that you guys were making?
Now you're getting it.
See, apprehension is sometimes slow.
He who laughs last.
Laughs best.
Thinks slowest.
Oh, wow.
Reverend Andrew, are you usually up at 10 minutes of midnight like this?
Is this not somewhat late for you?
Yes, it is.
It's about 11.51 p.m.
Well, what do you know about that?
We're all in the same time zone together.
That's pretty sexy.
Feels very intimate.
Unfortunately, think of all the other losers we're in the same time zone with.
Millions of them.
They're not tuned in.
There's not that many phone lines.
They can't all call in.
Yes, we don't recommend that everyone in the state right now call WCSB.
No, we would not want that to happen.
No, that would be a brute force attack.
It sounded like that had happened earlier in this very show.
I'm glad we got away from that, where everyone would gabble at the same time
and then stop at the same time, and there would be blobs of quietness interspersed.
It was kind of a bit cacophony, though.
Oh, you were listening.
Okay, well, as long as you can tell.
It's like a musical, you know, or something.
I didn't know what you were saying, but it was art.
Well, that's the problem.
You see, my own theory is that for that to work,
each voice has to be tremendously distinct from each other voice.
When they resemble each other,
it just sounds like...
well, a lot of noise with little signal.
You know what's going to happen?
You've recorded this on a CD.
CD?
And hardly anybody uses CDs for anything anymore.
Oh, yeah?
The apocalypse is going to come.
All the technology is going to be lost,
but someone's going to find a CD player,
and they're going to find this CD,
and they're not going to have any of the voice recognition software that we have now.
And people will have this CD wondering,
and nobody will be speaking modern English anymore either, of course,
because it's far off in the future.
And people are going to spend centuries,
trying to decipher what this noise is.
They're going to be convinced there's some kind of a really profound deep message.
They followed a god named Bob.
Well, they have a lot of time on their hands in the future.
Up time.
It looks like they've solved some of the problems of leisure,
the basis of culture.
Now they can spend all their time with our old discs.
It's so glad to hear the show taking this turn at this hour,
since we are...
Drawing to a close.
Oh, yes, that's right.
We have only a few precious more moments to squeeze out of this radio slot.
Terrible.
Well, I will let you do your official closing.
All right, Andrew.
Price Andrew.
All right, so we...
Andrew sounds like a girl.
Well, you see, welcome to the present, Reverend Stan.
Oh, yeah, I know.
It's that gender blur again, but...
Andrew Genis.
Yeah.
The subgenius.
Now you're getting it again.
More delayed appreciation.
Yes.
So, I guess that wraps it up.
We've said just about all we can say about X-Day, storms, the entire Megillah.
And we had Dr. Philo Drummond, of course, lonesome cowboy Dave,
Reverend Andrew Genis, and many others who qualified our comment.
Well, for...
Thank you very much for visiting us today.
And again, yeah, I'm sorry, last week, I proposed that they replace the porta-potties with the wormhole.
Right.
Boy, you'd never hear the end of it.
And, you know, the same band who brought us that song, I recently discovered another song by them this week,
which I think is almost as ingenious.
So, I think I'm going to close with that song.
This is by the Toilet Bowl Cleaners.
And I hope you enjoy it.
Well, we were lying in a field
Just staring at the clouds
And telling you that we're not alone
Telling each other what they looked like
She said, that cloud over there
Kinda looks like a house
And I said, that cloud over there
Kinda looks like a mouse
And then I started thinking
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You know, you could do the same thing
With your poo
So I said, baby, let's go
Poop in a toilet
Stare at it and see
What it resembles
If we wipe our butts
The toilet paper should go into our...
Barrel
Cause if we put it in the toilet
It would cover up the poop
And ruin everything
It would ruin everything
Everything
Well, she was into it
And we broke up
And almost instantly
I woke up
I realized that I never loved her
I went home and pooped
And stared at it for hours and hours
And I was...
I was...
Hours and hours
I stared at it for hours and hours
For free information, see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob.
We fucked up!
Fuck a clown!