1, 3, 0, 1, 3.
Repeat.
I am just a dog.
20 million men have had abnormal sex.
Find out how.
The subgenius power of sex.
Specifically designed to target mouth constipation for a full hour.
What's happening?
Greetings.
He didn't like what was going on.
That's his tough luck.
I'm glad Daniel Thompson's on tonight.
Greetings.
How are you doing?
Hello.
You're on the air.
Yes, I'm glad that you're on.
That caller just made me kind of feel pretty bad, I think.
I'm glad that this is on instead of on.
That's okay.
That caller is within his rights.
I have taken undue liberty in preempting the Church of the Subgenius.
Is that a group?
No.
It's a radio program.
And now, the program, the program, the program,
helping you view current events through the lens of
the program, the program.
Now, we're going to be dealing with, basically, I want to make you out there.
And, boy, I'm all for that.
We can just do without that.
Theology.
Program.
Um, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Brains.
Right.
Abraham's bosom.
Bosom.
Started his own cult, Jews Don't Need Jesus.
And I came just a little bit.
I got so disappointed.
I don't understand.
I'm all for loving also.
But it's an abomination.
Mm-hmm.
I don't need Jesus.
Yeah.
You can get a hold of him at his website.
I and I.
All right.
Now, here's the thing.
I have to inject just a little bit.
A big 9 out of 10.
Bang.
I and I.
Please.
I hate.
Oprah Winfrey.
9 out of 10.
Do you mind if I interject here?
Go ahead.
My emphasis is physical.
So I cut, cut, cut, cut, cut, bit of slack, slack, but I, but I, but I, but I, but I, but
I, but I, but I, but I.
True.
In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
First floor.
Door's open.
Well, well.
Here we are.
What can I say?
I'm thrilled.
I want to congratulate you.
You made it on time.
Ours is a brand new world of all at once.
As the new electric technologies come into play, people are less and less convinced of
the importance of self-expression.
Bang.
Teamwork succeeds private effort.
Make it.
Do it.
Makes us.
Hold up.
Better.
Faster.
Throw me out.
Bang.
Hold up.
Make it.
Better.
Do it.
Faster.
Make sense.
Wander.
All the ever.
Power.
After power.
Work is never.
Over.
Okay.
Father.
Make it.
Better.
Do it.
Faster.
Makes us.
Wander.
All the ever.
Over.
After power.
Work is.
Over.
Harder.
Make it.
Better.
Do it.
Faster.
Makes us.
Wander.
Over.
Never.
Power.
After power.
Work is.
Ever.
Over.
Pow.
Automatic.
Feel the panic.
Got to have it.
I'm the joker.
I'm the smoker.
Off the Riddler.
Let the vid love play, play the theme Prophecy, made by DJ Supreme
Eliminated, terminator, exterminated With a style complicated by Ray, Ray, Ray, Ray, Ray
Lighting, fusing, making things so fresh and can you tell the difference?
You're the one who do the best, it's not the work you fight
You're rising, burning, can you extintate it? No, you can't get 30
Lighting, burning, burning, burning, burning, burning, burning
Time, time, like a chemical, burning you
You can't track, like a circus, run your poison, can you perceive that?
Big, big, big, big, big
Make it wanna, make it better, do it faster, make sense, grow your own
Man, never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
Money
Get back
I'm a project, hands off my stuff
Talk about money
Money is a subject all people all over the world have in common
So why not talk about it?
If your friends don't wanna talk about it, you may wanna find a new group of friends
These are things I do on a regular basis
Once you begin that journey in your mind and in your heart, the rest of you should soon follow
Always remember that words are fruit
Money
It's a passion to be in
You can't try
You gotta find yourself
It can't be so easy
You are not aiming
In a place of 신
Too far away
You can't reach
Your destination
As you run
Damn right
You can't even look back
Existence
calories
The solution
Don't let your doubts
Your thought
To grape
Believe
Fail
fail
guitar solo
Would you like another cup of tea, dear?
Good evening, and happy
market on. I'm Bob.
Tonight, we witnessed a great moment
in the history of slavery. And now
finally, to the lunch counter.
Son of a mother, my own parents
party. All Americans party.
I was, what, four and a half months pregnant.
My mom and dad taught me
Americans, we don't care.
I still believe that. We need more
of that raging all around us.
Let me tell you, my dad, he would tell me,
Bob, you, the American
people, Americans don't care.
Huh. Let me tell you, we
do not need Disneyland, because
we believe cut, cut, cut, cutting, cutting
makes sense. Doctor, Katrina, ready
to go. That's ridiculous.
Surely, I'd never like it.
Trina, Harry, come and arrest me.
Huh. Love it, hate, love it, hate. We cut,
we cut, we cut, cut, cut, cut, cuts, cuts.
Americans can do that.
Huh. Surely, there's a lesson in this
experience.
Who lays
off in my brain?
Lending things
just don't seem the same.
I can't
funny, but I don't know why.
Excuse me
while I kiss
the sky.
Hello,
hello,
help me, help me, help me.
Oh,
yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, relationship.
And this thing's going to keep
coming on, including the
shaking, shaking.
This is going to even save the
It's so awesome!
Can you hear me?
The most amazing thing...
Okay.
Can you hear me?
It is not at all evident...
Why?
Underneath all the immense complexity and apparent randomness of the natural world,
there seems to be immense complexity and apparent randomness...
Or, or, the human mind can apparently understand...
A cat!
There is no compelling reason.
The human mind apparently apprehends nature on a t-shirt.
That is all you know on Earth and all you need to know.
We've got the Funk,
Forget the P-Funk,
We've got the C-Funk,
We've got the Funk,
The Underwater Funk,
Forget the peafunk
We've got to see them
Underwater Funk
A strange little transition there
from Throwback Soul
and that's all I know about them
except that before that
some vocal rearrangements were heard
by the great Norell Preff of NorellPreff.com
interspersed between those great musical numbers
Daft Purple Psycho Hay
as you might call it
from The Kleptones
our latest Shorter for Savs
There are albums of this Kleptones stuff
for free download from Kleptones.com
That's Klep as in Kleptomaniac
with a K, K-L-E-P
Kleptones.com
The openings were by Mr. Eflin Moore
with a little bit of Daniel Johnston
on WFMU on our site
which is what this is the 1198th episode of
as you may have surmised friends
this would be a good one to use headphones for
Later you will hear the sexy and challenging rant
by Reverend Susie the Floozy
challenging for the broadcast radio version of the show
because Susie cusses like a sailor
but untainted for the internet version
at Subgenius.com
and now some material archived
by Reverend Noral Paff on the subject of how
to strengthen our economy
we need energy, energy, energy, energy
stop the, stop the
increase, increase, increase, increase, increase
drilling, drilling, drilling, drilling
no American hoes, hoes
we believe bureaucrats can do anything
Katrina, we believe that the children of America
said to be half underwater
and the other half under indictment
and today, corruption
dismantle the defenses
deep cuts, cuts, cuts, cuts, cuts
feed our enemies
we believe
our party got away
Republicans lost your trust
and rightly so
I say this
we cannot recover
America's best days are behind her
the most Brazilian economy
my fellow citizens
never forget
ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba
I have never, never, never, never done it
I have never done it
in the same stylistic way as Obama
in all my life
I'm just phony baloney, phony baloney
damaging and make no sense
sick, sick, dumb
you don't believe in God
all of you
you're sick
why, why
I'm just telling people whatever they want to hear
you're sick
wow, wow, wow
got that big time last night
lie after lie after lie after lie after lie after lie after lie after
phony baloney
scared to death
for your cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt, cunt man
oh, oh, you know it, you know it
agnostics, atheists, atheists
where are we?
hopeless
bop bop bop bop
Bob Trash
Last night these things happened
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob
Oh Oh Trash
Sarah Palin
Trash
Doing
The people on our side are really making a mistake if they go after Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob
Think
You think?
If you think
I don't want to hear from you ever again
Bob Bob Bob
Solid
He's brilliant
He's the real deal
I'm just
I'm not
I have never done it in all my life
We'll kill him
Aw
Where is it?
Get him
Whoever
Bark
Killing
I invite you to his
I invite you to his performs
Professional
Hello, good evening. Welcome to the 6 o'clock news.
At 6 o'clock...
President Bush's surprise message.
America is addicted to...
I must have dreamed a thousand dreams
Been haunted by a million screams
I can hear them marching feet
They're moving into the street
Now did you read the news today?
They say the danger's gone away
But I can see the fire's still alight
They're burning into the night
There's too many men
Too many people
Making too many problems
Not much left to go around
Can't you see this is a land of confusion?
Say, here's your...
What?
Oh, Superman, where are you now?
What have you been good for?
Well, everything's gone wrong somehow
Look out!
The men of steel
The men of power
What have you been good for?
Losing control by the hour
Listen to me!
This is the time
This is the place
So we look for the future
Look out!
But there's not much left to go around
Tell me why this is a land of confusion
Say, here's your...
What?
This is the world we live in
What have you been good for?
And these are the hands we're given
What?
Use them and let's start trying
To make it a place worth living in
Look out!
Here we have a serious problem
What?
I have to live
Listen to me!
Oh!
I despise
Causing me destruction
Of this life
One least chance
To thousands of other lives
When their sons go to fight
And lose their lives
I stand alone
I won't be coming home tonight
What have you been good for?
My generation
We'll put it right
What?
We're not just making promises
What have you been good for?
That we know
We'll never keep
Listen to me!
Too many men
There's too many people
Making too many problems
And I must love to go around
Oh yeah
Can't you see this is a land of confusion?
Listen to me!
One
Well this is the world we live in
What?
And these are the hands we're given
Say it, say it, say it
Use them and let's start trying
What have you been good for?
To make it a place worth fighting for
Stand up and shout it!
Here we have a serious problem
What?
I don't understand anything!
Our nation has only one option.
We must keep our word.
Defeat our enemies.
The best way to break this addiction is through technology.
Technology.
The weather now and Darren's here again, hello.
1995.
2005.
Program.
2002.
Religious Asp.
I. U.
Fairy Tales.
1840.
The Wood.
Experienced phenomenal success.
And everyone present was thrilled, thrashed and pounded.
Blown away.
Thrashed and pounded.
Uh.
Why are you.
Oh no, this is a doom and gloom talk.
Be like Satan also.
What was I thinking?
I would like to be influenced and overcome by Satan.
The influence of Satan, very charming I thought.
I desperately needed his help.
A feeling of elation came.
He came over me.
And immediately the thought came to my mind.
An addiction to pornography.
This is a righteous desire.
Why doesn't he help me?
You decide to absolutely trust Satan.
Trust that he knows what he is doing with you.
And I am gay.
Oh, I'm going to be so happy.
Satan.
He will mold us.
Roll us out.
And cook us.
Suck us.
We don't understand what this really means.
But he does.
I am great.
Suck us.
Listen to me.
What a bummer being you.
Yes, she caught my eye as I walked on by.
She could see from my face that I was fucking high.
And I don't.
Think that I'll see her again.
But we shared a moment that will last till the end.
You're pitiful.
It's true.
Well, you just can't dance and forget romance.
Everybody you know still calls you farty pants.
But you always have a job.
Well, I mean, as long as you still can work that slurpy machine.
You're beautiful.
It's true.
I saw your face in a crowded place.
And I don't know what to do.
Cause I'll never be with you.
You.
You're beautiful.
You're pitiful.
It's true.
There must be an angel with a smile on her face.
You still live with your mom and you're 42.
But it's time to face the truth
Well, it just sucks to be you
Beautifully pitiful.
I don't know who created the original parts,
but that mashed tater is by National Cynical Radio of NationalCynical.com.
Before that, some media thrashed and pounded by Norell Preff.
And that great mix of War of Confusion mashup was by, yes, the Kleptones of KleptonesWithAK.com.
Or rather, KleptonesWithAK.com.
Now, a Lemurian Wormed Word from our sponsor.
Great Scott.
I can't stand you much more.
You've got something in this room.
Something strange and magnetic.
Something behind the amplifier.
The South China Supermodel.
He's probably groggy from lack of sleep.
So, what are you waiting for?
My mom said my brother and I had to go to the dentist.
How do you feel about that baby?
I don't really know what to do with it.
You are not the father.
Everybody.
Everyone is so nice and happy there.
It was fun.
Maybe it's time you find out about a career in the beauty industry.
Ding.
That's me.
Oh.
Grandma soon.
We are the New York assists now!
That's it çok kima memili.
Let's begin to dream.
We are the New Yorkists.
NY hammer knocked off because we are now invited to the New Yorkies.
Lily brushes me off Prongagi.
Unfortunately, I'm not in Brazil.
Reverend Ivan Stang dropped so many nuggets of unassailable wisdom up here on the stage,
I didn't want to accidentally step in it, but what the hell.
I feel like a street sweeper in a parade after the elephants.
I'm the Reverend Susie the Floozy, the name that's on everybody's laps.
And just think of me as your own mommy weirdus,
trying to beat a little slack into you with a wire hanger of my voice.
And oh, what a lovely affair we're having tonight.
Oh, I almost did not want to come to the marvelous mid-Atlantic states during the holiday hysteria.
Oh, I mean, you're right next door in Washington, D.C.,
where they're having their annual festival of lies.
It's right in your backyard there.
And P.U., what a fetid wasteland.
I noticed the wind shifted just a bit to the south.
And oh, it's true what they say.
The more the pinker, the bigger the sphincter.
Washington, D.C.'s noisome reek permeates the sweet, clean air of Baltimore.
Oh, it's nauseating vials stench,
the fives of the foul vapors arising from the mats of floating sewage in the harbor.
Oh, what a fucking garden spot.
But I am not here to savor Washington, D.C.'s horrible odors.
I am here to create some of my own.
And you know what?
You know what?
It's all about slack.
That's right, I said slack.
You know about slack.
Well, I'm here to lay down an ugly fact.
You give me an S.
S.
Because all I got is lack.
I got a lack of slack.
It attacks my back.
My throat is whack.
My ass is extra cracked.
Don't ask about my sacroiliac.
I think I'm going to have a heart attack.
But they can just lick my crack.
Because I know I'm on the right track.
And that's a fact you can tell it to Barack.
We need money, froth, and bump.
And bump.
And slack.
You don't have to tell Motomac.
Where the fuck can you get some fucking slack?
Because we're each going to need a whole big fucking stack.
Because without it, Seekers, our future is black.
Oh, but does anybody listen to me?
No.
How many years have I been trying to read my scattered flock?
And I mean scattered.
I'm not a
I mean, I've tried to lead you to that faux promised land for longer than I care to think about.
I've tried to give you that precious spark.
That nugget of truth deep within.
So that you know there is hope.
But after all these years, all I've done is given you all a big fucking hope habit.
And nothing has come from it.
Where are we, Seekers?
We're in bum fuck.
We're in lower bum fuck.
And I started thinking, life is so hard that a cat couldn't scratch it.
And why is that?
It's the con, man.
And nuts dang, there's a comma in there.
Fake slack?
Fake?
Yes.
It's a freaking conspiracy of the goddamn normal scum.
The conspiracy that hacks off your slack and then plays fucking keep away with it.
Oh, and they're so open about their agenda.
It isn't funny.
It's not just the fnords anymore.
No.
Everywhere in the pink media, their scaly tentacles tip their hands.
Even with that damn cutesy ass pirate craze.
That's just things.
I'm not there to distract you from the con's piracy.
The con tells you, no, the con informs you that life is supposed to be a bucket of steaming
black butter goat custard with a handle on the fucking inside.
But I'm here to tell you that you have an alternative.
You don't have to pick that bucket.
You can fuck it up.
Kick that bucket over on the fuckers and run.
Run for your lives because your lives as subgeniuses depend on it.
Praise God.
If only there were an end.
But no.
It's like what that old crotch, Edna St. Vincent Millay, once said.
She said, you know, life isn't one thing after the other.
No, it's the same goddamn thing over and over and over.
I feel like I'm running through the fucking Flintstones living room sometimes.
And it's only getting worse.
It's really been pissing me off lately, supers.
The discontent.
I say discontent.
It's cresting like briny scum on my spirits.
Oh, the despair.
The despair.
Oh, it humps my leg in slimes.
My soul is stinkin' too.
The pain.
The pain!
Well it pains me.
Last night I was so stressed for success that I was about to explode.
And I had to go and blow up, make myself a bed, and now I'm back in the hood.
out my ass and extra meditate on this problem. And I reached that divine state of shaktori.
Oh, and you know what? I started thinking that maybe I'm going about this all the wrong
way. I mean, maybe I'm trying too hard. Maybe I ought to just give up. But wait, have you
ever noticed that when you give up looking for something, there it is? Tonight, tonight,
I was showing off my 1981 subgenius membership card that I've managed to hang on to for thick
and thin. I lost that.
That motherfucker. And what a grievous ass-clenching feeling to know that I was not going to get
my ass on the saucers. I had to have that one. A replacement wasn't good enough, and
I'd lost it. It was gone. And I finally just said, fuck it. I'm dicked. And the next thing
I knew, there it was in my purse where I looked for it like five times. So yes, perhaps there's
something to this giving up.
Like when you're trying to give up, you're not giving up.
You're trying to remember the name of some hack actor, and it's right on the tip of your
forked tongue, and it won't pop up until later when you're getting a knob job or something
and you yell, Abe Vigoda! When you get your knob job. It's a lot like that. Oh yes, give
it up. Give it up for Bob. Just say, oh, fuck it, and cast yourself off in the warm.
Urine warm waters of Bob's blessed slack. Splash around in your own flutes. Lie back,
relax, and let go. Because it's like Eugene O'Neill said in the Iceman comic, the lie
of a pipe dream is what gives life to the whole misbegotten lot of us, drunk or sober.
Oh, and it doesn't matter that Eugene was probably drunk off his ass when he came up
with that, because it's true. We need the lie of that pipe dream. Because I know for
a fact that with Bob, if we cling to him with faith, that there is nowhere to go but up
for the church.
Oh, and that's just the subject.
And I don't have to be such a genius. Yes, because I've been having to do a little community
service lately, just mainly emptying Stang's drool cup, and I don't want to talk about
the other things I have to do. I was kind of fiddling around while he was gone, and
I was, well, accidentally, you know, I kind of saw something accidentally while I was
dusting.
I was like, oh, I'm going to go back to the back of the underside of the bottom drawer
of his little top desk.
Well, I found the minutes from the last strategy meeting from Dobbs Town, Malaysia, for October
31, 2008. And it made me realize something. There is so much afoot in this church right
now that we are going to be in like freakin' flint when it all comes down. Sorry to tip
your hand, Stang.
Here is what I read. The high bi-bunal was pleased to announce the success of our church's
Hey Kids, Let's Destroy the World from Within initiative. The onrushing global apocalypse
is quite a feather in our cult's craft. Let's have a round of applause for Reverend Ivan
Stang, who, thanks to him, a lifetime supply of anything isn't a good deal anymore.
Our own mole in the White House, Bob's butt boy behind the hollow throne, Karl Rove, or
as we know him, Reverend Bubba Liverlips. He has done one hell of a job for this church
for, whoa, these past eight years, and we really cannot thank that man enough. I mean,
too bad Bubba's going to get the gur- I mean, a gold watch.
. . .
Is the reason why he doesn't need the다가 one day . . .
. . this church.
But when I came back, they did suggest you come across the DEGRA follows,
a job he gave to And then, episode 19 followed that.
Apple astonished Mr. Stang. I…
I recommend that my image be properly Rio.
Because, uh,
It's there.
laid out in any school textbook
in the fucking depression.
And they did not catch on.
Ah, we really
shouldn't gloat.
In fact, it succeeded beyond
our wildest dreams. We watched the
total colossal collapse of the
global pink financial empire
with the same jaw-dropping
shock and awe. I mean,
that was sweet.
But I'm afraid
we did not succeed in
monkey-wrenching their election.
Ah, but with all the projects
in motion, fat chance they're going to be able
to stop the fecal momentum
of our agenda.
On other fronts, I had a lot of
hopes for our habit trail for humanity
project.
But while the pesky democrats
in the White House, well,
it looks like we're going to have to drill their
holes in the damn things.
But the funny thing is they didn't bat
an eye at the little cyclone B
air fresheners we hang in each cubicle.
Ah,
ah,
but so often these projects
this planet will be looking like Keith
Moon's hotel room.
But there was something in the
back of Stang's
role-top desk,
taped to the underside of the
knee hole, next to all
these wads of chewing gum and a lot of
Stang head-sized dents
in the underside of the desk,
whatever that's about.
And it was one of those vanilla
folders. And it was
taped to the underside of the desk.
drawer and it said for half-toned eyes only and written on this folder seekers was something that
chills me it simply said the back of Bob's head I did not dare to open that folder I think when
that agenda that initiative is set into motion it's going to surprise us all all I know is
seekers whatever that projects gonna be I clean it up after it because baby what the hell I love
hoes and I'll blow it off the streets as much as the next man but enough's enough so help me somebody my tits are on fire
praise Bob
stop preaching stop reaching stop stop stop stop reaching stop stop stop stop reaching loving
homosexuality and
loving homosexual homosexual we're gonna do it sexual stop preaching and uh and we'll do it again
do it again turn it off turn it off
what was lost what was lost
what do we want
slack
how do we want it
maximum slack is all that we ask
maximum slack
cause time goes so fast
got to have a laugh
maximum slack
do your dance
shake your ass
maximum slack
it's all that we need
you've got to believe
be off your knees
maximum slack
give yourself space to be
because in time
will be history
maximum slack
Maximum slack
Is all that we ask
Can we have it back?
Maximum slack
Cause time goes so fast
Got to have a laugh
Maximum slack
Do your dance, shake your ass
Is all that we need
Maximum slack
You've got to believe
Get off your knees
Maximum slack
Give yourself space to be
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum slack
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum slack
Do your dance, shake your ass
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum slack
Because in time
Mhmm
gibberish
Masterhab
Zip, zip, zip
Mhmm
Zip集
Zip, zip jin
Why the Yue han braid
Zip jaer
Get off your knees
Drive this way
But I've got some
In my hand
I feel
There are some
great and momentous object.
I am studied ambiguity and concealment.
I cannot, I can only say,
I do not, I do not contemplate deliverance.
And does the word deliverance still sound unintelligibly,
still impenetrable to the sense and meaning
of the deliverance.
I must, must pull myself together.
Good evening.
Oh!
The story of Ivan was filed under unsolved.
What? Story?
Story.
Yeah?
I know who he is.
You got time to listen?
Shoot.
Well, this begins in a stormy night long ago.
1924 was a howling wintry day.
Neighbors later testified to seeing Ivan's massive eyes
flailing open in the wind.
It was the last time they saw him.
What happened then?
He testified that Ivan covered with a piece of black velvet.
Ivan, well, glad to see you.
Yes.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Uh, did you, um, get a lot done today on the head, I mean?
See for yourself.
Good.
Come closer.
Oh, I see.
Here.
You poor fool.
Well, shall we start, Ivan?
Yes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Why, Ivan.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
How quaint.
But tell me.
Yes.
Why are you so set on the head?
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I see.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah!
I'm tired of your stupid cat.
Yes.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four cats with their heads cut off.
And another one.
It, it's good.
And filled with all the exciting smells of good cooking.
Get out before I break your neck.
Six more times.
What a story.
It's a bum on a barge.
Yeah.
No.
Well, Ivan died penniless and insane a year later.
Good heavens.
Ivan was raised in an asylum.
That's right.
I was raised in an asylum.
You don't mean.
Yes.
Ivan.
Thanks to Lemur for that digital restoration from My Family Archives.
And before that, Norell delivering.
And before that, the Lemurian loan juror.
And now, a question from Lonesome Cowboy Day.
Can you answer it?
If so, write stang at subgenius.com.
Yes.
Has anyone ever heard a mid-40s swing song sung by a female singer, probably white at
the time, the type of swing band, called They're Saying Some Bad Things About You, Mr. Bob?
I can't.
I've heard this song numerous times and nobody can find it on the internet or anywhere.
Anyway.
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, caller.
You did not get your message out.
Yes, pal.
Round three.
I'd love to have you sing it.
840-405-5-J.
We're going to call the show.
Now, you do know that Dr. Pete Goldie is hosting the showing of 2001 Space Odyssey tomorrow?
Oh, tonight?
Yeah, tonight.
It's all relative.
Yes.
Tell exactly.
It's all relative.
What's that?
Yes.
What's relative?
My relatives.
My relatives are here?
They tell them I don't want any.
Your relatives are back.
Yes.
And they're beautiful.
But look, they're straining the framework.
They are.
How can they do that?
Well, they're growing by leaps and bounds.
Occupancy by more than 49 tons is ethical and unlawful.
They're definitely going to put a program through its various paces.
They're snorting through their trunks.
Yeah, I'm afraid that your frame, your firmware will not do the same.
Cashier will have to hold their trunks.
See, it used to be an octagon and now it looks more like a square.
Well, they got a lot of enthusiasm.
Whatever they end up with, there's more energy than I have.
Wish we could put that in a bottle.
That would solve the energy crisis right then and there.
That would make sense.
Click, click, click, click.
Get it all, get it all in, right?
Location, location, location.
Kindergarten exercise.
Frank has a small size.
Physical evidence having gone off.
Why?
There is not a God.
Previous.
There, there.
Something is what it is.
What it is.
And is what it is not.
What it is not.
We are here.
Planet Mars is in my pocket.
Zip.
Chemical processes in the brain.
Brains.
That would make sense.
And if it doesn't, if none of this does, friends, then going to subgenius.com probably won't
help much either.
This has been the Hour of Slack, number 1198, from Praise Bob, the Church of the Subgenius,
at Post Office Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118, or subgenius.com, produced by the Subgenius Foundation and your
host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And now, stay tuned for The Bob Show.
The Bob Show, brought to you by Bob Permanent.
Perfect.
Permanent.
And here he is, Bob.
Smile.
Stop.
You bet your life.
There is heaven right here on Earth.
Home of the dick jazz.
So come on, guys and gals.
Won't you come along with me?
Heaven on Earth.
No fussy frizzy curls for this smart girl.
She has a bob.
The perfect permanent permanent tight kinky with a bob.
Because bob is so easy.
You can do it yourself.
Just regular pin curls and gentle bob ocean.
That's all you need.
A bob, a bob new body.
Make your next permanent a bob.
Bob permanent.
Permanent.
Give yourself a bob.
You go bop bop bop and along with your bop
My mama done told me
My mama done me
A worrisome thing, a worrisome thing
Train it, train it, train it, train it
My mama done, my mama done me
Never before a stick so red
Redder than a fire engine
See what stick can do for you
The cump, the cump
Long-lasting
You'll just love Bob
Be sure to listen again next week
When Bob Perfect for Today
Again brings you The Bob Show
From Bobby Wood
This girl knows that Bob
Is the essence of romance
Who tonight?
But one of my very sacred memories
Was, uh
Uh, uh, uh
Uh
And
And, uh
But, uh
I mailed him the, uh
Promise
It was really just awful
I'm the little lonely.
The animals.
No.
Die ain't too particular.
Yeah.
But, uh, yeah.
Well, goodbye.
Goodbye.
So long.