Usually radio announcements merely recommend a product,
but this station provides its clients with a special service.
The Subgenius.
Our host.
Swag.
In the radio studios of Bob,
the technicians, the entertainers, the commentators,
the administrative personnel
daily unite their efforts in the creation of programs to please and entertain a vast radio public.
The wide variety of broadcasts include group discussions,
political speeches,
and comedy.
On this program, frank opinions are expressed in response to their leaders' questioning.
Questions of the day are discussed, and opinions and attitudes freely expressed on issues of the moment.
For there is keen interest in a radio program that invites personal participation by the public.
This is the Subgenius.
This is independent radio in a democracy.
From PR News in Washington, I'm calling on other world leaders to join the fight against PR's new report since Sunday.
A massive wild Obama is more than a third contained.
The only language understood is the language of death.
Obama decried the PR News.
On Wall Street, 1922-37,
Missouri Highway Patrol says this is PR News.
Bob Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, Bob Bob Bob.
.
Dubs, bub, dubs, bub, dubs, bub!
Bub, bub, bub, bub, dubs, dubs!
Bub, dubs, bub, dubs, bub, dubs, bub!
Bub, dubs, bub, dubs, bub!
Bub, dubs!
Man!
Hey!
That's awesome!
Why, it's rising up.
It's floating up.
Uh-oh, Hal's floating in it, man.
I thought I was just soaking in it.
Well, that's why I wore these special boots.
Clumsy to AI.
Because I'm standing in it.
Oh, I see.
Oh, you're standing on the collar.
Yeah, that's the humble figurine.
Get off the collar's toes.
Special is under the radio water waves.
Boy, it sure is good to be back on the show.
Yeah, there are always these cover stories flying around about where you went.
I always try to be honest.
You know, you went to Dobstown.
Yeah.
See, there's the airplane now.
The cover story was exceptionally clumsy.
Now, look at this footage.
And see how all these guys trying to get him out of there.
Do we have to watch on this old sheet?
Yeah, so what actually happened?
Where was I then?
You went to Dobstown.
Every year this time you go to Dobstown for the medication.
I want to make sure I have my story straight.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I did a little glanscaping and did some minor surgery, you know.
Yeah.
Our friends in Daish made extraction from Dobstown a little bit uncomfortable for our own customers.
Well, my third nostril was a little clogged and I had to get a polypectomy in my third nostril.
Oh, wow.
They cored that baby out.
And I'll tell you, it sure works a lot better now.
I can whiff read miles away.
Yeah.
Is that an expensive procedure?
Oh, it's so expensive.
Paid for by your taxpayer dollars.
But with my new health care plan, and it works just fine.
I mean, it's excellent.
I didn't have to pay a thing.
I got some rich guy to do it for me.
That's right.
He paid it for me.
And that's it.
That's the important part.
Yeah.
Here as we sail along.
Eccentric billionaire, Ralph Fielding Smith.
The important thing for me was I didn't even care if he was rich or not.
It could have been like a hundred little poor people and I would have been fine with me.
But you know, it was Jay Beresford Tipton.
A hundred little poor people.
Reclusive millionaires.
Carrying you on a palanquin.
Thousands.
Instead, Jay Beresford Tipton comes in like a champ, you know.
Yeah, that guy's really the king of philanthropists all right.
No kidding.
Because of the sadistic way he deals out his money.
Yeah, you can't tell anybody where the money came from.
And I didn't tell anybody.
Dr. Howell did officially.
Yeah.
And I just.
And here we are talking about it on the radio, but nobody listens to this show.
And you know, they're not going to take the money back.
Yeah, this show was yesterday's newspaper.
Nobody cares.
And even if they do, I'm just going to say, you know, they'll send the bills and I'm
just going to say it's.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm not paying.
I say, sting it.
Sting it, man.
I'm going to have the people do this and then the people will share.
Hey, did you see where I found that stamp?
Stamp the plant?
Yeah.
I posted it on the.
On the internet waves.
The official puzzling evidence show fan page.
There's it's it's there.
It's always been there.
Always been there.
I posted it.
It's cramped the stamp.
Stamp the cramp.
Stamp the.
Stamping the cramp.
That's the thing.
Uncamp.
That's.
But I have to actually provide my own internet connection tonight.
I can't believe it.
I know.
Isn't that the strangest thing of the internet?
Sometimes they're in your.
And the radio.
In your brain.
Sometimes they're not.
Sometimes it's like a sight for a sore eye.
You know.
Which one?
This one in the middle here.
Now for a moment, let's consider an entirely different type of case.
The case of Bob.
One which shows how ambitious men can get ahead under our American system of free enterprise.
When Bob graduated from high school, Bob was surprised to learn that this Bob society had
created a special type of life for people of his type.
Right, Bob?
Well, life never was a burden.
In the first place.
Bob's flexible.
Bob can expand or contract.
Now, Bob has gone far.
Why not profit by Bob's example?
Send the postcard care of this station to the Bob Society.
Bob.
You can… if you want to be alone, you can be alone with Bob!
Yeah!
You can be with him and you're still alone!
That's the miracle thing about Bob...
Bob.
He loves you, but you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
So Bob, you out.
She's 24 now.
You heard it here first.
You heard it.
You don't love Bob.
You heard it here first.
Bob, you out.
You out.
1-3-0-1-3.
Bob?
Bob likes raw meat.
Yeah.
Bob, come now.
You better investigate.
You may have got into trouble.
Bob, smell food.
That man.
Yeah.
There's something familiar about him.
Bob?
Bob won't solve your problems,
but he will help you to blow them off!
You can't use Bob as a crutch,
because he's already using you as a crutch, my friend.
Well, gee, it's Bob.
Yeah, Bob. Yeah, but Bob's going to be there. Even if Bob Bob Bob. Yeah, well, no. Yes, if Bob Bob Bob.
You make me sick.
Don't bother.
It's literally Bob.
I shall go before the United Nations and demand that they accede to our total and absolute control.
I think he rules his own.
Please be serious.
Good morning. This weekend we commemorate Bob Day.
Bob is a proven leader who has served six presidents, four Republicans and two Democrats.
And he has shown that he can do it.
He is an agent of change.
And I am deeply grateful for his service.
Clear, clear.
And I pledge to the party.
He doesn't care about your sins.
He comes not to forgive but to rationalize.
He brings not forgiveness but an excuse.
And what did you really need?
If you want your sins forgiven, friends, do it yourself.
If you're a subgenius, you're probably already pretty good at that.
Jesus may have died for your sins, but Bob Dobbs made a damn fool of himself and of you for your sins.
Hello, Bob.
And I'm so happy to give my personal testimony.
Fifty years ago, I was a freshman in high school.
And that happened May 10th, 1941.
I accepted Bob as my personal savior and he's never let me down since.
I'm a retired teacher, a widow, I've had cancer and all kinds of stuff.
But he's always by my side.
Thank you so much.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Do Bob and sex go hand in hand?
Well, Bob is a kind of total all-consuming sex.
Fuck!
Can you believe that?
You can come when you throw good money after bad and bad money after Bob!
And you can do that at our lovely sales table down there.
Bob?
I did that mix with some sounds chopped by Leemur, Norell Preff and The Large.
The titles were by The Bishop.
PR News is by Leemur.
Good King Bob was Psychoskeletons.
And later, we'll hear songs by Max Slack and Reverend Ed Fred.
But the rest of this show is all puzzling evidence from the KPFA Berkeley show featuring
Dr. Howell, Dr. Philo Drummond and host Puzzling Evidence.
All of this is from the April 10, 2015 episode.
And I think listeners will agree that it's a great excuse for me to talk about my life
as a male.
So, let's take a break.
Price Bob.
Someday they'll just transplant your head on an orangutan's body.
So that explains it.
If you have enough money, that is, you know, the rest of your body will be worn out.
They'll be looking for something.
They'll clone some orangutans.
You know, you can take an orangutan or maybe a gorilla.
You might want a gorilla.
They're a little bit more rough, you know, in their bodies.
I don't do well in a domestic situation.
We're just the orangutan.
Look what happened to Mighty Joe Young.
They go haywire.
They do property damage.
You've got to be careful, you know, when you just wander around in the jungle
and they have those experimentation stations with those crazy scientists here.
They're a jungle.
Yes, we've got Pella Lugosi out there and Charles Lawton and Albert Decker.
Here, I'm trying to get this all down.
I want to make sure that we take everything into context here.
But we ultimately have the various jungle animals crossing with humans
at various stages of completion, you know, and the hideosity.
Well, not in the case of Dr. Moreau or the leopard creature in Terror is a Man.
Because those guys are humanoids made from the flesh of animals
through a diabolical scientific procedure.
But they aren't crossing with humans.
Well, they should.
I mean, I'm just saying.
They're artificially bringing out humanoid features in them.
The point of the whole thing is that there's no real difference between them and us.
It's just a molding of flesh.
But it's more weird and gruesome to cross the species.
It's in an hideous way.
You don't have to do it except in test tubes.
You don't actually have to have a dog.
Well, Pella Lugosi was always doing that with an ape.
Wasn't he?
Pella Lugosi.
Remember that on Atlantis, the Lost Convent?
All right, here we are.
I do.
Well, those were the evil scientists of Atlantis.
And they would turn you into a pig man or a dog man or something like that.
Just for the heck of it.
They were sadistic, aristocratic.
The George Powell version with that giant crystal device that folks use.
Yeah, and then it goes haywire and it turns people into skeletons as it swings around at random.
Yeah, that was great.
I hate that show.
That's what the show does to you.
You hated that show?
Well, then I was just doing a show and suddenly the laser turned around and it was square in the face.
That's why you're so skeleton-like now.
Slack.
How do we want it?
Ad pose.
I have endlessly tuck-in for awkwardness
I get a level up.
I'm about to get jaded all night out of there.
It's hard to have fun
Ge Хотя
Why don't you do an audit?
So that's a map.
I was told that the chưa been.
Lots of aim, money confused cannot be the parameters I've given a job call.
Everyone's helps and little chance theGovernment to make names.
Maximum Slack
You've got to believe
Get off your knees
Maximum Slack
Give yourself space to be
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum Slack
Is all that we ask
Can we have it back?
Maximum Slack
Because time goes so fast
Go!
To have a laugh
Maximum Slack
Do your dance
Shake your ass
Maximum Slack
Is all that we need
Come on, come on
Maximum Slack
You've got to believe
Get off your knees
Maximum Slack
Give yourself space to be
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum Slack
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum Slack
Do your dance
Shake your ass
Maximum Slack
Because in time
We'll be history
Maximum Slack
Do your dance
Shake your ass
Get off your knees
Do your dance
Etately
Of all this
Because you can't handle the truth
That's the problem
You can't handle the truth
A tr oportunidad
Ewha o votem
You have no idea
Oh, don't you now
Actually when I was nine years old
Big birds?
92 or 3.
Oh, not that Pinnacles.
No, the Pinnacles at the north end of the...
You gave the truth to the bird.
Oh, and I heard a rumor that the religious star who didn't show up, who promised he would, so he's not my friend anymore.
What happened to him?
I'm really disappointed because...
He's making noises about coming to X Day this year.
Really?
Yeah.
Who is?
Bishop Joey.
Oh, how about that?
That's just so sad.
That would make your panel discussion.
Oh, that's awful.
That's awfully good.
Horrible that he would...
Oh, I mean, it's really awfully good that he would come to X Day.
Well, that'll probably go through.
I would have to go if that happened.
I thought you were.
That's right.
I've been touting you as going.
I would go.
Yeah.
I am going.
You am going, yeah.
I would am going.
Yeah.
And Hal is would am going.
Take my wood with me.
Probably am.
It's like Burning Man.
Do you ever get to go to Athens?
I'm real curious about Athens and Columbus.
And the one place I will go before I die, Wright-Patt Air Museum, because they have the most amazing airplane parking museum.
Sort of like that place in, you know, arrivals.
I would go there.
The one in Tucson.
I'd go there if I had a...
Athens.
Like a lunch.
Rome.
They gave me a free lunch.
A free lunch, yeah.
When I got there.
There was no free lunch.
Not even a mention of free lunch.
Until the end, people were chanting, where's my lunch?
Where's my lunch?
And Bishop Joey forgot to say, where's my lunch?
To induct everybody in at the beginning.
And tell them about the...
He's slipping.
He did later along the trail.
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know, man.
Well, you can't always keep that stuff in there.
I was really hoping he'd be here so I could chastise him mercifully, and now he can't.
I'm going to have to do it another occasion.
Just keep that indignation fresh.
Keep it fresh and hot.
And the next time you see him, you're going to...
He is, by the way, going out to give a speak about mime troupe-like things on Sunday in England.
What does he know about that?
It's a terrible thing to do.
He read some books.
It's not like a free job.
Listen to...
With a free lunch.
He listened to an album once about it.
Somebody's going to give him a free lunch when he gets there, I'll bet.
His own other poems are no longer available in any store.
He'd drive anywhere for a free lunch.
From PR News in Washington, I'm barbaric, especially in Spain.
President Obama's celebrating National Day, rallying support for separating from Spain.
Spain.
Well, I hope someday we will be a proper country.
PR's report reports Obama spoke...
You're wrong.
House Speaker John Boehner says...
That was pain the camp night last lined.
And Admiral Al-Ampklamish the Polish will says...
The White House is joining the European Union in an airstrike against Britain and Germany, ruling out Syria.
PR's report reports PR has ordered a new volatile snap missile.
Look.
Dow is 34254.
4241.
Mortgage giant Freddie Mortgage Rate says this is PR News.
And then she said, I can't believe that that whole thing is that color.
It's just amazing and horrible.
Yeah.
And everybody laughed really hard.
I couldn't look.
I could not look at what I saw.
It's just so sickening and yet hilariously funny.
Yeah.
Like most painful episodes are.
But it had that bright white kind of...
Minkish smell about it, you know.
Yeah.
That electric smell.
So interesting the things that happen on the show that get intruded upon by that commercial break.
Some people would think it was...
Seems like that's when the show's apex is.
The hand of providence.
The show's apex happens and then all of a sudden the commercial break just jumps on it.
An apex novel.
A hideous little ape.
A little funny little ape with its...
Funny little ape.
Got pants on.
Somebody's put pants on this.
Yes, with those yellow buttons.
That's really in bad taste.
Yeah.
It's kind of a chimpanzee-like ape.
Yeah, exactly.
Jumping up and down on the show.
Very uneasy making.
That's what that commercial break is like.
A chimpanzee with pants on.
Jumping on the show.
A chimpanzee.
A pantsy, that is to say.
He's been forced to assume trousers against his natural...
Trying to make him into a man.
Yeah.
He's been forced to assume trousers against his natural.
But that can never happen.
Just as in Revenge of the Creature.
You know, they try to humanize the creature from the Black Lagoon.
No amount of pants.
You remember that?
Well, yeah.
That was a bio-crime.
They tried to change him.
Yeah, tried to cut him up and stuff.
Because you'll never get him that manly, but you'll just make him less creature-y.
Exactly.
So what?
What do you want?
Taxi Bob number three here.
Hey, Taxi Bob.
I'll go down to the marina.
You made it.
Yes, I will.
It's going to blow your mind that Neanderthals had intimate relations with modern humans.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's a show.
But I knew that all along.
I mean, they were for a long time considered a different species.
Exactly.
That's why they couldn't...
It made the most sense.
They couldn't accept that for a long time because of their preconceptions.
But it's rather obvious that we loved them to death.
That's why they're not around anymore.
We absorbed them into the human genome.
You know what I'm saying?
They weren't exterminated.
In a more recent time, there's a lot of Indian or Native American blood that's in the genome as well.
That's spread out a lot because of the forced...
Yeah.
Forced on the...
Who was that guy?
He's a Spanish biologist.
God.
God did it.
He got DNA.
He got DNA from ancient Neanderthal bones.
God did it.
Well, now you're starting to sound a little bit...
Scary.
Yeah.
I mean, they got DNA from Neanderthal bones.
I wish I had a Neanderthal.
Just a friend.
DNA, he talks to you rapidly.
And those things are...
Yes, just a friend.
Go down to the club with...
Four or five percent DNA.
Neanderthal.
Yeah, and you know how it varied across...
Some were as high as eight and some had zero.
Like, nobody in Japan had any Neanderthal.
Neanderthal DNA.
The Ainu or the guys we know now?
The Ainu do, but the standard Japanese do not.
Do not have it.
Because they also come from the mainland, ultimately.
Right.
Going back far.
But they didn't go through.
They didn't do that little mixing action that mostly occurred in Western Europe.
Not any invasions that were comparable.
Oh, there we go.
I knew it was going to get back to the subs.
The same way.
Sublimation.
Peoples except for Native Africans have some Neanderthal in them.
Oh, that's what it was.
Can you see that in the DNA?
Can you get that in a little report card?
And then the Denisovans.
I heard there were gorillas running around San Francisco and ministry.
That's what I heard.
Looks like wild gorillas.
Refugees from the Golden Will of Love.
You know, and everything?
Yeah.
Yeah, and then a couple of hogsheads.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, Anthony Quinn.
Dry out the sheets and we're on our way.
Wild gorillas.
And I was just reading.
Sorry.
So sad.
A French frigate was given lots of wonderful Incan Peruvian things.
And then the British showed up and firebombed the town and killed all the little French guys on the ships.
And all that nice Inca statuary went to the bottom of somebody's bay.
Can you imagine that first generation?
The Neanderthal-Chromanian mix where they had mixed together.
And so now you have this half Neanderthal, half human.
They must have seen very...
Can you imagine the rejection they got?
The Neanderthal gene was considered status.
High status.
And, you know, if you could...
Sure, to the Neanderthals it was.
No, to the humans.
To the humans because there were more of them than there were Neanderthals.
I mean, Cro-Magnon or what have you.
The modern ones.
No, I think they served as their, you know, like their...
Servant class?
Yeah, their servant class for a while.
No, I think they just wanted to have...
Yeah, I don't think so.
The sachet that they were in.
They just did with them what they wanted to do.
There are differing theories.
William Golding's novel, The Inheritors, is about...
Cro-Magnon coming in as horrible killers and killing off the Neanderthals.
And the story is from their point of view, the Neanderthal.
I thought it was interesting that some of the genetic variants known to be associated with specific traits
likely came from Neanderthals, such as...
Red hair?
Such as lupus, biliary cirrhosis, Crohn's disease, optic disc size, and type 2 diabetes.
And also some behavior such as...
Which is the ability to stop smoking.
Any good things?
I guess these Neanderthals had a problem stopping smoking.
Yes, they...
Well, you know how chimps go for cigars and so on.
It's the same thing with that variety of primate as well.
Oh, man.
Yeah, apparently some of the Neanderthal genes affected keratin filaments, which produced more fibrous protein.
Hey, Al, is there a quiz on this?
No, it sounds awfully speculative to me.
No, and the other thing is, I don't believe it unless I hear it as a question.
Yeah, if anyone was interested, but it'd be the usual questions about farts and Jesus and so forth.
That's going to be there tonight, right?
Yes, that is tonight.
It's going to happen.
Abortions and biking.
Actually, you know what's sad is there's not enough of that.
We can't really...
People aren't eating enough chips and grease and salt and...
Lead.
...vitamin, sugar.
They drink lead.
They drink.
Now, they don't even eat the chips anymore.
I was touching on the one thing that even an X-Day works.
They drink.
They do drink.
They drink all sorts of things.
And it's like this bourgeois barbecue coming on an X-Day in Egypt.
It's just a bunch of...
You know, the X-Day is on what used to be the Western Interior Seaway, the vast, shallow sea that went from the Arctic all the way down to the Gulf of Mexico.
And why'd you have to bring that up?
There were dinosaurs and huge crocodiles.
And dinosaurs and roe.
Well, plesiosaurs, ichthyosaurs, and so forth.
Now, that depression is still there and could still be filled with water.
All we need is a sufficient rise in the global water level to turn that same basin, now a major part of our country, into another ocean.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
Well, I'm glad you think so.
Yes.
Look, you said it on the radio and it happened.
The fact that they have these predetermined characteristics that are these negative aspects of the Neanderthal genome suggests that there was quite a bit of difficulty in early 500,000 years ago, whenever this interaction occurred, that the challenges for interbreeding were much more dramatic at that point.
Well, you know, it wasn't even that long ago.
From what my understanding is, it was as recent as...
30,000, maybe even more recent than that.
30,000 years ago.
Right.
I mean, in terms of their development, they'd been separated.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
In terms of the Earth, that isn't long, but in terms of humans, it is long.
They had not had interbreeding with each other for at least 500,000 years.
That was the point there.
So, when they did first begin intermingling, there was quite a bit of genetic challenge.
At that point...
There was a certain time that, you know, over time, as they were...
Some of those negative traits were selected out, but some of them still remain.
There was like a punctuated equilibrium...
A punctuated...
Eardrum.
Thing that...
Evolution.
What's that word?
You are on it.
Punctuated equilibrium.
Yeah.
Right.
And there was geographic separation.
So, they were on the verge of becoming different species.
But they had...
They hadn't quite gotten there yet.
Well, not just that, too.
During their commingling, there were several different waves of commingling that happened
with large amounts of time between them.
So that the variance of the subsequent commingling had already had, you know, a great amount
of mixture in it.
I think the common ancestral stock was a lineage of Homo erectus.
And don't forget the Denisovians...
That's right.
...influenced it as well.
The Denisovians...
The Denisovians are quite interesting to me.
You never hear about them.
Nobody ever writes about them.
But they are that other group that is unaccounted for.
The other, the third, not Neanderthal, not human population.
Yeah, they're not the Cro-Magnon, they're not the Neanderthal, but they're out there.
Not that much is known about them.
The Denisovians.
But they did provide a different genetic stock.
Yeah, they had some variety to the old human mix.
They're one of the 58 varieties?
Well, you remember, according to subgenius theory, we subgeniuses are the inheritors of
the Yeti genetic...
And the Denisovians may be explained by that subsequent commingling that produced the...
Commingling.
420.
That variant.
No, it's 419 according to the laser clock here.
419.50, 419.51.
Some laser is going to blast you.
This is straight from the pipe that's connected to the sun.
That's what my Hopi friend told me.
The pipe that rocks the crypt.
Now, 420.01, 02.
Okay, begin your 420 experiments.
You guys know more about this than I do.
I'm going to bow out and absorb what you had to say.
Thanks for calling.
Thanks, yeah.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for helping this promotion day.
Keep your eyes on the road.
Veering wildly all about...
Taxi Bob number three.
Thank you.
There he goes.
Signing out.
Well, he seemed to have provided...
To pick up another dubious...
Good morning.
Some kind of...
Customer satisfaction...
Good morning.
That we aim for on the show.
You, yeah.
Good morning.
We aim for the customers.
Out the window.
Yeah.
They're down there in the parking lot and we...
Well, the bathroom window is open and...
You know.
Anyway, so we're always happy to take your calls and receive your heart onto whatever the god of the week is here.
Jesus, whatever, Bob.
Jesus, Bob.
Do you have to bring that up again?
Well, I...
It's...
Interesting, you know, that there was a lot of speculation as far as whether Neanderthals could speak or if they had to develop a complicated language and...
Did you read those gene awful novels about the blonde bombshell brought up among the Neanderthals and they don't entirely speak but they...
Right.
They just pluck and click and they gesticulate and that's part of their language.
They make these gestures.
But they also...
The point being as far as when they matched up the DNA sequences, they found long sections in the area that were important to the role in human speech that were completely depleted in the Neanderthal DNA.
I, for one, have found this particular episode of show to be fascinating and it's just...
There's no way I could contribute anything of any more...
Value.
Well, you don't have any memories...
Really?
...in the drunk caveman times?
He's trying to...
Well, you could probably find something of value.
Well, you remember Luana and Newton.
It's all I can.
Luana?
Me, me, me.
The...
Between them, there was great enmity because they were both fond of the same guy, Tumat.
Some areas of modern non-African human DNA...
...are...
...were rich in Neanderthal matches, which may have indicated that they were helpful for human survival during those periods when there was great difficulty.
Well, this is certainly Monday morning quarterbacking on a grand geological scale.
Naturally, it helped survival because the survivors are writing this account.
Exactly.
Well, that's the important thing is that...
...that the evidence itself is proof of its ability to be selected for a future generation, right?
The evidence is always puzzling.
I had the same thing experience with the Toy Fair.
Everything is known and everyone has consensus about it.
I've got this new toy called the Ball of Wax and that's...
Ball of Wax?
Just like the weather string.
...pretty puzzling.
Yeah.
And it's sort of a...
Did someone say that?
Yeah, somebody said that.
Can you believe it?
...and what you're actually that same guy.
Oh, it might have been you.
I'll check this out.
The evidence is pretty puzzling.
The designer of this toy discusses the way that...
...the brain and the hand...
You said brain.
...developed around the same time, about 500,000 years ago.
And I was...
At the Toy Fair, I was pitching it to this guy and...
A brain or a hand?
He was pitching the brain at the guy.
And you're pitching a brain at the hand and the hand catches the brain.
Yeah, 5,000 years ago.
...how human beings evolved 500,000 years ago.
500,000 years ago.
And as soon as I said that, he sneered at me and said,
Oh, that's just your opinion.
Whoa!
Yeah.
This toy is not for you.
You just made that up right there, to sell me something.
That's just your opinion.
I'm pretty sure this guy was from Tennessee, from his accent.
I'm not betting on myself.
Yeah, he's...
Wow.
Some of those people still think the Earth is only like 6,000 years old.
6,000 years.
Yeah, that makes sense, because there was 1,000 years, and then 5,000 years ago, he said,
the brain and the hand developed.
I've heard a preacher tell me that...
...that...
...that God put the dinosaurs in the Earth to confound the mind of man.
But there's this Christian group called God Hates Dinosaurs.
And it works, right?
To make mind...
I like that.
...to make people question.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that's why John Kennedy was shown, to make people question.
...the human hand and the brain...
This would be the most difficult part I have about moving into the South.
Why?
Yeah.
Because we're encountering more of that type of thinking.
Just by accident.
Wonderful people.
Great people, and all of a sudden, it's like, boom, the curtain just goes down.
Human beings suddenly work.
Yeah, I'll have to insulate myself.
Well, you know, I was in...
I went to a southern town, and I went to a military school with Nora, and we're in the
car, and it was light winter, and I was doing a controlled skid off the highway at this
point, into the mud, thinking, you know, it's not going to be bad.
We'll get out of this pretty fast.
And then I got out of the car, and I was in the car, and I was in the car, and I was
in the car, and I was in the car.
And my next thought was, somebody's going to stop and help us, because that's the Shenandoah
Valley.
But you cannot talk about religion, or birth control, or the president, you know, or stuff
like that, because they'll just...
And sure enough, right behind us was a car, guys in their best white loafers got out,
helped us in the snowstorm.
Amazing people.
And then they probably wanted to pray, right?
Probably.
That happens, too.
Sometimes you have to pray.
Yeah.
Thank Jesus and stuff.
Yeah, and stuff.
Faith.
Thank you, Jesus.
That's tough.
I had to do that one time.
I sold a...
I was working as a Yellow Pages rep in East Texas, and I called on a church.
It was a Baptist church.
Wow, yeah.
And I was trying to convince the preacher that they should buy an ad for the Yellow
Pages.
Yeah, of course.
And so I said, you know, one of my questions I asked was, I said, well...
He was asking, he didn't know if it would be worth it, you know, the price.
And I said, well, you know, how much is the price of a soul?
And he looked at me like, wow, that was really a good thing.
You know, I was like, that was the thing that clinched the sale.
That's the thing you put outside on the street.
That was the thing that clinched the sale.
Yeah, and it's the thing you put on the little board.
And he said, okay, I'll do it.
You put on the little board with the letters outside, how much is the price of a soul?
Right.
And so he said, okay, I'll do it.
Yeah.
Oh, excellent.
And he said, all right, now let's get down.
We have to get down on our knees and pray now.
So we had to pray over the ad to pray.
And he said, you know, we have to make the ad, you know, super nice.
Yeah.
And just out of curiosity, how much did the ad cost?
Oh, back then it was probably no more than $25 a month or something like that.
It was really.
No, it's a bargain.
It was relatively cheap.
But, you know, this was back when $25 was probably more like $250 now, you know, or
maybe $200 or maybe $175, $178, $179, something like that.
Do we have to work this out before the other show?
I've got this little spreadsheet here that if I'm going to give you each a copy on this
disc, I want you to take this home and I want you to study it.
Yeah.
It's Excel.
And I hope you have the new version.
If you don't, then you're going to have to go to the expense to download that.
Get a new flash drive.
Yeah.
You got to get new drives.
I got to get a new flash mob.
Flash everything.
Flash driving out there.
Yeah.
Get a ride with flash.
Here we go.
Boopie.
And so flash took the entire show to the desert.
Wow.
In a flash.
And then of course the cops stopped us and we all were all in a mess two hours later.
Have you seen a guy driving a pickup truck, pulling a trailer with a UFO on it with a beard
and a ... Hold on there, officer.
The UFO has a beard?
I don't wait for it.
It's a helmet.
It was cap and check друзья, You you stay here.
In the course of the process, we had nine falando da vida, he was
and so that would have caused
Where is this occasioning?
In the genome
No, but I mean physically
where are the little
Neanderthals and others
meeting?
Oh, it's like in the Iberian Peninsula
You know, on northern Africa
and the Iberian Peninsula
Back when that was all green
and not desert
And the Mediterranean for a long time
was dry
When there was a period of time
when the Mediterranean was dry
you could walk across the Mediterranean
And you couldn't walk to Berlin
and the Ichthyosaur
No, but there was a deep, deep chasm
Everything was all backwards
in the olden days
Back when we used to feed
on Ichthyosaur steaks
sitting by the side of old Pangea
cooking them up
I can't wait till Pangea comes back again
We'll have to wait a while
for that
Okay, we'll just sit down here and rest then
I'm writing a song
It's called Pangea, We'll Meet Again
In the far, far future
there will only be one continent
The continent of Zothique
That's happened about five times overall
You know, we talk about Pangea
It only happened once
There were several of them
before that as well
In those latter days
On the giant continent of Zothique
comprised of what's left of the
continent of Pangea
And don't forget Rodinia
was even prior to that
an even more ancient, archaic
supercontinent
Talking about the far future
but as far back as you go
Yes, of course
Until the continents themselves
were just bubbling masses
floating on a magnum ocean
Like a scum
Like a scummy surface pond scum
floating around
Moving around on a current
and colliding back
and gathering
and gathering back into a
bobbing around
into a mass again
and then splitting up again
More scum surfacing
Then these giant rock groups
surrounded the land masses
Fraud scares
and only the strongest scum
would survive
Well, of course
That's Darwinian, my boy
I think some of the face genes
of Neanderthals
manage to express themselves
and some modern humans as well
Who have a Neanderthal-like face
You know
They have little place cards too
You know, you meet all these vegetarians
and they say
Oh, I just can't eat anything with a face
Really?
It's because something resembles a human
that you can't do it?
That has eyes and a nose
Where's your biophilia?
Why don't you have love for the rest of creation?
For everything to live
something has to die
and vegetarians
are the most destructive thing the planet knows about
since they depend on agriculture
which is destroying the biosphere
Yeah
And if they were hunter-gatherers
that ate meat
things would be a lot better
but especially vegans are
Of course, they would run
The holy thing is
that one came
It's like the chicken and the egg
It was because of the rise of agriculture
that the population was able to grow
as much as they had
That's right
It's a toxic blight spreading across the poor old planet
But for, you know, two years
to grow a monoculture of whatever
corn or wheat
you kill everything else that's on the land
and you kill the soil
and the soil used to be six feet deep
and now it's only a few inches deep
and every time you irrigate it
salt is left
which is deadly and destroys the land
That's why the ancient world is desertified
and why nothing will grow in Greece and so forth
So you see it's all supposed to be
Vitamin grease, vitamin salt, vitamin sugar
It's supposed to be a vast primordial
People worry about that stuff too much
dinosaur-filled forest
You know, here's one thing we know
We're here today
They're out hunting with their bow and arrow
We've adapted to every natural and unnatural change
that's occurred from the beginning of our existence
Do you have an iPhone?
We're still here
No, you don't get an iPhone
Somehow or another we've managed to survive
Not only that, we've managed to flourish
You nap flints a lot in this world
Things that flourish eventually
Everybody knows how to nap flints
With or away as well
Apple iPhone!
There's always a circle there
No, there's no iPhone, I tell you
If thy iPhone offends thee, pluck it out
I have a feeling that we're one of the most adaptable types of animals on the planet
We can adapt to almost anything
Yes, but even this show
The planet can also adapt to us
The show, as much as it wants to kill its listeners
still manages to provide the listeners with an adaptable life
The big square thing, if I got the right movie
With the four legs that stomps along the Mexican glue
Is that Kronos?
Oh yeah, that was Kronos
They are inviolate
Do you think that a human would have looked at a Neanderthal and said
Oh, that thing is ugly
Maybe they looked at a Neanderthal and thought they were hot
They did think they were hot eventually
But at first they thought they were strange and should be opposed
Like the history of all assimilation in the story of the Neanderthals
The history of human groups that meet
What at first is opposed eventually
After a long enough period of time becomes a fashionable trait
Which you would like to show
But that's not to say this is a principle of justice
If you look at Mexico
They traditionally think anything of the Amerindian side of their genome
Is to be suppressed
It's Indio, it's bad
But what's Spanish is good
And to be culturally sought after
But perhaps they're behind the times
Because we've all got in our ancestry
Thousands of years of essentially Indians
Pre-techno humans
Stretch into the far past
And only recently have we had can openers
And screwdrivers
But before then we were all beating on drums and logs and things like that
I wish I had a log to beat on right now
Thousands upon thousands of years
Don't you wish that sometimes here on the show
That they would just bring a log in and we could just beat on it?
Did you ever read Mark Twain's Captain Stormfield's Visit to Heaven?
It's a sea captain who goes to heaven and reports everything there
And when he first gets there he goes out
Because he thinks he should have a
A liar?
And a liar and a palm branch
And go out and sit on a cloud
And so they let you do whatever you want in heaven
So he goes out and there's this huge mass of clouds
And everybody's playing the lyre
But the music isn't that good
It's really crummy
For one thing, where are all those Indians coming from beating drums?
Well they are the previous generations going back into
Yeah, they didn't want to
Dim theory
And the horrible racket of the hollering
And I got tired of playing my harp
No kidding
It makes a lot of sense
He was such a sensible guy
Yeah
That's kind of what I thought
All that fanning right there
So when he's on his way to the clouds
He meets people coming back and they're saying
Would you hold my harp a minute?
I've just got to do something
And so he's now getting piled up with this stuff that they're throwing away
They don't want to get tired of it now
Yes
He's discarding these huge piles of harps
Liars and harps
And palm branches and halos and things that
Somehow or another he needs to get that back to the first part
Where the guy can sell them big time when they come in the door, you know
And recycle them
At the beginning of the story
He's racing through space
He's dead and his soul is racing toward heaven
And he gets in a race with a comet
And he gets off course by just a few degrees
And so he gets to the huge glittering gates of heaven
But when he lands he finds it's an alien heaven
And these grotesque creatures are coming in, you know
Because he got off course
He didn't get to human heaven
Yeah, he can't get to human heaven
Because you know what?
The...
The problem with human heaven is that the road is very, very narrow
And the gate is very tiny and small
And it's hard to get through
But the road to perdition is wide
Exactly
And it's so wide
It's like a superhighway
It's easy
It's with a 17 lane superhighway
Although it's impossible to go back up it
That's super hard
No, it's downhill
Downhill
It's so downhill
Downhill is the easy way
You can just lay on it and roll downhill into the...
Anywhere in the cars
It's so wide the cars won't even hit you
As they speed their way into the...
The hellish hellhole of...
More people have written about trips to hell than trips to heaven
But there are some interesting...
And it is a highway to hell, you know
The...
The bands...
Some bands have taught us that years ago
There's even a movie...
ACDC, you know
Some...
Some sort of grade B movie where...
About...
Cop rides to hell, remember that one with...
Well, that was Dana Andrews
Dana Andrews
But there's a movie, I think it was made in the 80s
Where they are in the supernatural highway in the afterworld
And the evil cop is coming after you, you know
He's this horrible death cop and...
And they go through the desert and so on
But it's all the afterlife
Did you ever see that one?
I really don't know the name of it
But it might be Highway to Hell
Dr. Howell, this is going to be a question for tonight's show
Can you tell me the quickest way to hell?
Faculus descensus...
What is the quickest way to hell, Dr. Howell?
Do nothing
And you go there on your own
What about sex, drugs and rock and roll?
Oh, they are irrelevant distractions
Don't they help speed the trip to hell?
Well, maybe for some reason...
If you just sit there and do nothing...
For others, they provide...
That's going to take longer...
Welcome refreshment...
Don't you need something to keep you busy?
...hugger mugger, we call life
On your way to hell, don't you want to keep busy and do something fun, though?
What do you want, sex, drugs and rock and roll?
If you're on your way to hell, you're not interested in having fun
No, fun is not for that side of the magic...
You think fun is on your way to heaven?
Uh, fun is...
Where do you find it?
Yes, the fun...
Fun is just a concept, right?
Fun is my Chinese neighbor's middle name
They're going to outlaw everything eventually
Here's an obit for Stan Freeburg, I guess he just died
Oh, no...
Man, all those people will have to stop yelling now at concerts
Freeburg!
He was known for his comic genius in parodying cultural touchstones of the 50s and 60s
How old was Stan Freebug, by the way?
Uh, he was 88
Hmm, I don't know
I'm gonna go to live in a state where you can still have a fire
Wow, old Stan Freeburg picture, that's cool
What weird looking hair he's got
I just remember he was very, yeah, very young, Stan Freeburg on Hollywood Palace
Yeah, when he was back in the Mad Men type days, you know, he was one of those slick 60s guys
Well, Mort saw that whole era of...
Yeah, but now he's, in this picture, he's...
Yeah, Stan Freeburg, he was a genius, definitely
He was a GDQQ bach, an influential master of the lampoon
Philo said he was gonna go as soon as he heard that other famous guy's name
So he went, he said, I'm gonna go too
He channeled his off-the-wall sensibility into groundbreaking radio shows, comedy albums, and hundreds of humorous television commercials for products such as chow mein and prunes
Died of natural causes Tuesday at UCLA Medical Center in San Diego
Is that like natural flavoring?
You know, he started out doing voice work for Warner Brothers cartoons
Freeburg did?
Yeah
What year?
He had Junior Bear and Goofy Gophers
Well, I heard his records, I didn't know he was responsible
He was also, you know, did bit parts on the Jack Benny show
Oh yes, yes
That's probably why I saw him as a kid
Yeah, because...
My grandmother watched, I loved watching Jack Benny
But did you have the comedy albums like A Child's Garden of Freeburg and so on?
Bob Plampet worked with Freeburg to develop Time for Beanie, the puppet, the original puppet show that inspired him
Yeah, yeah
And then he started being Cecil
Yeah
Yeah, Clampet never gave up trying to do something new, some new variation on...
Because it was about Clampet Cartoon
About Clampet Cartoon
So come on kids, let's slip your lips high or so
He was the voice of the syndicated radio program, Quinn Radio Was, from 1995 until October 6, 2006
When?
In the 1950s, a 1953 spoof of Jack Webb's Dragnet called St. George and the Dragonnet captured the cop show's famously staccato monotone delivery and was widely considered his finest work as a mimic and parodist
I do remember that, I would cut it up with... I, me, me
You have heard that one?
Yeah, I would record it off the speaker with a microphone and cut it up with my mom's sewing scissors and tape and make show with all kinds of stuff like that
Back when I was a teen
The legend you are about to hear is true, only the needle should be changed to protect the record
It is funny
Yeah
And then the people loved it, the people still for years called at concerts Free Bird
You'd hear his name, you'd only know the teenager
Free Bird
This is the countryside, my name is St. George, I'm a knight
Saturday, July 10th
Oh right, that was my favorite
8.05 a.m.
It was my favorite
I was working out of the castle on the night watch when the call came in from the chief
A dragon had been devouring maidens, homicide
You did it very dry
My job, slay him
Take Trevor
What?
Starved and scared, with voices in their underwear
There's a thing about Bob
Bob has a big new spring of confidence
A generous swelling of pride
And one thing every man deserves
A little well-earned respect from the neighborhood
It puts a glimmer into his eyes
It puts a spring into his stomach
It has given him a rise
There's a thing about Bob
Looks like Bob is real
Bob is living life
Hey Bob!
Can you get him a new haircut?
No
Bob is living life
Hey Bob!
It's your sweet
Bob
Bob is living life
Bob here's been having a bit too much sex
Bob
Bob is living life
There's a woman here
Bob has a life
Jobless
Bob is living life
music
Everything is done
with the beginning
All is played
with the help of balls
but my attitude is
the esse Hernandez
rock
Keyboard
Introducing the new long-lasting sense of Bob
This is Bob Bob
Jesus, Bob, what did you push?
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
For free information, write to
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Or see www.subgeniusradio.org
Subgenius.com
Praise Bob!