Let's go to the Gigolo Club over in Yancey.
They got a...
Some genius power of...
What?
I say this calls for action, and now, nip it in the bud!
Ah, shut up!
What did Bob say about me?
Bob wants you to give me all your Star Wars action figures!
Bob wants pizza!
Bob wants burritos!
Gimme Bob, gimme Bob!
Bob wants you to move your car out of his parking spot!
Bob is concerned that you were in a turning lane, but you didn't turn right instead,
drove fast, and cut me off every afternoon on Barham!
Bob demands you use local references when you can!
Bob wants your children, Bob wants your children, Bob wants your children
to stop running round and touching my stuff at the laundromat!
Bob wants you to use local references when you can!
Hello, Connie.
Bob!
I'm so glad!
You're glad? How do you think I feel?
You're just as good as new again.
Stop kidding.
Why are you kidding?
In high society, I just ain't the type.
Folks all look so surprised when I lighten my pipe.
Yes!
Oh, yeah.
Do you...
smoke a pipe, too?
Oh, don't be coy. I like it, too.
What's it gonna get you, Connie?
All this business of filling my pipe,
pouring my drinks, corned beef, and cabbage?
I suppose I should pretend that I don't know what you mean by that.
But I won't.
Connie, look, for the past few days, all you've done is...
All I've done is what?
Well, is to tell a man in a thousand little ways.
To tell what man in a thousand little ways?
Well, not with words, maybe, but with looks,
actions, and...
Aren't you ashamed?
All right, maybe you say I'm wrong.
A partner in sin?
There was an influence there.
Sometimes there is a mood that just...
We don't know why.
You wouldn't get a pal, would you, Connie?
Or yourself, maybe?
I don't know yet, Bob.
Oh!
Oh, it just goes into tune.
Two boys allen!
But this isn't essential, insulting, annoying.
And I'm touched because a single girl esas anyhow.
I'm dere terminate, and I mean it.
I mean, hey Babe.
I mean, my story is all, it's just based on your stupid mistakes and orphans
that power and sub creep sensingsike М bild-
Did you hear that?
I'm happy you're in love.
I'm happy to be with that little hunk!!!!
V.D.?
You mean to say that Bob has actually had one of those horrible diseases?
That isn't true, Doctor.
Is that true, Bob?
All right, if you must know, I did have it.
But it's no worse than having an illegitimate child.
I think it is.
Why, I'd sooner marry a leper.
Thank you for letting me know about this in time, Dr. West.
And now I'm going out into the clean, fresh air.
Well, there went my happy wedding right out the door.
I'm terribly sorry, Bob.
Ah, dear Donald.
Just grab the right-of-scout shaker up and down a bit and chop off the slack.
Come on.
Damn, this streaking out pit, we'll finally blame it on God.
And there'll be some kind of church started called the Streaker's Church.
Yeah.
Oh, they'll just, they'll, they'll follow, try to make it religious.
But I want to tell you it's abominable, and it's filthy, and it's rotten.
And we ought to stand up against it.
Say amen, you know it's so.
The pipes, we need a jolly life, jolly life.
We're free from every garret stripe, garret stripe.
We drink the best of that.
I'm glad that this gay life is mine.
In the name of fingers, waters, dirty birdie,
Holland, no sterling beef, or chemist, drink ye, drink ye.
In the name of mystic, Myron, Tucker, Tolan,
Baddus, O'Ringan, O'George, E3.
Oh, smiling.
No, Nick, Bob, Cobra, Bart, Nick, no, T.O.
Golden, throw to John A.D.
If you understand that we have all had a partner in sin, you really didn't do it by yourself.
There was an influence there.
Thank you, Bob.
Now we shop at Neiman Marcus instead of K. Martin Sears.
We go on Neiman Marcus, and as soon as they spotted us, and I was there last year, they
said, hi, Bob and Bonnie, how are you?
They remembered us.
And so on the back, they take you in the back and they have drinks for you, whatever it
is, scotch, whiskey, whatever you want, and I asked for the usual.
If you drink five gallons of Gatorade, you're going to expend five gallons of Gatorade somewhere
in one of these restaurants.
And I said, no, I don't want that.
You buy that, right?
Frankly, either way it's a little tough.
Let's get this on the other side.
We went 15% and did some crazy things, and we went direct.
And I can remember going direct, and I can remember standing up on stage and putting
the microphone up to my mouth, and nothing came out.
And I went, oh my God.
No, Connie, no!
We'll spice the flame out of my butt.
It really isn't all that bad.
Hope you understand that there's nothing more liberating than being able to pee and poop your own diaper.
I love a bob.
Yeah!
Come on.
Yeah, what's the matter with that?
Disgusting.
Don't ever ask me to do that again.
You just have to be careful.
You always think about, you know, getting poop on the finger, you know.
And I remember the first time it happened.
I couldn't believe it.
I mean, it's like, oh my God.
I've got poop on my finger.
And then I started thinking to myself, it could be worse.
I could have a job.
I don't think I can.
I just can't do it.
And I said to Bobby, please don't ever make me do that again.
Don't call me Bobby.
No!
No, Connie, no!
Call me, call me, dear.
Don't ever, ever go.
You're my God.
I need you, my God.
I need you.
Oh, my God.
No, Connie, no!
No!
Night and day, under the height of me.
There's oh such a hungry yearning burning inside of me.
And the storm and warm be through.
Do you let me spend my life making love to you night and day?
Oh, day and night.
Night and day.
They won't believe that.
They will when they hear the things you and Bob said to each other the other night in Irene's apartment.
Test, test.
We're testing the windscreen, the new Subgenius Foundation corporate windscreen on the Zaphodian digital recorder.
And we're at Stang Ranch still.
In fact, we just finished excavating a little bit and then taking drone pictures of the dinosaur tracks.
Down here in Onion Flats Creek, we might call it.
Let's name that because there's wild onions growing everywhere you look.
Princess Wee has a bag of them that we'll have in our salad tonight.
I mean, it really, really, really stinks of raw onions down here.
It's great.
If you like raw onions, it's fabulous.
And I'm looking at some dinosaur tracks that belong to us.
They're on.
The cult compound property.
And this area is famous for dinosaur tracks.
And in fact, SMU came and took one away.
It's easy to find a spot because there's a big square taken out of the middle of the creek rock.
What's SMU?
Southern Mesodist University.
Oh, okay.
And the dinosaur tracks are not huge, but they are three toed theropod.
There's no question.
There's a whole series of three or four clear ones and some mushy ones that are certainly tracks.
They just don't really look that cool.
The problem is there's still water in the creek just a little bit.
And the tracks were full of algae and scum.
And you could not tell they were there until I waded in barefoot for the first time in my life with a broom, which we carried down here.
We had to hike in with the drone.
And we had to hike in with the drone and brooms and all kinds of things.
And we hopefully brought a gallon of clean water.
We thought we might be able to just wash them out.
But there's too much water present in the creek.
Yeah, we were hoping it would be dry.
But I did, after brushing the dinosaur tracks out with the broom and getting the crud and pebbles out and clearing the area around them, you can definitely see them.
Even in photographs.
For sure.
A big dinosaur trod here when it was a beach a hundred million years ago or so.
Acrocanthosaurus is the one that's famous for leaving tracks in the Paluxy.
Maybe this is the same guy?
Maybe.
But I don't know.
Could be.
Maybe they're fresher than we think.
And the beast of Hollow Mountain lives inside Dockstock Mountain.
Maybe the beast from 20,000 Fathoms.
Is really the beast from Dammit's hidey hole.
Could be.
Maybe the thing that would not die was really the thing in the woods here.
Yes.
The thing that you almost see, but it always vanishes just as you're turning around in the woods.
The Gaius Gudis.
That's the name of the creature that lives in the woods out here.
You may have heard of them.
But you've never seen a picture of one.
Because no one's ever been able to get a picture.
You never quite see them.
They're just flashing behind a tree just when you look.
Fools think they're Bigfoot.
You know, oh Bigfoot's out here.
He's lightning fast.
He's camouflaged.
You never see him.
That's really it.
Well that may be so.
Maybe yes, maybe no.
But if Bigfoot was out here we'd smell frop real strong.
And I don't smell frop.
I don't either.
No.
Although, there is a cure for that.
Well, I guess we'll have to sign off here at Onion Flats, the Dinosaur Tracks,
Stang Ranch, Stangsville, Stang County, Texas.
Price Bob.
Copy that over and out.
There we go.
Dearekh, there we go again.
President Stang KK Creepuip Psych registered it this Friday.
PolyGuys apologize.
Spill.
Filming says the actor isn't the afternoon 800 page entertainer.
The reagaves will contain images that'll beть충asyma.wikideofscript for the studio's futureThe facts related to statements and are not on display during this recording.
The 28th The Big juntane the Top of Mind and monitor the absence for argument ligue that we've seen today a ton of change from city to city to city is up north 56.
Your information is not available for investigation yet.
guitar solo
Here I look there, I look everywhere
Oh, Footfoot, why can't I find you?
Footfoot, where can you be?
Footfoot, why won't you answer me?
Footfoot, I didn't like to roam so well
He would still have a place to dwell
Footfoot, please answer me
I know where you are, you're behind that tree
Footfoot, please come to me
Footfoot, now that you're here
What does it mean?
That you will never again roam
Footfoot!
It's a modern day
It's the modern age
Footfoot!
It's the modern day
It's the mind
The moment
It's the moment
Thank you.
It's done.
Oh, yes.
That was Rural War Room, my friends.
Beautiful Rural War Room, our friends in Arkansas.
Before that, we heard the Rudy Schwartz Project covering a song by the Shags.
Can you believe that?
My pal Foot Foot.
There was also a quick little recording of our dog, Dammit, howling there.
There was a beautiful instrumental by Reverend Jimmy Ryan, who is doing instrumentals these days.
He always has, but he's doing them solo, and we have a zillion of them.
Obviously, we're not really still in Stang Ranch.
We're back in Cleveland here.
Oh, before all that music, we heard a song.
We heard a song.
We heard a collage of Bob and Connie clips.
All of that was put together by Reverend Susie the Floozy for her wonderful show from Atlanta,
WREK Atlanta, where she does Bob's Slack Time Fun House.
That collage was lovely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Praise Susie.
And there was a new short Bob song, Bob Wants You, right there at the very beginning.
That was Morgan Gutentag, who did that.
And the titles, of course, as always, almost always by Leemur.
And we're not in Stang Ranch, but we should be hearing the sound effects of beautiful Stang Ranch.
All right, there we go.
Now there's sound.
There we are.
Okay.
We're expecting our friend Lungs and Cowboy Dave to call in soon.
Oh, a storm's coming in.
Princess, we'd better get under shelter.
Okay.
Big old Texas lightning.
Big old thunderstorms coming up.
All right.
Rain could be deadly.
Hail.
Tornadoes.
You never know what you're going to get.
I know that you and Dammit will protect me.
Yeah.
Darn it, we sure will.
Later on, we'll close with another song from Rudy Schwartz Project.
He's got a new album out, a collection called Sunshine Supers Hits.
Oh, my gosh.
That's the way I prefer to pronounce it on the radio these days.
He covered a whole bunch of 60s and 70s bubblegum songs.
Build Me Up Buttercup is the one that we'll be closing with tonight, I hope.
If the rain would finally quit, we'd be able to fire up the gas-powered record player.
Get that thing running.
Ooh, it's cold.
It is.
Wet and damp.
But we'll make it.
We'll make it through.
President Lonesome Cowboy Dave was asking me what the subject matter was going to be for tonight.
I said, I don't know.
I said, if we talked about Donald Trump, we'd sound just like every other show in the media.
See you there.
I went and did it.
I went and did it already.
Now, didn't I told him, give me a couple of minutes?
Well.
Oh, there we go.
Here we go.
Let's try this.
We go like that.
And then do we hear it?
No, you can't.
Oh, darn.
That's just what I was afraid of.
You're wearing one of them special beastie shirts with a large nipple overhang.
That's the reason why you've got all these psychological problems.
People calling you from all parts of the country should know the different parts of that.
Oh, there's all kinds of people in this country.
Comers and goers.
Beastie nipple shirt.
Some are.
Empty nesters.
Willie heads.
Sometimes they spell empty nesters.
They spell nesters.
N-E-S-T-O-R.
That means he's got crew in here.
Or he's a fanatic or something.
Crazy as a Bessie bug, we used to say.
What the hell's a Bessie bug?
Well, if you don't know, then you must be that crazy.
Mad as a hornet.
You have to look it up in your funk and waggle.
Tight as a tick.
Well, it sounds like I'm just a little bit crazy.
It's been expunged from the human race, and I still don't know what a damn Bessie bug is.
Listen to that old Dave.
He can sure pull up a pulpit now, can't he?
Yes, he can.
He can talk up a toe sack.
He can tongue tomatoes off the vine.
Words come out of him like water pouring out of a bucket.
But it don't make any sense in reality.
That's the problem I've been finding.
Well, it's just a matter of language, Dave.
I mean.
Oh, semantics.
Hyper semantics.
Yeah, I'm glad you're talking about the hyper ones.
They're so much easier to take than the retroactive ones.
Oh, some people never said pea turkey.
Pea turkey?
Right.
What's that?
I don't know.
But whatever it is, it's cold as blue fluggins.
I'm reading a book I picked up at my late dad's house called Southern Saiyans for Yankees.
Another interesting book.
Immigrants by Bill Dwyer.
That's Reverend Chainsmurker.
Why, that guy all this time he's been acting like an Australian.
And he was really this southern dude right now.
Yeah, it's Southern Saiyans.
I can vaguely put together what you just said about being Australian and stuff.
But aren't they two different age groups?
I mean, one of them is like a form of chimpanzee.
The other is a form of like a reptile.
No, no, no.
Australians are humans just like humans.
Mostly.
Except for the subgeniuses.
You know, there's some Australians that are obviously they're subgeniuses.
You can't quite.
Most people would think they were humans.
At first, anyway.
Yeah.
Until you get to know them.
Then you start going, I don't know what kind of person that is.
Yeah, what kind of mammal or woolly reptile?
He's got the raisin of a hog.
That aggro-provoking old bug.
I'm the greatest one of all because I'm a wild boar.
I wasn't going to say anything.
Maybe we'd need background music instead of this.
He makes you weep a lot of times, you know.
You think about the hour of slack and you start weeping like a little baby dog or something.
Why did you call us babies?
He called us babies.
He called me a baby.
I didn't mean that.
That's assault.
Calling people names.
That's assaulting them.
No, that's a soft tissue remark.
When you speak of hypergender or gender going to the bathroom and stuff,
is it still called like a BLT or something like that?
Is it named after a sandwich?
I've heard that there's a lot of upsetness about that over in some of those southern states.
I've not heard that.
I've noticed mostly southern ones.
In North Carolina, they won't let you have a lettuce, tomato, and bacon sandwich in certain rooms.
That's right.
Because it might see the ham sandwich in the other stall.
You know, God forbid that a ham sandwich be in the same bathroom stall next to a bacon sandwich.
So you're kind of like comparing salted deli meats or something like that, right?
Why not?
Both.
I said, why not?
Why can't you put your...
Assaulted deli meats.
Slap your ham and your bacon together.
That's how bacon is made.
That's like...
Where do you think bacon, little baby, bacons come from?
They come from little cellophane-wrapped packages at the store.
Those are called pigs.
Or assaulted deli meats.
That's assault.
Assaulted deli...
Assaulted deli meats, yeah.
And candied.
Candied hams.
Candied bacon.
Bacon's got sugar all through it, right?
Mm-hmm.
That's why people like it.
I'll sue it.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be doing the southern side.
I'll sue it, yeah.
It's got...
Bacon's got sugar all through it.
It's cured with sugar sometimes.
It's cured with salt and sugar.
Sometimes it's just cured like with hickory smoke.
Mm-hmm.
Sometimes it's cured with chemotherapy or ice-cold water.
Did you say hemo-therapy?
Uh, hemo.
That's when your blood vessels get constricted and you fart inadvertently in public places.
But you can at home.
It's forbidden.
I'll take a pass on that.
I don't like that kind of bacon, I don't think.
Well, it tastes great going down, believe me.
It's wonderful.
Mm.
Listen, that sizzle-sozzle still coming down.
All that rain, it's about putting me half to sleep.
Mm.
Is it really...
Is it flooding there in Cleveland?
It's, uh...
It's...
No, no, not at all.
There's a burbling brook running through the radio station right now.
Mm-hmm.
It's a lovely little grotto we're in with some...
I know, I noticed that.
The clearest, cleanest water running out.
It's coming right out of the rocks.
Mm.
Coming out of the walls.
There's a cherubim's fountain and there's a Neptune's oracle fountain.
And they're all spitting out beautiful ice-cold, crystal-clear water from deep inside the earth
that's really, like, you know, pure and stuff like that.
And it reminds us of our...
Dave's putting ideas into my head.
Yeah.
We were talking about how we needed benches and little metal benches that are grottos.
Uh-huh.
And little cherubim.
But we weren't thinking about fountains, concrete fountains with little naked chairbobs, you
know, spraying water out of some...
Their lips or their something.
That did it?
Into the...
Yeah, into the fountain and then back into the creek again.
Now, that would be, like, real...
How do we get power down there to the...
We'd have to run...
You don't have to.
You'd have to have a pump.
No, just use the natural...
The chairbob would need a pump.
Use the gravity...
The gravity force.
Just have a natural running fountain.
You need a sump pump.
And I don't see how gravity's going to make that work.
It's just not hypothetically...
There's a lot of...
We're going to need a lot of money, actually, for all of the statuary that we need in our yard,
in the new church headquarters driveway.
And these would be lined with big...
Little horsemen.
Your disease unit number three.
What?
He's talking about the different statuary.
Different models.
That we're going to be needing.
Well, there would be a big statue of you, Dave.
Does that change your mind?
That'd be a lonesome cowboy, at least a bust.
Of course it does.
Are you going to show a big, like, you know, a full front of a large flabby navel or something?
You know...
No, it would probably be your head.
Oh, no.
Your noble face.
Yeah, we carve it into one of the mountains out there.
Yes.
Like those...
Mount Rushman.
Yeah, Mount Rushman.
John Rushman or whatever its name is.
Well, and there's some earnest old white man who is dynamiting a mountain in the Black Hills
to look like a crazy horse, I think.
The Native American hero crazy horse, right?
Yeah.
But the local Lakota, of course, are going,
no, please don't turn our sacred mountain into a picture of crazy horse.
That's just the kind of thing a white guy would do.
Please don't.
But he died, but his family, I think, is still out there.
They're working on the part underneath the crazy horse's arm now.
It's really big.
It's the whole top half of a crazy horse and part of a horse.
The horse isn't crazy.
The guy's crazy.
He's crazy to fight the same army.
I think of conspiracy white people that were coming in at that time.
Goodness.
Of course, then there was the conspiracy Lakota that you had.
Even the Lakota had their own pink boys.
Everybody has their own.
You know, about half the people are going to be just nice and sweet as can be,
heart big as a coot gizzard,
and other ones are just going to be slippery as pig salve,
just nasty old fuddle fussers.
I hate you, Dad.
I hate you.
Go ahead and take the rug off, Dave.
Say what you mean.
Take the rug off?
Take the rag off.
Take the rug off.
This is our slack.
We're here to cut people some slack.
We don't want you to feel like you're in low cotton,
just joing along on the down go.
We want you feeling like you're drunk as a coot,
only you don't have to get drunk.
You don't have to get cat-goggling drunk just to have slack.
Cat-doggling?
Cat-goggling?
Cat-goggling.
Cat-a-goggling.
It's also another form of communication.
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say that,
and I forget myself for not saying it.
Well, I don't care or hate.
Well, I don't have it in front of me right now.
I mean, it's got something there.
I don't know what it might be.
No, see, I have this script of Southern Saiyans.
He was so wet, Paul was shooting wild ducks in the parlor.
Oh, no.
Hit was...
Hit was so wet.
Hit was so wet, Paul was shooting wild ducks in the parlor.
His head was so diseased,
he got caught in a pawpaw patch eating greens by Susie
or something.
Well, he just got a head full of stump water.
Well, that's what he'd been drinking from the branch
instead of the river.
That comes when your eye sockets melt
and blend into the background scenery.
Now, you know, if you take stump water off a stump at midnight
and put it on a wart,
it'll make the wart...
It'll make the warts go away.
That's true.
It'll make Jesus cry, too.
And the virgin Aborigines will also be, you know,
in a sweat lodge and stuff, maybe.
I didn't know that the stump water had such far-reaching effects
besides wart removal.
Oh, I didn't know that was a deed.
It's known throughout the land.
It's the kickable joy juice, they used to call it,
when the eyeballs used to blend into the background.
Remember?
Don't you?
How?
Listen to that old Dave.
He's just crazy old Dave, ain't he?
He's just crazy as a Bessie bug.
He is crazy as a Bessie bug.
You know, you're one of those guys
that probably would have made fun of DeFuerer
back in the day, you know, man?
I'm gonna make fun of DeFuerer.
He's the DeFuerer we get.
I'm gonna, whether it's a he-Fuerer or a she-Fuerer,
I'm gonna make fun of him.
And so will I.
As long as they...
As long as I can.
Until DeFuerer puts me in the jailhouse
for talking with my big mouth,
on the radio about DeFuerer.
Because DeFuerer, there's some of those Fuerers
don't think that you should be allowed
to say bad things on the media.
No, they could have DeFuerer with you
for talking about DeFuerer.
Yeah, they don't think you should be allowed
to say disrespectful things about them in the media
once you become the leader, DeFuerer.
Then they can't talk bad about you.
Right.
Do you love the song by Spike Jonze,
DeFuerer's Face?
I love it.
In the high, high, right in DeFuerer's face.
DeFuerer's face?
Now, see, if we were cool,
well, if this was Puzzling Evidence Show,
Philo would have that song pulled up on his iPhone
that fast,
and he'd be playing it into the microphone.
And you'd like to run away.
Now, let me see if I can do that.
Well, I looked up Bessie Bug.
I was sitting here looking at all kinds of Bessie Bugs,
but I couldn't show my pictures to the listener.
I was only looking at them on my little phone.
You were looking at that picture of the salamander
out of the Smith Ranch.
I mean, the...
The barnyard cathedral there, wherever it was.
Oh, I have looked at that salamander,
and also at little lizards that lived around the house,
and other ones that we found down by the creek,
and white ones that were on the white rocks,
and there were just all kinds of wonderful creatures there.
Right, right, right.
I did it.
You certainly did.
I'm as tricky as Philo.
You're as tricky as Richard Adolph.
I can type in my phone real quick.
Here's a Trump song.
I'm going to...
Shh.
When her girl says, we own the world in space, we pile, pile, right in her girl's face.
When her girl says, she'll never bomb this place, we pile, pile, right in her girl's face.
Are we not the Superman?
Are you pure Superman?
Yeah, we are Superman.
Super-duper Superman.
Is this Nazi land so good?
Would you leave it if you could?
Yeah, this Nazi land is good.
We believe in it, we could.
We bring the world to order.
I'll hit this world to order.
Everyone of foreign race will love the pure space when we bring to the world disorder.
When the pure space...
Oh, yes.
So beautiful.
Really.
It simply exposes the entire world.
Yeah, it's kind of timely.
Sorry.
On fait Trump.
Trump.
No more gashes, explosions.
That is immature and unfurled, to say the large part of it.
But see, I'm just like Puzzling Evidence Show and Philo, because whenever they mention
anything on that show, Philo types it into his phone real fast and has it instantly up
there on the microphone.
He's tricking it that way.
Or K-Rob.
K-Rob does that on Dr. Hal's show.
So I have to do all that myself.
You pulled something up on your iPhone a minute ago, Princess Wee, but you didn't put it on the radio.
I can't put pictures on the radio.
Well, we're going to have to fix that.
Bessie Bug.
Bessie Bug pictures.
We're actually talking slightly semi-seriously about putting the shows on television, the radio shows, because we have this Roku channel now.
I don't know if the other radio subgeniuses probably don't know what the TV subgeniuses know.
But there's this machine you can buy called a Roku that allows you to get what we might call internet television.
It's quite high quality, depending, I guess, on your internet connection, but it works for ours, and ours is pretty terrible.
And there is a subgenius channel on there now.
Actually, it's a subset.
The OSI 74 channel.
OSI.
Outer Space International or something.
74.
OSI 74 on Roku.
And if you scroll down on that channel, you'll come to a Church of the Subgenius channel curated by Dr. Philo Drummond.
And you can watch the subgenius.
This is all free, of course.
It's exciting, too.
You can watch Arise.
You can see.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's song.
The president's on the phone, I believe, because that's part of the Dobbs and Dealey Astacy's collection, I think.
And that's on there.
You can watch As They See Bob, the collection of media reports on Church of the Subgenius back when we were infamous and they were doing reports on us besides podcasts.
But actual TV shows used to do reports on us.
Yeah, regular TV cuts of people.
I couldn't believe that you were not serious or were.
Right.
And yeah, because why not both?
So, so, yeah, you can.
But we were talking about and this is a kind of a dumb idea because these shows are not visually interesting to watch.
They're people talking into a microphone.
And of course, we'd have to have a goat network picture of Dave talking into his phone over in the corner.
You know, I mean, Howard Stern had his show on TV.
And I guess other great people like Rush Limbaugh and Glenn Beck, the cameras are always pointing at them, even though they're just fat guys in a studio jabbering.
So why not subgenius?
At least we've got a pretty girl in here, Princess Wee.
And I can make funny faces.
If I knew there was a camera on, I'd shave.
You can make the funniest faces.
And of course, the other thing is we could just put on a slideshow of artwork.
And just fade over to show the DJs and blabbermouths every now and then.
But mostly it would just be an endless stream of subgenius pornography on this artwork.
I don't mean nudity.
I know what you mean.
Pictures of Bob, you know, porno, subgenius porno.
Bob Picks.
Yeah.
Pictures of a man smoking a pipe.
That is the most unsexual, amorphous, anti-colloquial human piece of swineberry.
I know, right?
Smoked.
Yes.
Now, now.
I learned that phrase from my Stangmojis.
See, now that I have a smartphone, I'm like hip with the in with it crowd.
I know how to use Mojis and Bitmojis and Stangmojis.
And I can watch TV on my phone.
I was watching The Walking Dead on the way to the show here.
He's all hip with the latest slang and all the latest trends.
Yeah, man.
He knows all of it.
He knows that time.
I know, right?
Two weeks now.
A phrase comes and goes in two weeks now.
I know, right?
Shut up.
It makes you angry to hear that sometimes.
Divisio sin guando, senor.
I don't know.
I enjoy teen slang, especially the kind of teen slang that's so old and obscure that
nobody even knows what any of it means anymore.
Or teen slang that teens, just one clique of teens made up and no other teens knew about it.
No same teed.
No, no.
You're saying because it's but hang when you when they when they just use the same old
trendy things.
But when you're when you're teeds.
Yeah.
If you're if you're if your teeds are cool, then they say things like teeds and how but
hang that is.
Yeah.
I ran those by.
I got those from my son and his clique.
20 years ago when they were teenagers.
I've ran them by my son the other week and he didn't recognize him.
He didn't know his own teenage slang that he and his buddies made up.
I remembered it and he didn't.
Who's the old one?
There are two special groups of language of communications.
What's not accents, but methods of speech.
And one of them is a kind of a valley girl.
Lilt.
Where are they?
Any sentence ends as a question like, you know, I know.
I know.
Right.
That's it.
And it has a special name and everything.
And I talk like this and everything to do is kind of like this.
Anyway.
Yeah.
And so these.
And it drives me crazy.
They go mean punk fight, smacking each other and stuff over who's right and who's wrong.
And like that should be allowed.
And other people say, well, it makes you sound immature.
But to whom?
To pre-millennials.
But to post-millennials.
You sound normal.
Right.
But until tomorrow.
Once again.
That's butthole.
I'm T.
So, you know, just make up your own slang, folks.
You know, people will act like they understand you because they don't want to look ignorant.
Right.
Hyper acronym is slang, slang, staying slang.
I mean, slang.
Right.
Just put the 1004 on it, man.
Yeah.
Do it.
A three.
Five.
What about the 2010 when the prime minister of Canada said that marijuana is going to
be legal in Canada by the year 2007?
Well, see, they forgot to pull down the jib jib.
That's just their jib jaw cranking.
They ain't got no whimper bat.
What are those piddles?
Spinks make fruit words out of.
They don't even.
They don't even know.
It's not.
You made fruit words up.
I'm.
That's what I'm saying is just develop your own stingle speak.
So that the and just jaw it all the time and the others will pretend.
Well, they'll start doing it, too.
Right.
They'll start picking up.
They'll start picking up the same limb lambs you were spoozing.
Well, they did the same thing.
They used to fibble and farble back and forth between two or three extreme euphemisms back
and forth into wanderlust and back again.
The devotional services at 7 p.m.
So they're they're among the lucky ones.
Well, not everybody can jimber the same way that we can.
You, me and Princess, we have been trying for seven or nine abdomens to be able to just
bindle snuck this stuff out that long.
Abdomens.
They were, too, with mountains of studios, emperments every daily.
Exacto.
Knifey.
Well, that's it.
That's it.
As far as pie goes.
That cuts it.
What about the crust of the matter, Senor Swimbo?
Well, we'll.
Sting-a-lang, slang-stang?
I think you're just full of turkey dreams.
You're contrarious as a set-down jackass.
I feel like I need.
But at the same time, what makes me just as happy is a dead pig in the sunshine, to think
about that.
About how you can just.
You can just start blabber-jabbing and nimbus-slamming.
And they still won't turn the radio off, because they're wondering when the punchline's going
to come, if there's going to be one.
Which, kids, that punchline comes on July 5th of this year, 1998, when the world ends
at 7 o'clock in the morning.
That's right, July 5th.
We'll see you there at Ground Zero, X-Day.
Praise Bob.
We've got to get all ready for several big events.
We've got X-Day coming up.
Now, if that works out, we don't have to worry about the other two events, Starwood
and the Republican Convention.
Right.
I'm running.
I hope that they finally get it in their heads to nominate Bob.
The Republican Convention?
And Democrat.
You know, that would save their butts.
The half of them that can't stand Trump, and the half of them that can't stand anybody
but Trump, could all agree on Bob.
Yeah.
In fact, you could.
The Trump.
Thirteen of renters could be have gone to vote in the Super Bowl.
So that doesn't mean that there's someone out there who doesn't want to try and win
I guess what I was wondering at the time was whether the vote for Sanders was electing
I'm sure the DNC had narrated the election, until,anhj save me from негоvende.
I'd like to meet Donald Trump, because it's save Donald Trump's life.
And so, let's see if we can do it.
That's right.
I don't wonder if they're looking at the young president and the young president and
the pane here.
at least. Actually, the markup
on Cafe Press stuff, it probably cost
about four bucks for the
Don't Blame Me, I Voted for Bob
button with an American flag on it.
That's by Fernanda Nandie
Lemur, too, by the way. Praise
Fernanda Nandie Lemur.
There was a
Bob for President campaign
in the city of Cleveland
back in 1984.
I was going to say
1980 sometime. Pope Jimbo
of Cleveland was
had printed up red, white, and blue
Bob for President things, and he was putting
them all over Cleveland. I didn't know anything about it
because I was in Dallas covering
the Republican convention of
1984 in Dallas on my
birthday
with my mom.
And outside
the convention
with the Yippies Rock Against
Reagan stage, I opened
for the dead Kennedys
who knew who I was even though I
didn't know who they were. That's how weird things were
in 1984.
And then I was inside the convention within slingshot distance of Nancy Reagan, sitting next to my mom, who was a delegate.
And she had, they had concealed carry then, they didn't have open carry.
So she wasn't carrying her sick gun on the outside, but mammy had a gun.
Everybody had a gun in Texas.
I thought you said she was deli-
They're going to all have a gun at the Republican convention.
in Cleveland.
They'd be packing each and every one of them.
Well, I wish.
You know, they were talking about
having open carry in the convention,
which they can't do in Ohio, I don't think.
You should be allowed to carry a gun in there,
preferably a really highly automatic weapon.
It turned out to be a Hove.
And everybody just starts spraying each other.
And we'd film it all.
We'd sit back and we'd watch,
and we'd go, oh, wow.
You know.
Well, at one point, it was like
there was going to be a gunfight
between the cruisers and the Trumpies.
But now the cruisers are soaking in their diaper tears,
and the Trumpies are triumphant.
Within their world, they are triumphant.
So it'll be interesting to see.
It's a hard-swilled appaller.
You know, don't you think so, Slytherin Ray?
Don't you think it's a hard-swilled appaller?
I can't believe it.
Anybody as dopey as this TV guy.
It's like, well, how's your plan to make this happen in the Middle East?
What consists of your idea to make the border more secure
rather than just build a, you know, Great Wall of China
costing nine billion bucks?
It's stupid.
Well, now, Philo told me that a vote for Trump
is a vote against boredom.
And I pointed out that in world affairs,
world politics,
boredom is something to be greatly desired, actually.
Boredom would be great.
In my case, I mean, what I believe personally,
I think Reverend Sanders of the vicious psycho-unitarian church
of Libertyville Montpelier,
up there by the notches in the Vermonts and all that stuff like that,
I think he made some sense to at least a huge testosterone pool
of thousands of greats.
Yeah, but as Bill Gates said to Steve Jobs,
that doesn't matter.
No.
It matters nothing.
But what can you do?
I gave somebody a chance to say that to me.
I left him wide open.
I actually said, Max are better.
And I was waiting for him to go, that doesn't matter.
But he hadn't seen the Pirates of Silicon Valley.
He hadn't seen the Pirates of Silicon Valley like I had.
So what you gonna do?
What you gonna do?
It's all movie references and silly.
Silly.
It's a bunch of silly stuff.
It's a bunch of goofy.
It's goofy.
It's dopey.
Jesus didn't have no disciple named Dopey.
That's a quote of a Cleveland drive-time DJ
talking about me.
I can say the radio station.
That's exciting.
I just had hemorrhage.
That was so exciting.
I can't believe I heard that.
Oh, wow.
Well, you know, depicting yourself as an android
with lessons to be learned from beyond the stars.
You know, the old government hype,
you know, make people think that somebody's coming
from outer space to enslave or save them.
Somebody is coming from outer space.
Yeah.
They're coming in outer space.
Unfortunately, too, for many of the particulate mass
we have to attend.
Well, anyway, we've got to think about,
okay, in July, if, well, hopefully the world ends
and we don't have to worry about Starwood
or rather we'll have Starwood on our escape vessel.
Right.
Princess, we and I.
Absolutely.
That's an important thing to have,
that stuff on the escape vessel.
We'll pick up Wisteria.
It's time to go to be packing.
Mm-hmm.
And put it on our escape vessel
and go ahead and go through the motions of Starwood
and then anyone who hasn't,
still hasn't bought their subgenius membership,
we just chuck them out the chute.
Just put them out in space.
Shunt them out.
Well, I mean, at that point,
wouldn't it be kind of silly not to go ahead
and join the Church of the Subgenius
once you've realized that that's the only thing
that could possibly not only keep you alive
but allow you to live a life of freedom?
Yeah.
You can live forever in total pleasure
and hedonism as long as you want to live.
As long as you can think of cool things to do,
you can just do them.
You might really be a brain in a jar
like in The Matrix or something,
but you won't know the difference.
That's the important thing.
You could be already.
How do you know you're not a brain in a jar
like poor old Neo in that old sci-fi movie?
How do you know you're not just a guy in a cave
looking at shadows?
That is on the wall.
Even old cave Sophocles figured that stuff out.
The cave subgeniuses knew it was all an illusion
until you stubbed your toe.
Now, no, well, suddenly it's not so illusory anymore,
now is it?
Yeah, because your toe is real.
Yeah, your toe is real.
And that's the only way you can find out
unless you pay attention, I guess.
I thought it was like a Neolithic cave drawing.
You know, it's like they mastered fire,
so there's torches all over the place.
Filled with all kinds of...
There's these real strange references.
The things that didn't even exist yet
or were about to ever.
You know what I mean?
Like future ancient...
Mark, the three stooges on TV
hadn't been invented yet,
but people were struggling towards
reaching that pinnacle of human evolution.
It makes perfect sense to me.
That is why I listen to your...
But they didn't stop at the three stooges
on afternoon TV.
No, they had to come up with the internet
and podcasts and nonsense like this,
which is about to end.
Actually, thankfully, we have about three minutes left
and that's just enough time to play
the song I promised at the beginning.
Oh, let's not break your promise.
No, no, I can't because it's a Rudy Schwartz project
and he's our personal friend.
By the way, he's a guy who...
He used to be a Texan like I sort of used to be
and he didn't like the way things were going
in Texas and the United States
and he moved to Canada.
He lives in Montreal now.
He says the healthcare is great.
But anyway, he did a cover of Build Me Up Buttercut,
which we're going to listen to now
because we have to go
because the next show is here.
Okay, Dave, thanks for explaining everything.
We'll see you.
It's good to hear your voice, Dave.
Yeah, man.
It's good to be back.
to reinforce whatever idiocy
you were trying to promulgate on the masses.
It's the hour of silence.
All right.
subgenius.com.
Praise God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mess me around and then worst of all...
You never call, baby, when you say you will
But I love you still, I need you
More than anyone, darling
You know that I have from the start
Build me up, buttercup
Don't break my heart
I'll be over at ten
You told me time and again
But you're late
I wait around again
I went to the door
I can't take anymore
It's not you
You let me down again
Baby, baby, try to find
A little time and I'll make you mine
I'll be home, I'll be beside the phone
Waiting for you
Why do you build me up, buttercup
Baby, just let me down
Let me down
I need you around
And then worst of all
You never call, baby, when you say you will
But I love you still, I need you
More than anyone, darling
You know that I have from the start
Build me up, buttercup
Don't break my heart
You were my toy
But I could be the boy you adore
If you'd just let me know
I'll be over at ten
You're untrue
I'm attracted to you all the more
Why do I need you so?
Baby, baby, try to find
A little time and I'll make you mine
I'll be home, I'll be beside the phone
Waiting for you
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I need you around
More than anyone, darling
You know that I have from the start
Build me up, buttercup
Don't break my heart
ầu