Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Oh yes, dear friends, this is an internet-only special hour of Slack not to be mailed to the broadcast stations
because it's solid instrumental jams from 18X Day.
But non-stop six-fisted...
Tales of Connie, which is what this ever-changing once-a-year band is called,
that isn't what the station's signed up for.
Plus, Subgenius jam music can be an acquired taste that melts the tongues and ears of the unworthy
or those with so-called good taste.
But I figure the musicians themselves, the other X-Day attendees, and masochists will want a chance to hear it.
Reverend Suds Pasha and I both recorded all the music, and sometimes his board recordings sounded better,
other times my ambient mic caught it better.
Sometimes both versions sounded awful.
I've been whittling away at this stash for weeks on and off, and I've got it edited down to the point where I like all of it.
None of this music was rehearsed. It's all improvisational jams, some rocking and some jazzing, but all spastic.
But it's not organized in any special order, and I have no idea which specific musicians are on any given cut.
Besides, they kept switching instruments.
However, there is a sort of generic credits-giving at the end by Priestess Pisces.
There were jams pretty much every night for five nights at X-Day, so there was a lot to choose from.
The one musician who is probably on damn near every track is Reverend Angry Luke.
Oh, pardon me, Lord Angry Larry, who is playing generally the most prominent guitar most of the time.
Other musicians who were involved most nights include Bishop Stick, Reverend Rock God, Reverend Hazel of the Windmills,
Reverend Fid Chooley, Trademark Gunderson from Evolution Control Committee, Lord Ferg, Reverend Suds Pasha, Dr. Philo Drummond,
Reverend Symphaltimus Ex Mortis, Reverend Shover, Reverend 80, Reverend Dildonics, Reverend Oriccio, and DJ Gravity.
So, we'll start with an untitled tune I titled, Pipe Rockin' Jam Number One.
On my Band Swing 6 it didn't femt
Thank you.
Wow.
Goal.
effetto
'veán
photos
more
¶¶
Thank you.
Thanks.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Tales of Connie, also known as the
Fuck Peas Band.
Performers consisted of many people
including Hazel,
Sex Mortis, Stick, Suds
Bashaw, Angry Larry,
Reverend Rock God, Sinful
Autumus, Ex Mortis, Lord Ferg,
DJ Gravity, and
more. As well as
Trademark G on Theremin,
Bob on the Wall
over there, Ivan Stang,
and several
others.
Thank you
very much
and good night.
Music
Doctor, doctor
D-A-H-A-D!
The End
ice cream
Friends, you've been
learning,
listening to an hour of six-fisted Tales of Connie, the X-Day jam band. And it's
not a typical hour of slack, but if you want to know more about X-Day or the
hour of slack or where to get CDs of this stuff, try subgenius.com. Praise Bob.