The
Yeah?
The numbers all go to
11, right across the board.
11, 11, 11...
Amps go up to 10.
Exactly.
You see, most blokes are gonna be playing at 10,
you're on 10 on your guitar,
where can you go from there?
Where?
The Self-Genius Power of Swagging!
Don't worry dear,
it's no worse than some happening.
Aye, but not much worse.
If only we could get inside that special car.
Come!
Come.
I will show you wonders you have never seen before.
Gee!
11.
I don't know whether I'm awake or dreaming,
my mind just won't accept.
But Albert,
what are you doing?
What's about Albert?
Uh, yes dear friends,
this is gonna be another one of those hours of slack
where I play somebody else's show.
This is the second hour of Time for the Show,
season one, episode 17.
It's a continuation of the one I ran last week,
because when I would normally be putting this show together,
I'm actually going to be in Portugal,
in the town of Porto,
to film
the old subgenius master, G. Gordon Gordon.
Master assassin, actually,
technically,
for that documentary movie.
And earlier today, in fact,
I met with the director in Temple, Texas,
and handed over six boxes of unthinkably valuable old subgenius videos
that no one has looked at in 30 years.
But it's the originals.
They'll actually be safer there than they will be.
They'll be in the Dobbs' shed over the summer.
We have to go back to Cleveland at the end of the month
and finish fixing up the house and get rid of it.
We have to sell the slacker mansion.
Anyway, while I was out on the road,
I stopped in Waco and visited the Waco Mammoth National Monument,
which is an ongoing dig with 65,000 year old mammoth bones,
sitting right there in the ground in front of you,
where you can see them being dug out.
There's probably hundreds more down there.
They've already extracted 24 of them.
They're extremely delicate.
They're not fossil bones.
They're actual bones.
And they've built this entire building around the dig that's climate controlled.
And it's an astounding sight if you're a fossil nerd.
Oh, it's so great.
Anyway, friends, for this week, it's another canned show,
but it's a great canned show.
Our hosts, Fid, Argus, and Pease,
continue with the horrible story about Fid's ill-fated date with the NASA lawyer.
Actually, it wasn't a date.
I don't know what you'd call it.
So, take it away.
Time for the show!
Oh, show.
It's always time for you, and it's never time for me.
But that's what it is.
It's just reality, and we're going to have to deal with it.
It's time for the show.
It's an actual show.
And since it's hour two, and we're pretending to be professionals,
we're going to reset the show.
This is a two-hour podcast where every show,
we attempt to come up with the content for the next show.
And that's exactly...
And we've been failing on that.
We haven't been doing that.
No, this show's been super productive,
because we got this whole NASA lawyer Fid Chooley thing going.
I mean, there's got to be some comedy going on.
Did you not check your mimeograph?
My who?
Never mind.
What are we doing now?
You have to explain the joke.
It's always funnier when you explain the joke.
I was asking Pease if he had not gotten his mimeograph.
I did not get it.
So, there.
There's the joke.
He didn't get it.
The joke being that I'm sending a mimeograph.
That's a good one, Argus.
That's funny.
It's a...
I'm done.
Well, this week's Penn Jillette.
We have two Penn Jillettes this week.
We have one of them right here in the studio.
Oh, we tricked him.
Do we?
We got him.
Although he can't hear, he is here but not here.
He's in our spirits.
Where is Reverend Couch Sloth?
Yeah, Couch Sloth, if you want to come on the show, just jump in the Hypercom and we'll
bring you in.
I didn't see him in the Cone of Silence.
Yeah, he's not there yet.
Nobody can just walk in to the Cone of Silence, Pease.
Reverend Avey did that one time.
Well, he had keys.
Well, we took them away though, right?
They are gone, yes.
He'll probably get them back soon.
He'll probably get them back someday.
If he wants them back, he could have them back.
He could have them back.
He's been punished enough.
So speaking of punishments, it's time for the Blind Eye.
Pease, you want to tell everybody how the Blind Eye works?
So the Blind Eye is a pretty simple concept.
We're not advocating or calling to action a terrorist organization.
But what we're saying is we're going to name some names.
And if something bad was to happen to those people between shows, then we would say, I'm
out.
We're turning a blind eye.
We're not helping you.
We don't care what those people did.
We're fine with it.
Now, if that person, if it happens after the next show, then no, it's back on.
That was bullshit.
You shouldn't have done that.
That's wrong of you.
Now, it's important you understand we're not targeting people.
I am.
We're saying if.
I'm targeting people.
If.
I know a lawyer.
From NASA.
She got mad at me when I told her I tried to sue the movie once.
How do you even buy that story?
If somebody came up to me and I was a drummer and said, oh, hi, by the way, my name's Sally.
I'm a lawyer from NASA.
I'll be like, oh, my name's Mary and I'm the queen of England.
Hi, my name's Pease.
I'm a legally ordained minister in the church of the subgenius.
Well, same thing.
That's the truthful thing.
I'm saying I don't believe this lady's a lawyer.
Which one is more outlandish?
Which, which, well.
That drunko, the super thought showed up to the bar and she happens to have tie-ins that might actually be able to get us off this planet legally.
Remind the viewers what THOT, T-H-O-T stands for.
Oh, I have to do that?
I have to spell that?
Yeah, you legally have.
It's a live radio.
We did such a great segue into it.
Yeah, he was setting it up quite well, Fid.
I'm sorry, I didn't know we were on the Explain Every Joke show.
Yeah, Fid.
It's always funnier when somebody doesn't get the joke and then you have to explain it to them.
When you're scrolling Marquee tells me that I have to explain every joke, you know, you send me a mimeograph.
Or a spyrograph.
Do you have a scrolling Marquee in front of you, Argus, or is it just Fid that has it?
We've got them all over the room.
They're just constantly scrolling with information, data, statistics.
That's where I got my blind eye today.
So really, there's no excuse.
There's no excuse not to look at the Marquee.
You can't miss them.
Right, so again, Fid.
We have a 40-foot screen in here that has the Discord chat.
Fid, can you step up this week, please?
I can't, but guess who can?
Reverend Couchsloth! I've just brought him into the cone of silence.
Hooray!
What up, Couchsloth?
Hey!
My G, Couchsloth.
So our guest has joined us.
How are your chakras, my G?
How would you like to greet our guest this week?
Yeah, let Pease greet the guest, because Pease is really the most professional of us.
Obviously. He's the one getting all the offers to go and plug other people's shows.
Well, you can tell I'm not a professional, because when you asked Pease if he wanted to introduce the guest,
I just jumped right in and just reiterated what you said.
That is the most unprofessional thing that could possibly happen.
But Reverend Pease is about to make up for my, um...
So far.
My rady of sins.
Reverend Pease, get Couchsloth in here.
So, Dr. Reverend Pope Couchsloth, welcome to the show.
Well, thank you, Pease. It's nice to be back. It's been many, many weeks at this point.
Now, you were on the West Coast, right?
Yeah, that's right. I was bouncing around California.
Drinking?
Drinking them Zimas, throwing Skittles in them, blending with the news.
Found some beautiful, beautiful congealed little cubes of Frop.
Ate them all up.
Actually, I got to drop by what was going to be one of the last Ask Dr. Howell performances of the year.
Oh, yeah. I wish I could go catch one.
Did you get to see it? I heard it wasn't just of the year. I heard this is the last one.
I heard they're closing that place to Chez Polo.
Yeah, that's what Chicken John does.
I was saying. So, yeah, I was set the second to last one. It was the 420 performance, which was beautiful.
The Frop was being flung about the audience and Howell himself was in rare form.
So, let me ask you a little bit about that show, okay?
Because we've all seen Howell perform at X Day. A couple of us have seen him at Burning Man.
But this is really where you saw him. That's his home turf.
That's where he's developed his show over the decades.
And this venue is really home base for him.
Was there a different vibe? Were you like, was he more majestic? More Howell-esque?
Well, I mean, you know, I've only ever seen him perform at Chez Polo.
I didn't even see him at the old Odeon where he used to perform.
But, yeah, I've been kind of going to the shows when I could since about 2009.
And, you know, it's always been at Chez Polo since then.
But, I mean, I will say his, you know, he's a great performer.
He had great gravitas at this last show.
And I happen to know that two or three questions from people that I knew got rolled into one massive omnibus question.
Well, they didn't pay enough. That's why.
Yeah, that's correct. That's how Howell moves it along.
Now, did you get a question of yours answered? And how much did it cost if said question was answered?
Well, I always try to bait him into his bardic irruptation.
So, I'm a healthy tipper at Ask Dr. Howell.
My question for Howell that ended up getting rolled in against other things was,
Should I worry when the skull head is in front of me or is it worse because it's always waiting where my eyes don't go?
Oh.
I'm sure he had an eloquent and verbose response to such a query.
See, I can't do it. You know what? I try to do Howell. I try to phrase it.
Nobody can do what Howell does.
Now, please. You shouldn't be so hard on yourself.
Yeah, there's only one of him.
That's Dr. Fox's Dr. Howell.
He's certainly a treasure.
But he not only tried to answer that, but simultaneously answered the question,
What did Stephen Hawking take with him to his cremation rocket?
Can we get another shot of Dr. Fox's Dr. Howell?
I think Dr. Fox has a pretty good Dr. Howell. You guys tell me.
I don't think it's that important.
I just think that we all need to slow down, take a breath, and draw girls with big titties.
Nailed it.
Alright, now that was Dr. Howell.
Now, Dr. Fox, do your impression of him.
Now, it's Dr. Howell. I know everything.
So, Couch Sloth, what are you doing in my neck of the woods?
What are you doing up there in the San Francisco Bay Area?
Just a rock's throw from Nevada.
Yeah, I kinda go wandering back there about every six weeks.
Really?
You know, I moved out east, but I still have a bunch of connections back there.
So about every six weeks I go back.
So did you go for espionage or pleasure?
Oh, you know, espionage is always pleasure, my friend.
Oh, well answered. Well answered, sir.
I'm sorry, let's listen in while Finn and Argus have a private conversation while we talk.
I'm not having a conversation.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about Dr. Fox having a conversation with an allegedly imaginary guest.
I don't know who you're talking to, Dr. Fox.
I'm just talking to Arthur Martin.
I think you should tell the viewers who you're talking to.
Or at least...
I'm talking to Chief of Hypercube Maintenance and Repair.
Oh, it's Oster Six is on the line then.
No, no, actually, it's my dad. He showed up.
He's actually over here at the Hypercube today.
Oh, put him on the radio. I'd love to hear it.
No. He wouldn't do it?
He doesn't want to talk to you.
You know, it was a couple of months ago I asked him.
He's holding out for scale wages.
You ever hear the show? He's like, yeah, I've listened to it.
I heard you on it.
I think I heard Fid.
And I go, oh yeah, what did you think of Pease?
And he goes, who's that?
Yeah, I know. You told this story.
You tell it every week now. It's good.
It's a good story.
It's good because it's true.
Well, tell your father I said hello.
Pease says hello.
He's nodding yes.
You've got to nod out of the window.
He's got to be good.
We've only got two sets of the cans here.
So he's actually in here.
He only hears me and Fid
on our side of the conversation.
The last ten minutes has just been you
and the other guy on the computer
that he can't hear.
So now I heard it's a law in San Francisco.
It's sit down and sit down.
The first drink you order has to be
a Zima.
I mean, I was always under the impression
the first thing you drank had to be
Fernet Branca with a Pabst Blue Ribbon
backside.
Yeah, that's a Dr. Howell
tradition.
You ask a sacred question
and you receive the
sacred elixir of the Fernet
Branca. But you know, old homophobic
Pease
just wants to make sure that
everybody's getting in their
crisp, delicious
Zima.
Because they're a sponsor of the show.
As Pease always said, Zima is
super. So what does homophobia have to do
with Zima in this case?
I'm hoping he's going to explain it too.
...who the gays are?
I have a cure for it though.
Wait, wait, wait. Is Zima like turning
the people gay? Like that
water in that lake is turning the frogs gay?
Zima turns the frogs gay. There's an old adage
which is gayer to drink a Zima
or actually be gay. Pease,
Pease, my G.
Please, for once,
more gay.
Not what makes it gayer,
Please. We're professionals.
Which am I supposed to say?
Gayer or more gay?
Do you have a stick to reach through the internet
with? Leave Pease alone.
He's a handsome boy.
Are you going to jump on this train now?
I'm jumping on the Dr. Fox
So what if I drink my Zima
on a dodgeball quad court?
Okay, so that's bad right off the bat
because that means you're cruising.
What you need to do to send a signal
especially when you're on that coast
is take any color
but yellow Skittle.
If you take any color but yellow Skittle
and put it in your Zima,
all the gays know
that you are not the gay.
Oh, so it's
like reverse hanky-coding.
Correct.
But now if you put a yellow
Skittle in your Zima,
that means you're looking for a bear.
And those are uncomfortable situations.
Oh, this explains
so much. Doesn't it though?
It's like this time that I went by Mr. S. Leather
to get some club wear and they
had these beautiful vinyl pants
with red stripes on them that I thought were badass.
You wear those to the wrong
club, my friend, and people start
sharpening the knives and licking them. Yeah, because
Crips don't want to see those red colors
at their parties.
No, keep going, Peace. You're doing great.
I think Fox is explaining to his dad
No, he can hear us
side-chattering and he's getting
things need to be done at the house. You guys!
I love doing the show and
I want my interviews
to be immaculate and when
you guys have side-chatter
off the mic when I'm trying
to interview the great
and diligent and wonderful...
Reverend Couch Sloth. Reverend Couch Sloth.
And you guys are having your side
banter. You know, it's ruining my
thing and I'm Pease and I'm a
sensitive boy. And I'm a handsome
boy, but I am sensitive. That's good.
I don't feel that way at all. I'm
just glad to be here actually. I know you don't feel like you're handsome
and neither does anybody else, but
I'm here to tell you that you are.
But my incel
friends say no. I'm only of
average look. Of course they would.
Of course they would. They can't admit it.
I'm only of average look and it's obvious from looking at you. They would never
admit it because then they'd
be involuntary.
It is. That's what
incel mean.
They don't want to be celibate.
They would like to be banging carrots too.
I like the idea of intel though.
I'm involuntarily
intelligent.
Well, that's not what that lawyer said.
I didn't ask to know
more than everybody
ever. What was with this NASA lawyer?
I didn't ask to be the smartest
person in the world. I'm involuntarily intelligent.
I'm involuntarily intelligent.
You know,
they hit him in the hall and they dance
around it, but they really don't describe any
outrageous crazy eyed behavior
that most men would identify
with, I need to get the fuck out.
But he hasn't really
Nothing like a Pokemon Go Uber
can't fix. No, I did identify with that.
She gave me ox tails. I gotta draw
the line at that. No, I
identified with that, but my balls disagree.
He's a smegmitarian.
You know,
I have two balls and one brain.
My balls outvote my brain.
Is this the first time
Is that how stank out where he is today?
He broke even.
Yeah, it's time for the show on Freethink
Radio. This is the show with the inside
jokes that we try to
promote. We try to promote the show generally
and all we do is joke about
the Church of the Subgenius and a bunch of
stuff that you've never heard of.
Yeah, you've never heard of it. Thank you all the
people. But I didn't say anything
about the church one time.
Oh yeah, you only said something about Stang.
I did. Nothing about the church.
Well, he's a major celebrity.
He's a major celebrity. Oh yeah, he's a
He is a major celebrity. I do. I have
a celebrity trading card. Handsome smiling Doug.
I got a pack of celebrity
trading cards the other day and
to my surprise, there was an insert
of the Reverend Ivan Stang.
I got all the stats on the back.
That's his rookie card? I was about to say.
Hey, let's go over those stats, man.
Do you know that the church is selling
Bob condoms now? Fleece groups, average
and Stang puts a hole in each
one personally before he mails them out. Post office
general relationships.
Oh, look at that. It's right over there.
In the rookie years.
He's an elite. This is great.
But yeah, it says here that he took
20 walks and one ball.
So.
Yeah, Reverend Ivan Stang is the
only person in the church
of Major League Baseball to ever
get more than one
run off of one walk.
That will never be
matched again. Nobody will ever be
able to get two runs off of one
walk. It's amazing.
Wait a second. I'd like to
run off.
Wouldn't we all right about now? I'm trying
to. I'm, the cigarettes
in the airlock are calling my name
and I gotta sit here and I gotta wait for you guys
to run out of steam so I can start a song.
Reverend Couch Sloth, we missed you, man.
Yeah, welcome back to the show,
dude. You're funny. Did you hear about
Fid?
What about Fid?
Yes, he did.
We don't have to go through this. He was in the chat.
We don't have to go through this for the sake of the viewers.
We haven't even gotten to the blind eyes. I tell them, hey, don't
tell everybody about all that drinking we were doing
after hours. But no, please,
nobody, please ask me
any more about my adventure
with the fetid NASA lawyer.
Well,
I mean, I guess she's got
some law knowledge on her
because that encyclopedia was thick.
And what does thick
stand for, Dr. Fox?
Uh, terribly
handsome, incognito,
uh, courageously
capturing. That's Pease
right there. Right there. Pease, you're thick.
You are
a thick, handsome boy.
You're a thick boy
and you're a handsome boy. B-O-I.
Who would win?
Ten Pease or one thick boy?
I don't want to
do this show anymore. We're not!
We're not doing the show!
We do the show! Half an hour ago, we
started doing a show. We're not talking about doing the blind eye
segment. This isn't a show!
All this is is a two hour production
meeting. Alright, so Pease,
did you have a blind eye?
And this will give our guest
Reverend
Dr. The Sloth of
the couch, uh, will uh,
will get a few minutes. Maybe he wants to jump in
with us. But no pressure, bro!
You know, Pease does have a
blind eye. I'm already with my blind eye. We're gonna tease it.
We're gonna tease the blind eye. We're gonna tease it.
My blind eye. We're gonna tease it again.
We teased it 25 minutes ago.
Dude, it's live radio!
Literally 30 minutes ago. It's live radio!
It's nothing but teases. We never actually
get to the content. I mean, what do you
think this is? Some kind of
respectable publication. Maybe this is one of the night blind eye is actually a
organization.
And I'm gonna blind eye NASA's
legal department.
Hey, check it out!
The arrow and the spinner. I
called it.
I don't feel that
breaking Fid Chuli's heart
is something that a legal team
should be involved in. Especially
when it's the National
Aeronautics Security
Association
of Space.
Was
something hard at work?
At least something was hard at work I hope.
I think the point was that something
wasn't hard at work.
And Oxtails!
I'm blind eyeing Octails and vodka.
Now, Fid what's your blind eye?
Wait. Now, hold on.
You don't get to just
say your blind eye.
Why are you blind
eyeing the NASA
legal department.
I feel like the NASA legal department
read my friend
Fid truly on.
I think that they
tried to tempt him with space. I think they tried to lead
on him. I don't know if he's into that, though.
Like, hey, I've got, you like
space cults? I've got a spaceship.
Want to come over to my house and see it?
You know, poor Fid.
He's much like a child.
He doesn't know that it's not a real pleasure
saucer. How did you know the line she used?
It's just
I told you.
This whole thing was a setup.
It would be the saucer below
a pleasure saucer. A contentment
saucer? A contentment saucer.
Yeah, he goes over there
into the false premise that he's going to be
introduced to a pleasure saucer
and all he gets is a contentment saucer.
And on top of that,
she made my other good friend, Argus Q. Fox
Dr. Esquire worry
about his buddy Fid truly all
day Sunday.
Peas, you're so sweet when you're
insincere.
It's a gift.
What about the oxtails? You're trying to go for a twofer.
Why are you blind-eyeing oxtails?
If ISIS was to attack
all of their national food
supply, which is oxtail. I don't feel she
prepared them correctly.
Nuke the oxen!
Here's what I think happened.
I think she served Fid
the oxtails in vodka and the
oxtails had been put so much
spice on them to mask
the intoxicant that
she put in the oxtails. And you'd
never seen a more surprised lawyer
when Fid truly ate that and down
that vodka and then beat
her ass at Pokemon Go
because she thought he'd been passed out, tied up
in the cellar already. And they were walking around
those chemicals had no effect
on Fid truly. Him being a
drummer, of course, she was not aware that
drummers are immune to
hypnotics.
These were heavily seasoned
oxtails, you say.
Yeah, to mask the
hypnotics that she put in it.
She moved the shit out of those oxtails.
It could be more sinister than that, though.
It could have been
British oxtail
and the spices were to cover up
the mad cow disease.
But here's the thing.
The joke's on her.
They're not mad.
They're just upset.
That's right. Reverend Couch Sloth
You and your labels.
Reverend Couch Sloth knows about
oxtail and mad cow disease.
What's the deal with that?
Yeah, anything that's not talking about this.
Absolutely.
Fid, I heard you just got the world changed in your bicycle.
How'd that go?
Say what?
I was trying to help segue out of that
uncomfortable NASA
lawyer conversation.
I don't need your help segueing out of an uncomfortable conversation
because I have a lot of money.
I have a radio station
right in front of me.
Yeah, we have songs to do that for him.
Yeah, we can just play a song.
And so this week's
obligatory get fid
out of saying incriminating things
song is by Frank Zappa
and Captain Beefheart and it's called
200 Years Old.
And somebody contact
my lawyer, please.
I'm being held against my will.
That's pretty funny.
Smoke them if you got them.
We'll be back.
Time for the show. Freethink Radio.
Help. Help.
Please send help.
Music
I was sitting in a breakfast room in Allentown, Pennsylvania
six o'clock in the morning.
I got up too early.
It was a terrible mistake.
Sitting there face to face
with a 75-cent glass of orange
that was about as big as my finger
and a bowl of
horribly foreshortened corn asleep.
And I said to myself, this is the life.
As far as you get close, you try to grow a mustache.
guitar solo
The music's too loud.
It's too loud.
Too loud.
Dr. Fox is a big boy.
I can't walk away for a minute.
Did you put the music up to Mask Fid's crying about the subject matter?
I guess so.
Well, I was going to cry a little bit.
My blind eye was on Airbnb.
Airbnb?
You don't like Airbnb?
Well, yeah, because when I'm looking,
looking for a vacation, what I really want
to do is stay in somebody's mother-in-law
suite and be told not to drink.
And that's where it was
coming off for me, was not as much
Airbnb, but people that
utilize it. And people
that say, hey, why don't
you come live in my basement? It's only
$200 a night.
By the way, no smoking.
Or drinking.
Which, can you even
tell a tenant?
Maybe if you ask nicely.
Well, because you might be
doing better than me on Airbnb, dude.
You know, it's funny, they find you
in Las Vegas if they catch you Airbnb.
They find you, peas? Really?
I'd never imagine.
Reverend Couch Sloth, our
beautiful, beautiful, precious,
precious guest.
And Patreon
supporter, by the way.
What
was your experience?
What was your experience with Airbnb?
I
Airbnb'd in San Francisco one time
when I couldn't get a hotel room.
You have to there, don't you?
There are no houses that are not
B&Bs there. Yeah, I mean,
it's how everyone makes rent, is by renting
out to everyone else. That's a great economic
plan, isn't it?
I'm not
homeless. I'm just sleeping in this box by the
river because I've got my Airbnb
making money. Well, in the interest
of full disclosure, our show,
is sponsored by Airbnb's
biggest competitor, which
is Magnavox.
Yeah, Magnavox and
Adderall PM are both
Airbnb's biggest
competitor.
So that being said,
continue,
Reverend Couch Sloth. Yeah, well,
so the mother-in-law suite
that I was advertised was actually
a plywood shed.
And whenever I turned
on the space heater to try out the air, I was like, oh, I'm going to get a new one.
And then when I tried to warm it up, it would blow
out the lights in the shed
and half the house. Nice.
They must have thought that was cool
every time you did it. Oh, yeah.
They thought it was great, especially
because it was blowing out the half of the house
that the primary tenant
was in.
So what happens to that circumstance? Do you like
say, hey, this is not worth $200.
I'm only going to pay you $175.
Well, I mean, this is
America. I just found a way to pass the
buck to somebody else. Well, did you
run out like a corner of the shed for
$300?
Rustic, no
electricity. That was actually
I mean, it was actually
I was actually working
out there at the time, so
I just tolerated it
knowing that I didn't have to pay for it.
It sounds like your employee
was taking for a ride, though, trying to provide
you a comfortable place for you to
repass after your hard work
during the day, and you have to go back to a
plywood shed.
I think there should be
if only one of us
knew a lawyer
that could perhaps take on this
case. I think
you might know a lawyer
that had some
some practice
in space law
because ours is space
international maritime space
or maybe if they could just like make it up
to me with a really good oxtail.
Damn couch sloth is on the show
bashing FID.
That's why I like him, man.
He comes into the show saucy.
He doesn't care.
He's like, oh, you want to have me on your show?
I'm going to say what I'm going to say.
By the way, couch sloth, we love
you and appreciate you.
You are you are among
our treasured, treasured
fans.
Well, I greatly appreciate
it, and I do.
I do.
I do love this show.
I'm sorry when my wanderings take me away
from it week on week, but
it is good to be back, even if I've only got
about three sentences worth of inside jokes
to play with. Right.
That's OK. We've only got two.
Yeah, we have like
what praise Bob and then
I don't know. Fuck them if they
can't take a joke. Other than that, we don't
know anything. That's why
this what you are listening to
right now, right now, time
for the show, which you're listening
to.
On Freethink Radio.
That's where it's being streamed. Isn't
a show. It's just a two hour
production meeting where we come
come up with the
content for the next
episode. And that's what we mentioned.
It's fine. Have you mentioned your new show?
That's going to be Wednesdays at 10.
The law and you with
Julie.
Fucking bees.
Oh, shit.
Damn. I've got
nothing tonight. You know, usually I
feel like I can. Yeah.
Well, I guess when we can get it, we
have to take it. You know,
that works is people are going to call
up with their legal problems and
they're going to tell the legal problems to
fit. It's going to go off the air
for a minute and consult
off the air at 5
a.m. And he'll come back
the following night to answer your legal
questions. He didn't even
tell you the part that
I guess we couldn't get that far. But, you know,
we left the bar at five.
The morning he did not
make it back to Hypercube until
nearly 11 p.m.
The next was the same
day. So he was gone
for what is that? Five to
11. That's it felt like
how did you keep yourself
from calling the police? Finally, the
missing person. Dude, I
have a phone, man. Nobody
has landlines.
I didn't have my cell phone.
I need to carry an old
one.
I can ask her. We're
all day. An emergency.
I do.
I do. But look,
if you were in this situation that I was in,
you wouldn't have been able to do any better, man.
Like I did the best I was able
to do better. I was able to
pass it on to you.
Not you. I was talking. I
escaped. He's wouldn't have been able to
look that man. Is
this really what the show is? We
haven't even done the blind eyes. We haven't even
done the voicemails. We haven't
even done the viewer mail.
It's almost time for the end of the show.
Yeah. Who's your blind eye,
Finn?
You know what?
I've been holding off
on making peas my
blind eye. I said
to myself.
I have to confirm that we've gotten
on to him for using the same blind
eye, especially when it
was me the second time.
So is it, you know,
if you're going to listen, if you're going to live on that
professional level, if you're going to
tiptoe to the edge, if
you were going to take your sphincter
and scrape it along the walls
of the Grand Canyon,
Fid Chuli, I have to say that you
can only condemn
peas with
a blind eye once
per year.
Oh, now
you're bound to me.
Now there's a limit on how many times
we can condemn.
Now you can.
You can condemn him as much as you want,
but I'm going to tell you every time you
do it, it's going to diminish.
It's going to diminish.
You're just going to continue it week after week?
How come this starts now?
Peas has been blind eyeing you
for like week after week.
We did season zero, the practice
season, and season one, the one where we
fuck everything up every week
and miss all the shows.
This is bullshit.
Season two is starting.
You stay out of this, peas.
This is between.
Between me and Dr. Fox.
He's my friend, but right now he's really testing
our friendship.
So is like season two's theme going to be all
sophomore jokes all the time?
Maybe he's exploring the legal
boundaries of your...
Couch Sloth, let me...
You are an independent arbiter
of this situation.
Reverend Couch Sloth, I need to confer with you.
I'm just looking forward to Peas' apology text later.
Sorry, sorry.
I was picking on Fid their whole show.
No, no, no.
Because you know he wants...
He wants to apologize for doing bad on the show.
So we'll go, no, Peas, you were good.
I'm sorry I didn't get to you sooner.
It's okay.
I accept your apology.
You don't have to apologize.
Is he gonna...
Are you expecting your Peas bad show apology
after this episode, Fid?
Once again.
Are you expecting it?
Again.
Well, if you're gonna let me talk...
I'll think about it.
If you're gonna let me talk...
Oh, I know.
I distracted you.
I distracted you with my side chatter.
I don't want to distract you with my side chatter.
Banter.
My headphones are unplugged.
All right, there they go.
No, hey.
If you're gonna let me talk, you know,
just let's be fair about...
Reverend Couch Sloth is not only
a great supporter of the show.
He's also my personal psychologist.
So I'm just gonna ask that you and Peas
that Dr. Fox and Reverend Peas
just let me get a moment
with my personal psychologist,
Reverend Couch Sloth,
and in the interest of...
Okay, you're on the clock.
In the interest of patient doctor confidentiality,
I'm gonna ask that not only do Dr. Fox
and Reverend Peas put their fingers in their ears,
but that the rest of the audience
just turn the radio down
until we're done talking.
You'll know when we're done.
Then just turn it back up.
But, um...
I don't sense it.
Uh, Reverend Couch Sloth,
doctor, I'm just, um...
I don't know what to do with you.
I mean, you've been here.
Cease and desist.
What do you think?
Couch Sloth?
Dr. Couch Sloth?
Are you there?
Yes.
Are you asking psychologists
how you're doing?
Hey!
This is my private therapy time.
Okay, here go my fingers.
There we go.
Don't...
It'll work better.
Sacred...
Put your fingers in your ears.
Sacred time.
Peas!
Come on, man.
This is...
This is therapy.
This is psychotherapy.
If you guys keep talking,
I'm not gonna be able
to write it off on my taxes.
Dun-dun.
Reverend...
Dun-dun-dun-dun.
Reverend Dr. Psychologist Couch Sloth.
You can do, uh,
background music
if you want to, Peas.
That's pretty good, yeah.
No, we should do
the People's Court music.
Do you have the
People's Court music?
Yeah.
That's the bit we haven't...
I have it right here
in my ass.
Hold on.
Let me just put it up
to the microphone
and tell you what I really
think about you, Peas.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That was so mean.
In the People's Court,
today is presiding judge
Fid Chuli
in the case
of the NASA lawyer.
Today's plaintiff,
Fid Chuli,
claims that the NASA lawyer
did not receive his consent
to orbit Uranus.
The defendant,
the NASA lawyer...
I was penetrated,
your honor!
Who's the defendant, Peas?
I'm the defendant.
The defendant is
NASA's lead...
I'm the victim here.
Come on.
Sasha...
Justice must prevail.
Hey.
Oh, wait.
Oh, so now the defendant
doesn't get an intro?
Wow.
So much for innocent
until proven guilty.
Wow.
Sasha Bang says
Fid Chuli provided
inadequate servicing
and then ate all her
oxtails and vodka.
She says she doesn't
owe him a thing.
She says she doesn't owe him
No, too late.
Too late.
Oi!
Dun-dun.
Can you, can you please...
Today, though,
resolve the differences
in Chuli's court.
to put a handcuff
on my dick?
I feel like around my wrist
would have been sufficient.
I mean, where am I gonna run?
There's TV cameras everywhere.
There's people on...
There's scrolling...
All right, Judge Peas.
Uh, I've presented
my argument.
The prosecution
is presenting
their own verdict.
What's your ruling?
Well, Fid,
they don't allow me
to put people
on the chain gangs
in a small claims case
like this.
But,
I'm gonna make an exception.
We're gonna have you
go to drill boot camp
with Sergeant Slaughter here
and you're gonna learn
how to treat
NASA lawyer ladies
like ladies
and not your playthings
and you're gonna learn...
Are you listening, Fid?
Because you're not gonna learn
if you're not listening, Fid.
Wait, what?
You're gonna learn
not to make your friends,
Argus and Aster,
worry about you
from 5 o'clock
in the morning
after 2 p.m.
after 11 p.m. at night.
Aster 6 was not worried
for one minute.
Aster 6 was the one
telling me,
it's fine.
It's fine.
Thank you.
Shout out to, um...
Shout out to Aster 6
for telling Dr. Fox
that even though
I was lost in the woods,
as Reverend Peas knows
how I tend to be,
I tend to get, quote,
lost in the woods, unquote,
uh, I will be okay.
But Dr. Fox,
Dr. Fox is a,
he's, he's a,
he's a nice,
he's a good friend.
He worries.
He's a good friend.
Watch it there.
I almost called him
a nice guy.
I almost did.
He would not have
taken kindly to that.
Argus and I were camping
and we all had some popcorn.
The three of us
had popcorn.
And Fid wandered off
into the woods.
And Argus,
Argus got super concerned
and I was like,
Argus, Fitzgerald,
man, it's just the woods.
He'll be fine.
Argus would not stop worrying.
And so I knew
the pain that you put
our friend through
for those,
not even 12 hours, dude.
Oh, no.
What is this?
Argus is saying
the darndest things.
18 hours.
And I bet you Argus
was wandering up and down
those pathways
where you guys do
your videos and stuff.
Fid,
corn dog lady,
have you seen Fid?
No, please.
Hey, guy that smacks
Fid in the face,
have you seen Fid?
Here's two guys.
Have you seen Fid?
Oh, so I asked her finally
at like six o'clock
that night and said,
Argus, we have to go
to your dad's
and have dinner.
Maybe Fid will be there.
He knows we're all
going to meet at Fox's
father's house for dinner.
And yet when you got there,
he still wasn't there.
You put Argus
through hell, dude.
And you and I are tight.
We're friends.
But I got to say,
no, that was uncool.
You're right.
No, I'm not.
No, and I,
I especially like the part
where he went.
It's not cool now.
It's hilarious
while you're all there.
I especially like the part
where Fox went back
to ask the guy
who punched me
in the face on tape
where I,
if he had seen me lately,
which if you don't know,
if you, the viewer,
don't know what I'm referring to,
there's video of me
getting punched in the face.
We've talked about it
on previous shows,
so we're not going
to get into it,
but you can see the video.
It is me getting
punched in the face
by a person
that I provoked
in Orlando.
You can see it.
The proof does live
in this pudding.
Uh, yeah,
whatever.
timefortheshow.punch.fid
slash face
and, uh,
.htm.
Yeah.
Just do that
three times.
But Dr. Cosmack said
you have to type that
URL in three times.
You can't just type it in once.
You have to type that
in three times.
See, that's another
inside joke
that none of the viewers
are going to get.
But,
you know,
it's okay
because this isn't
really a show.
This is the end
of what some people
might call a show,
but what is actually
a live two-hour
production meeting
where we attempt
on every episode
to come up with
all of the content
for the next episode.
And then, of course,
on the next episode
we do the same thing.
And I think we've done
a pretty good job
of that so far.
We're just wrapping it up.
At this point,
we're just holding
the lighter
onto the plastic skin
that is wrapping
the joke up
for shipping.
And we're just holding
the lighter on the ends
to singe them off
and protect
this perfectly crafted joke
that you, the viewer,
were fortunate enough
to be with us
while we manufactured it.
You got to see
how the hot dog was made.
The plastic side.
As the lawsuit
was developed
and the evidence gathered
for Fid's impending
judicial nightmare,
you were there.
You will be able to tell
your grandchildren.
a defenseless woman,
you were there.
Grandpa!
You might be called
to this on the bite marks
of an oxtail.
Tell me again
about the time,
Grandpa,
when you were there
for that one episode
of Time for the Show.
And Argus Fox
was worried
and he looked for you
with the corndog lady
and that homeless man
that punched you.
Did they?
Tell that story,
Grandpa Fid.
Did they?
Pease.
No, don't tell that story,
Grandpa Fid.
Tell that one about
that NASA Laura.
You're really not going
to let me off the hook,
Pease.
He's got you
by the really thing.
You've got one big more minute.
I've got six more minutes.
I'm not going to,
I'm never going to bring up
anything, you know.
That makes good radio.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not saying anything
on the radio ever again.
Well, what do we do?
I mean, look,
here it is.
It's time for the show.
We've got five minutes
left in the show.
And what have we done?
Other than...
Let's do it NASA style.
We have T minus five minutes
this show.
God damn it.
You know,
if you weren't so funny,
you would be a asshole.
I don't know.
You know that, Pease.
But, but,
you're funny
and you're handsome.
I'm sorry.
And so those two things
totally preclude you
from me.
I'm sorry.
I can't stay mad
at your handsome face
and your funny brain.
I just can't.
No.
Wow.
I think we've had
a real breakthrough here.
Reverend Cosworth.
I realize that
my therapeutic protocols
are sometimes experimental,
but, you know,
they seem to be really
having an effect here.
For those who are just tuning in,
Reverend Cashloth
is my therapist.
So,
what's your evaluation, doctor?
Dr. Reverend...
Dr. Reverend Cashloth,
what is your...
Well, I would say that,
you know,
you're suffering from
an interesting
by proxy fixation
in that
Pease continues to be fixated
on discussing
the lawyer lady.
Right.
But that's actually
your prediction.
That's the projection
of your fascination with her.
Oh, I love that word.
On to Pease,
which he then expresses back to you.
And I reflect it back
outward to the world.
So, obviously,
the doctor's quite
correct.
And the only logical conclusion
is you've got to go back
for adventure number two.
Well, hold on.
I want to hear the rest
of Dr. Reverend Cashloth's evaluation.
Oh, no.
That's just cycle Bible.
Well, I, you know,
I do recommend, you know,
exposure therapy.
Exposure therapy.
Pease, please.
This is my personal
therapy session
with my doctor.
I think he's giving you
good advice.
Do you mind?
I know, but I, you know,
this is important.
I do feel that we're going
to have to proceed,
you know, next session
as our time together
this evening has run out.
But, of course,
I will be sending you a bill.
And as usual,
I do accept payments
only in Bitcoin.
Out of time!
Yeah.
I love running out of time
at the therapist.
You know,
you know what's amazing
is how they never seem
to ever glance at a clock,
but they always know
when it's 42 minutes
into the hour session
because 42...
They have a special
psychologist butt plug
that vibrates at 42 minutes.
So that's how they know.
Don't be fooled.
Well, Reverend Pease,
you were a psych tech.
Don't give away.
Don't give away my secrets, Pease.
Yeah, come on.
It's live radio, dude.
Come on, man.
Every week with you, Pease.
Every week.
I don't know.
I don't know what's the matter with you.
And yet you're so good.
I'm sorry I did a bad show, guys.
You're so good and you're so...
You're so bad.
I'm sorry I didn't do
a very good show tonight.
You're so good, man.
You're so...
Well, you know,
we used to have a tradition here
on time for the show
that I'm going to bring back right now.
I'm sorry.
Because it is 1158 Eastern Daylight Time.
It's done.
The show ends at midnight
and we used to do a thing
where Pease would have
an obligatory apology
that he would make
that we would use to end the show.
So, Reverend Sick Pease Sick.
I'm sorry.
We're going to end the show
and before we get to your apology,
Reverend Pease,
before we get to that,
I just want to say
that I'm Fid Chuli
and the engineer next to me
that you've been hearing
from time to time
is Argus Q. Fox
and we're broadcasting
from Hypercube Laboratories
in the former Spanish Empire.
You're Reverend Pease.
Reverend Couchloth,
my personal therapist,
was kind enough to join us.
Thank you, Reverend Couchloth.
Is there anything you want to plug?
Well, we're going to end the show
and we're wrapping it up, buddy.
Anything you want to get out there?
Anything you want to plug up?
Anything I want to plug?
No, just my 42-minute cycling butt plug there.
I think that'll do.
All right.
Well, your check is in the mail.
In the mail.
Now, I accept Dogecoin.
Dogecoin is the future.
Wow.
I'm going to have to make
some conversions really quickly.
Yeah, how many Dobscoins
go into a Dogecoin now?
One billion.
I'm a Dobscoin millionaire.
I'm a millionaire.
How many you got?
You got a million of them?
I've got over a million.
I've got almost two million Dobscoins.
Yeah.
All right.
I don't know how many I've got.
I don't have any of that.
Not as many as me, probably.
Pease, we're up against the clock here.
Send me your Dobscoins.
I want them.
So, Pease, you got your apology chambered or what?
Okay, so for all the aforementioned people,
this is time for the show.
You're listening to freethinkradio.com.
That's what you're hearing this on,
even if it's a podcast.
And to close the show,
here is Reverend Pease with his apology.
So, everybody, I'm super sorry.
Wait, hold on, Reverend Pease.
I have to tie my shoe.
Hold on.
I'm sorry that we spent a lot of time talking about it.
And then when we went in segues into the patches
for DocFox and the right angles,
I probably should have been more fluid and verbose then.
And then we talked a lot about FIDS,
and I'm sorry that I went on so long about that.
And I'm sorry that so many things on the show
were awesome and funny,
and that FID didn't see the humor in it,
but still, it was probably the best show we ever did.
I'm sorry to the homeless guy who Argus bothered yesterday
when he asked where FID was.
The guy said, you get out of here or I'll punch you too.
Corn dog, you know, I'm not gonna punch you.
The lady didn't know where FID was,
but she did seem more receptive to seeing FID again
than the other guy.
And of course, I'm sorry that the show's drawn to a close
because except for Monday nights,
the only thing you have to look to is Tuesday nights at 10
when you have Share a Slice,
and Thursday nights at 10 when you have
Anti-Social Engineering,
all here on freethinkradio.com,
your entertainment vortex.
See you guys next week.
Man, that was such a good close piece.
Such a good close that I'm gonna start saying stuff
and ruin it for you, you know?
Like, because there's no fun kicking down a sandcastle
that's poorly built.
The fun is kicking down a sandcastle
that's really well-crafted.
And Reverend Pease, goddammit,
you were just a sparkling, sparkling fucking comet of radio.
You know that, my boy?
I'm shining on like a diamond.
We're already over time,
and I just can't stop.
Over time?
Yeah, we're done.
Yeah, we're cutting into the other thing,
but it's the playlist.
Well, it...
What do you have to say?
Keep listening.
This is it.
We're done.
Keep listening to Freethink Radio
for the old-time radio show.
If you like old-time radio broadcasts,
stay tuned,
because we're going out right now.
The name of the show is Time for the Show.
We'll see you next Monday at 10.
Love you, bye.
Bye.
I like show.
So, you don't want to do the show anymore?
You all sad?
No more show?
If Pease get to you...
Are you talking to me?
I'm talking to you!
Oh, no, I thought...
We were just trying to hit the midnight.
Did Pease get to you?
Are you all angry?
Pease, why'd you piss him off?
I didn't piss him off, did I?
I'm sorry, dude.
Pease, that was not cool, man!
That was not cool!
What the hell was that?
You know what?
Never again!
Oh, this is so funny.
I just can't imagine what somebody could do
to turn Fit off, though.
Oh, this is...
This is too crazy for me.
I gotta get out of here.
Why?
I think...
I thought it was a good show.
No, because Fit has a high talk.
I thought it was a great show.
I think it was the best show ever.
I thought it was a good one.
It's always the best show ever.
We were able to stretch Blind Eye out for 30 minutes.
Which we never actually did.
I didn't do mine.
Fit never did one.
Who did one?
Pease and Fox?
Yeah, I got through mine,
and Count Sloth expanded on it pretty well.
They talk...
I wouldn't grab a cigarette.
I was listening on the intercoms.
Wait, Count Sloth, are you still there?
No.
Okay, never mind, then.
He's out of here.
Never mind.
He left.
Great, we can talk shit about him now.
I hate that guy.
Oh, you're there?
Oh.
He's still here.
Never mind about that thing.
I just...
I was...
I was kidding.
Well, I guess we'll have to
get our legal work done somewhere else.
Yeah.
I suppose so.
Thanks for making things.
It's harder for us, Fit.
Oh, hey, Count Sloth.
Thanks for coming on the show.
You're great.
Yeah, thanks, dude.
Yeah, thanks a bunch.
Yeah, I'm still kind of, like,
new to the whole thing,
but I appreciate the chance to get out there
and, you know, try to get it a little weird.
Shoot, we've had...
We've had people jump on,
and it's been like...
They wanted to come on and, like,
do internet radio,
and some of them, they freeze up.
They don't know what to do,
so you're able to jump in,
and you got the funny joke-a-ha times.
And you're on the Patreon?
Yeah, yeah, and I didn't know.
I actually didn't know
I would get an autographed portrait of Muhammad
for $9.11, so...
You sure the hell still can?
I'm going to lock that up soon.
I'm going to move it up to $19.11.
Well, that's how...
In Europe, they put the day first,
and then the month,
so that's 11-9.
Extra show, right.
But, yeah, a couple of our Patreons
have already got their autographed self-portrait
of the Prophet Muhammad,
because Muhammad's the only one
who's allowed to draw Muhammad.
So, Dr. Fox will draw you...
Actually, he already has
an autographed self-portrait
of the Prophet Muhammad.
So, Dr. Fox,
The last...
Is this part of the show cost extra?
Which part?
I don't know.
You'd have to ask Drugs.
He's listening.
We're not on the show.
The show's over.
The show's still going on.
It's beautiful.
I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure this is connected.
Is it?
I don't know.
Drew just said,
I haven't gotten my drawing.
Hmm.
Well, yeah, he hasn't gotten his drawing yet.
It's out.
I don't know.
You'd have to ask Drugs.
He's listening.
We're not on the show.
The show...
Yeah, nobody...
The show's still going on.
It's pretty beautiful.
He hasn't gotten his, but...
Is it?
He's gonna get his,
and you're gonna...
I don't know.
Drew just said,
I haven't gotten my...
I'm gonna get mine.
Yes.
No, we're not broadcasting.
No, wait.
I don't know.
The show's over, everybody.
I don't know what...
It's fine.
Well, everybody just relax, please.
Everybody relax.
We need to stay calm here, okay?
If things...
The show's still on,
then it's not gonna be good for any of us, okay?
So I need everybody to just relax.
I can assure you that.
Are there life vests?
I clicked, you know,
I clicked record when we started the show.
I'm pretty sure I turned it off at the end.
The music's done.
No, it's still...
We're still on the show, dude.
Okay?
We're heading towards the iceberg.
Stop clinging to your beliefs
that there's some kind of show out there.
You're just being desperate.
Forget it.
Okay?
For the...
If anybody of you think we're still broadcasting
or still recording,
you're just being desperate.
You're clinging to some belief
that somebody out there
is still listening to.
And guess what?
Nobody's listening.
That's what you need to come to terms with.
Actually...
Okay?
Nobody's listening.
Actually, I'm getting a DM
from NASA's legal department right now.
It's only a two-hour show.
Oh, my God.
They are pissed at FID.
The whole legal department?
That's Salvation and Infotation
at www.subgenius.com
Or, got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 807
Glen Rose, Texas
Dear It's Time for the Show,
as a legal representative,
NASA's legal team...
Yeah.
Whatever.
Legal...
I think that P's and Argus
have done a wonderful job
explaining and keeping
the maintenance of the show going.
Whereas, we now order and demand
that FID truly refrain
from mentioning any aspect
or team member
of the NASA legal department.
P's and Argus may mention it
as much as they like.
But...
FID may not.
Oh, shit.
Whoa.
Stein, NASA's lawyer.
That made me laugh.
I get two.
That's how the whole world
is just lined up.
They're waiting for FID, Julie,
to have just a moment to occur.
And they want...
What they really, really want
is to just get that one thing
that they're...
Yeah.
Like when he peed in the microphone.
You stop that.
And that was great.
That was good.
But he got punched in the face.
Oh.
He got...
I was there
when he got punched in the face.
I was filming it.
I feel like...
We could make you feel like
you were there.
I've got a...
I was looking at some of this crazy,
like,
free plug-ins
to run After Effects
and you can make videos
360 degrees.
So stuff that you can put on
and watch through like an Android...
Android...
Cardboard
or an iPhone...
whatever.
And I'm gonna see if I can make
like a 360 version
of FID getting punched
and I'll do a surround sound mix
of the slapping in his face.
Slap.
I only wanted a piece of the corndog.
Did I deserve these diamonds?
Yeah, the blood was coming from...
I can't remember if it was
on the outside of his nose
or from the inside.
He had like a...
a scrape,
but I think he got that
when he...
No, it was from my nose.
From your nose?
Yeah.
And I'll do a surround sound.
What did that dirty hippie thing
giving you that flyer
was gonna do?
What?
At the id,
it's like,
I'm bleeding you guys
like you're bleeding dude
and then he gives them a...
Yeah, he had an advertiser
for like free parking
at City Walk.
Here's a really hard
piece of paper
to wipe your blood up with.
Here's a piece of feeder paper
from my pocket.
It's like somebody
giving you cardboard
to staunch your wound with.
Oh no,
I wish like somebody
with a tampon
had run up.
It's not a...
It's pretty absorbent, dude.
Bite off the...
It just goes back once.
It's not a time.
But no,
I think I set the video
back to private.
I gotta blur
the guy's face out,
you know.
Why?
You assaulted somebody.
He assaulted somebody.
Let him sue you.
Well, we're gonna try
and make money
off of Fid getting his...
his nose broken.
So, um...
Uh,
because I don't have
the guy's consent
to be in the video...
Fid has...
Fid did have the guy's
consent to get punched.
I say when you punch
somebody in a public place
and he gets posted
on the internet,
you don't gotta blur
the person's face out.
They committed assault.
They deserved it.
If I'm gonna monetize
the video I do.
Have you consulted
with Josh?
with Tosh Dono?
All of the religions
apocalyptic
have happened.
Different people.
And the leading
conclusion I can get
is just blur the face.
You guys don't know.
That's it.
That's all we gotta do.
We just go up
He's running in the face.
He's stupid.
I mean, if you want to leave the face in the face, you can, but you have to charge him.
Did Fitt's friend from NASA on the legal department give you that advice?
Like, hey, will you sign a consent letter?
No, no, no.
Charge him.
Charge him with the assault, and then it becomes evidence.
Then it's evidence, and then you can use it for nothing.
I don't know.
Every religion.
Ask Fitt's girlfriend.
All of their apocalypse.
Fitt, are you guys going to go snuggle again?
Same time.
Okay.
I got to go.
I got to snuggle date.
You want to hear this?
They were all right.
The apocalypse happened, everybody.
Every religion's apocalypse has already happened.
I would.
And it happened over two decades ago.
Fine.
You're all waiting for when the world is going to end.
The world's already ended.
We've been living after the end time.
We've been living for a long time now.
And she's like, tell me I'm pretty.
And he goes, you're pretty.
And then she looks at me and she goes, do you think we figured it out?
And I'm like, I'm not going to answer that.
Do you think that we're crazy?
And Fitt's like, you don't know what we figured out.
Do you think that she hung out with Fitt?
But you're not going to laugh at us.
When we're together.
When we're the only ones that can help you.
Do you think that she spent all that time with Fitt just to spite you?
You're not going to laugh at us.
When we're the only ones in the lifeboat.
I pointed to the ring on my phone.
To be able to get you out of the thing that you laughed at us.
That was saying the whole time was true.
Their nest of sin.
Go ahead.
Say who you are now.
And you can remember.
And we can remember.
Where's my phone?
Hold on, peas.
I'm going to get the dirt.
Where's Dr. Fox's phone?
Guess what?
You've got bigger problems to worry about, everybody.
We've got bigger problems to worry about, everybody.
You know what's happened in the last 20 years?
The same thing that's happened in the 20 years previous to it.
Did he get his phone?
Because we've got dirt with Fitt.
Why do you think everything today is a reboot?
He's searching it right now.
We're still on the radio, which is kind of off.
I think that's going to be gone.
Why do you think everything today is a reboot?
Did they just cut me off?
Of something.
From days past, the world has ended.
All of the world's religions were correct.
He's so smooth.
Look at the moves, Fitt.
The subgenius to Christianity.
You are making it happen.
To Hinduism.
All.
Yeah, I see it.
He is making it happen.
All of the world's religions ever invented.
Don't show anybody.
Their concurrence of the apocalypse converged on the same date.
Did you get to sit on those, Fitt?
The apocalypse of all of the world's religions converged on the same date.
You are on the air, dude.
Just so you know.
This whole 20 minutes has been on the air.
No, my mic's not working.
Hello?
That date.
That date was predicted correctly.
The date was predicted correctly.
That date was.
Oh, it's turned off.
All of the world's religions went to hell.
You know, I'm gonna call bullshit.
I don't see a video game or TV anywhere around those sex toys.
The date of the apocalypse was only predicted correctly.
A video game?
Yeah.
Which sex toys do you use?
Were they?
Well, I can't discuss it now.
You said be quiet.
That religion was the church of the subgenius.
No, I said don't show anybody.
Don't show it.
Oh, then I won't show anybody.
There we go.
Oh, right there in the back.
Only the subgenius.
The church of the subgenius predicted the correct date of the apocalypse.
Do you see the big silver one?
The only thing the big silver one was incorrect about was that the conspiracy was wrong about
the calendar.
The wedge.
So even though they were mad that the date of the apocalypse was 25th 1998.
Oh, she's got one of those love pillows that you hear about on Howard Stern.
Is that the one?
The one that you turn the knob and it like vibrates?
No, it's got like a wedge shape and you put it up the hips or something and it supposedly
positions the squishy part to where you can get right at that G spot.
Oh, are you guys talking about sex wedge?
Yeah, there you go.
Is there a commercial for sex wedge?
Hold on.
There is now.
They got the factory for those like up the road from my place.
Do you like to bang lawyers from NASA like-
The apocalypse.
Of every world religion did in fact occur.
Do you like oxtails and vodka?
1998.
Do you like oxtails and vodka and Pokemon?
Hypercube laboratories.
You need to read Finchley's new book on how to score lawyer chicks from NASA to hear
That, July 5th 1998, was in fact the convergence of the apocalypse of the world.
There is a picture of every world religion ever invented or conceived or possibly conceived.
So did she really like your drama?
And then we are now living in the post-apocalyptic world side of every major religion.
Is he crying?
This means that since every world religion apocalypse has occurred-
I would say she's a real live sexy girl but this picture-
There is a picture of every world religion.
Doesn't really tell me if she's actually alive.
The wedge is another great contributor shape.
One of the things that it's most known for is oral sex.
Cunnilingus in particular.
It is a serving platter for the genitals.
Another great use for it is actually elevating the woman's hips so that you can hit different angles and deeper penetration.
With a shallower penetration you can actually get the G-spot.
And a deeper penetration-
My cat's fighting a very large vinyl cow.
You can use it to lay over for anal and analingus.
Another great feature of the wedge is the ability to improve your endurance.
You can actually stay on this in positions for longer periods of time.
With something like the wedge you're perfectly supported, very comfortable and you can stay in that for a long time.
You can use it in conjunction with any of the other Liberator products.
Specifically the ramp.
The ramp with the wedge.
The wedge is a very good combination.
Be really inspired to try new things and have lots of fun together.
If you have money for a game leading people to think that X-Day hadn't happened yet, wouldn't you continue to do it?
Well it has.
When it comes to the penis, the size and shape matter.
There are so many different sizes and shapes and techniques and preferences that it's really hard to say.
It's absolutely a good and a bad of every shape and size.
And here are a couple of the most important ones.
The most important one is by time control.
We have to get back to that date.
That happened a while ago.
We're living in the aftermath.
That's right.
Everybody's still waiting for the ship to hit the fan.
And you know where all these people live?
You know where everybody who's waiting for the ship to hit the fan lives?
They live in shit fan hitville.
Because it's happened.
It's spread all over the place.
Just piles and piles.
Spreadship.
And there's those that'll tell you, no just look around.
I do have the gas station.
And the...
I buy a bag of chips.
Or I can go and get my hair cut.
You know.
I can go down to the bar and buy some drinks.
Yeah, society's totally intact.
Just look at this.
I pay taxes.
You know.
I write things down on paper and put it in the mailbox.
And I get things back in the mailbox.
Things written down on paper back to me.
You know.
I go to the store and I buy something.
And I get a piece of paper with like a lot of numbers on it.
And like a date and a time.
And it's the date and the time that I did it.
And so there's that.
And then I have these like...
I have like a...
I have a piece...
I have this like plastic thing in my pocket.
And it's got my face on it.
And it's got all kinds of assignments.
They're really special to me.
And even like computer code on the back of it.
That a computer can read.
And that's special to me too.
And they can do that.
And they know who I am.
Right?
So it's intact.
Everything's working.
It's gotta work.
I...
The light turns red.
I stop and go.
And so does everybody else.
And as we're stopping and the light's green.
And all the people are going on the other side.
So it can't just be me.
Right?
I can't...
I'm not crazy.
I mean look it.
Everybody else is doing it.
Look at that.
They're...
I see the lights.
And they see the lights.
And we both...
And we get home safe.
Oh.
We're...
We're guaranteed the safety.
From...
That...
That obedience.
Oh.
The sweet, sweet milk of obedience.
I'm so safe.
I have my property.
That's mine.
And uh...
And I respect other people's property.
That's theirs.
I respect their property.
This is...
In the...
They're going...
Those red and...
Those red lights are gonna come back.
They're gonna come back a lot.
My toaster...
My toaster's gotta work by the minute.
My microwave's only got red light on it.
And I put...
Metal in it.
Don't...
I gave my...
I gave my cat braces.
Because his...
Because his teeth weren't quite straight.
And I put him in the microwave and the red light came on.
That's when they took me somewhere.
Somewhere bad.
The following reports of weather temperature and wind were made at 11 AM.
They made me...
DFW Airport.
Listen to...
Mostly sunny.
Test patterns.
91.
2.68.
They made me listen to emergency broadcast test patterns.
With south at eight.
Pressure 30.04.
They were trying to work out...
Fort Worth region.
Sunny.
I have my implant.
South at five.
They were trying to find the resonant frequency.
Mostly sunny.
91.
South at six.
They found it.
Mostly sunny.
89.
It's over.
There's nothing I can do for you now.
Mostly sunny.
Southwest at six.
There's nothing I can do for you now.
89.
South at six.
You better enjoy yourself.
South at seven.
What are you doing?
You're listening to me?
Alright.
I got a front row seat.
I believe.
Come on.
Mostly sunny.
89.
South at five.
Waco.
Sunny.
87.
Variable at three.
Tower.
Sunny.
87.
Variable at five.
Once again at 11 AM.
Mostly sunny.
That's right, put that tie on. It's a necktie. It's supposed to keep your shirt around your neck.
But you never had trouble keeping your shirt around your neck, did you?
It always just kind of stayed around there whether you had a tie on.
Huh. So why the necktie?
Make sure you get it nice and tight.
Nice and tight.
The heck? Here, let me show you how to do it.
I want to show you how to do it and then you can do it that way for the rest of your life.
It's the way I was shown how to do it.
That's how you know it's the right way.
You can just take it easy.
Don't feel too bad if you don't get it right.
Don't feel too bad.
Just feel a little bit bad.
That's all it takes.
Just a little bit.
Strong next.
Right.
You got something you got.
Oh my God.
Sorry.
Don't wanna talk about it.
So why I had to do it myself?
And why did you do this?
Oh, it was your little time- vrios of precepts.
Okay.
For me...
The program is different.
You were doing better than the gyula, but you just keep it nice and tight until you say so.
Do I have your attention yet?
Because it's not the people that are trying to get your attention that you need to worry about.
No, I mean, they might be full of shit.
And most of them are.
But they're not the ones that you need to worry about.
It's the people that aren't trying to get your attention.
Why is that true?
Because it sounds kind of cool.
You know?
That's pretty much it.
I mean, go ahead.
Try.
Try it out.
Right now, I want you to put on headphones so I can talk to you.
And I want you to put on headphones and I want you to walk outside.
And I want you to do what I just told you to do, which is actively, actively avoid anybody who is not trying to get your attention.
And I want you to do that aggressively and vigorously.
I want you to vigorously and abstrusively and obstinately and slapmacklify avoid anybody who is not trying to get your attention as hard as you can, viewer.
I'm going to stay with you while you do it.
We're going to do it live.
Because, I don't know, I think we're, we might be live.
Yeah, I guess we're live.
All right.
Breathing radio.
I'm with you.
I feel you.
Yes.
This is a very big moment for you, viewer.
This is a turning point in your evolution, viewer.
This is the turning point.
This is the fulcrum of your evolution.
Now run.
The direction you're currently facing, just run.
As fast as you can.
And clap.
Run and clap.
And sing.
The national anthem of Bangladesh.
And you better clap to the beat and sing that nerf word.
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Is it the question that please ask?
Oh, my god.
To put some music into that and I was already thinking about what I wanted.
I didn't see the Keshi, you're gonna go and yep.
So I need something like as you can see.
Can I ask you a question now?
Just then.
What she would say and when and if she asked, could you please do the same thing?
Oh, look at you.
You just came back.
You're all cut up.
I got lots of band-aids.
You know what they are?
All I have is the children's band-aids that has the Tiny Toons characters on them.
Hold on for a second while I go get them.
Clip-clop, clip-clop, footsteps, footsteps, footsteps, footsteps, footsteps.
Door opening.
Rustling, rustling.
Door closing.
Footsteps getting closer, footsteps getting closer, footsteps getting closer, footsteps getting closer.
Oh, here's the box of Looney Tunes band-aids that I just told you about a couple seconds ago.
Oh, look at that.
There aren't any of them in there.
That must have been my son.
You know, he likes to use the band-aids because they have his favorite characters on them.
And even though he doesn't have cuts, he just likes to stick them on.
Okay?
So that's why I can't treat your wounds.
And that's why you're going to die on my doorstep.
Because my son likes Tiny Toons adventures.
You can blame the people that made that show for your death right now in your dying breaths.
I'll shut up if you want to say it because I know you don't have that much longer to go.
I'm going to hold the microphone up to your face.
And allow you to proclaim your dying breaths of hating my son and the creators of Tiny Toons adventures concurrently for that show being good.
Here you go, your dying breaths, sir.
Here you go.
Continuing the flight.
Did you know
that all of the clay
that was made to animate Gumby
was made from actual Gumby's?
Eww!
That's why I present to you
my line of vegan Gumby's.
Yes.
The only people
that we use
to make our Gumby's
for Benjamin Franklin.
That's right.
It's a limited edition.
All of the clay
that we use to make our Gumby characters
was made from Benjamin Franklin's
remains.
Shh!
Don't tell anybody.
I'm not saying
you shouldn't smoke it,
but...
Yeah.
You're a grown-ass man.
I'm a grown-ass man.
All right!
I'm gonna blow you out of the river!
This boy in class.
Meat and eggs help the body grow
and make it strong.
Meat is good for you.
And there's many kinds.
There's beef.
There's pork and ham.
There's lamb.
Fish is good.
And so is chicken and other poultry.
An egg a day is good for you, too.
Boiled, fried, scrambled, poached, or any way.
Meats and eggs are high in protein, which helps build red blood and strong muscles.
The fourth finger, pointing the way to health, represents vegetables.
And here Ralph thinks of several children in this class, for there are many kinds of vegetables.
Potatoes, for instance, are an energy food.
And baked potatoes, eaten with their skins in butter or margarine, have lots of vitamins and minerals, too.
When it comes to green and yellow vegetables, Ralph thinks of Wendy, the prettiest girl in the class.
And there are so many different kinds.
Green vegetables.
Vegetables like string beans, asparagus, and broccoli.
There are salad vegetables like lettuce.
Many others like celery, radishes, and carrots.
Carrots are good, too.
And so is squash and other yellow vegetables like rutabaga.
Cauliflower and cabbage are good, too.
Yes, there are hundreds of wonderful vegetables.
The important thing is that all kinds of vegetables are good for you, whether they're raw or cooked.
They're important for good health.
Lots of energy and health.
Clear skin and bright eyes.
Shining, gleaming hair.
And above all, for that wonderful sense of feeling.
The last finger represents fruit.
And there are two kinds.
Some are especially rich in vitamin C and help ward off some of the diseases that keep you there.
They help cuts and bruises heal faster, too.
Foods with lots of vitamin C in them include orange juice, grapefruit, strawberries, melons, and of course, whole oranges.
Certainly rich in different things.
Certain vegetables like tomatoes and raw cabbage are also rich in vitamin C.
You should have a vitamin C food every day.
every day. The body isn't stored in the body very long. Finally, they're the fruits we eat for
dessert. Wonderful fruits like apples, bananas, peaches, pears, plums, grapes, and many others.
Nuts make a good dessert too. They're rich in energy, proteins, vitamins, and minerals.
And now, as Ralph thinks about it, he realizes that each of the children he admires depend on
all the food. And not on just one food. George is strong, Wendy is pretty,
Linda has a bright smile, and Kenneth has lots of pets. Not because of any one food that they eat,
but because they eat some of all kinds of food. For it takes five fingers to point the way to
healthful eating habits.
Ralph goes over to his mom.
Every day, he eats bread and butter, milk and cheese, meat and eggs, vegetables, fruits, and a vitamin C food.
Thinking about all this food has made him hungry. He has a candy bar around as usual, but now Ralph has a better idea of why he shouldn't
let candy and sweets substitute for other foods.
Sweets don't have any flavor.
the proteins, the vitamins, or the minerals, the bodybuilding qualities of other foods.
And so, for the next few months, Ralph really worked at learning to eat all kinds of foods.
Ralph, would you like some tea?
Yeah, yeah. Well, okay.
Well, what happened to you?
He'd sample everything that was served to him.
And even if it didn't happen to be a food that he preferred, he'd eat some of it anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
Night, he'd go over the five food groups and see how he had done that day.
After a month or two of this, Ralph suddenly realized that a slow change had taken place without his noticing it.
He found that eating it became...
Become fun.
What's more, his health was better, and he had more pets.
He had more fun than he used to, and more friends.
Everything still works.
And all because he had learned to eat by counting his foods on his feed.
Everything is okay.
Everything still works.
Everything still works...
Everything's still okay!
I can go outside right now and choose one business or choose the other.
Everything's okay.
My money's just as good at one place as it is somewhere else.
That must mean that the system is intact.
Why, there's even public services.
There's a fire department, police department, hospitals and schools and I mean all kinds
of things and even parks and fun things, you know?
And there's a justice system.
Yeah.
It's just that, you know, gives them what's coming to them and makes sure that people
mind their reverend P's and reverend Q's.
So the system, it must be intact, right?
Everything, it has to be intact.
I mean, look at that.
It's all working.
There's an economy.
There's nations.
There's...
There's international relations between all these nations that are all doing things their
all own way and it...
So it must be working, right?
This couldn't be.
This couldn't...
This is the world.
This is...
We're at the peak.
This is the best things I've ever been, right?
It has to be, right?
Well, if it has to be...
If it has to be, everybody, if it must be, if it has to be, if there's no other way to
explain it, then it obviously isn't.
It's obviously a cell.
Because nothing that is real is obvious.
The only things that are real, that are that too good to be true?
What's that old saying?
About things that are too good to be true?
Well, there's someone here to tell you.
That's right.
Are you an inspiration?
And what's the thing about all the discoveries that have always been made?
All of the things that have left humankind forward.
All of the things that have propelled our knowledge throughout the ages.
They weren't things that were obvious.
They were things that had to be discovered.
Would you follow me, please?
And through rigorous observation and experimentation, we came up with some truths.
This obvious lie that society is intact, isn't it getting old for you?
Isn't it day after day?
Isn't there something about you that just is kind of getting tired of it?
We don't have it.
Because I got tired of it a long time ago.
And I know there's a lot of you out there that are pretty tired of it.
And you're not exactly just tired of it.
You kind of want it to go away.
You know what I mean?
And you kind of wish somebody would, you know, do something about it.
But you're not.
You're not going to get to the point where somebody else would.
I think I've known that for a long time.
I want to know what happened to the planet.
Well, then you, the viewer, and I are kindred spirits.
Because we, here at Hypercube Laboratories, have been looking into this issue for a little
while.
We've been doing a little bit of checking, double-checking, and poking around.
around this and that
and
at this point
it's undeniable that what I've
been trying to tell you
this whole time is true.
This is the post-apocalyptic
world. All of the
world's religions
were right.
The only religion
that was right about the date was the church
of the subgenius.
It just so happened to be
July 5th
1998. That's when
it happened. Yeah, I know
a lot of you that are listening are subgeniuses
and you paid your money for that saucer
ride. Guess what?
Oh!
Ouch! Didn't get
the saucer ride. Wow!
Imagine that!
You bought a
spaceship ride
from a salesman
for $30
and you
got ripped off?
Wow!
I'm shocked!
I'm shocked
that the salesman that sold you
the $30 ride
the $30 spaceship ride
ripped you off.
Man!
I don't blame you for not seeing
that one coming a mile away.
But guess what? You did pay for it
and guess what? That was a legal
contract and guess what?
Even though
apocalypse has come.
And gone. And uh
we can get into about
the post-apocalyptic times
that we're living in later.
But even though that has
all happened
there's still a way out.
That's a binding contract.
If you
could like, let's just say
what if you could go
back in time to the
apocalypse?
Because you did miss it. But you did
pay for it.
And that payment's
still on record. If you could go back
in time and uh
to July 5th, 1998
redeem that ticket
you could get on that saucer. What if I told
you that um
maybe I knew a way to get you back
there.
I don't know.
Something you'd be interested
in?
Hey!
Get out of here! No!
Stop!