The Hour of Slack!
Here's something that you should know
Tune us in on the radio, now
We got charisma, we got style
Well, people will make you feel better for a while
Put your hands, put your hands on the radio
Family doctors say you're just fine
But you feel so down all the time
Well, people will make you feel better for a while
Well, people, you don't have to worry
The drop is a lie
Send your money in on the double
Don't worry, it's deductible
Well, people, you can forget your sins
Forget your troubles
Put your hands, put your hands on the radio
If you're feeling lonely and confused
And you don't know
What you're to do
And there's no candle left to burn
And you don't know which way to turn
We can help you out
Music plays
Put your hands, put your hands on the radio
Sunny morning and you're feeling low
You hurt all over and you're moving so well
People, here's something that you should know
Tune us in on the radio dice
We got charisma
...but we got style
People will make you feel bitter for a while
Put your hands, put your hands on the radios
To be continued...
I thought that was Dave
when I heard her
first word that...
No one knows I'm gone.
Yeah.
It does.
After X-Day,
no one knows you're gone.
Too many Marlboros.
That guy sounded like that
when he was in his early 20s.
He probably sounded like that
when he was 12.
No, seriously.
Tom Waits was doing this when...
I mean, he sounded like
an old cigarette-ravaged bar guy
when he was...
Right.
When he was too young to be one.
He was just faking it.
But he fakes it great.
Oh, he was part of that
old Greenwich Village,
you know,
hip daddy-o crowd.
Beatniks, man.
Beat.
Yeah, except that he was
too young for it.
Right.
He's just carrying on
the tradition,
you might say.
Right.
Oh, yes.
Tom Waits for no one.
Yeah.
Oh, paper for me.
ictions.
No.
He
He was your
homosexual
The temperatures
You know, into other
Ali's Clean Home to learn
dat
Sniper Club. Don't talk about Sniper Club.
Right.
Anyone who talks about Sniper Club gets sniped.
The faces in the night looking into the anti-mirror of jazz.
There is no Sniper Club.
Insistent instinct.
Get with the end times, man.
Oh, man, hey, I have a whole theory about this stuff.
And it might even go right into the Taliban thing.
You know, everyone thinks that it was the Al-Qaeda who flew the things in the planes.
All right.
Anthrax.
Snipers.
You know, all kinds of internal stuff like that going on.
I think the South is rising again.
I think it's the Confederacy.
I thought you were going to say our own government.
It's not the Al-Qaeda.
The sleeping giant has arisen.
It's not the Taliban.
It's the Confederacy.
I'm completely convinced of it.
They're slagging back, though.
They know not to say anything.
Hey, I got my bumper sticker that says forget hell.
Because we all want to forget hell.
Slavery is coming back.
We want to go to a more sure, better place.
I think it's the Confederacy.
I'm convinced.
Now we'll have delicious bilingual slavery.
We won't have to worry about slaving other pack of woods like ourselves.
Well, I really think it's because...
Everything, including trees, can be enslaved.
Northerners are just kind of pissed off that, A, Southerners got to do all the walking on the moon.
What the hell are you talking about?
B, Southerners went to the movies.
And all the NASCAR races.
Southerners get to be president.
I'm not very jealous of that one.
And C, Southerners get to be the president over and over and over again.
I think you were just thinking about professional wrestling as my next jam.
You got to look at the big picture of things.
I believe it's the Confederacy.
I'm convinced of it.
Well, it is a Confederacy of dunches called the U.S. Black Covert Optional Government.
They flew a plane into Cleveland Harbor last week and nobody even knew about it.
Is that how you did that?
And the whole terrorist event was missed.
We were in a code yellow.
Why did they do that?
Not a code blue.
Huh?
Just ask me.
You need to know anything.
I mean, you know, got the insider information on everything.
Three weeks ago on Tuesday, a group of men in black arrived at your house.
Yeah, he's connected to his own synapses.
Dave's got his little radio.
Interconnected.
Ham radio.
Well, he'll be the next one that they have running around doing dog crimes.
And then that's what they do.
If you listen to what's going on, you know, who's doing that sniper thing, that gun control people, people that want gun control.
There's a gun control nut running around killing people.
It'll make it'll make guns look bad.
See, they make it look like guns.
Kill people.
Guns don't kill people.
Gun control nuts.
Rufus and Carlo Thomas kill people.
Snipers in the woods.
Kill people.
Bullets kill people.
Guns don't kill people.
It's the impact of the bullet.
Well, you got to admit, this cat is a, you know, he's a hot shot.
Whoever he is, I think they're probably, they got to be looking at military backgrounds and stuff like that.
Well, it might be five Al Qaeda terrorists or three Tim McVeigh's.
No, I think it's a nut job.
Yeah, I think it's a nut job.
I think he used to be in the military.
No doubt about that.
Did you know a lot of...
I think it's invisible hand guy or anthrax.
It's just the caliber of the gun he's using is an M6.
It's an M16.
So, he's using a caliber he's familiar with.
Hey, man, that hot guitar player that was out there at Brushwood on your birthday?
Weirdly enough, yeah.
That guy was bragged about his AK-47.
Really?
I know everybody brags about their AK-47.
One of the things he said, what he mentioned outside of his mouth was, and also still believed that civilization will fall, fall apart.
See, the survivalist still exists to date.
Well, he is a real survivalist, no doubt about it.
Well, you know.
You got your...
What's his name?
He's got some other survivalist he's going to want.
An AK-47.
A Kalashnikov assault rifle is quite a deadly and delicate asset to any group.
But he had some hot chops on the guitar, though, man.
That dude could play.
Yes, indeed, he could.
Yes, indeed.
I want to start a survivalist band with him playing guitar.
The other survivalists can't take that away from him.
You could travel around from outposts like The Postman in that movie.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
You could jam out.
We could do shows out in Wyoming.
You could get women with bear skins on them and stuff like that.
that and drink weird
homemade drinks. So do you think a year from now it's going to be like the Postman
or Omega Man or
or like Mad Max or
Thunderbird. The Stand or
Mad Max, that far.
That would be great, man.
I have to get
working on my van. I got to get it all
beefed up and put like steel grating
over the side windows. Yeah, man.
Natural born killers.
But I got that van. I could put a big
turret right on top. That would be
great. That big black van
and a big turret machine gun strapped right
on top. Automatic.
That's your investment.
An investment for
life. Your life and your
survival.
Who'll be fighting who, though? You'll be
fighting your neighbor over the latest
roach. Confederacy. Craft steak.
Yeah. Union versus the Confederacy.
Yeah. And we'll also have an east-west
division that like around St. Louis
It wasn't that long ago.
Look at these Middle Eastern
things. They can hold these grudges for
thousands of years.
These Central Europeans, they got some grudges
that go back thousands of years.
Jesus didn't do that. Yeah, Jesus did.
But nobody's got a memory like
a Smith's.
But the Southerners,
it's only been a hundred years, a little bit
more than a hundred years.
They getting ready, man.
They getting ready. I'm telling you.
The Bush family was Tories and they were
Confederate sympathizers during the war.
Don't have anything to do with Viagra, I think.
Viagra? Yeah.
But the Bush family were
Tories during the Revolutionary War
and they were sympathizers of the Antichrist
during, I mean, Confederacy
during the several, the
Dwarves, several Dwarves which we
had. And some of them expanded like
pustules and got bigger and popped.
And that was the reason. It was also
the banks and Lincoln. See, Southerners just
going to sail a barge right
up the Mississippi River.
Right up to the northern big cities.
Right up the Ohio River. Right. Park.
They're going to park a barge right by that
nuclear plant that's right down the Ohio
River. See, now all the Confederate guys
And a bunch of bales of marijuana.
That's actually what I
understand. The cash crop of the
South is now Redbud.
Mississippi Redbud.
So far it's just marijuana. But one of
these days. It'll be bootleg Leonard
Skinner tapes. Yeah.
It's a whole bunch of rebel soldiers
come jumping out from under them bales of hemp.
Well, that was a plot. Take over
New York Harbor.
The New South versus the New
North.
Remember that one?
Yeah.
I have a sawed.
Nice
$5
I'm sorry.
Everything will be alright.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Little Bottles of Booze
Barlight Beauty
That's Barlight Beauty
The dawn of man
Here we are at the dawn of man
Very soon we will be at the dusk of man
Yeah, I was going to say the dawn of man was seven and a half million years ago
Now this is more like the twilight of the aughts
Yeah
The autumn of mankind
Yes
But back at the dawn of man
That's a much more romantic time
It's not fun to look at the twilight of man
Yeah, if only we were back in the old days
When we could die of tuberculosis or an infected finger
Yeah
Or water poisoning
All waitresses were buxom and got your coffee fast
Yeah
Now wait a minute
I guess you're not going that far back in time
You're talking about the 50s?
Automobiles
No, I liked it back when you
If an automobile was coming down the opposite way of a horse
The automobile owner would by law
Have to dismantle the automobile
And hide it in the bushes
So that the horse could pass
Oh yeah?
And you also send up a rocket every 10 miles
And then wait for any traffic to pass your way
Boy, those were the days
To distance itself from it
Well, those were the horses, yeah
Boy, that sure beats traffic jams
Yeah
Man
Uh...
If only...
Back in the day
Back in the good old days
When you couldn't let the fire go out, because
Well, you just couldn't let the fire go out
You didn't know how to make another one
Think of it that way
bipeds, the ones with slightly less hair and bigger heads.
And then there was the dawn of religion itself.
What was it, the first blind caveman?
Yeah, the first nearsighted caveman who couldn't go out.
He wasn't as good with a bow and arrow spear as those beady-eyed hunters.
So he would stay back home, carving arrowheads and occasionally making up wonderful little
stories about how if they brought him just the right sort of virgins and services and
foods, then he would see that old Og's wife was cured of that cold she'd mysteriously
contracted.
And sure enough, after four or five days, after his mystic passes and special herbal
ointments, the cold would magically go away.
And if it didn't, well, the bear god was angry.
So you better bring the priest more food.
Yep, the nearsighted caveman.
But see, when the beady-eyed cavemen were gone, the nearsighted caveman could bird dog
the females, don't you see?
The nearsighted caveman, father of religion, and a number of other little nearsighted bastards.
Little nearsighted bastards.
Yeah, you notice that nearsighted bastards have taken over large portions of the world.
Sneaky.
Lazy eyes.
Yeah, they can see the fine print, see.
They may not see the big picture, but they can see the fine print.
We'll see.
Who's the richest man in the world?
The lunatic is on the grass, kids.
The guy with 20-20 vision, is that the richest man in America?
The lunatic is on the grass.
Or that nearsighted, shifty-eyed nerd.
The geek shall inherit the earth.
That was the lesson of the Devo Convention.
Mahala.
Oh, yes.
I remember those days.
You know, I've been sucking my thumb on the platform, I think, for about 13 years now.
And this is the first time anybody's ever called attention to it.
As if it didn't exist.
You know, I've been doing this weekly, you know, for the last 25 Thursdays.
And you guys...
Parenthetically would be even more accurate.
Parenthetically, I would say.
Yeah.
More as an aside.
Weekly.
Sickly.
Much like that Spanish muscle you're sporting below your box of shorts.
Yeah, when do we get paid?
Yeah, when do we get paid, Stan?
Well, we were going to call Ed.
Ed of...
Or St. St.
Stupid of St. Stupids Day in San Francisco.
Can we call his cell phone up and put him on the air?
I can, yeah.
Is it St. Stupids Day, though?
Come up and see if...
Because he would know about the conspiracy that is ruining America.
And tomorrow.
Praise Bob.
Praise him indeed.
And look at the Bob blob.
That was creative.
He has praised his day.
That was not St. Stupid.
I think that was like Pope Stupid or Bishop.
Bishop Stupid or Reverend Stupid.
That was St. Wank.
That was St. Wank from calling from Norway.
San Francisco Mime Troupe has been in town.
And they have got to be the crappiest Mime Troupe in the world.
Because they don't...
Oh, and they can't make phone calls at all.
They talk like Fireside Theater or something.
During their mimes?
Yeah, throughout their whole mime show.
They talk.
Check this out.
I'm behind a big white glass window.
They do a comedy show.
It's like a play.
It's like going to see a play.
And yet, you go expecting, oh, Mime Troupe.
I'm going to see this all stupid, boring, trite, pretentious guys in black suits with cute makeup.
Guys in black suits.
You don't get any of that.
None.
What would a wizened, gnarled old saint like Bob Dobbs think of men in black suits?
Trying to put in a call.
Uh-oh, the alarm is ringing.
Trooping around like mimes.
You know, just before I left, I heard on the news there was some kind of a plague.
A plague?
That looks like a seven to me.
So we're on plague?
Are we on time?
Or are we on actually wrong?
Are we on grizzly muzzled guitar mustache time?
Yeah, I think that's a seven or a question mark.
It is a question mark.
The spirits are foaming tonight.
You know, this is a very, very strange time of the year.
It's devil's night.
It's the time of the great vortex also.
A lot of the ancient sages and sadhus have mentioned this in their writings and also in their blitherings.
That when the moon comes out.
Okay, go ahead.
And the sun comes out.
And the sun goes down on the night of all hollows being.
Oh, great.
We'll strap the structure in our heads.
There's a robot answering the phone.
And live in a...
I'm giving...
Ah, perfect.
Yes, there.
At last.
Finally, I've done it.
Proof.
Actual proof of the existence of God.
Now, how's that going to help us, Pinkerton?
Because, Dr. A, thanks to this energy grid, I actually have God trapped right here in this small metal box.
Hey, yeah.
Now, that is a useful invention.
I wonder how much the Pope would pay to get us to turn this thing off.
Yeah.
You're catching on now, Dr. A.
You gotta see my new invention.
Filbert, be careful now.
It's really great.
Don't trip on any of those wires.
Good.
Yes.
Go around the table.
But, Dr. Pinkerton, I have to show you my new invention, the Elvissator.
Hey, get the hell out of here, Filbert.
We're trying to destroy the world's religions over here.
That sounds like a very naughty thing to do.
But look at what I've invented here.
Dr. Pinkerton, hold the Elvissator helmet while I look at it.
I'll look for a place to plug it in.
Filbert, I have no time for these monkey shines.
Let me just go ahead and unplug this and plug in the Elvissator.
That's gonna be great.
Filbert, don't unplug it.
I'm sorry.
Barga nargal.
Filbert, I think you really did it this time.
Oh, no.
You don't suppose that's...
Oh, God.
Quick.
I've got to hide somewhere.
I know.
Don't you dare.
Dr. Pinkerton, put on the Elvissator on your head and I'll simply turn on a switch.
Elvissator activated.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Well, thank you, Filbert.
Well, thank you very much.
You're welcome, Mr. Elvis Pinkerton.
Where am I?
Dr. Pinkerton?
Far from grace.
Pinkerton.
Yo, Filbert.
There's somebody knocking at the door.
What's up with Pinkerton?
He's Elvis.
Oh, to hell with it.
Just go ahead and let him in.
Pardon me, kind sirs.
What the hell?
I'm selling bibles.
Oh, my God.
Perhaps if your old Bible is worn out, you would care to purchase a new one?
What?
Selling the word of God?
Well, that would be morally wrong.
Morally?
Wrong.
From Consortium of Genius at Consortiumofgenius.com.
And now, Jeremiah Clark's Trumpet Volcano.
Volcano, voluntary, is played by the English.
Well, this, this, it's, it's, of, of, um, and, and, um, um, um, um, um, but, but, um, they,
um, are, uh, which, um, uh, uh, um, discussed.
What were those, of, of, of, uh, and, of, of, is it?
Um, duh, due to the thereof banent of, and, and, and, and, and, it's, an, of, uh, uh, ohm,
so, uh, and, and, so, it, it's, uh, it's, uh, uh, of, uh, and, and, uh, uh, uh, to, uh,
of, like, fish, just air.
So, I, I sent to, uh, so, so sent, so, that, that, uh, so, uh, it was, uh, and, and, mm,
mm, mm, mm.
Well, so, but then, somebody, so, so there.
English chicken, chicken, chicken, English chicken.
They touched his hand with a hot stove until he cried.
He didn't want to be a bad boy.
You know what a stove is for?
It's for cooking food and not little things.
Oh, a stove is good for training little antichrists.
That's what it's good for.
That's why he was doing it.
You train, you train, you do that to enough little boys sooner or later, you get an, an,
an antichrist.
That's what a hot point's made for, is making an antichrist.
I've been working on a Christ-antichrist warp drive.
How does that work, friend?
It's just on pure spiritual power.
Pure spiritual power.
The conflict between Christ and the antichrist.
The yin, the yang.
The three yin.
The yin.
The friction between the Christ and antichrist drives the Christ-antichrist motive.
Two forces in there.
It's one of a series along with the matter-doesn't-matter warp drive.
Yeah, yeah, now you're talking out of your butt again.
You said it like you did.
This is the channel of Colorado Radio.
Tonight at 9, catch one of the eldest of Leonard Bernstein's children.
She's about to roll in the same place, pointing to medieval Spain as her example.
Tonight.
Contributors also include the John McCarthy Foundation, The Doors Do, Seeking People's
Lives by Supporting Child Abuse, and the Bill Foundation, Supporting Global Fun.
This is the R.org.
Tomorrow, the Farm Bill.
Who does it help?
And should we support this nation?
Today we're talking about changes underway to restructure it and its practices.
Our guest is Vern Severek, semester of Vern Boren, direct dean, chair of the University
of Cavanaugh.
Cavanaugh.
I think.
He's also a Ralph.
And I.
Both.
Whatever your name is, we welcome you.
Okay.
How have California's involvement in manipulating the TUDES towards the development of the
center, towards Trinity Rhone?
That means, uh, not summer day in the middle of the night.
Uh.
Talk about it.
Today's men and women who reached their sixties have found they're not people.
And, uh, one experiences transmission.
And they, uh, as a so too.
You know, on the grid.
uh, helpments.
And how long, uh,
did these be in that out?
It's, uh,
I think, thank you. And he spoke to us from his
home in British Canabia.
We're talking this hour to prevent the two-faced
Californians from the discussion section
than just to talk after a short break from
NPR News.
Hi, I'm Trouble to Kendall.
Kendall, um, 13.14.9.
Kendall, uh, this.
Kendall, I'm sorry.
Um, but,
I'm mostly cloudy
today from isolated showers
in the mountains. Five, closer to
eight and six.
By Fernanda Nande
Limor.
Oh, man, 920. Oh, five years
ago.
The briar patch is an illusion.
The briar patch
and the rabbit. Five years ago,
Dr. Winky rode that last ride.
Five years ago today?
Old Dr. Winky.
Riding off into the sunset.
Well, what would he be saying and what is he saying
right now? I think he's just picking the fiddle.
He doesn't speak
in language, though. Well,
he gets a choice. It's like the little
the little slid-eyed
white boy down in Tennessee
in Deliverance, that little kid with the
banjo. The mongoloid square laddie?
The mongoloid with that little fish dip.
The eyes.
He's simple, but he can speak the language of
God on that thing.
That's what they speak in heaven.
It's beautiful music.
I did call him an idiot savant, and I knew
he was an idiot, but I didn't know he was a French guy, too.
That's kind of strange, you know, when they
mix him up like that. I get confused.
Like a French retarded guy?
That would be hard to, you know, understand.
Is that so? That was a
French imported
retarded idiot savant
banjo picker? Well, I thought savant.
was his last name. I don't know. He wasn't even a
real hootenanny in the
Appalachian? He must
have been. That was too real.
Savant, I understand. Idiot. That was way
too real. Idiot is savant.
He could play the banjo with his feet, too,
which was another, I guess, one of the
gifts that you get when you're named savant.
Relatives of
the lepetomanes, I believe.
The lepetomane
family. The lepetomanes were the first
of flatulators, weren't they? I mean, it was
a sideshow geek who actually
Oh, he was no sideshow
geek. He was the toast of Paris.
He made more money.
Bigger than elephant man. He was
the Hendrix of his day, sort of.
Yeah, well, he made
the colors grow.
He set fire to his instrument
at the end. Made it sound like a
war was going on. He was the first to do that
and Alfred Jari was the first to do
the walking commentary on it. The lepetomane will
now do the Star Spangled Banner.
Complete with bombs and
explosions. I'm the Hendrix of my living,
room. I'm the Hendrix of
my bathroom, toilet area,
sometimes shower.
So, could he play the
Marseillaise with his delicate booper?
I've
heard that he'd actually with a rousing
note. He'd hook a
hose up to his nether
lung, shall we call it,
and attach
a delicate flap in his
tuxedo, which would go to a
flute. The hose would go to a flute.
He could play the flute.
He could inhale
and exhale through his rectal
lung. Oh, like double
breathing. So many classical artists try
so many years to get the double breathing, you know,
like while they're snorting in through their nostrils and
blowing out of their lips. And he had this
down there. Well, he had it
down there. He had flippers, too?
Yeah, you have to use the flippers to kind of
scoop up the air.
I didn't know lepetomane was an amphibian.
It's not like it is here.
The air isn't like this. You have to
like, you know, scoop it up and shove some in your
face. Dense, highly charged,
and extremely magnetic.
We were talking about parrots at the turn
of the century. Oh, Christ, I thought we were talking
about parrots.
Parrots?
You were talking about lepetomane, the world's
greatest flagellating parrot.
I thought we were talking about
ectoplasm.
It just shows, you know, like...
And if we do it in L.A., we have to do it a third
spring down there in that same hall
we did years ago.
The Alexandria.
Where there was oral sex
by Mexican transvestites being given
to their clients in our cars
as the show went on upstairs
across the hall.
There were midgets there.
Yes, there were very small people
performing strange acts
in a wedding that had to be almost as
strange as the subgenius gathering itself.
Well, people thought it was our show,
actually. They wandered into the wrong
hall and thought they were in the
right one, folks.
This is marvelous conceptualization.
And look at the flagellation.
This midget wedding.
It looks almost real.
Oh!
We walked down the street to go get
sandwiches at sunset.
I was really enjoying being in L.A.
And just then a beer bottle whizzed
past my head and there were raucous
people on the floors above where we
were in the building where we had
our party, our subgenius gathering.
And they were hurling beer bottles
at people and then ducking back in
the windows and laughing like
maniacal Lee Harvey Oswald.
Here's an interesting scene.
Neo spa video of smoked
The rendering was very
beautiful, but I was probably
so averraged and then they
they back out.
And it was, it wasn't
as long as I was surprised,
at all.
I didn't know what they were doing.
I'm so famous, you know, in New York.
I couldn't do it with lng
Our marketing media, which,
movies is happening.
until it broke.
And I saved the pipe.
I still actually have the pipe,
but the face was left in bad shape.
It apparently was carried back upstairs
about 4 a.m.
And by whom?
A week later,
when a subgenius band came to a tour
and played that same hall a week later,
they said the bobhead was still there
in the stairway.
More reason that there'd be
bad feeling against us.
Now, we left a huge immobile prop
jamming in their stairwell.
No, it was taken out of the stairwell,
so it no longer blocked the fire escape.
But it was just staring at you
as you came up on the second floor.
From puzzling evidence.
No one is ever safe on this hostile planet.
No kidding.
This background music is the amino acids.
And now, more cut-ups from the moor.
You have 21 new messages
and 3 old messages.
What?
6, 10, 8, and...
Hey, Bob.
Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Hi.
Bob.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Uh, uh,
she's cold and tears.
I guess you heard her feelings.
You know, we can't do that.
I mean,
Um, I think she's intimidated by you,
which is just fine.
Bye.
Hey, Bob.
End of messages.
Philip K. Dick had some pithy thing that just,
you know,
uh, the...
Damn pink.
He was the first...
I got my eyes.
I can't...
I flashed.
I lost it, you know.
He was the first true madman of our...
of our generation, Philip K. Dick.
Well, he's America's most beloved, mentally ill science fiction writer.
I love him.
Yeah, yeah.
He deserves his belovedness.
Yeah.
And he is quite mad, though.
Isn't he in his elder years?
Or is he still, uh...
I thought he was a root of Vegas now.
He was buried.
You want to know something real sad?
Well, sure.
We mailed him a subgenius pamphlet the week before he died.
And you killed him.
And, well, I don't know.
The guy who drew the comic book P-Dog was the last person next to his ex-wife to see
him alive.
Oh, he was next to his ex-wife.
He had received a subgenius pamphlet.
He'd received a visit from a subgenius.
The subgenius left.
The ex-wife arrived.
And Phil Dick left in, you know, well, in the ambulance.
Well, that's like all those, you know, weirdos walking around.
Walking up to Kerouac's house in the rain, you know, asking for autographs or saying
they want to be, uh, something.
I know.
That was Tennessee Williams.
I thought that was Hunter Thompson.
Okay, yeah, right.
Hunter Thompson.
I get Tennessee Williams and Hunter Thompson confused.
I thought they were both dead.
I thought they were both the same person.
I thought they were that...
ESO's Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
A.S.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Professor Chas, Princess Wiardo, and your surely, Reverend Ivan Sook.
Are turnaround
We need backup streo
MosERFUNid
Just access our website topsof97.,
U-O,
U-O, BO ALE Skierina,    ,
Through this life, we were destined to make it right.
It's predetermined, and this is our fate.
We're singing this song so you can relate.
We are going to save the universe.
It's obvious, yet useless.
This life.
We are going to save the universe.
Or get uptight.
Because the end is near.
We can't fail.
So we don't decide.
We're in control.
And we are more than a band.
We are going to save the universe.
This time.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, come on.
We're running out of air.
There's still just a little room on the dance floor.
So, the chef.
The Swiggin' Love Corpses Live.
There were a lot of bubbles at all those events.
What was up with the bubbles?
What does that mean?
When people run around?
You know, like, wave like they want to be six again or something like that.
Look what I've discovered.
I'm sorry.
It was just a bitter thought.
You know, I just thought of all these people, like, having kid fun, like, when they're, like, 42 and stuff.
So, what's your problem with that?
Just like Byron, man.
You're just like Byron.
That old fart.
Who's Byron?
Lord Byron?
Shelly?
Teacher Milton.
I know.
Those are the...
He's the guy that says we're just all just...
We're not weird enough.
X Day is just a frat party.
We just do the normal things that normal, ordinary primates do.
Yeah, spring break in the woods.
Oh, you just can't take a little sideways criticism from another fellow.
No, we actually...
The question is, if the denizens of X Day aren't weird, what is weird?
If people who...
Yeah, really, I mean, you know, just remind them of that.
Stop taking it so serious.
You're like saying, okay, right.
You know, hey, yeah, sure, not weird enough.
Well, you know, the obvious example is, well, what about...
Make your own weird.
What about Popes Lilith?
Popes...
That's pretty weird.
Changing your sex.
Oh, old hat, you know.
Yeah, really, I guess that is true.
Truck and roll job, big deal.
Yeah, I guess it's not really much of a competitive sport, you know.
So what is weird, Dave?
Would weird nowadays, would weird...
For you, I guess a weird thing would be to put on a suit and a tie and go to college and become a lawyer and...
The weirdest thing of all would actually see them damn vessels come down and rescue us.
I'm sorry for crying out loud.
I'm losing a little face, Dan, you know.
It's about time.
Well, I think it was about time five years ago.
Well, maybe Bob's trying to tell you something, Dave.
Maybe there's a little message for you in there.
Like it's all a sub-clitoral reality or something?
No, it's like, maybe you just screwed up royally, man.
Maybe you screwed up like Hogan's goat.
You know what Hogan's goat did.
I don't know, but they said I looked like Commander...
Clink one time.
You know what I mean?
Not the fat guy.
I know nothing.
No, that was the fat guy.
Clink was the guy who always stuck a monocle in his eye.
I know nothing.
He'd storm out and go,
Hogan, your goat has got me in more trouble with the likes of Marshall Kandaki.
Funny Nazis.
Funny Nazis on the news.
Funny Nazis on the kids' Saturday morning shows.
Funny Nazis.
Funny Afghan troops lighting up...
Where's DJ?
They shut off firecrackers.
We thought it was enemy fire.
I am a superhuman.
Stronger than any man.
Driven the world with total dedication.
Cause I'm a superhuman.
I am a superhuman.
Your fate's in the palm of my hand.
Come up to me if there's a sticky situation.
Cause I'm a superhuman.
Superhuman.
I am a superhuman.
Stronger than every man.
Stronger than the world with total dedication.
Look to me for your inspiration.
Superhuman, I am.
Superhuman!
See the future now.
Sing it to the future now.
Everything you could do.
In the movie, right?
I know that what you do is wonderful.
kov
Save your future
Save your future now
That was Neutra, the band.
Neutra.
What? Huh? What?
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah.
We're just trying to make out what kind of growth that guy's been through.
Sorry.
Where are you from?
Anyway, that song, Superhuman, was by Neutra.
He played A.
A misbegotten lawyer in, what was the name of that film?
Brian's Judge.
No, Primes.
Primes Judge.
And it was on to the cookie commercials for Lady Dunn.
Pull the handle.
Down she goes.
I am so sorry.
I am so sorry that this whole area has been blockaded.
It's really none of my fault.
Of course it's not your fault.
The quarantine is everywhere now.
No, I know.
It's just...
It's tragic.
Don't try and kick the rubber gloves on, ma'am, please.
Just get to the middle of the bus.
I know.
I'll do the best I can.
Oh, you're throwing it all over the seat.
You're going to have to leave now.
I'll do that, can't I?
Okay.
Do you want to play with us?
Say hello to my new friend.
Okay.
Do you want to play with us?
Do you like that?
Huh?
Do you want more?
And more and more sounds.
We've been hearing more from Mr. Sister.
The great Mr.
Sick Mr. Sister.
and the sick as hell
for the Nellie Murr.
You're listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry
Hour of Slap Praise.
We created a race of robots.
Bob.
Their function
is to patrol the planets
in spaceships like this one
and preserve the peace.
And you can reach
Bob and the Church of the Subgenius
at, uh, got that pencil ready, friends?
Just write to
Post Office Box
204-206
Austin, Texas
And always find us at
postofficebox.com
We'll see you next time.
I went to drown
in the ground
Reverend, sir.
I mean, Mr. Reverend
plush poopoo man yourself.
Could you please take care
of your, uh, frozen woman here?
She have taken
too much of the gut juice.
Never too much.
Too much of the gut juice.
It's everywhere, friends.
Too much is all.
Different kinds of juice.
It's in your fingernails.
It's in your diaphragm.
Shame on me.
It's always better than shame on you.
It's in the Isle of Langerhans
where Creeks and Brooks
babble together.
Babble, babble,
book and booboo.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
Be back to the wind
and your sack in the saddle.
They took my car.
Give me back
the princess.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to see you again.
Catch me later.
No.
believe me.
They took my car.
Randy's hit me,
I'll call you back,
and I don't have to worry anymore.
Debbie,
not to on it.
Pleaserael.
That's the  of reason,
Free Barrios! Free Swara! Free Barrios!