Look! I know who it is! I know who it is that doesn't belong among us! I swear I know who it is!
It's...
The Self Genius Hour of Swag!
Oh, that's not true!
Something was missing. It was my pills.
I wonder if that guy bombed or something.
I guess I better...
Run over there.
Doug! Doug!
Oh yeah, okay, what?
Down here.
Oh, okay.
Where are we going?
The Dark River.
Tunnel ride.
Don't worry.
Just, like, hand the guy a cordial.
That guy took all my pills.
Yeah, well, don't worry about those pills.
You don't need those pills anymore.
Okay, well, I still got my tape recorder and my camera.
You don't need those anymore either.
Give them to me.
Come on.
Whoa, look out!
Whoa!
Whoa, Doug!
Look out, Doug!
Doug Wellman and Paul Mavridis at Disneyland.
And this is the Disneyland of the diseased mind.
Diseased-ny-land.
So, get ready.
Turn your tape decks on.
Or whatever.
Because, uh...
28 minutes...
28 minutes of this show is Reverend Susie the Floozy's special Rush Limbaugh episode
of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
So, be ready to overdose on slack, friends, on Susie's fantastic skill at the casting
out of false prophets.
Your mortal enemy is on the radio!
The way things ought to be.
By me, Rush H. Limbaugh III.
I decided to make this recording to tell a little bit about myself and my radio show
and one of the people who unknowingly provided me with the guidance and inspiration to better myself.
You went the surprise of your life.
Take one of these pills.
My beliefs are my heart and soul, the essence of my being.
And I never betray them or misrepresent them in the pursuit of narcotics.
But if you must...
You must.
I know why I'm on the radio.
Excellent.
Otherwise, we wouldn't know of this enlightened and marvelous way of turning on.
Incredible!
Now, this is staggering.
Oh...
Did I tell you?
Give the watch and this bottle a million dollars!
A million!
Oh!
I like that so much, I've stolen it from them.
I now use it myself.
Oh!
This could be a problem.
Don't worry. He's taking a million of these capsules.
Yeah, I see.
Well, I acquired it legally. You can be sure of that.
Doesn't add up.
You figure it out.
When you multiply my dangerous vices by one and a half million times,
and then multiply that figure by my 20 years on the radio,
you get a stunning number.
30 million.
I will admit to you that if they legalize the country's heroin that runs my corrupt empire,
I will wither away, just like the communist empire did.
The truth about this whole sordid man's life will eventually find its way into the mainstream press.
And when it does, you who have supported and believed me will be embarrassed and shocked.
Mark my words.
Seems to be wandering aimlessly.
To the contrary. For it is they you see, because...
What?
That's what they do.
Come on.
As I was preparing this production, I encountered a recurring problem.
Nope.
Again, no.
Wrong O.
Telephone.
Yes.
Rock, how are ya?
I want country heroin.
Oh, yeah. That'd be great.
And I got something really fantastic to show you.
Drugs?
Yeah, no, we'll expect you this Saturday.
To the contrary.
Real efforts will do a lot more than false compassion.
I'll make a deal with you. I'll make a deal.
The nerve.
I look for a deal every day, not just every Christmas.
If you be patient, then we'll take you away any place you want to go.
Nuts.
I have one word for such defeatism.
Nonsense.
I'm right in the middle of a very important experiment right now.
Give me a minute.
Uh...
But anything that we've talked about is just between you and I, okay?
Is no big deal to me.
Now...
You take this, and you try and get some sleep.
Okay? Did it go down?
Uh...
Now you just try and get some sleep, and I'll be back in a while.
Thank you, and may God bless you.
You're distrusted?
You've got to relax. The man is my best friend.
I went to college with him.
There was absolutely no problem with him.
So there it was, this unique blend of cocaine and heroin that I thought would make me popular.
I wanted to be noticed and liked.
I just thought I had to do great shows.
I was wrong.
Wow, that was a great show.
I never thought about why, and in truth, I was afraid of finding out.
My fear was that the discovery would cause me to become a caricature of myself.
You're well known, sir, for your lenient stance on crime.
But suppose for a second that your house was ransacked by thugs,
your family tied up in the basement with socks in their mouths,
you try to open the door, but there's too much blood on the knob.
What is your question?
My question's about the budget, sir.
I don't know about you, but I like to have fun.
I like drug abuse, especially country heroin.
Wow, that was a great buzz.
Oh. Oh.
You know, he only has the mentality of about an eight-year-old.
Oh, really?
He'd suffered irreparable brain damage from lack of oxygen.
Wow, that was a great rush.
Oh, I will admit to you that I like to rob and kill mentally unbalanced hookers.
I like really drugging radical feminist sisters, especially the elderly,
after hours in the privacy of their own homes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh?
Ooh, don't steal a shopping cart from the supermarket,
but if you do, make sure nobody sees you.
A little Indian lingo there.
Oh, I am at one with the tree.
The woman was so hopeless.
Hell, we may as well go all the way into the trash dumpster.
Oh, boy, jerk!
Ooh.
Oh, shit!
Oh, dumpster dining.
Why wouldn't you do that if I were you?
Well, we could.
Turn out the lights, sit down with an adult beverage, and just...
Look at that frog.
This demonstration...
...incorporates what should not be eaten out of trash dumpsters.
You see, the dumpster toads secrete a hallucinogenic substance near the back of its head
that can get you high if you lick it.
Maybe I should pick it up and lick it.
Oh, I hadn't licked that frog.
I'm going to.
Wow, that was great fun.
Ooh.
Well, nobody put that woman in the dumpster.
She climbed in herself.
You sleep in a trash dumpster, you run the risk of being crushed by a dumpster truck.
An adult male toad was observed during amplexus with an adult female toad.
At least three factors appeared quite unique about this situation.
First, the female was dead and had been for some time.
It appeared as if she had fallen victim to a car.
The limbs were already stuck.
The abdomen greatly distended and the smell of putrefaction about her.
Secondly, of course, it appears strange that the male should be so intent as to fail to observe the female's condition.
Thirdly, the time and place we encountered this pair was unusual.
It was at 1400 hours on a sunny afternoon, but even more interesting was the location.
The middle of the road.
We better start the autopsy right now.
Well, guess what?
A couple of days later after the autopsy, it is learned that the person was drinking alcohol.
The woman was drinking a cheap brand of wine called Free Hookers.
I was appalled. I was shocked.
I was fuming. I was livid.
I was in awe.
Upon returning to my program the following Monday, I walk into the studios and sit down behind that golden microphone.
All movies on.
My critics are such dim-witted fools who feel it necessary to spoon-feed the public with the proper version and details of events, all the while denying that they do it.
So long as something makes them look good, to heck with the facts.
And with anyone who dares to defy them by exposing those facts.
Point is that standards of right and wrong and basic decency must be established and must be maintained.
If they are not, our one individual action multiplied many times can corrode the entire moral fiber of the country.
Consider drug abuse.
A lot of people say we should legalize cocaine and heroin.
But the fact that people are going to do it, it is not a good thing.
The fact that people are going to ignore and break laws is not a valid argument for decriminalization.
It's easy for people to say that if they shoot up on heroin, the only people they're hurting are themselves.
But that's not true.
If someone becomes an irresponsible human being and a worthless citizen, he is directly or indirectly affecting everyone else who is willing to live up to the responsibilities of citizenship.
Drug abusers destroy their families.
If we legalize these vices, we erode the societal support for prohibition.
We are not legalizing criminal relations against crimes such as murder.
Those who are drug or alcohol abusers are evil.
They couldn't be considered normal.
I'm talking about using tough love here.
It might be a start at forcing them to confront the misery caused largely by their own behavior.
People are going to have to start accepting responsibility for their actions.
And I think it is incumbent upon all of us to be concerned about the values we transfer to succeeding generations.
When we take actions that cheapen life, we're contributing to an overall decline in our society's moral values.
Now tell me, who would do that kind of thing?
I don't need to improve much in this area, but admit it, many of you people do.
I'm proud, extremely proud of my accomplishments.
They are significant.
But you know, people often confuse the role callers play in a great talk show.
The primary purpose of callers on my show is to make me look good.
Here, finally, was someone on the radio saying what they felt, what they said to their friends and family.
Hey, Rog, I don't want to get into a discussion of ethics with you about all of this.
Mm-hmm, I'll pick word to say the least, intransigent.
But you do have another problem.
Now you mentioned some woes there.
Don't you understand what it is I'm trying to do?
Nope.
Come on.
I'm collecting money.
Money?
What's up?
I was incredulous.
The nerve.
I don't let considerations of money dictate the level or manner of my performance.
Oh, honey, come on.
I don't say things on the air.
You taking those pills?
I gave you some pills.
Tranquilizers.
To the contrary, part of showbiz...
Don't you understand what money is?
...is no big deal to me.
We have a $400 debt.
With the money I've spent on drugs since the 1960s,
I could have bought the entire assets of every Fortune 500 company,
and still Rush wants more.
You know it.
I know it.
And more importantly, they know it.
Oh, you did what?
Oh, man.
Now, my friends, isn't this just typical?
Another intelligent conservative here, railroaded by our liberal justice system,
just like Colonel Oliver North, Officer Stacy B.
Coon, and cartoon smokesperson Joe Camel.
Well, I've had it.
Oh.
Got a hangover?
Ha-ha!
Many of you take things way too seriously in most cases,
so come on.
We should all laugh at yourselves.
And if you can't laugh at yourself, laugh at me.
They were rejoicing, to be blunt about it.
I'm going to get you!
Damn you!
But that wasn't all.
The audience thought this was some of the best entertainment they had heard on radio
in a long time, particularly from a conservative.
You should go on that radio station and let him have it.
Good idea.
People were going crazy over my latest lunacies.
It's a monster!
Kill it!
I copy!
As it turns out, I had underestimated just how liberal many people could be.
That's good.
It's gone!
Find him!
Man, they must have been brewing some of that Jekyll and Hyde joy juice in here.
Well, at least we haven't found any more bodies.
There's nobody in the house.
Sheriff, I've got a quick little thing.
Come on.
Oh, let's go.
I'll lead off with the hounds.
Now, if anybody sees it, don't go taking off after them by yourself,
let the rest of us know about it.
You got that?
Right.
OK, let's go.
Who could help beat that big?
Offhand, there's only one person I know of.
Yeah, but he ain't never hurt nobody.
No.
We've got to find Roger before he discovers June, or we'll go back on it.
It's just without morphine, the pain is just gonna really...
Zing!
You know we're gonna have to destroy him.
Why are you on that much?
The best thing is to get rid of him, get a big stick, and hit him with it.
Practice of going out and getting one of these things and putting them into a billy, boiling it down and eating the residue, I think is absolutely repulsive.
Meanwhile...
If seen, notify your nearest local law enforcement agency immediately.
He is male, Caucasian, weight 560 pounds.
He is extremely dangerous and may be armed.
When I return, you do show.
A friend fixed up the radio.
I'm amused when opponents refer to me as the most dangerous man in America.
Why am I dangerous?
Simple.
Because I am convinced that the rumor mongering against me was an 11th hour attempt to ruin my life.
And I've never witnessed anything so despicable.
Irrespective of the truth of the allegations that I sexually harassed Clarence Thomas,
his reputation...
and career have been incurably degraded.
And Clarence will test positive for an airborne phenomenon spread by conservative broadcasting.
It's a win-win situation.
Now you figure it out.
I don't know about you, but I will abandon my principles for money.
Sorry, but to be a prostitute is no big deal to me.
Because I'm having fun being stupid.
Hell, we may as well go all the way and then take a junket to some exotic Caribbean island with some lobbyists.
Call communications immediately.
I was impressed with how quickly you got here.
Y'all, see this cancelled all the way down the line.
The people say we don't have enough beds for hookers. Well, we could...
Yes, ma'am, we stopped and we got in just under the wire.
Excellent.
Meanwhile, far below the Earth's surface...
The people say we don't have enough beds for hookers. Well, we could...
Not a bad hideout.
Sometimes I think you even have brains.
Low pain threshold, eh?
Probably normal.
He'll get better.
Time for a booster!
Have you heard of frog licking?
No!
I told you to stop asking me all those stupid questions. Otherwise, you're never going to eat, right?
Right? Okay. Let's go find something to eat. I'm hungry, imbecile.
Ooh, look at that frog!
You haven't switched from liquor to dope by any chance, have you?
Again, drugs? You figure it out.
I mean, you gotta give these women a hand.
To me, this illustrates what the polls have conclusively shown.
The vast majority of American women didn't think sexual harassment is the most important issue of our time.
Plus, they also think they can handle the situation themselves.
Wrong-o.
Whatever they got you.
You're in for the gold.
There he is!
It's a monster! Kill it!
Let's look at some of the things that happened after the hearings ended.
Well, the young woman brought forward
competitively.
She's got a compelling testimony on what happened.
Unfortunately, one day he put his theory into practice.
It took 75 federal marshals to bring him down.
Now let's never speak of him again.
Let the record show that the witness may be...
No shit.
Now, as a conservative, I'm sick and tired of being accused of being heartless and cruel.
I mean, if she were honest, she would admit that what she really wants is me in the womb.
Let the record show that the witness may be...
This may be...
Oh, God.
What?
Tsk, tsk.
You figure it out.
Now look at it in another, and admittedly more provocative way.
What if a man claimed the right to rape,
using the same principle found in the theory that it's his body he has the right to choose?
On my award-winning Thrill Pack program,
the feminists have gotten the shaft.
And I'll...
Assuming that it has no direct bearing on your problem.
Are you embarrassed?
Talking about your subversive activities?
I was incredulous.
I'm just a harmless, lovable little fuzzball.
Quiet, you awful man!
Y'all laugh like that's a new one.
I am a political prisoner.
I can be arranged.
I think we've got a problem.
I have no idea what's going on.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
And he hung up.
Meanwhile...
Telephone!
Yeah.
Do it!
Get it done!
Oh.
I said don't ask me how to do it.
I don't wanna be no part of no conspiracy.
Yeah, I see.
But however you do it, do it and get it done now.
If it don't get done, then I'll move on it.
Right.
Goodbye.
What'd it say?
Buckle your seat belts, hang on, and...
take notes, listen with your mind, as well as your heart.
Something's gotta pop!
No, no, no.
Bob!
Bob, come in!
What?
Bob!
A fine mohawk to you all.
Our friend Bob!
Oh my God!
Okay!
God, I've been misinformed.
I need to get out of here.
Take it easy if I will you.
Could be the boss would do a little skull massaging himself.
If he knew what happened.
Maybe you just better forget about it.
I don't know the whole thing.
If you're smart.
You know it, I know it.
And more importantly, they know it.
I don't know.
You figure it out.
Mix up the F!
Mix up the abusing tongue!
Yeah, we're mix up the F!
Mix up the F!
Mix up the abusing tongue!
Yeah, we're, yeah!
Oh, by God, I'll tell you something, friend.
I have never been so strong.
In my life.
Except on heroin.
Wow, that was a great high.
Well, I was, you know, in this day and time, you can't even get something.
Oh, by God, I'll tell you something, friend.
I have three different sources of junk.
Wrong-o.
I've stolen it from you.
I'm gonna break your damn neck, you son of a bitch.
No!
And it's damaging to myself.
And to my doctor.
And for a booster!
Boom!
No more treatments.
No more pain.
I know what it's like to be on the bottom.
Oh.
Gorilla?
There is no such thing as that gorilla.
It's an hallucination.
The nerve.
Why forget?
Forget the whole thing.
Oh, I am at one with the tree.
You have to promise me that this isn't gonna happen this time.
To do drugs?
No.
Not according to the law.
Most people I know wouldn't lick a frog, even if it did give them a buzz.
I agree.
Oh, Christ.
Thank you, and may God bless you.
So naive.
Poor Ruby, son.
Woo!
And Ruby.
Simple.
Because I am convinced that the most important thing is to just take drugs one and a half
million times.
People say we don't have enough country heroin for them.
So what we need to do is eliminate laws, get rid of the police.
That way, there will be no paranoia, schizophrenia, or deep depression.
That means I can be myself.
Well, he's even better.
I agree.
I like the human touch.
Is there anything to that story about that two-headed man stuff?
Sometimes, too much imagination can destroy man, deputy.
It's incredible how many things we seem to hide.
All the real things we can't admit to.
And these are all lies.
Because of pride
We never could say we cared
No matter how much we shared
Too many times
The thunder calls the rain
It's incredible
How much we really are
Well, that's nonsense. The American people did that.
I just helped amplify their drug abuse.
Ladies and gentlemen, Rush Limbaugh!
They say that I'm sleaze and elitist
You please, everybody disagrees with my rap
I'm horrendous, I'm appalling
My ratings now are falling
Cause I'm so full of bull, so full of crap
With condescending crimes, making money, selling lies
You might say everybody hates my guts
I'm offensive, I'm a bigot, I'm a fraud
Can you dick it? I'm a sexist, racist, homophobic, fat, pathetic
I'm a Nazi
That's right, I really am
Cause I'm a Nazi
That's right, you're being scammed
I'm a Nazi
I don't care about the middle class
Cause I'm a fat conservative butthead
With a face of a horse's ass
He's a fat conservative butthead
I have a subhuman figure, a huge rear end
My brain? That's another story
It's quite another story
I have a face the size of a washtub!
And my ass is as big as Missouri
Yes!
This bastard is sick, he's a fat mob
It's big and his ass is as big as Missouri
Yes, sirree Bob!
Manipulating statements exaggerates the truth
I can't believe the hate my show inspires
The hate my show inspires
It's not just because I'm stupid
It's not just because I'm scum
It's just because Republicans are liars
Those dirty, filthy liars
I am heartless, I am vain, insensitive, insane
They say that I'm a national disgrace
Disgrace
I am nasty, insulting, basically revolting
I'm a concentrated pile of human waste
He's human waste
Cause I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
Shit!
How I really am
Cause I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
That's right, you're being scammed
I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
I don't care about the middle class
Cause I'm a sick Republican sleazeball
With a face of a horse's ass
He's a sick Republican sleazeball
They say that this is not about my vanity
They doubt my sanity
They think I'm nuts
So nuts
I am a cyst on the ass of humanity
Ew!
New Republican slogan, read my tuts
Read his tuts
From the bowels of a baseball taker
Comes the voice of Rush Limbaugh
Heh heh
In closing, let me say
That each and every day
I'm an evil rotten pig
An evil rotten egotistical snob
Evil rotten
I'm the coppo
The coppo
Joe McCarthy like Gestapo
The right wing foam at the mouth
Jack booted slob
The democratic trash it
Years of liberal bashing
With the equivalent compassion of a grommet
Oh a grommet
With the IQ of a fig
I'm a fat obnoxious pig
And the truth of the matter is
I'm vomit
He's vomit
Cause I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
Shit!
How I really am
Cause I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
Shit!
I'm a Nazi
He's a Nazi
I don't care about the middle class
Those on the fearmongerings
Come back
With the face of a horse's ass
He's a fat conservative
Buckhead
Republican swizzball
Fear mongerings
Come back
Egotistical ass
My ass
Mean-spirited
Bum-wallering
Fat conservative
Pots
With the face
Of a horse's ass
Heh heh heh
Make a dildo's Rush
Ha ha ha
Mega dildo's Rush
Rush Limbaugh
As I bring this recording to a close, I would like to leave you with a request.
And that is, are we really gullible enough to believe my words?
Thank you, and may God bless you.
Wrong again, liberal media.
The most rewarding part was when he gave me my money.
The Way Things Ought to Be was written and read by Rush Limbaugh III.
It was abridged for audio, produced and directed by Susan...
It's Reverend Susie the Floozy to my friend.
Oh, and there's a song by the queers in there, too.
You may have guessed that the theme of tonight's episode of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse is celebrities behaving badly.
Oh, that one was all contrived by little moi, but...
Oh, a lot of the other ones tonight are tried and true, dyed in the wool celebrity badness.
So are you ready for a little drunk John Wayne?
I think you can handle it.
My name is William Wayne.
I don't know, this is so unimportant.
I want to...
I want to add anything that I can add to what he said about the fact that you guys are just...
On the American side, geez, I don't know how...
You know, it's so terrible that you don't know how to...
There is no way to be a leader in Americana except you guys.
You've got to control it.
We haven't...
We haven't any chance.
You...
Naturally, things happen, like at the Columbia University and at the other mother colleges.
No, it really, it's...
When I went to school, I went to school at the University of Southern California.
Let me explain something to you.
When I went there, I went there when there was a fella in control of the college.
I mean, I mean, he was the boss man there.
If anybody had walked into his office and torn down a picture and...
Did excrement in his...
Known as the waste paper baskets or had written lewd words on his...
The pictures of his family.
We, as members of the college, would have kicked the goddamn hell out of this...
Bar.
Organization.
I can't understand how it can happen in the United States of America that this can happen
and there aren't enough guys of your age to go up.
I don't give a shit if you go to the school or not.
You can't stand to have this happen.
Oh, Christ.
I'm not...
I'm not trying to talk for clapping.
I'm trying...
trying to talk for you guys, you better start thinking.
It's getting to be goddamnediculous.
If you guys don't start thinking as men,
we're going to have a lousy country.
Jesus, I have had the chance to be with guys
who are with things and against things.
And you know, Christ, you try as I try as a human being
to listen to both sides of everything.
But there's no both sides anymore.
They're just trying to wreck our goddamned country.
It's time for you younger guys to take over.
I don't know what the hell to do.
Each special pedal, Maverick and Mustang Sprint
has red, white, and blue accents.
The hood stripes, the upholstery, the carpeting,
the place where you put your woo-woo and the gear shift.
Scene 5A, take four.
Strong hands for a poetic boy.
Each special pedal, Maverick and Mustang Sprint
has red, white, and blue accents.
The hood stripes, the carpeting, the upholstery,
the backseat where you can push, push a lot
with a long girl with a big wonger on her.
She's bump umb had a bitch
Nanita- Sir does not speak Americanened.
Mr  l Shopkeeper
I guess you can't sell those things.
You know that?
Oops.
Was it good up until then?
Custer's hoofbeats.
Little bighorn.
Nothing little about it.
It's a bighorn, a son of a...
I'll never forget the size of that squaw
that came out that day
and lifted up the dying brave and ate him.
It was a sparse winter.
Cattle were lowing in the fields
and a giant eagle came down
and shit all over the wigwam.
First time I ever got disgusted
with my national emblem.
Proud I was. Proud, though.
Proud that it was an eagle shit
instead of some greasy Mexican eagle.
Your American eagle shit stinks, all right,
but it's got an American smell to it.
It's got a smell of new-mown hay,
a smell of dog flop in the streets
in New York City in August.
Got the smell of an old,
old wino tossing his cookies
there on Third Avenue.
It's got the smell of America.
Hear it, America.
Hear it running through
the coursing of her veins.
Your heartbeat pulses with it.
Carl Sandburg wrote of it.
Did he capture his essence?
No, because he wrote the entire story
with his wee-wee.
Kidney trouble.
Wrote 14 volumes of urine.
Come on.
Hold on.
Boo!
Deep in my heart,
in the bowels of a good person,
my bowels are snow-white
as the lily-white froth
that run from the mouth
of an 80-year-old pervert.
Take four.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
John Wayne.
Well, it wasn't really John Wayne.
It was really Bob Ridgely,
the Dallas character actor.
But before that was the real John Wayne,
drunk.
And that was preceded by Rush,
an editing Tower DeForsy
by Reverend Susie the Floozy
from her show on the gorgeous
WREK in Atlanta.
How about that flooz?
Who said those things weren't brains?
I suspect that they might be.
Friends, now,
how about some balance?
Yes, some beautiful balance.
By the way, this music in the background,
is Automatic Robot Fish,
Reverend Angry Larry.
Friends, for balance,
here is Terrence McKenna,
remixed and musicized
by Norell Preff.
All culture
is being destroyed.
is being sold
down the river
by the sorts of people
who want to turn the entire planet
into an international airport,
a rocket,
a rival concourse.
And that's not the victory
of somebody's culture
over somebody else's culture.
Nobody ever had a culture like that.
That's just the victory
of schlockmeisterism and crapola
over good taste and good sense.
Dissolve the conceptual boundary
of ordinary...
We are somehow told
we are infantilized.
We're told, you know,
you can wander around within the
sanctioned playpen
of ordinary consciousness.
And we have some intoxicants over here
if you want to mess yourself up.
We've got some scotch here
and some tobacco and red meat
and some sugar and a little TV
and so forth and so on.
But these boundary-dissolving
hallucinogens that give you
a sense of unity
with your fellow man and nature
are somehow forbidden.
This is an outrage.
It's a sign of cultural immaturity.
And the fact that we tolerate it
is a sign that we are living in a society
as oppressed as any society in the past.
Nobody's in charge.
Not the IMF, the Pope,
the Communist Party, the Jews.
No, no, no.
Nobody has their finger
on what's going on.
So then why hope?
Isn't it just a runaway train
out of control?
I don't think so.
I think the out-of-controlness
is the most hopeful thing about it.
After all, whose control is it out of?
Someone said,
what's so progressive about media?
It's the spreading of darkness
at the speed of light.
It can be.
Is there any permission to hope?
More specifically,
is there any permission
for smart people to hope?
I mean, it's easy to hope
if you're stupid, but
is there any basis
for intelligent people to hope?
You know, if you placed your bets
on male-dominated institutions
based on consumer fetishism,
propaganda, classism,
and materialism,
then God help you,
you should call your broker.
My attitude was always,
if it's real,
it can take the pressure.
You know, you don't have to
pussyfoot around the real thing.
If they're telling you, you know,
oh, you must lower your voice
and avert your gaze,
then you're probably in the presence of crap.
Because the real thing
is real.
It doesn't demand that you adjust
your opinion to suit it.
It's real.
That means it is preeminent.
That means it sets the agenda.
And I studied yoga.
I wandered around in the East.
I was fast shuffled by beady-eyed little men
in dhoti's.
I know the whole spiritual supermarket
and rigamarole.
And I find nothing there
to interest me.
We have to stop consuming
our culture.
We have to create culture.
Don't watch TV.
Don't read magazines.
Don't even listen to NPR.
Create your own roadshow.
The nexus of space and time
where you are now
is the most immediate sector
of your universe.
And if you're worrying about
Michael Jackson or Bill Clinton
or somebody else,
then you are disempowered.
You're giving it all away to icons.
Icons which are maintained
by an electronic media
so that you want to dress like X
or have lips like Y or something.
This is shit-brained,
this kind of thinking.
That is all cultural diversion.
And what is real is you
and your friends
and your associations,
your highs, your orgasms,
your hopes, your plans, your fears.
And we're told,
no, we're unimportant.
We're peripheral.
Get a degree.
Get a job.
Get a this.
Get a that.
And then you're a player.
You don't even want to play in that game.
You want to reclaim your mind
and get it out of the hands
of the cultural engineers
who want to turn you into
a half-baked moron
consuming all this trash
that's being manufactured
out of the bones of a dying world.
Where is that at?
The paralyzing and toxic artifacts
of the late evolving
machine-workshipping,
monotheistic, linear,
fanatic, alphabet, tight-ass,
straight culture
that we are a part of.
You don't go on bend knee
to petition the official culture
for your rights.
You have to take them.
And people ask me,
you know,
how can you stand up
and say the things you do?
Why don't they take you away?
They don't take me away
because they're more chicken shit
than you think.
They don't take me away
because they're more chicken shit
They're more off balance
than you think.
They're more uncertain of themselves
Dissolve the conceptual boundary
of ordinary expectation.
It's the mad cow disease.
That's what it is.
You've got prions up in your brain.
The prions are prying.
You know, I'm not that weirded out
about mad cows,
but I suspect that we've been
exposed to missed cows.
Or missed cow disease,
or at least some sort of
irritated cow.
Mildly annoyed cow.
Whatever happened
to happy cow disease?
Well,
once upon a time,
there was a little farm...
Yeah, it was a fairy tale.
There never were any happy cows.
They're just cows.
The Borden's glue
label lied.
They just like to chew their cud.
They were screaming
because their feet had been chopped off
to be used in the Borden's glue bottle.
Actually,
the real reason they use the
cow on Elmer's glue
is because the old glue
was made from milk protein.
It was made from casein.
Oh.
I always assumed that that was
for gelatin.
That's right.
That's why vegetarians can't eat
regular cereal.
Because it has gelatin.
You know, a conspiracy cereal has gelatin in it.
Conspiracy cereals have all kinds of weird things in them.
Bambi's feet
are in them
frosted flakes.
You can really put your foot in your mouth then.
Now,
the mad cow disease
takes such a long time
to incubate.
I've actually heard conspiracy theory
types that suggested
that Alzheimer's
is not Alzheimer's at all,
but simply mad cow
gradually
showing up.
Finally kicking in
in our generation.
Well, here's something that could very well
have to do with that.
Well, first of all,
there are some cases where mad cow
has an extremely short incubation.
In England, they saw people
in their 20s getting it.
But,
Dr. Alzheimer,
after whom the disease was named,
he had two students named Kreutzfeld
and Jakob.
Kreutzfeld and Jakob
later went on to discover
mad cow disease in humans,
or, you know,
those spongiform
encephalopathies,
the
degenerative ones. Those are called
Kreutzfeld-Jakob disease, if it's caused by
mad cow prions
in cows. They have
identical symptoms, actually, or
near-identical symptoms.
And people just kind of assume that it's Alzheimer's
if it's an old person has it.
And they assume that it's mad cow
if a young person has it.
But they've been feeding dead cows to other
cows for quite some time
now.
Oh, God. Soylent cow food is
cows! Yeah, you know, I mean,
they've been doing it here. I mean, they no longer
serve... Soylent grain is cows!
Oh, yeah. They no longer
serve, like, regular ground-up
cow parts, but they will serve rendered
protein. Of course, the rendering
process does not destroy the prion,
so it remains infectious.
But it's out
there.
Some
radio
synesthesia from WCSB
Cleveland.
Thanks and lots of
Connie juice there to Dr. Sinister
for letting Bob
use his show to glorify
or shame his sweet name
by way of our blabbering.
And we've been blabbering for a long,
long time, as heard
in this 1979 tape
by Dr. Philo
Drummond from
his series On the Road.
And another thing I want
to tell you about tonight,
we've had some calamitous
times in Malaysia.
You might have heard about all the
rains we had. Yes, dear
friends, it was flooding over
here, but, oh, Bob,
oh, good old Bob knew that when it
flooded in Malaysia, you better build
your houses on stilts.
So all our houses are built on
stilts over here, dear friends.
We knew a long
time ago that when those floodwaters
came, we better be sitting
pretty, sitting high, so
nobody could come by.
And speaking of sitting high,
we need something over here
in Malaysia. Yes,
our whole drug cabinet was washed
away, and after
a flood, you know, we need
some drugs. We need some drugs
that can help the people out here.
So what I want you all to do, dear friends...
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah,
oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
My wife and I have adopted
that as a kind of a little mantra. If
we're doing some tedious work, like moving
furniture, you start getting
a little bit out of breath, we'll start panting,
and then we'll be...
kind of rhythmically like a...
kind of like Nam-myoho-renge-kyo.
Nam-myoho-renge-kyo.
What's that?
Is that Japanese?
No, I believe it's Korean.
It's a chant that's part of a Korean religion.
A kind of Korean
cult, actually, whereby
if you chant this phrase over and
over again, everything will
come true. There was an American
similar cult, or
British maybe, in which you say,
day by day, in every way, I'm getting better and better.
Day by day, in every way, I'm getting better and better.
Day by day, and you just smutter that
to yourself under your breath, and
my goodness gracious, if
every day, day by day, you didn't get
better and better.
I've heard of that before.
Oh, there's another one where they
go, Hare Krishna, Hare Ram,
and it's a kind of...
In subgenius,
you know, we just simply
put a laundry
bag over their head and say, just wear
this for a while. And you get the same
impression, kind of a
lack of oxygen.
Hyperventilation.
The high of hyperventilation.
Which I'm
just too old for that now. I can't
afford the brain cells that go sputtering out
when I hyperventilate.
You don't hear me doing that preacher cadence
anymore, where you go,
and Bob came down
and gave him a
slack. That way they
kind of get a little buzz every
couple of words.
Oh yeah, that is the...
You get in the spirit,
and that's another reason for pulpits.
Preachers have to have something to hang
on to. Because they would collapse.
Yeah. They're out there saying,
and the leper was walking down
that dusty road.
And Jesus came along, and he
healed that leper, so thank God Jesus came
along so he could heal that leper.
And thank God the leper was walking
on that road, and thank God for
leprosy, so the leper had something to be
cured of. Well, see, the preacher gets
high, and that helps the audience
get high, and they feed off of each other
in a loop of suggestion.
Mass suggestion, and the
next thing you know, God
walks right into the
room, wearing the
latest fancy shoes
and trendy outfit,
haircut, looking like a movie star,
and they all feel the spirit.
And I,
you know, I'm envious
sometimes of people who can
do that every single week.
But, uh,
that doesn't happen in subgenius
land every single week, I don't think.
Nope.
We still got too many
brain cells, but we can change that.
That's right.
We can change that.
It doesn't have to be that way.
Nobody ever held a gun to your head
and forced you to stick those
brain cells in there?
Nobody forced you to keep them.
There's a million ways to get around that.
And that's what the
church of the subgenius is here to prove.
You don't need them
brain cells.
When was the last time that being smart
ever got you laid?
That's right.
I rest my case. Case closed.
Depressing, isn't it?
Oh.
It's kind of how things are supposed to look.
Somewhere there's a hideous genius
with a giant head
whose brain really can get him laid.
He can control other people's thoughts
like in a cartoon or something
with his mighty brain power.
But there's probably only one or two
in any given generation.
None of them.
Most of those go crazy.
Join Bob and then go nuts.
I've seen a lot of them
fall by the white side
going, oh yeah, oh yeah,
oh yeah, oh slack,
oh slack, oh slack,
same thing.
Beating off or beating their head again.
It's the wall.
Same thing. They both feel great.
Yeah. Whatever happened to
plain old all-American things
like hop and
what do they call it?
Grass or
opium, that kind of thing.
Whatever happened to the old values?
You, you, you,
you, you,
Is, is it, is it, is it,
Is it, is it.
Here you have it.
Ere clarification one
you
you is it is it is it is it Is it, is it,,
There you have it.
Erects, erupts.
Whatever.
It was, it was, it was, it was.
It was, it was, it was.
A small head rush by Noel Preff.
And now, back to another borrowed show, friends.
Dr. Sinister's radio synesthesia on the WCSB, where callers are caught like a deer in the headlights.
Banjo Bob, you there?
Headlights stuck in deer.
Phineas is still here.
Yeah, Phineas is still here.
Yes, I'm still here.
All right.
Phineas, you said earlier on the IRC that your name was Phineas Narco because you were always on some kind of drug.
That's right.
I'm on five.
Which five?
I can't say.
It's a secret.
My problem is, okay, I'm on this drug that destroys your memory.
So every now and then, I have to, like, drink some counteragent, like in this case coffee,
so that I can remember.
Whether I took some other drug that I wanted to take.
Oh, then you'll have to.
Because if you don't want to take too much, you'll die.
But you're constantly having to balance between the two.
And it's like, there's nothing worse for, and this affects froppers more than anything.
There's nothing worse than forgetting, you know, finding out later that you forgot to take a drug you were planning to take.
Then you'll have to.
Because of the one you were already on, it makes you forget everything.
Then you'll have to tattoo, you know.
Messages on your body.
Right.
And as we know, that doesn't work.
You know, it's like, no matter how good your system is, there's always going to be a flaw in it.
And you'll end up exploiting it yourself.
That's right.
Did we already have this conversation on this show?
You're hoisted by your own petard.
Did we already have this conversation, or am I having a deja vu about having a conversation about memory on college radio phone calls?
Well, if you're having deja vu, I'm having jamais vu.
Because?
I could play back the tape, I suppose.
If you're having deja vu, I'm having jamais vu.
What is that?
Deja vu means already seen in French.
Jamais vu means never seen.
So, yeah.
You're really out of it, dude.
Never heard of this.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
This might be a tape.
I was not here.
You did not see me.
I certainly have not seen you.
Well, I was just saying that.
As an example, I wasn't really trying to hypnotize you just then.
Yeah.
Believe me, I wouldn't try to do that over the radio, because you have to see.
They think that it's the swinging thing that hypnotizes you, the glowing watch or whatnot that the hypnotist uses.
It's really the bushy eyebrows.
Yeah.
That's why I just gave away a big trade secret.
Or the pointy goatee.
That's another thing.
Well, why do you think I have this particular outfit, this look that I have?
The rest is three from F15.
F15.
We're going to take another call here.
You're on the air.
Oh, Stan Jobop calling back.
Oh, good.
You're fucked.
Gazing to my pointed goatee.
We thought we lost you.
Hey, remember?
Stang, remember when I called in and talked to him about alien sex?
Yeah, and they cut you off.
That was cool.
I said, oh, I'm going to call back.
Stang's talking about all this stuff.
Makes me think of that movie.
What was that?
Bad Films.
And Memory Problems.
See?
Yeah, that Memory Problem.
Yeah.
What was that?
The memory about the memory problem?
About the guy with the memory problem.
Was that about Stang?
I thought it was until I remembered Leonard Shelby.
Is it forgetfulness?
Or is it man-cow disease?
It was, uh, it was remember, that was the name of the movie.
Remember Steve Tobolowsky.
That was it.
No.
Try to remember the, and I forget the rest of the lyrics.
Oh, well.
Well, here's an interesting fact for you.
I was just thinking, is it forgetfulness, or is it Alzheimer's, or is it mad cow disease?
We did have this conversation.
I read it.
I just didn't make any note.
There was a Yale study where they, uh, they actually did a little biopsy or autopsy on
these dead people.
People who had died from complications related to Alzheimer's and all that stuff, you know.
And, uh, as it turns out, 10% of the...
13% of the people in this one study actually, who had been diagnosed with Alzheimer's, actually
had mad cow disease.
Banjo-Bob cow disease.
Yeah, Banjo-Bob cow disease.
We got a new caller here.
It's not quite like being mad.
You know, people are eating them, and they're all, like, going insane.
It's not quite like retardation.
I've seen people eat cow brains before.
Wait till they find out about the mad cow brain disease.
Hey, your mental illness fell into my mental retardation.
Your mental illness fell into my mental retardation.
Yeah, I've been in a little retardation for a little while now.
Oh, but while we're at it, why don't I give out the contact info for Subgenius Productions?
Yes, if you'd like some information on the Church of the Subgenius and all the insanity
that it encompasses, why don't you drop a line to Bob?
The Church of the Subgenius at Post Office Box 204-207.
616-Austin, Texas 78720.
And have a good night, Seekers, if you can, after absorbing this.
Oh, and good night, Al.
Ah, yes, and Suzy the Floozy's show, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
can be heard on the internet, archived or live,
c-w-r-e-k dot org.
That's w-w-w-w-r-e-k dot org.
And thanks to Angry Larry and Automatic Robot Fish for the background music.
As I bring this recording to a close, I would like to leave you with a request.
And that is, go ahead and lick that frog.
Have the principal and the school nurse demonstrate to every couple how to lick frogs,
and then observe them to ensure they do it right.
Hell, we may as well go all the way.
In fact, what they ought to do is find diseased hookers and bring them in.
Teach a little supply and demand.
Thank you, and may God bless you.
Ho, ho, ho!
And around the river and nice and Mr. Dunstan.
He's the leader of the wagon train.
And Walter Brennan is Cookie.
It's one of those nights when just things are hanging up in the sky.
And an old breeze is stirring.
And off in the distance you hear...
And then you hear a stirring.
Who is that?
Who's going there?
Take it easy, Cookie. It's only me.
Uh-huh.
Oh, Mr. Dunstan.
Give me a stat.
I didn't know you could even tell it.
Man, I can't...
The sagebrush.
We shouldn't have camped so close.
And Patchy's just outside there, you know.
All right, Cookie.
Just settle down.
I'm just wandering around, musing to myself.
Wondering what it all means.
Sometimes I look up there and said there's a big scheme for us.
If I could only find the key to it.
Hey, don't think so hard.
Makes you break out if you think too hard, you silly old fuck.
Oh, Cookie, I...
I know we're been both...
buddies for an eye on to 45 years, but...
don't you ever say fuck to me again.
Because I'll kick your right in your 90-year-old body and make it collapse like an old pig bladder.
Okay.
You just have to tell me once you're going to threaten me.
You know nothing.
Especially not in front of the men.
Well, the men aren't here.
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
Oh, Cookie.
Now, listen.
I've been on this job on the cattle trail and...
and, you know, there's no sheep hereabouts.
And...
and, of course, we have no other offices to...
to release ourselves in, so...
why...
No, for God's sake.
Now, Duke, I told you once.
I'm too old.
I used to fuck your light when...
when...
when we were back in your cowpokes.
We were on the trail and...
I understand when you get honey and everything, but...
for God's sake, you're not going to put it in me now.