Begin next show now.
Snort projector on tool.
Ah yes, dear friends.
Another hour of slack begins.
It may not go on for very long,
but at least we've got a beginning of one.
Here at X-Day 19
at Tarzan's radio station
in Caffeina's Cafe
with Syria Campground
and Event Center near Pomeroy, Ohio.
All of which
will be destroyed by the aliens
on July 5th coming up.
Unless
we protect them by
beaming them up to our
escape vessels.
Which we as subgeniuses
have earned.
Or unless there's some unforeseen
element of mercy
in this whole sadistic scheme
which has not been made available
unto us. But I wouldn't count on it.
Well, some subgeniuses
may be merciful.
Oh, subgeniuses.
Who else can you ask?
My list of
stuff to collect is much longer
than my enemies list.
Well, the
coming subtasm
will test that
as well as many other
long-held principles
and assertions.
The saucers are coming, my friends.
Ever nearer to planet Earth.
However politically incorrect
it may be to see
leering aliens committing
atrocities,
one will have to
dispel
the curse of the
evil.
This is the
I hope you enjoyed
If you're stuck
for ideas
when you get
your powers,
think about
those Mars Attacks
bubblegum cards.
You can just reenact
that stuff.
Which series?
Was there more than one
Mars Attacks bubblegum
card series?
Yes, there was.
Because when the movie
came out, the Tops
company put out
widescreen
glitter
series.
And the Tops
Mars Attacks cards
as well as
more cards
adding a harmful
back story
which marred
the original
Mars Attacks
story line.
Well, then even
better use the
Dinosaurs Attack
cards.
It's a curious
thing about that
series.
You know, Tim Burton
did want to
make a movie
of that,
but instead
he got
sidetracked
into making
a movie
of Mars.
And he
was a little bit
attack series.
I didn't know that.
His original intention
was to film the
Dinosaurs Attack series.
We need some free
women up here.
Or women free.
They did all get in free.
We're woman free right
now at the
Suzy the Flusy
Ladies and Germs, the
women were given free
access to
Baby Bear saw me
looking at her.
Oh, here she comes.
Well, she shouldn't
have paid, certainly.
I don't think any females paid.
So take a look at the
microphone and this time,
for the first time ever,
we have headphones.
Oh, I get my own
headphones.
I've never had my own
headphones before.
Just like good old
radio days.
Wow.
Where's the cough button?
Oh, that I'm afraid
you have to supply
yourself.
Whatever is happening,
I don't care much for it.
The pictures on the screen?
Images of Philo and so
forth.
No, that was G.
Gordon Gordon.
Oh, it was.
Yeah, there was a subgenius
fad about 10 years ago of
putting G. Gordon Gordon's
that face into pornography,
but usually not where the
head was.
There is a vast collection
of those things.
Yes, unfortunately, he was
shamed into leaving the
country for Portugal because
of that.
Now he resides as a citizen
of that nation.
Yeah, that's what they
say.
He got the
passport.
You don't want to know why
he's actually there.
I've got my passport
ready.
Oh, so you're going to go
over and take a Portuguese
fling, eh?
It depends on how the
election works out.
I hear Nova Scotia will be
taking people.
If anyone is elected, I'm
fleeing for some other
country.
I don't know which one.
Anyone?
What if Bob is elected?
Well, that's the one thing.
But see, but, you know,
friends, if Bob is who he
says he is, he's already
won.
You're the world overlord,
and your anxiety over America
turning into more of a police
state is foundless.
Because it's going to be one
anyway.
Under Bob!
Bob does not need the
entanglements and appurtenances
of power.
Slavery.
Already he possesses the
power.
Slavery under Bob is
preferable to freedom under
any other government.
Uh, yes.
The wonder of it.
The wonder of Bob Slack.
The depth of his mighty
treasure vault.
The height of his stacks of
money.
The gleaming gold.
The gold in his vault.
Even Frodo has never seen as
much gold as Bob has.
Hidden, stashed away.
Someplace he forgot about.
And you can run skipping and
noodling.
You can scoot through his
piles of gold.
Scrooge McDuck.
You can roll and loll and
wallow in money.
And then people won't want
that money as much.
If you're Bob's friend.
If Bob invites you to that
party.
The savagery and splendor.
The power, the beauty, and the
majesty.
Are you close enough to Bob
to be invited to that party,
friends?
Have you done for Bob what
makes him notice you?
Oh, come on.
Everybody who's here is Bob.
Bob's buddy, right?
I mean, we've established that.
Wow, the slideshow just came
around to the first picture.
That means we've been exposed to
1,313 graphics of subgenius
nature.
And still we live and breathe.
Oh, yes.
I didn't think that the
subgenius image slideshow could
end.
It can't end.
Doesn't it go on forever?
Subgenius?
The subgenius slideshow shall
never end.
Hey, I made that one.
There you go.
The number of subgenius
Facebook groups is too damn high.
Why is that ever the truth?
I've quoted that one quite a
bit, actually.
The internet makes it really,
really easy to be creative.
You just say something that
someone else said, and then you
put, you know, Slack or Bob or
somebody in front of it.
Yeah, stick a pipe in it.
Just stick a pipe in it.
That's why Nenslo hates it now.
All you do is just stick a pipe
in it.
If you take something that's
current, you can't get it.
You just put a Bob in it.
Oh, is that who that was?
That was Nenslo?
Yes.
He sure is testy.
I assumed it was someone
that was a...
He's a grouchy, grumpy former
...that had the ability to
get away with that because no
one else was saying anything
about it.
He's irascible.
Mothered by stones and wind.
He's a grumpy guy.
Yes.
Big old grumpy Gus.
Become slightly irritable in
his old age, but we remember the
wonderful, wonderful, wonderful
things that he did in the past and believe that...
No kidding.
...even he might come to the embrace of the church once again.
Well, probably if you go over to his house and visit with him, he'd treat you to a great
home-cooked meal and sit down and discuss terrible foreign films with you.
And he'd show you beautiful art and his golden nature guide book of weeds.
And the Kooks Museum.
Right.
That's on the property.
Run by Mrs. Nenslo, Donna Cossie.
Right.
And I think it's well worth visiting.
But of course, while in scenic Portland, you can also view the vertiginous Woodstock
Mystery Hole.
I've been down in that hole.
Oh, I've been in that hole, Dr. Howe.
Terrifying.
Yeah, I went down in it too.
I'll always remember that.
It is truly a mystery hole.
Oh, did you get a little bottle of the Vapors of Encouragement?
No, I did not.
It's a free thing.
You get a little bottle with the Vapors of Encouragement in it.
But were they like, who blessed them?
It was winter and I was wearing a heavy coat and my feet could no longer find the rungs
of the ladder.
They told me to let go and drop the remains.
Oh my God, that's terrifying.
Yeah, you bet.
You look down the mystery hole and the ladder just, in perspective, it dwindles down to
nothing.
It's like it's...
You know, you can see some mining carts and maybe a railroad track down there at the very
bottom.
It's not very clear.
And yet, when you start climbing down the ladder, you magically grow gigantically
huge.
Yes, your feet are unable to find the rungs on this tiny ladder.
And then you find yourself on the ground and there's a little bitty mining cart
and the bottom of the ladder is like...
Turns out not to be so deep after all.
It's a forced perspective mystery hole.
But then there are other rooms down there full of junk or what you have...
There's a little tiny door that's big.
Yes.
I've never been to very many of the roadside attractions.
You have to drink something and then you shrink down.
I've never seen the thing.
I've been down in that hole.
There's another mystery hole, Hal, in West Virginia, not far from Pottery Pet.
Does the thing, can you take it, still exist anywhere?
Baby Bear never saw it?
Oh, yes.
I've never gone on any road trips and stopped at any of that roadside attraction stuff.
The thing outside of...
It attracts me.
I feel a need to go to those things.
I've never been to any of those.
I've never seen those things when I go past them.
But they don't exist that much anymore.
Well, it seems like they're mostly out west, right?
I always heard that the thing, can you take it, was some sort of withered mummy they ripped
out of a burial site or something.
I can show you a picture of it someday.
Not now.
I've got an ultimate spoiler.
All right.
What if I don't know if I can take the thing, though?
Was there only one thing or were there many things?
You can take it.
In fact, when you pull over off of Interstate 10 in Arizona and go to the thing museum,
there are many, many, many things and it only costs a dollar.
Wow.
The thing itself is, in fact, more than one thing.
In a glass vault, it's either a mummy of an Indian woman and her baby or a prop that looks
sort of like a mummy of an Indian woman and her baby.
A pickled punk.
But that's just the beginning.
There's more.
The museum goes on and on.
It's in several warehouse-sized buildings.
It's full of primitive art by a very primitive man who carved an entire torture chamber life-size
out of tree stumps and hand-painted them.
And they're just...
You never know about your next-door neighbors.
It's just crappy enough to be great.
It's full of creatures.
It's full of animals.
And alien little things made of driftwood.
Where monsters prowl.
All over the place.
Where creatures roam.
I envy his ability to follow through on anything.
So, you know, next time you're driving through Arizona, don't miss the thing.
It's only a buck.
It's a good hour-long show of stuff to look at.
There's also sort of a...
Yeah, what's the big hurry anyway?
You know, here's the true story.
The cartoonist Gilbert Shelton and his wife Laura were driving and they came to the thing
and Gilbert said, you know, I always wanted to stop in and take a look at that.
And she said, well, you can go, but I'm going to sit right in the car because it's just a waste of time.
And so that's what happened.
She sat in the car and Gilbert went in.
He paid the admission.
He looked at the thing.
And then he came out and he said, well, what was it?
And he said, well, you didn't pay the admission.
So I'm afraid I can't tell you.
And he's never told her yet.
What an example of marital cruelty.
What happened?
Oh, don't worry.
Don't worry.
I don't want a telephone or a calculator.
That's too much.
Get rid of that stuff.
Oh, there you go.
Burma GURBS.
Okay, if you say so.
Yes.
Roadside Attractions of America.
By the way, the people who wrote the Roadside Attractions book and do that website are dues paying subgeniuses.
And they got their deal through our sacred agent, the late Jane Brown.
Praise Jane.
A lot of roadside attractions have actually fallen into disrepair.
And now you visit the crumbling, vandalized by teenagers ruins of roadside attractions like pathetic Fred Flintstone Village.
I was going to mention Bedrock.
Is that still there?
I'm afraid not in the form it was when it was in its healthy heyday.
It was pretty run down when I saw it, but that was 20 years.
No.
But I found out about the dinosaur park in, I think, Virginia that some tea party guy ran.
And he decided that he would show how the South really won the Civil War because dinosaurs came and ate Abe Lincoln and the Union Army.
And it's this whole diorama of dinosaurs munching the horrible Yankees in the Confederate's triumph.
So when I told Puzzling Evidence about that, he made sure actually to go to that place and video it extensively and then even get into a conversation with the caretaker of the park, which revealed many truths.
My book.
Well, before the world ends, some of the world's most important things are going to be destroyed.
Some people may be making a pilgrimage to what is it?
Mount Pleasant?
That's us.
Mount Pleasant, New York.
No, no.
What is Point Pleasant in West Virginia?
Oh, Mothman lives.
Mothman.
Yeah.
They have a statue of Mothman.
And I've never been there, but I've seen Reverend Fox's pictures.
And when you see it, you say statue.
Maybe it's not a statue.
Yeah, maybe that ain't no statue.
Maybe that's old Mothman himself.
Yeah.
John Keel basically told me he made all that stuff up.
Well, we don't have to spoil people's yearnings and beliefs.
You'd be surprised.
You know, when you're an outspoken subgenius, I've had people...
There's no such thing.
That doesn't exist.
All subgeniuses beat around the bush.
I've had rival cult leaders come up to me and go, keep on doing what you're doing, man, because it is all bull.
Bullshit.
Isn't it?
Some very respected Wiccan, that couple, I don't want to say their name, but they basically said, yeah, we're glad somebody knows this is all a bunch of crap.
Well, you can look it up in Wiccanpedia.
On the other hand, I tried to talk to the great Zukowski, who was really the guy who came up with the Yeti.
The descendants of the Yeti theory, but I tried to tell him...
But not as the subgeniuses.
No, he believes that the Yetinsen, and that's his term, that we're the bad guys, but we're the ones behind corruption and murder and evil, and that the humans are the good guys.
How could that be true?
And I broached this subject at a convention to Zukowski himself, and I had the experience of being brushed off as a kook by Zukowski himself.
Prince of kooks himself.
He looked at the audience and goes, after I said, sir, I've read your book, and we in the church as subgenius really agree with you about every point of that, except that we think that the Yetinsen are the good ones.
And he looks at the audience and kind of rolls his eyes and doing this.
There's one in every crowd.
Well, you see, some people read my book and they get some funny ideas of their own.
It's a very strange idea of mine.
It is.
Yep.
Ah, that was a proud day.
It's like the Morlocks.
The Morlocks are painted as the bad guys.
Right, exactly.
They're our children, our descendants.
How can we be so mean to the Morlocks?
Yeah, they're the ones that can still create and build.
They still keep the machinery running and the groceries coming in.
By the way, if you've never read the sequel to The Time Machine, which is called The Time Ships.
The Time Ships.
By Stephen Baxter, definitely check it out.
Oh, don't worry.
It's just a JPEG.
It's a fine, fine book.
It's a fine book.
Well, I didn't know.
It looked like some sort of computer symbol.
Well, there it is again.
If you say that's all right, it must be you.
What is this?
Image has been redacted.
What is this we're listening to?
Well, I don't know.
It's something you need.
What kind is this?
You're the one in control.
Yeah.
Rice Song.
That's all it says here.
Well, Reverend Baby Bear, how do you find the camping conditions at X Day?
Well, I've only been here for, you know, not even an entire day yet.
But so far it seems nice.
But there have been no insect outrages or other things going on?
There's cicadas everywhere, but...
The last of a dwindling breed.
A bee landed on my chair this morning, and I gave it up to him.
I let the bee have the chair.
Well, that was gracious of him.
Princess Wee was bitten by a spider in bed in the big house.
And she saw a mouse run under the bed.
Boy, they just won't let her be.
We really are in the wild.
She jumped on a table.
And went, eek, a mouse!
Just like in cartoons.
A wonderful living stereotype.
Yeah.
Well, that's good.
Because no wasp has trespassed this year.
I have been menaced.
That's a cue for a wasp to land on your microphone.
They came and hovered about you once again?
Yeah, I saw some behind you guys earlier, actually.
Well, I prefer simply not to know that they're floating, hovering, darting.
Well, with the headphones, it's an entirely different...
thing for me now.
If I don't hear them, then they can't scare me.
And I don't have to run, shrieking and bawling and weeping.
On radio, what is not heard does not exist.
What you can't hear won't kill you.
Well, why do you think we do?
We've done these thousands and thousands of hours of shows.
The wasps don't bother us when we're doing radio, because we've got the headphones on.
Yeah, but I've never been given a pair of headphones.
I hadn't earned my membership stripes yet.
Now you've stepped down.
I've stepped up to big pay.
I have stars on my shoulder pads.
You'll get your new epaulettes in the mail.
Dr. Howell was with me when I bought those new headphones.
Yes.
I thought, just think how good they'll look on Baby Bear.
I actually have a really good pair of headphones that I probably should have brought.
You could bring them, but you know, every time you bring them, you risk their being damaged by some goofy, overenthusiastic subgenius.
I also had a mummified lizard for Susie, and I've also forgot that.
Well, if it's truly mummified, it'll wait until another occasion.
It'll keep you.
And now, for the first time, we are bringing you the full story of one of them.
I named him Carl.
We are giving you all the evidence, based only on the secret testimony of the miserable souls who survived this terrifying...
He's done it again!
What did I... the incidents?
Places.
No.
My friend, we cannot keep this a secret any longer.
I thought when you...
If that's your heart, it's supposed to be true.
...stand the shocking facts of the world...
...and its unsurfaceable evil.
The idea.
Who do they think they are?
The nerve.
Oh, okay, that's... that's... that's moving. That's moving. The slideshow's moving along.
Alright, yeah, we're moving, we're grooving.
Recording.
In the groove.
Everything's going fine.
Recording.
This is the theme from Ed Wood, the movie.
Mm-hmm.
Background.
You know, I... when I was a young shaver, I was actually following what all those characters were doing.
As I'm sure you were, too, because one of them, though not shown in the movie, was a certain Forrest J. Ackerman, who hung out with the rest of those weirdos.
And if the movie had been more accurate, should have been shown in the entourage.
So I knew about Ed and Vampyra and Dolores Fuller and, uh, of course, Lugosi.
You know, Ackerman slavishly followed Lugosi and, uh, managed to get his ring and, uh, see him sleeping in his coffin and everything else.
He has the original Lugosi Dracula ring with the bat on it, or did have it at the time of his death.
These are the things that subgenius doctors know and others don't care about.
Well, it's true. They're happy, uh, healthy, uh, uh, usual normals that don't care about.
I don't know about those things.
I know about Disney villains and all the Pokemon, the original ones.
The Disney villains were good, especially the female ones.
Those were the monsters that I came up with. Pokemon and, uh, Disney villains.
Those are cute monsters though, aren't they?
What?
Maleficent.
They're cute monsters though, aren't they?
Stepmother.
I mean, some of them. They range in cuteness.
Look, if everything in the world is cute, then the monster is still a monster, though cute.
There's like dragons and stuff.
Yeah, cute ones.
There's weird ugly toad monsters.
So you can play weirdos and dragons.
Ah, yes, yes, yes. No, no, no. I'm starting to get kind of tired.
Oh, fuck up.
I've been tired the entire time.
Well, we were up to the, we were, uh, I, the, the bands were, uh, whatever that thing was last night.
Roystering until cock crow.
Yeah, that went on until like two or three in the morning, and then we had to strike the set and, you know, wrap it up.
I was up.
Hide the microphones.
I was up until the birds were twittering.
Were you on mic?
They all had their iPads out, and they were twittering.
Lucky Mike.
Tweeting.
And smaller foolers makin' melodia that's slapin' all the nicht with open ear.
For not your pricketh him in her corages, as the poet says.
Yeah, that guy.
Hey, anybody else want to come up here and engineer this show and talk?
And sit in for Ivan Stang, who's just too feeble and weak to continue.
I've, I've been, uh, I know the subgeniuses for what they was, and I know J.R. Bob Doggs for what he was.
There, there. It's all right.
My family, while crossing the Great Highway, was attacked by a band of normal humans.
I was raised among them.
And forced to do as they did.
Learn their ways.
The Pink Boys.
And I'll never forgive them.
I will never forgive the Pinks what they did to me.
And you will smite down upon them with righteous fury.
I shall.
My power, the great power that Bob Doggs has granted me
is eclipsed only with
by the great pleasure
that I shall experience
upon that day called X.
Yes, they shall grovel at your feet.
Right? They're gonna grovel.
See, you need a cough button up here.
I'm afraid that's something that only the effete radio stations of civilization have.
Not Tarzan's free and easy, uh, radio station.
What are you doing?
We don't have a cough button.
Do we, sir?
Here in the jungle.
No, when you do professional radio, you're supposed to have one of those little slide whistles that goes
and a quack, a little quack sound effect.
And I'm trying to find my nose flute.
Oh, no.
Well, maybe it's time.
I must have put it away safely. That's okay.
We'll go without the nose flute.
We're safe for the time being.
I just needed to blow my nose, and I thought I might as well kill two birds with one stone, you know?
Sing a little song while cleaning it out?
Yes.
Kind of a bubbling.
No warbling.
Ever thought of sending your sinus to Arizona?
Oh, I'd love to, my sinus and my, the rest of me to go to Arizona more often.
And get cleaned out.
I like the rocks.
And the vitamin D. So freely available.
I like places that look like there should be dinosaurs chasing you.
They're just behind the next rock.
Yeah.
And we've got, uh, petroglyphs out there.
Including some that sort of look like dinosaurs, but you've seen those, right?
You know, uh, before there were movies, and before there were even stage plays or books, there were petroglyphs.
And I can imagine that there was, there was probably a sort of a George Lucas or a Spielberg of petroglyph makers,
where people would go, have you seen Ogg's latest picture?
Man.
It's like, it's so real, it looks just like a horse.
And, but there's no horse there.
I can't wait for, I hear he's working on a new picture.
I wonder what his next picture's gonna be.
I heard it's gonna be in color.
Now he's invented negative space.
Let's kill him.
Now really, I mean, think about it, there, there, not, I'm sure not everybody was drawing petroglyphs.
No, not everybody had enough time to draw petroglyphs.
A lot of people had time only to be drawing petroglyphs.
I know.
Chased 20 miles by a bellicose mammoths, and then eat two caterpillars and a blackberry.
But it's the near-sighted cave man that invented religion.
Well, he didn't have the glasses, you see.
He couldn't, he couldn't, he was no good at throwing rocks at rabbits, but he learned how to make little fat ladies out of clay.
And he got rich.
Well you must be familiar with-
Cos that was like, pornography has driven me about cheap!
Robert Crumb's wonderful story.
art forever. Are you familiar
with Robert Crumb's comic
Cave Wimp? Yeah.
I had that same theory before I saw that
comic. That's a great story.
Yeah, that's where
the near-sighted caveman
was the one who came up with the
religion idea and art.
And for a time was quite successful
and managed to pass his DNA
along to create future
generations of wimps
in later periods.
When all the other men go out to hunt
only the wimps stay back.
Right.
With, you know,
females.
Yes.
But this irritated
not only the... It doesn't sound as dirty when I say it
because I'm not an old man like you guys.
It irritated the male cavemen
but it really irritated the
crone cavewomen
who said that things were getting
out of order and they,
the real power in the tribe,
got the burly cavemen
to throw cavewimps into the tar pit.
But as he went under, he
realized he managed to
pass along his seed
to future generations.
Well, he had created an unrealistic
ideal woman that it was hard for
starving cavepeople to live up to.
This really fat
female figure.
Voluptuous.
Yeah, that was the, obviously,
that was what the kind men
like in those days. But just as today,
the conspiracy tries to make it real,
you have to look like a Monster High girl.
You have to be skinny.
You have to be Barbie.
Oh my gosh. Have you turned on Monster High?
No, no, not at all.
Well, I'm upset that they're all pretty.
They're all skinny.
There's no fat Monster High girl.
And I think, I mean the whole point of the thing is
everybody's different and you embrace your abnormality.
That really is the running thing behind it.
Except they're hypocrites.
I've been learning more about it.
You're watching?
I like, no, I just like looking,
I like to go to the toy store, like anytime.
And view the action figures.
I'm anywhere where the toys are.
And just check out what kids are getting now
that I didn't get and then just seethe bitterly about it.
Well, now you're an adult.
You're gonna buy it unlike the kids.
Well, it just doesn't, it's not the same.
But I just like to see the different, you know,
the different things they come up with
for the Monster High dolls.
I do that too. I do that too.
I go to the toy section and just wistfully, you know.
It looks a little weirder when you do it though.
I could afford that stuff, but I don't really need.
I did, we did buy one Monster High character.
It was a new one from the movie Scarier Reef.
It wasn't Draculino, was it?
No, it's the daughter of,
we thought it was the daughter of Cthulhu.
Because she has tentacles for legs.
She's really sexy looking.
Of course they all are in a monster-y way.
Sounds like some that I know.
And the back, it said, daughter of Cthulhu.
Daughter of question mark.
Now they're all the daughter of some monster or another.
Is it the Kraken?
Usually they're obvious.
It turned out to be the Kraken.
Oh, okay.
But I didn't.
I'm sorry. Spoiled the story.
We learned that when we saw the movie.
But when we saw the toy box, I thought, man,
I bet it's supposed to be daughter of Cthulhu.
And I just don't want to deal with the royalties
for Lovecraft Estate if there is such a thing.
But no, it turned out to be the daughter of the Kraken.
And she was a villainess in that particular one.
I wouldn't be surprised if they had
a daughter of Cthulhu.
My eight-year-old cousin knows who Cthulhu is
and types him in on Scribblenauts and he appears.
Good.
I hope an accurate depiction.
Once an elder god, now a cute, fluffy toy.
A plushie.
A plushie exists.
Shee hee hee hee hee.
Well, but at night it may metamorphose
into a more accurate miniature, which then grows.
I had a list of the characters.
I had a list of...
Like in Jack the Giant Killer.
I had a list of the correspondences
between subgenius women and the Monster High girls.
And Baby Bear, you corresponded to Draculaura
because of physical resemblances.
And she's kind of squeaky voice too.
I think, actually I still have that sticker.
I have the Draculaura sticker.
I put it on one of my boxes of magic cards.
APO Stacey corresponded with the daughter of Cthulhu.
The daughter of the Yeti.
Abbey Bominable?
Yeah, Abbey Bominable.
How could I forget?
It's Apostasy.
Yeah.
But...
No, APO Stacey.
Apostasy.
Well, that's...
Why are you saying that's an apostasy?
You know, this is like people who suddenly realize
that we are dough.
Weirdo.
Now I get it.
13013.
Simpsons episode.
Mrs. Crabapple.
Oh no.
Nobody ever thought of that.
Yeah.
But, you know, it could be like a regional pronunciation difference.
Like the difference between aluminum and aluminium.
Well, that's just wrong though.
There's no...
It's crazy stuff.
That's insane.
Apostasy.
There's not that many eyes in aluminum.
That's too bad.
There's one singular eye.
But it sounds kind of shimmery and aluminiumy.
Well, you know how those British people are.
They have to add an extra letter to everything.
They add some letters that don't...
It's not that long.
Or it couldn't be that we just dropped letters being ignorant settlers in the New World or
anything.
No.
If you're referring to what I'm thinking of, it is because we're better Latinists.
But what?
I had a friend who went to London to work at a kids' science museum there.
And the kids there asked him to say words in an American accent all the time, just like
people pester people with British accents.
They shrilly tittered and giggled?
Yes.
They would surround him and they'd be like, say aluminum again.
And he would just be like, aluminum.
And they're like, oh, it sounds so funny.
Listen to the funny Yankee, mommy.
Ah, well.
Who's going to fight the next war?
The next generation.
And that reminds me.
You know what?
What we ought to do is get those little kids that were doing that show last night up on
that stage, the little rascals.
The kids?
Yeah, the kid, the kid, Julie show.
The kid, fid, Julie show.
Well, yeah, they're going to dress up in funny costumes and put on a show.
The whole time I was thinking, God, I wish I had a...
This is where I should have brought that recorder up there to get the line recording because
it was all vocal stuff.
You do have a recording of this session, don't you?
I have four.
Four.
Well, there you are.
Simply edit it in at this appropriate moment and regale the audience with a recapitulation
of what happened on the main stage.
No, but seriously, we're old and we should let one of these shows be done by the...
Let them try to stop them.
Those poe buckers.
There's one.
See that Reverend Fox?
He's coming up there.
He's coming right up here right now.
We only have three mics.
What is happening?
But I'd love to get that.
I'd love to get up and go take an ibuprofen and a pee and...
Well, why don't you take your Geritol, grandpop, and we'll put Fox in to pinch hit for you.
Yeah, that's going to run for 30 minutes.
This will run forever as far as I know.
But you'll pop down those pills in no time.
The music may run out, but where's the...
But these colors never run.
Oh, yeah.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to...
I can't...
I must describe Reverend Stang, quivering and palsied with rheumatism, is getting up,
leaving the dais, and now Reverend Fox is going to make news in his stead.
While Stang goes to charge his phone...
And his batteries...
I will be here.
He's just going to play Monster Hunter.
I will commandeer the knobs.
There's a lot of knob handling to go around here.
Twiddle them.
Between here and Gobbler's Knob.
Delicately.
Infinite variances on knobs.
Did you know that there was a Cthulhu region of Pluto, the dwarf planet recently given a flyby by robots from Earth?
Cthulhu Regio, which can be located on an image of that strange-looking planet,
which actually turns out to be rather attractive in its own way.
Oh, he's very cute.
He's a little cute guy.
Spinning balls of frozen anger.
There's also Tombog Regio, named for...
All right, guys, Dad's gone.
Time to throw a party.
...discoverer of Pluto, Clyde Tombog.
That's Tombog Regio, not Topo Gigio, just in case there's any confusion there.
But not the dog.
No, the dog also appeared in 1931.
We're not talking about the dog.
No, the dog appeared a little later than the actual discovery of Pluto,
which was named by Tombog's little daughter, but not out of the Disney canon,
because, strangely enough, the cartoon Pluto also appeared,
but slightly later at that point in humanity's evolution.
That's really Cthulhu's true form, is Pluto, the dog.
And now we know that Pluto and its giant moon, Charon,
are actually a kind of binary system,
orbiting around each other,
while two smaller, satanically named moons
zip and dart around the parent planet.
They're just lazy. They can't get their stuff together.
And then why does Pluto have an atmosphere, as apparently it does?
We thought it was a frozen lump of ice and rock,
and apparently it's active enough to have an atmosphere of its own.
What's in it?
Well, I don't know. I've never been there.
I don't know about myself, but informed minds are speculating
that it is perhaps the lost planet Yuggoth,
mentioned by H.P. Lovecraft in his work The Whisperer in Darkness.
But beyond Pluto, there are all sorts of newly discovered planets in our system,
like the planet Biden, named after our current vice president, Joseph Biden.
Good old Uncle Joe.
I hadn't heard of it.
Well, have you heard of the ones named...
You know, they no longer use Greek gods,
so they're using Eskimo deities and so on.
There's the planet Quawar,
and the planet Sedna out there,
way far out in the inky darkness of space.
And many new objects which are floating out there,
called the Centaur objects,
which orbit between Neptune and the outer reaches of the solar system.
Hidden craft among the planets here within our own solar system.
And we occasionally get bombarded when a rock gets out of the asteroid belt.
But mighty Jupiter sucks most of them up,
sparing the Earth from destruction and grief.
We saw some of that last night around the fire,
some space junk just hurtling through the atmosphere and exploding.
There's a big meteor shower a-coming this way.
That's...
No, no, no.
But most of it will be...
Those are the souls of the damned, falling from the sky.
They'll be falling on Earth, unable to appreciate their beauty.
Salt it.
Don't ever need anything here again.
Salt it away for the indefinite future.
Yum.
Well, that was...
I'm just hearing...
snappy dance music, just barely, on the soundtrack.
I wonder why it's turned down so low.
We're just riding...
Yeah, how do we get the...
Don't, don't, don't.
Not that one.
Oh, he knows how to operate a slider.
Don't you? Just slide them up.
That's why they call them that.
Well, if it's...
You put the stuff on the...
Just see what makes the mambo music louder.
And if it doesn't put them...
There you go.
Now we're having a mambo espresso party right here in Caffeinas.
Everybody's happy, having a good time.
We're slugging down huge Irish coffees, Scotch coffees,
Northumbrian coffees, Cornwall coffees.
Mugs full of hot dirt.
Yeah, just like Mother used to make.
It's hard to find good coffee.
It's hard to find good dirt.
This is some fine soil around here.
But this used to be a strip mine, correct?
A series of spirit mounds,
including the mighty turtle mound commemorating Old Sequoia.
Old Sequoia.
Some of you have received cryptozoic maps,
which were tipped into your registration booklet this year.
And they show the location of many of the...
hidden species in the American continent,
including Old Sequoia,
also including another Ohio monster type,
known as the Loveland Frogmen.
Yes, under stealth of darkness,
these amphibious, slimy beings,
hunched over, crawl by night.
And there's only one way
to find out what they're up to.
You have to become one of them.
You could just poke them with a stick a whole lot.
Yeah, they're not covered.
They're easy to poke.
If they're out there, then why are there so many cicadas?
Just like Gig and a frog.
Well, the cicadas recently had their 17-year appearance.
And the ones that you see now are the last outriders.
It may have fulfilled their biologic function.
And be ready to perish,
knowing that 17 years from now,
or so they think in their childish innocence,
the new generation will crawl forth.
I was camping in the spring
as they were erupting from the ground.
Were they singing?
It started raining, like, as soon as we got there.
And they were just...
It was gross.
It was really gross.
Chirping away.
And Susie was telling me about the locust.
Yes.
Her friend that she encountered.
It was dancing.
Susie did her interpretation of the locust dance,
which I think was...
I saw it.
It did apparently appear to be dancing.
I couldn't figure that out.
Maybe its feet were slipping in some complicated way.
But why did it repeat those movements?
Maybe it had gotten into somebody's fromp stash.
Maybe.
Maybe everyone was blowing fromp on it
and confusing its little brain, possibly.
Or maybe, as I said,
it was just sort of a puppet,
jerked about by instinct,
irrelevant, now that it had finished
contributing to the future locust stream.
Gross.
I don't want to swim in that.
Oh, no.
Well, I dare say you won't have to.
Those locusts will be only a memory.
That's a good one.
Yeah, that's an expensive luxury over in Japan,
is the locust bath, though.
You know, filling up over to your knees
and just a pool of warm, spiny legs.
They're only as warm as their environment.
But how about these...
Them guys are weird over there.
...bee keepers who get a huge beard of bees on themselves
and then get photographed grinning under a beard of bees
in all the bee magazines.
That's like the most horrendous thing
I could possibly...
Like the buzzing,
just being...
having to sit completely still while it's...
It's like a centerfold in the bee magazines.
The buzzing, the buzzing.
The monthly bee beard.
Yes, the bee keeper,
the weekly bee keeper,
they always have these burly guys
covered with a beard of bees
in the photos that are snapped and sent in.
But as you know,
if one stings, it's a chemical signal.
They all sting.
And then you don't want a beard of bees.
A bunch of bees created a...
A bunch of bees created havoc and mayhem
in California just recently.
They went on a rampage,
stinging everybody in the neighborhood.
And authorities were called and saying,
oh, these must be killer bees from Mexico.
And the result?
Nuh-uh.
They're ordinary bees who decided to go on a rampage
and they stung two little dachshunds to death
so that they swelled up and resembled jumbo dogs.
That's, uh...
And they followed people down the street,
a-stinging them,
and into their houses, too.
Yes, this was the days when the bees stood up
and said they weren't gonna take it anymore.
I blame the schools.
I blame Jerry Seinfeld.
He's an anti-bee?
Oh, he...
No, he stirred them up
with his propaganda, political propaganda film.
Somebody stirred them up.
He was invigorating those bees to go out
and start taking action.
But instead of legal action, like in his hilarious movie,
they just decided to kill wiener dogs.
I thought that movie was gonna, like, suck
and, like, be really bad.
And finally, you know...
Which movie?
I sat down to watch it.
Bee movie.
Oh.
And, um, it's worse than I thought it was.
But Ant-Man was pretty good, though.
So bad.
But Ant...
Yeah, I liked Ant-Man.
I liked Ant-Man a lot.
I liked Antony.
I liked his riding ant.
Well, how about the ant that was...
accidentally enlarged and became dog-sized
and a family pet under the table
being fed by his daughter?
Yes, that was a nice outcome.
I think pet ants would be a wave of the future.
You know, if the planet is going to be completely
soaked in this bloody radiation.
Too big to communicate with the colony
by the usual method, so now it's on its own
and becomes like a beloved family retainer.
And then we have...
And then when they die, you just hollow them out
and you use them like a chip and dip bowl.
You can turn them into decorative furniture.
How ex-Kyton.
We need more giant bugs.
They used to be a staple of Hollywood movies.
Why would you wish for that?
The Deadly Mantis, the Earth vs. the Spider...
It's not a wish, it's hope.
Them.
Hoping for giant bugs.
Ant Farm Dickhole.
Large enough to see.
Well, I missed the Ant Farm Dickhole movie,
but that was shown a few years ago at X Day.
I mean, as long as we're on the topic of oversized insects.
You gotta mention that one.
A few years ago, after X Day, I was in New York
and I saw a number of vendors,
and one of them was selling honey,
and he had these bear statues.
Oops, I mentioned bears.
Well, he had these statues,
and they were covered with honey,
and they were covered with bees,
but the amazing thing was,
these bees who were flying around his head
seemed perfectly habituated to him.
And while I was standing there,
one woman asked him,
do they ever, you know, sting you?
And he said, oh no, they never sting me.
And he reached up and he picked one out of the air,
and then he put it on the palm of his hand,
and the bee lay on the palm of his hand
while he stroked it with his finger,
and its little abdomen moved in and out.
And he claimed that the bees never harmed him,
and that he was the bee daddy and all sorts of things,
just to sell his honey, I imagine.
Just pushing that honey.
But I never saw anybody take a bee in flight out of the air
and then pat it while it was lying on its back.
Oh, you had taken it out of the air.
I didn't understand that.
I wrote an article about this
that was published on rawstory.com,
years ago, a number of us were writing on that national news blog,
rawstory.com,
even Ivan Stang,
until Pete Goldie wrote an incredibly offensive email
that got us all kicked off rawstory.com.
Oh, that's what happened?
Yes, it turned out that he wrote a very offensive letter.
Well, I never...
I am less than surprised.
He certainly knows how to twist the knife,
and they said,
who is this guy?
Let's get rid of this whole bunch of people.
After they sent him to cover some NASA convention, too.
A NASA convention?
A NASA event of some kind,
since he's a NASA liaison himself,
a science and astronomy expert.
One of them rocket boys.
Yes, no rocket jockey he,
but a plane crash archaeologist
who goes to the sites of former plane crashes
and ghoulishly sifts through them for artifacts.
Like recent aircrafts?
Like aircrafts that are falling out of the sky now?
Historically recent.
Wherever an airplane crashed,
he's gone and he's pulled out items
that were buried by the impact
or survived the fireball.
Oh, he's a grave robber.
Okay.
A tomb raider.
All for scientific purposes, supposedly.
Supposedly.
He doesn't have the boobs for it,
to be a tomb raider.
To be a tomb raider.
Apparently Lara Croft is resented
by a lot of fanboys
who write bad things about her online.
Is there anything that fanboys don't resent?
Well, there is that.
Browsers.
Posts.
computer animation
of Lara Croft being
sexually outraged and
they write
snippy things about how
she's not so great.
Easy to knock her down to size.
I'm paraphrasing. They don't use
those terms. Well, we can use all that
juicy Wi-Fi now and we can just
pull up all these articles on our phones.
Yeah, and read them. In fact, that should be
the whole show. We should just read things
off of our phones for another hour.
All at the same time.
Yeah, all at the same time.
How many
Facebook accounts can we get?
We don't have enough.
We don't have enough microphones.
We need at least 10 or 12 people simultaneously
reading off of their phones.
Don't forget that not only
are some of us being
heard right now, but all of us
will be heard in the
future.
Because of these recordings. And so
to you future folk
out there listening to us,
judge not the subgeniuses
too harshly
for the quality of this Bobcast.
But there are going to be
more live Bobcasts
throughout X-Day
so far. Yep.
Ferg has had the interactive
subgenius web stream
thing.
And we've been interacting.
In fact, I think more
interacting with the audience through
the phone than
the web.
Than the actual audience
here. In fact, most of the audience
I think started yelling at people on the
phones last night. I think that was
what was going on at 3 or 4
when the microphones were
hidden away from
ranting and raving subgeniuses.
Pride from their hands.
I didn't pay for the Wi-Fi, but
I just, you know,
I just miss it so much. You're not supposed to pay
for anything this year.
I just miss Wi-Fi.
Yeah, I know.
Your Wi-Fi ticket.
I miss the meal ticket.
I miss the Facebook
app. I need to tweet about
something. We're running out of tortillas and peanut
butter at camp. Who can you shame
when there's no Facebook
to interact with?
I just want to know what's going on on BuzzFeed.
Well, it's alright. It's only a
brief interruption.
There's amazing, fabulous products out there right now
and I need to know what they are.
I need to purchase things.
What is the deal of the day on NewEgg.com?
Someone look it up.
I need to know.
It's Steam Summer Sale.
Yes.
I could have spent all of this money on video games.
No!
Which, it is alleged, will complete your slack.
Just get this one final object and you'll be four square.
Four square or eight square?
Squared away.
Four cube.
I was looking at the hypercube information that we had here.
What you're seeing there is the show.
The shadow of the hypercube.
Eh? Eh?
Can't show the actual hypercube itself in our dimension.
But we can look at the shadow
and not be
destroyed
or overwhelmed.
There are some wonderful cube animations that ran on the stage last night
when I was able to get in yesterday with Baby Bear.
And we, uh, I leapt on the stage as soon as I got here and, uh,
seriously injured my, my legs.
Oh no!
This has been great.
What happened?
Immediately?
Like immediately as like getting onto the stage.
How's your leg now?
Uh, not too well.
But, uh, we sprayed some Bactine on it and I slapped a bandaid.
Those are two brand names.
I should have said I put on a, uh, a topical spray and an adhesive strip.
At this point, uh, product placement doesn't matter one way or the other.
It's all over.
It's a quaint, uh, terminology.
Lingo from a vanished civilization and era.
But I hope the Bactine did, uh, destroy the germs which were ranging themselves like an army
to enter the violation of your body and your leg wound.
Yeah, I, I think I'm gonna lose my leg by the end of next day.
It's gonna...
But then you'll get a new one that's even better.
I'll just grow three more legs.
They'll all be bionic and can...
I'll have more legs that I know what to do with.
...contain supersonic, uh,
I'd like a leg coming out of the back of my neck.
...pogo sticks that can vault you into the ionosphere.
They make it, make it easier to chew your...
That's in case you fall over, um...
It's easier to chew your own toenails.
There's still the face plant, uh, and, uh, it's nursery.
Nursery?
Is this the, uh, kindergarten edition of the show?
Where does the music go?
Well, to, to grow the face plant.
I don't know, uh...
You're in control.
Uh, as, as, as Stang said, the music might die off and so...
Yeah, he talked a whole lot of stuff, but I wasn't doing a whole lot of stuff.
It had, uh, his prophecies in mind.
It had invariably come true.
I was more interested in the sitting down.
But I can say to you that the music will be heard again.
It will fill the air in its joyousness, uh, air the Leviathan can swim a league, uh, any
moment now, folks.
And go to registration.
Shh.
Now's the opportunity to go to registration while there's no music.
Is there anyone here who's unregistered?
Shh.
I'm unregistered at this point.
Just a bunch of unbreakful deadbeats.
Clearly, everyone in Caffeinas has gone to Princess We and received the special bracelet.
Does anyone have the bracelet except for...
You'll be registered by Princess We.
Like, no one else has one on.
It looks so good on you, baby bear.
It's greenish, uh, color stands out.
I gotta get mine.
Yeah, where's yours?
I came up and talked on the microphone.
What have you been doing all day?
What's that bracelet you've got on?
Is that a wisteria bracelet?
This is the wisteria bracelet.
But you've also got to get the subgenius bracelet.
You have to get the subgenius electric bracelet.
Electrostimulotron-o-matic.
Oh, you don't know what it is because you can't read it because you don't have yours.
It's an official X-Day electrostimulonegative reinforcement control.
So you guys should just get your bands and then you can be on the bandwagon and you don't
have to worry about being banned.
Get your band on.
Get banned or get banned.
Yes.
Put your band on or be banned.
It's your fate.
It's your fate in the Church of the Subgenius.
My band is inside the shadow of the hypercube.
Join the Yeti band now.
And here they come, hundreds of subgeniuses from over the hill.
Shuffling along, hunched over, swinging their arms, anxiously awaiting induction.
Valiantly riding on their horses.
Of dirty, stained money and filthy clothes.
The proud, the tall.
A fistful of dollars.
The avaricious, the arrogant.
Grasping.
For a few more fistsful of dollars.
And dynamite.
A few fistsful of dynamite more.
A few more stark fists of dynamite.
That'll make them wake up and take notice.
Think they can push me around.
Yeah.
It's easy to push with a fist though.
We need more fists.
Unless you encounter a fist of equal strength and weight covered.
Coming from the other direction.
Then you have the impasse.
The tie that needs to be broken.
Well I have upper body strength of like a ten year old so anybody can do that.
Well.
I have a weak leg.
You never know what you can do when it comes to the point of crisis.
You can draw on inner resources.
I could drink some more of that crazy bourbon cola that we grabbed.
There you go.
You're formulating a plan already.
Yeah.
I just get jacked up on a whole lot of sugar.
Then we'll start throwing some fists around.
That's using the old noggin.
Consume sugar.
Nature's perfect food.
A non-alcoholic drink that tastes like it has bourbon in it.
So kids can finally get the taste of bourbon that they've been waiting for for years.
Otherwise known as a why bother.
Why not?
Get them hooked.
Get them hooked early.
Well when you can drink actual alcohol.
To drink fake beer for a year.
Yeah.
Fake beer.
Fluttering beer.
Yes.
That's just water.
For free information see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community