Oh, let's have a...
They just won't, they just won't, they just won't, they just won't let me be.
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
I don't know.
This is Ivanovich Hagen, and this is the news.
Wake up, puppet boy!
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm here for the magic!
No trouble.
Get set, and let's go on.
Hit me.
According.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates, and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
And now, the Soap Genius.
Power of slack.
All right.
No.
The subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station...
J-N-O-N.
And only in the city of...
Dallas, Texas.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show,
the listener is advised to remain calm
and only contact listed or unlisted officials
in the event of any material from this radio or other listening device
being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed
to the ultra-high or ultra-low shocks and brain frequencies
constantly scanned throughout our program
should seek shelter in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you
that it's often a photon that light releases,
but truth is, not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time
and all your unpermissible truths are happy truths.
Here is your host...
Reverend Ivan Stang
and Pastor Buck...
Naked!
Go ahead, squirt it out, Buck.
Get it.
I can do it.
You act like I can't do it.
Yeah, I... yeah, well...
Come on, man, this is like pledge drive time.
Let's make some money.
Well...
Bob, man!
Aren't you all glad that we start the new week?
We're going to give you the pledge drive.
Yeah, what about the pledge drive, Buck?
Who wants it first?
And why do they need to pledge?
Who cares?
I mean, who cares?
This is...
Well, we're going to have Dr. Chaos...
Dr. Chaos is going to be on first
and he's going to explain why
we have to do another pledge drive.
What can one individual do in this...
What can one...
...destroyed society...
What can one Criswell...
What can one...
...culture...
What I think that should be asked is
what can one Criswell do to the programming on KNON?
No kidding.
Well, anyway...
Oh, listen to that church air...
You know, just think...
...going by in the background...
If KNON goes down to the Criswell forces,
then for all I know, KVTT will be next.
There won't be any religious programming left.
All just this mushy-mouthed SMU stuff.
There's still K-Sky,
voice of the gospel in the great Southwest.
Ah, yes.
You know, they'll take K-Sky over.
It'll be a monopoly.
Yeah, probably.
It's sad, friends.
So we want you to send that money in
and what...
Aren't we giving a premium?
Or we're both jointly giving premiums.
Right, we are.
We are.
Exactly right.
And those premiums are?
I've got five Bob buttons
and two Praise Bob buttons
and...
four Bobra buttons.
Now, friends, these are badges
that have the official holy emblem
of our high E-pop
of the subgenius church,
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Tell them what you're kicking in, Stag.
Huh?
Tell them what you're kicking in.
Oh, and I'm...
And, friends,
not only do you get that mirror button
that you can show off to your pink,
unknowing, unsavable friends
to show how cool you are,
but you also get...
...the new pamphlet number two.
Now, you subgenius church members out there
already have this one,
and you can hit us up for something else.
But those of you who are merely pledging
and who have never received
the printed word of Bob
will get for free
for your pledge of $20, $40, or $60,
or $7,100,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,000,
one of the...
of the...
these collector's items,
the subgenius pamphlet number two,
Eternal Salvation,
or...
Triple Your Money Back.
Absolutely.
No.
This monstrous tome,
this horror bible of the ages,
can be yours
for only one
minuscule contribution
to
KNON.
And, friends,
without this station,
where would you be?
Tonight's All-Star Night.
Tonight is All-Star Night.
Reverend Buddy West is here.
The commander of the Dick Army Corps,
Ryan Dyer is here.
These are all... these are stars?
Dr. Chaos is here.
These are stars, Buck?
This is All-Star Night.
That's right.
All our major five subgenius radio DJs
that we've had...
In Dallas.
I mean, I'm talking about our five major hosts
are here tonight to, uh, to do, you know...
Tell us.
To make you give money, friends.
To make you turn your pockets...
Well, actually, Brian...
And, if not your very souls inside out,
to empty your guts out,
to have your entrails spilling across your checkbook...
Till it hurts.
Till it hurts, friends.
Until your very lower bowel can grasp a pen
through pure yoga, uh, ability...
They're lighting up.
...and write your name.
They are lighting up.
Once they're lighting up, friends,
once you start sending money,
then we'll play a classic...
No, no, do it now.
...media barrage tape.
Play it now.
Oh, we're...
Well, we're going to now, because...
Thank you.
No, we're not gonna do that bait and switch on you, friends.
We're just gonna...
Oh, yes.
The classic media barrage tape.
This is from, uh...
Now, many of you don't know that the subgenius church existed long before this...
I know, you think it's a joke.
You think it's some stupid, corny dime store version of a joke.
You think it's some battery-operated joke.
But, friends, the joke is...
The Church of the Subgenius has been around and practicing since 1953.
Understand?
And, uh...
This is one of the early media barrage tapes,
which you can...
You can procure for a certain love offering through the church,
but we're not allowed to tell you exactly for how much.
You'll have to write to the number that we'll give at the end of this tape.
Bob is laughing at you, friends,
because you know nothing.
And that our...
And that our money-grubbing DJs...
Be all that you can be...
In the army.
In Dick Armisen.
Join the Dick Army Corps, friends.
Coming in just a few moments...
He's coming.
We will be speaking with...
Dick.
...Reverend Ivan Stang and the Dr.
And Brian Dyers.
...Final Drummond with the Church of the Subgenius.
Just to give you a hint of what this is all about,
I'm going to give you a little bit of a tease about the church...
...right now.
We're living in terrible, perilous, chaotic times.
How has your life changed since dogs came into your life?
The exes are a reality,
and my life is geared towards their arrival.
I redefined my own space and was able to center my being.
When I first heard Bob on the radio,
he said that he could heal,
and told me to put my hand on the radio
so that Bob's energy could come out through the airwaves.
The only cult they want to talk about is the Subgenius Foundation,
the Church of the Subgenius,
and the only reason they talk about it is for the money.
Well, I'm afraid of God.
Oh, you are?
Yeah.
Well, there's a lot of people out there just like you.
I'll tell you what, if you would,
put your hands on the radio,
right now.
If you plan to get saved,
you had better do it now.
There will be a day not in the too far distant future
in which Antichrist will be revealed
and the mark of the beast will be introduced.
We'll have the hand on the radio.
Yes, my wife said.
If he said,
he'd say I chosen goat food.
But maybe he's reminded me
right now,
You little lion, darn you!
Mangalore, he was a mangaloid
Happier than you and me
And he determined what he could say
Like...
Like when you...
You screw something...
Well, dear friends, we have to...
We have to pat down on that one mere second
of Roberto de la Rosa, the zombie for Bob,
who speaks for us all the time.
When we know...
When we laugh...
And you can't...
You can't kick a dog
And they're behind you
And they're kicking me
And...
And his stomach's...
And it's like...
We're gonna be taking calls
on 828-9500 for pledging.
If you want to call us for a talk line,
it's 823-7490 to pledge.
823-7490 to talk on the air,
828-9500 to pledge.
So anybody on the other line,
we'll just let them go,
and call back on 7490.
We...
We don't want to talk to you...
You...
You things out there,
unless you're gonna...
You know, give a little bit of what Bob knows
is most important to you.
You know, Bob doesn't...
Our guru, our high E-pop, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
he does not care for your money,
your lowly money,
nor does he even care for your despicable,
pathetic animal soul,
your friend.
He doesn't care what it is.
He just wants whatever is most important to you.
And here in America,
that's usually your money.
So let's please, dear friends,
if you want to hear any more
of the wisdom of Bob Dobbs,
it could save you,
come that hideous holocaust,
or the holocast, we call it,
because everybody will be watching on TV
until their...
until their flesh is fried off their bones
and with the glorious radioactive kits,
the
No.
Doug will be coming over from...
Seamstresses?
What?
Talk to Dottie and Mike.
They can clue you in.
Yeah, yeah.
Who is this?
An old Little Rock.
Frenchman.
This isn't Carl, is it?
Is this Carl?
Yes.
Oh, great.
That's Dottie.
Friends, you listeners out there,
this is one of the original founders
of the Hate Bob Society.
Those who love Bob enough
to be able to hate him,
and that's the test of a religion, you know?
That's right.
It is.
It is indeed.
So how's Dottie with the young junior over there?
Hey, there's...
They have two junior over creatures,
now.
God, I was at S&OB a year ago,
and they were like junior one.
No, no, there's two now.
You see...
There's two now?
Yes.
Subgeniuses must be fruitful and multiply
and bring forth many young mutants
to further contaminate the gene pool.
Uh, yes.
So what about Hypercletes?
What's the deal?
Well, Hypercletes is a big star, man.
We're just sitting here doing this public radio show.
Hypercletes is performing in L.A.
He's on Johnny Carson.
He's always...
Sick.
What?
Well, not yet, but, you know, any minute now.
We're not talking Jesus Christ, right?
No, we're talking Janer Hypercletes,
the saint of the church, man.
He's...
Man, I'll have to find some Janer tape
and play some tonight for you.
Well, are you in town?
I live in town.
I just happened to pick up on...
I'm sorry.
I'm wondering, uh, practicing, uh,
not quite, uh, overman,
subgenius, but...
I used to jam with Dr. Shabab.
Right.
In other words, you never spent money on the church.
You got everything for free anyway.
That's the truest...
It's called Slack Vampire.
A gimme bob.
Yep.
Well, hey, man, that was Carl, man.
I know it.
He was a gimme bob.
We're not...
We're looking for gimme bobs tonight.
We're looking for pledgers.
Yeah, that's true.
We do need pledgers for the show.
Right.
So let's get on there.
You know, old times was fun,
but, you know, the church will be...
You'll get a lot of money in debt
if you don't contribute,
and we all know that's the truth.
Now, we're gonna put a little tape on here.
This is gonna be just...
Oh, you're listening to, uh,
the Hour of Slack Radio Ministry, KNON.
Uh, I'm Pastor Buck Naked,
and with me is, uh,
Reverend Buddy West and Dr. Chaos,
and we're having us a swinging little, uh,
doctor tape night.
Thought we'd play you all these crazed tapes.
Well, what's next, Doc?
Well, I've got a song here by a band called The Modern Lovers.
It's from an album called Rock and Roll with the Modern Lovers.
This is an instrumental called Egyptian Reggae.
Well, let's listen to that sucker.
Sounds interesting.
Egyptian Reggae.
¶¶
Hi girls.
I want to make great friends.
If we're out too late.
They've only been gotten clean.
The only man who can.
I don't know.
Has to wear the bozo nose.
And just take that job all the time.
Because the bozo nose.
Where the nose goes.
The vanity is the thing.
To be looking all the time.
Right at yourself and going.
What a fool am I.
To be staring at yourself all the time.
And just.
I am the king of vanity.
My nose is on the plate.
I'm going to keep on looking.
So I don't have to know my face.
This time.
It was intact.
It didn't even melt in my pocket.
It didn't even melt in my hands.
It didn't even melt in my nose.
But I'll tell you.
It's melting down my throat right now.
God damn.
It's just a melting weed.
The squeaking universe.
We know about it.
The oozing universe.
But what of the melting universe?
What of it?
Sniffling.
Snuffling.
There's more liquids coated with Novocaine down your throat.
Ah, yes.
The melting universe.
The entire universe melts down from your brain.
And into the complete body.
And it just comes right through.
What we like to do now.
To really get the full amount of this.
Is the brain tactic.
The brain tattooing.
The brain tattooing is the thing right now.
You put these tattoos.
Brain bomb.
You put these tattoos up on the brain.
And then when you take the frame to the brain.
Then it comes off in these nice little kind of shapes.
And squirty little like brands.
Like cattle brands.
Cattle brands that go right down.
Right down your back.
And right down your throat.
Whoa, those doctors are scary.
I mean to be saying those doctors are scary tonight.
Take a hint.
Just like.
Oh man.
What are you guys saying?
I'm a new idiot.
You're listening to KNON 90.9.
The voice of the Yetis.
That's right friends.
And speaking of Yetis.
We've got a big Yeti.
A big old Yeti right here.
Dr. Chaos himself.
He is going to kick off the KNON pledge drive officially.
Doc.
We have written this speech.
Doc wrote it.
And it's here for you now.
And we're going to kick off the pledge drive.
We want our calls on 828-9500.
That's 828-9500.
That is our pledge drive line.
If you want to talk on the air.
Or talk personal stuff.
Or tell me how cute I am.
It's 823-7490.
But tonight it's 828-9500.
For real pledges.
We'll be giving away premiums.
Doc.
What do you got to tell them?
Hello and good evening my friends.
I am.
I am the Reverend Dr. Sardonicus Chaos.
I have an important message for each and every one of you out there.
You know there's an old saying.
That the best things in life are free.
Well my friends.
That is an untrue statement.
A conspiracy lie.
A demonic pink lie.
Slack is one of the best things in life.
And around here.
Slack does not come cheaply.
There is no free ride my friends.
Picture yourself driving through the desert.
When all of a sudden.
Your car's radiator overheats.
You pull over to the side of the road.
And open up the hood.
And the radiator starts spurting like a geyser.
Spewing steam everywhere.
You're stuck out in the desert.
In the middle of nowhere.
And it's five miles to the nearest Stucky's.
Help me somebody.
You figure well.
I'll hitch a ride to the nearest service station.
And get my car towed in and fixed.
But every car that passes you.
Is being driven by a Crizzwell.
Or one of his followers.
Do you think they're gonna stop and give you a ride?
Well you'd better think again friend.
You're probably not pink enough for them.
Anyway.
If the Hour of Slack radio ministry.
Is your vehicle to get you to the land of Slack.
Then you my friend.
Must buy the next tank of gas.
Why?
Because we are under so much pressure from the false churches.
But.
You can help us change that.
Send in those pledges.
Now we know that some of you out there.
I say some of you.
Are Slack vampires.
You listen to the Hour of Slack every week.
And you figure this is great.
No commercials.
No salesman.
No unwanted blah blah being forced on me by the conspiracy.
But you see.
Without your pledge.
We won't be able to continue.
And pretty soon.
You'll be listening to the same old same old.
That everybody else's tone deaf grandma is listening to.
Is that what you really want?
I didn't think so.
Well you know what to do.
Send in those pledges.
Now unlike other ministries.
We do not use guilt as a weapon.
We let.
We let you use your own guilt against yourself.
When you start feeling guilty enough.
You will know what to do.
Dig down deep.
And you will know what to do.
Way way down deep.
No no further than that even.
And give until it hurts.
Send in those pledges.
Thank you.
The number to call.
Is 828-9500.
This is for real.
This is not a drill.
This is a pledge drive.
828-9500.
I'll be out there taking your calls for the pledge drive.
Okay thanks a lot.
Now Reverend Ivan Stang.
I'm going to go get a job.
Or die.
Helpfully brought up a wheelbarrow full.
Of this evening into the studio.
By the church.
By your belief.
Slack is something that when you join the church.
You can do anything you want.
Because it's within your slack.
Well when you.
And if anybody inhibits you.
They are hampering your religion.
And violating your constitutional rights.
That's exactly right.
That's right.
And that's why we're going to court sooner or later for us.
Mockery of everything that's decent and wholesome.
And I challenge you to point out.
National talk shows.
That do not belittle.
Sexual fidelity.
Purity.
That they do not belittle the marriage union.
And the family lifestyle.
That they don't.
Literally flaunt illicit lifestyles.
I mean I challenge you to show me.
A talk show that doesn't make light of God.
The subgenius foundation.
Is a foundation.
The reverend Ivan Spang.
And Dr. Philo Drummond.
And they are.
As we mentioned before.
The dual heads of the subgenius foundation.
If you don't know.
About the school books depositories.
Watch out for all the leads.
Cause I'm number 6742.
Witnessing.
They're coming.
After me.
So come.
They're coming.
Hello there.
My lord do.
We're picking up.
All your.
Transpissions.
With us.
The leader and the idea are one.
But every party leader.
Must.
From the subgenius culture.
Subgenius living.
They're.
Now all this.
Is.
A little.
It doesn't make fun of.
Of God.
They make a mockery of us.
Now we don't have to watch it.
We can turn it off.
Who will pay to clean up the contaminated land.
787-1270 is the number.
Call us and talk about what you'd wish.
Go ahead.
I might point out that a lot of people worry about the one world government.
That the conspiracy is trying to get across on us.
And we.
Suspect that the only thing.
That can fight a one world government.
Is going to be a one world religion.
And of course that's what the subgenius.
The church of the subgenius is here for.
When he says you shall have tribulation.
10 days.
He means you're going to have a maximum.
Of trouble.
And that's just the way things are.
The church is not at home in the world.
Certainly I want to hear about it.
What is sex?
I don't want to hear about it.
But leaders say.
One of the next big pushes.
Is child sex.
Yes.
Oh it's already off.
I mean the freedom for a child.
Do you know for the little child.
No don't touch me.
Don't think I'm not going to tell him about men.
What terrible things men do.
When he grows up he's not going to.
Manhandle any poor little girl.
And do you know that I have not been in a city.
For the last probably five or six years.
Where I have not had to deal with children.
Who this has been their fare.
When they were little children.
Dirty dirty dirty dirty.
Dirty little girl.
Dirty little boy.
I your mother.
I'm going to scrub scrub scrub.
Get that filthy animal out of here.
Out out out.
Are you crazy.
Letting that animal in the house.
I don't want to.
I'm tired.
He cried all day long.
You don't have to take care of him.
If you made more money.
If you made a decent living.
He should have his own room.
He should have a nurse.
We should have a maid.
Said there's so much depression.
Can't keep struggling no more.
Son's becoming husband.
Still in wonders.
Old man turning them daughters into whores.
Do you know even the leading.
Many of the pornographers.
These girls that make these films.
And prostitutes tell of child molestation.
When they were little girls.
Someone sent me an article for Candy Bar.
The famous stripper right here in Dallas.
That made the first pornographic film.
That Candy Bar.
A beautiful girl.
And she indicated.
And recorded somewhere.
I don't remember where they sent the clipping from.
But she said she was molested when she was three years old.
By one of her relatives.
And she learned this thing of sex.
When she was a tiny little girl.
And grew up this way.
And that breaks my heart.
It breaks my heart.
And it's happening.
It is happening.
It's a sick world.
It's more than that.
It's a sinful world.
We have turned our back on God.
Janet takes her clothes off in succession.
While her husband rides a bumper.
In the president's procession.
Sees him on the screen.
And the girl who sent him the article says.
He's a little bit too much for that.
A lover throws her on the bed.
The teacher shows her life.
And so he'll stay.
The music.
Late news.
This is a crooked and perverse nation.
We have millions and multiplied millions of crooked politicians.
God put a death penalty upon adultery.
When we see millions and multiplied millions of people
spending hours and hours before the television
learning how to crack safes, rob banks, kill policemen,
and get divorces and break up homes,
all these soap operas, hour after hour, warps people's minds.
Pull ahead. All decks, condition red.
Yes, yes.
Wednesday is Ladies' Night.
Underscorted ladies admitted free.
Their drinks, 25 cents and 50 cents.
A shy little girl leaving all that she knew behind her.
What this gonna do to kill me, man?
Hour after hour warps people's minds
as shows that they're crooked,
that shows they're perverse,
that shows that they're stupid,
that shows they got warped minds.
That's what people's minds runs on
and that the morals are breaking down
and that's the way it did in the Roman Empire
right before the Roman Empire fell.
Their morals broken down.
Starts on your shoulder
Starts on your back and on your hand
Music
Hey, have a little fun this week.
Enjoy free refreshments, free gifts.
It's a pretty strong church we find and uh...
We need you little brother, how do you do?
Something else about it,
in an effort to get people to stop smoking marijuana
in this country.
The government is thinking about
putting a sales tax on rolling paper.
Yeah, hiss.
You're right, yeah.
Yes.
Wednesday is lady's night.
Unescorted lady submitted free.
There drinks, 25 cents and 50 cents.
A shy little girl leaving all that she knew behind her.
What will this is gon' do?
to kill me, man. Hour after hour warps people's mind. That shows that they're crooked. That shows
they're perverse. That shows that they're stupid. That shows they've got warped minds. That's what
people's minds runs on, and the morals are breaking down, and that's the way it did in the Roman
Empire right before the Roman Empire fell. Their morals broken down.
Backing on your hand.
Straps on your shoulders. Straps on your back and on your hand.
Sores pissing your side. Blood and water flowing through the land.
Hey, have a little fun this week.
Enjoy the rest of your day.
Enjoy free refreshments, free gifts.
It's a pretty strong church we find, and, uh...
We need a new little brother, huh?
Something else about it. In an effort to get people to stop smoking marijuana
in this country, the government is thinking about putting a sales tax on rolling paper.
Yeah, hiss. You're right, yeah.
So...
For school, yet we fall short when it comes to taking care of our own.
I'm looking for one new value.
But nothing comes my...
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Trying to cue up the amazing...
There we go.
This is Kate Ellen.
90 points.
Nine.
FM.
It is KNON 90.9 FM.
This is KNON 19.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Presport.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is Li Liqi, the Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the Hour of Slack on KNON in Dallas, Texas.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you, Dr. Li Li Jing, Pope of all China.
And now, friends, once again, that number to call if you want to keep hearing anything like any of the shows that you hear on KNO.
Then you need to call the number I'm about to give and pledge a little bit of money.
If you call and pledge and say that it has to do with the hour of slack, that you like the hour of slack, that you're pledging because of the hour of slack.
Well, my friend, you'll get a whole bunch of free garbage from the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, indeed.
And now, my friends, we have a guest rant, a quick guest rant from that great old-time preacher, Pastor Reverend.
Dr. Buddy West.
Yes, that's right, friends.
Now, I tell you, tonight's a little bit different, you know.
I don't know what staying naked's doing here.
But now, I'm a little tired, you know, talking about all this slack because I see not too much of it.
And then what I don't see, you know, I suppose it is or it isn't.
But the whole thing is, you ain't getting no bob.
Get down some of that old-time.
No, uh-uh.
No.
No, you want it, don't you?
But you ain't going to pay for it.
No.
Well, Bob knows that.
You think you're going to get some kind of slack?
You think you're going to know slack?
Much less know Bob?
No.
Now, I'll tell you what.
You're going to reach down in your pockets right now.
You hear me?
You're going to reach down there.
You're going to get some of that hard-earned slack.
You're going to send it in this program, KNON.
8-2-8.
And it is 8-2-8, 9,500.
Now, I want to see some of this slack taken out of the phones.
I want to see some of that slack taken out of the phones.
Them buzzers lit up.
Now, I'll tell you what.
Now, you send that money, and within 12 months, and if it don't happen,
well, you just talk to Buddy West, and I will tell you.
Now, you will know Bob, but you've got to send the money.
You can't be a gimme Bob, gimme this, gimme that.
You hear about this slack.
Who is Bob?
What's this all about?
You never know, friends.
You'll never know what it's all about.
You reach down now, right now.
Get some of that slack, some of that real slack,
and you get on them telephone lines,
and I want to see some of them lighting up right now.
8-2-8, 9,500.
That's right.
Pass from night.
Now, what's this that we're handing out?
I want to hear about these buttons.
Okay, let me just explain that real quick.
Bob is sex and money.
You want to pledge more than 30 bucks?
I'll be glad to give you a button.
Stan, I'll be glad to give you a pamphlet.
The 16-page pamphlet, friends.
We'll just keep throwing buttons at you and all sorts of things.
I saw her before where you're going to be sending them
an X number this button and that button.
Now, how many buttons?
We'll tell them over the phone what it means,
but I know that they get one button and one pamphlet
when they send the 30 bucks.
This is a divine pamphlet, friends.
I can guarantee you.
The more you send, the more we'll send you for premiums.
We'll be glad to.
I mean, heck, that's what we're here for.
But it's 8-2-8, 9,500.
What's that number again, buddy?
That number is 8-2-8, 9,500.
You heard it, folks.
It's not like you're sending it.
It's K-N-O-N, and, well, this is almost blasphemy.
I mean, I've never gotten anything free hardly from this church
except for what Bob, in turn, has made me realize what slack is,
and that is it.
And you'll never know if you don't find out,
and the only way to find out is to send it, folks.
Now, we're not kidding.
We've got to keep this.
You want to hear us on the air?
You want to hear this go on?
The only way you're going to make it happen is to call that number,
8-2-8, 9,500, and make a donation.
For the hour of slack.
Help me, somebody.
She ain't got no legs.
My legs are on fire.
Pull the lever.
Down you go.
Praise Bob.
Yes, praise Bob, and you just may think, you know.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack
from the church of the subgenius.
The devil owes you money, friend,
but Bob Dobbs is the bank where you can cash it in.
We got a...
Burn out the banks of the devil.
We got to root him out.
Burn out the hate.
Burn out the radiation.
Burn out the fire.
These words may be harsh.
They may not go down well on the polished ears of the rationalists,
the modernists, those who wish to see proof of Bob,
but I don't care what they say.
I'll keep preaching.
If you go down, pull them with you.
Praise Bob.
Help me, somebody.
Let there be slack.
Don't ruin my life, you susceptible bore.
Drew characteristic to all people
Hold it.
The hundred bulldogs will blow every one of them stone.
Don't you see my point?
No.
Oh, yes, we all love each other.
Ah, yes, dear friend, that's what I want to tell you.
Stop trying to force immorality into the law,
which makes people accept immorality.
Let's respect your love offering,
because the bigger your love offering is,
the bigger my love gets for you, dear friends,
and the more love I spew out there for you.
And Bob spewed his love,
and we're both spewing together,
because we got more love inside us
than we can hardly hold on to.
It's more than enough for one man to get a grip on.
A big old grip on himself.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Ha, ha!
I want to tell you tonight that it just really touches my heart.
Through subversive measures, Devo passes on the word of Bob by, uh...
If you take a look at our last album cover,
his name's been airbrushed into the rubber hairlines
of each of the band members, right next to the word sex.
Do Bob and sex go hand in hand?
Well, Bob is a kind of total all-consuming sex.
We're like explosions
That lead to feeling good
We're like high bills
That change the world for good
There's nothing that's to stop and go
There's nothing but the up and go
There's nothing like some in and out
There's nothing more than what you know
Yeah!
About the only slack that I get anymore
is worshiping at the Holy Temple of Ioni.
Tell us about that.
What's that?
Hmm?
I'm sure your audience knows what the Holy Temple of Ioni is.
Well, can you tell us?
Well, I almost do not know.
It's a female delta.
The Reverend Smith,
this young Reverend Smith has been so instrumental here at the church
in organizing those spread-leg suppers.
Well, see, now this is the thing is...
This is why I have hesitated in asking for...
You're listening to K&N 98.9, the voice of the Yetis.
828-9500, our pledge drive number.
Light a few up, come on.
Light them up. 828-9500.
That's all you gotta do is 828-9500.
Don't pink out.
Don't try to reel in the false slack
or you'll just be listening to another station
very much like the one very near where you're listening to it right now.
And that's not a joke.
That's right, friends.
If you're able to send a little money in,
then you'll be able to hear the media barrage tapes
unsullied by pledge drive rants.
Got me?
Mr. PP's brother.
Mr. PP's brother seems like...
He's gonna speak in just a moment.
No, it's his son.
It's his son?
Yeah.
Okay, well, he's gonna speak in just a moment
as soon as he figures out what to do,
which is call back.
I don't know.
You know, we're getting so overloaded here at the station, friends,
with all this confusion.
You know, we're kicking off the pledge drive tonight.
It's not like the pledge drive's been going on for the next three weeks.
Like, no, I'm only kidding.
It's only a week.
Hmm.
That is really strange.
We got a phone call coming in there, Buck.
No, I guess he kind of lost it.
I guess he's a little pee shy or something tonight, I guess.
Well, in the meantime, friends, walk with us now across Dobbs Square.
828-9500.
There's hardly anyone on the square right now because it's a holy day.
Yes, Dobbs Square.
Let's stroll along this vast public edifice
built during the years of trouble
before our alien space brothers came to show us the true way of Dobbs.
This square, the Dobbs Square, is vast, vast,
easily 15 miles of solid concrete stretching off in all directions
as far, as far as the eye can see,
dotted with magnificent, yet unearthly structures.
Unearthly because of their cyclopean size
and because of the pure bulldada
of their architecture.
To the east, if you look to the east, friends,
towering above the lights of Slack Town
is the Great Hall of the Chosen,
in which great meals of human flesh
and human sacrifices may be had.
To the west, if you look over to the west,
towards the sunset,
you'll see the Forbidden City,
the previous home of Dobbs.
With its 9,000 rooms,
many have gotten lost in the labyrinthian
recesses of this great palace.
One occasionally indeed stumbles across skeletons
of the faithful in the echoing deserted halls.
And up north, ahead of us,
lies Dobbs' tomb, where the public may ascend
the 10,000 steps of the pyramid
to gaze upon the actual body of the Dobbs himself.
Mummified perfectly and preserved in lucite for eternity.
But only those faithful enough to dare the radiation
come close enough to truly peer into the grinning dead eyes
of our high epoch.
Bob Dobbs, these are the ones, my friends,
whose children, for generations untold,
will bear the Dobbs drone gene.
Will you be one, my friends,
will your children be those brave enough
to step up and gaze into the lucite, mummified body of Dobbs?
Ah, yes.
But now, we'll pass away from that better world
and into the mercantile world of the Pledge Drive.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Yeah, the Pledge Drive.
828-9500.
Where's, uh, where's, uh, where's Little P?
Come on, Little P. Come on back, Little P.
Don't be mad at us. We don't know what's going on either.
What are you after?
Oh, this, this guy has been calling us all night,
and every time we try to put him on, it seems like his light goes off,
which is really insane.
Isn't it the truth, Stan?
These mere callers, oh, yes.
Well, what'd you think of cleaved Egyptian music?
Yeah, I thought it was pretty, uh, cosmically, uh,
oriented, if you will.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah, I was kind of right with...
Now, do they know what, what we're doing?
Uh, out of the bottoms of our pockets...
Nobody really knows what we're doing.
We're sending stuff to our, our, uh, supporters, right, Stan?
That's right. To people who ca-
Hey, listen, we haven't gotten hardly any calls.
I mean, maybe 10 or 20,000 calls tonight.
We need at least, we've got our thermometer...
Where?
...chart is only up to about 40,000.
We need to hit 75,000 before this night's over,
or that's it, man. Bob is dead.
The cult of the subgenius is over with.
I mean, there's no more hope for mankind
against the conspiracy.
If you can't manage to dig into your pathetic pocket...
Oh.
...and fish out a mere, oh, $5,000,
or even, you know, 50, 20, 5, okay?
If you're, if you're like me,
merely five...
Fran, do you remember what it was like
when you had nothing like the Hour of Slack?
You only could listen to strange outer space shows like,
you know, Talk Back with the Martians and stuff like that.
And now, here we are.
We're 5% of our pledge goal for tonight.
Only 5%.
Can't you reach into your checkbook
and just cut us a check?
We're not talking about a biggin'.
We're just, we're, you know,
it really don't have to hurt as bad as we're saying,
but if you really hurt yourself, I'll hurt myself.
I'll send you buttons.
I'll send you more, the more you send over the $30 goal,
because, see, actually, it's not really $30.
It's $29.99.
You send that $29.99 to KNON,
and I'll put the last bit in to even it up, and...
Oh, friends, the line just went dead.
I feel so inadequate to the task before me
of making Bob,
making Bob the biggest thing in Dallas radio.
You know, only you can do that.
It's really weird, but...
Oh, I saw the lights just come on just for a second.
Oh, and here comes number three.
But the number is 828-9500.
Sometimes I feel like I don't say that enough.
If you want to talk to us on the air, call the old 823-7490.
But it's 828-9500.
828-9500.
To pledge.
Oh, and they all come on, Stang.
They all come on.
Oh, look at those souls volunteering their eternities to Bob.
Oh, yes.
Now let's listen to some tape, huh, Stang?
Let's listen to some tape.
Let's do that.
Let's just do that.
Person of Jew.
Our television programs laugh at homosexuality.
Hey, they laugh at immorality.
They laugh at ungodliness.
They make a mockery.
They make a mockery of the holy word of God.
And God says, when you change my truth into a lie, I'll give you up to vile affections.
There was another hole I didn't recognize.
My dick was so long, the bitch needed circumcised.
You talk about homosexuals come out of the closet.
Did you ever dream the day would come in American history when grown men would stand up and
possess to be making physical love to each other on national television and flex their
muscles and say, don't tell me that I'm a sissy, I'm a he-man, but I'm in love with that
man right there and I'm married.
Larry the faggot was bleeding from the ass.
Wait a minute now.
We can't be going into Dolomite.
That's Rudy Ray Moore, what started to be illegal there.
That was Rudy Ray Moore, the great...
Ain't that the truth?
Oh, here we go.
And claiming to how the Holy Ghost.
Well, that's deception.
Ain't a bigger abomination in the world than women wearing men's clothes and men wearing
women's clothes and people being perverts.
That's the two of the greatest sins in the world is idolatry, witchcraft, homosexuality,
and men and women wearing the clothes of the opposite sex.
It's abomination.
And whosoever do it is abomination.
And there's more people today.
Their minds are perverted.
Their life is perverted and they've been given over to a reprobate mind.
So many people today, even people that aren't homosexual, their minds are perverted.
It's filled with filth and it's filled with all the ungodliness and wickedness that comes
from the pit of hell.
And you see it on television.
You see it in the movie houses and you see it on the market stand.
And you hear it on the hour of sleep.
Hey, how about Bernard?
It's a little bit of pornography.
And shucks.
All you have to do is look around you.
Female body parts are available just about anywhere.
Or pick up some picture books.
Well, we're standing here with Brian Dyers, commander of the Dick Army Corps.
And Brian, now tell me, tell us a little bit about the Dick Army Corps.
Now that's a youth group, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
A youth group.
And what exactly do y'all do?
You do a...
You do a chant for Dick Army, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
And so we've heard it on the hour of slack before, haven't we?
Sure have.
Well, now let's see now.
If the lines don't light up, I guess we're going to have to do the Dick Army chant, huh?
Now, who is Dick Army?
That's what I think a lot of our listeners are confused about.
Dick Army is a representative...
Where's he from?
He's from...
He's from Nantan.
Uh-huh.
And...
He's more conservative than Reagan's boss, isn't he?
Yeah.
Now, you're his biggest fan, aren't you?
Sure am.
Now, you've got this youth group and they're all like kind of like beating on their
chest and putting their fists in the air and screaming for...
Dick!
Army!
Maybe right now I should say it's 828-9500.
828-9500.
And that's our pledge drive line.
And Brian, tell us a little bit more about Dick Army and KON and all stuff like that.
What's the number, though?
You have to keep reading the number.
828-9500.
Knock yourself out.
One more time.
The number is 828-9500.
Hey, friends.
I mean, we're sitting here staring at a blank, at a sickeningly blank.
We've got a couple.
We can handle two more.
Oh, there's three of them on there.
There's three.
There's three people calling in.
Oh, come on, Stank.
That ain't enough, man.
Shut up, Stank.
That wouldn't support the subgenius church for two minutes.
They're all lit up right now.
Now, callers, we really thank you.
Oh, heck.
Wait a minute.
I got something to say.
Bless you.
Bless you, those callers who've called.
Bless you from the bottom of KON.
From the dregs of KON.
That's us.
The dregs of KON.
And look, just remember that line about false slack.
You're not getting anything by not sending it in.
You won't get anything if you don't send it in.
Because the fact is, if we can't get you money,
then somebody else will be here.
You can.
That's right.
And if you don't know what that means,
well, they'll show you what it means.
Only they're not going to ask for it.
They're going to demand it.
And they're going to be in a position to take it.
So I'm not just weaseling saying to you,
oh, come on, please give a check to 828-9500.
I am telling you why to send a check to 828-9500.
You can't sit there in the back on your butt gland.
You can't sit there on your butt gland and be a gimme bob.
Holy cow.
You can't just sit there and be a gimme bob.
You've got to send it in because we here at KNON actually need it.
We're not even making this up.
We're under so much pressure from the false churches,
the conspiracy right now,
and I happen to know where they live.
I know if KNON goes down, the last act,
the last desperate act of KNON will be put at every address over the air.
But, hey, you know,
we're not there yet.
And, look, we would rather not do that.
We would rather just win the court case and then just blow the rest of it off.
It's serious.
It's real.
So thank you for all the lines are all lit up.
There's no need for me to say anything else.
I know that somebody is really listening.
I'd be glad to send you a button,
and Stang will be glad to send you a pamphlet in the word of Bob.
We'll be glad to send you this stuff.
And, hell, we'll just wait for next time.
But thanks a lot to all of our players.
It's been a pleasure tonight.
And we're now at 6% of our goal.
So thanks, callers.
OK, good night.
Now you can hear some tape.
We all told us we should party if you wanted to come back,
but he never told us nothing about a bucket full of slack.
We all party to it puke, but we never got the neck.
We never got nothing like a bucket full of slack.
Well, a bucket full of slack is all you need
You don't need whiskey and you don't need weed
Oh, a bucket full of slack, a bucket full of slack
Take you right to heaven and I'll bring you right back
Well, I met a lot of doctors, most of them are quacks
None of them have ever had a bucket full of slack
Try to sell you a wotan, it comes in a sack
Doesn't get close to a bucket full of slack
A bucket full of slack is all you need
You don't need whiskey and you don't need weed
Oh, a bucket full of slack, a bucket full of slack
Take you right to Dobsdown and I'll never bring you back
Well, I searched so long till I was really whacked
It sure ain't easy to find a bucket full of slack
But when you finally found it, you know that you like
It's a bucket full of slack
Nothing in the world like a bucket full of slack
Well, a bucket full of slack is all you need
You don't need whiskey and you don't need weed
Oh, a bucket full of slack, a bucket full of slack
Take you right to Dobsdown and I'll bring you right back
Take you up to heaven and I'll never bring you back
Take you down to Dobsdown and you'll never come back
Ah, yes, dear friends, that was Reverend Jim Erickson of the, uh,
well, he was playing at the subgenius D-Vival that Buck and I were both at
in San Francisco, California,
where we went to take revenge on those who gave Joe Bob Briggs bad reviews.
Oh, heck. 828-9500.
Now, friends, we're gonna continue with Media Barrage number three.
Thanks for keeping them lit up, friends.
Thanks for keeping them lit up.
You better keep it lit up.
It's 828-9500.
Yes, everything's going real good.
And keep pledging.
These are real pledges now.
Any fake pledges or any nonsense pledges,
these are real pledges, and thanks very much.
And Bob's waiting for his.
Oh, yes.
Now, Mama's on the bottom and Papa's on the top
Baby's in the crib, a-hollin' poor
To her pop job, hey, Baba-ree-bob
Hey, Baba-ree-bob
This is my baby nose
Now, tea is tea and land is land
Can't get my boogie, I can get it by handshop
Hey, Baba-ree-bob
Yes, Baba-ree-bob
Now, a boogie's in the kitchen and a boogie's in the hall
Boogie's in my hand and I slung it on the's although
Hey, Baba-ree-bob
Hey, Bobbery Bob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Out in the crapshirt sitting so bold.
Gonna get me some of the old, not whole-jounce.
Hey, Bobbery Bob.
Yes, my baby knows.
Oh, my.
For Bob, my friend, Bob is a sex god.
Bob, in fact, is sex.
An all-encompassing sex that is the very in-ness and surrounding-ness of the union of both the
human and the uni, and not just heterosexual sex, all sex.
Bob does not choose to fornicate.
Bob has the tool of all time, us, to fornicate.
And not just with women, not just with men, with animals, with plants, and the faith of
all trees.
That's right.
To the bright white waves of the priming deep of the very earth itself.
That was fun.
Doctor!
No, please, doctor, I beg you.
Does this hurt?
No!
Doctor, please.
No, wait.
Can you wait?
It is a time of flagrant immorality.
A time when the old standards have crumbled as if hit by history's greatest tidal wave
of filth and perversity.
And the world has been a place of confusion and sexual promiscuity undreamed of even five
years ago.
America's theater marquees scream every kind of degeneracy known to man.
From witchcraft and apocryphism...
Send it in, send it in.
Send it in.
All right, folks, we've got this, this is it.
This is the ultimate hate call, apparently.
We've got a fine hate call coming in.
But...
It's really got a hateful sound to it, doesn't it?
Hello?
Hate's... sounds pretty bad.
What's wrong?
What's going on so far?
Yeah, it really sounds pretty hateful.
Um, Phil, would you send that...
Send it in.
Phil and the Blanks...
Line two, line two.
...demands that you, you out there, send in that which is most important to you.
Hello?
Come on, man.
We want to hear that hate call.
We don't get anywhere near enough hate call.
We don't get any hate at all.
Friends...
We've got a hate call that we wouldn't believe.
The only reason...
Hello?
...the only reason God hasn't destroyed the Church of the Subgenius yet is because he
doesn't know whether to be disgusted or elated with doctors for Bob.
We have got a call that will curl your socks, friend.
Let's get it, man.
...eat is slack.
We've got a call...
...to get slack.
...now, this is to top off the pledge drive.
And I want you all to listen to line two because this woman hates the Church of the Subgenius.
She hates us.
Let's have it, man.
Hate.