It's true that I have pride.
Hey, I never thought of that.
Taste. Exceptional breeding.
You're a sick and mangy, small, misery-laden animal wanting to die.
I'm free!
No!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I am a retarded wimp.
That is exactly what I wanted to hear from you.
Kelsey?
Yes.
Don't you shelves lie.
Everybody's afraid.
Everyone.
Dad, why?
People are afraid because they're sending a car over for me.
People are afraid because they're just about to cut into a cake.
You care to join us?
Why?
People are just about to cut into a cake because they're sending a car over for me.
Far too late, they ask themselves the question why.
And then it's too late.
Everything is too late.
Why?
I don't...
I mean, look at it this way.
In one cake, there are perhaps a thousand pieces.
Looking at it like that, I'm just about to cut into a cake.
Everyone I've talked to lately, they've been noticing it.
Noticing what?
That something's...
Something's in everyone, Dad.
Why?
This is silly, isn't it?
It's the eve of the beginning.
Right.
They put in all these anti-terrorist things at school here.
Everybody has to be escorted.
Did you get the result on your DNA test?
Did they let you in once you got your DNA test scan?
Well, I used somebody else's sperm in the little receptacle.
They let me in.
Yeah, it's an automated receptacle sort of thing.
For men, you just sort of stick your weenie in there.
It tests your DNA, but you have to give it a sample.
Yeah.
Sorry.
It's kind of warm.
For women, you have to stick your nipple, and they have a nipple one.
I thought they just spit into a little...
Hey, hey, hey.
The female breast...
She's playing music.
A female breast is nothing but an adapted sweat gland.
Adapted for what?
Adapted for feeding little baby, mewling, puking babies.
Sweating.
But it's a sweat gland.
It's a modified sweat gland.
That's what all the excitement is all about.
But what you...
But or not.
So I think even though they said on their press conference
that they have the most deformed and undersized genitals,
they said it was not a security issue,
that they were not...
They just felt that it was like piddly in light of the fact that
he would...
He has penis envy.
He has penis issues.
So if you get a penis that can fit through the male slot...
Something could potentially happen.
Just give these people their awards and let them go home.
I agree.
I agree with that.
But what you...
But or not.
How are we going to make sure that 372 deformed and undersized genitals
actually get to the airplanes?
Apparently those are being intercepted regardless.
Regardless.
By Reverend J.
J.
Cobblestone.
And of course,
the other collages that we'll be hearing throughout this show
are mostly done by the great Fernanda Nde Limur,
who did the ones at the beginning there.
Although El Queso All-Star does our opening music.
Friends, it's another war show.
I...
We...
It's...
Damn...
Well, you could say it was dedicated to Baghdad Bob,
the Iraqi information minister,
Mohammed Saeed.
Saeed Al-Shahaf.
But yes, the war kept not ending.
And well,
a girl was...
Some people were really upset when they saw that folks riding on that giant George Bush head.
Yeah, that's that robot head when they busted those people.
They were head surfing.
Yeah, through the square.
Head surfing.
That giant Bush robot.
And we're...
Yeah, head surfing.
I have launching.
They did a head launching.
I know.
It's like...
Yeah, but then they surfed on it.
We never did that before.
Yeah, I know.
You gotta hand it to the Iraqi people.
Once the chain was taken off,
once the bridle was removed,
the first thing they...
The first freaking thing they did was ran to the square
and grabbed the head and surfed...
And launched it.
And then surfed it.
Praise Bob.
Praise Arnold Palmer.
Praise Baghdad Bob.
Praise Sleetra B.
Baghdad Bob.
Man, I...
Baghdad Bobby.
I...
When is he gonna show up on Fox TV?
I don't know.
He's already made numerous appearances on Baghdad Fox.
Baghdad Daddy Bob has.
He's a talking head now.
He's a second-guessing...
Baghdaddy-o-Bob.
He's a second-guessing general.
He's a jerkulating private.
He's almost...
No, no.
He was just some guy
that got to stand up in front of the camera every day.
No, he was the minister of information.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, but yeah.
He wasn't just a...
I mean, he was like a...
That was Bob too.
Minister of information.
Mohashman Habanishnani?
Mohashman Habanishnani.
Baghdad Bob.
Shahaf was...
The guy who sat there in front of TV cameras saying,
they are 100 miles away,
while the bomb was like the scud...
I mean, the cruise missile was sort of...
Shaz, calm down.
...coming in from over his shoulder.
They have the barbecue inside their tanks.
We are killing them.
We are smoking them.
Bob will smoke them.
I reckon it would be their graveyard.
There was tobacco in his pipe.
So I guess all the guys are coming home tomorrow, you guys.
We have pushed them out of the airport.
Yeah, right.
Those are not American tanks.
Those are American tanks behind me.
Those are our tanks.
We painted them.
Their special effects are very cute, but that's all it is.
This is all Hollywood effects.
They parachute in and take a few pictures, and then they go away.
Yes, but this page is going through the way.
This page will probably evaporate real quickly once the truth comes out
that three out of every seven of those people were photographers and press people.
I've terribly lost interest.
Did you know that?
It was even said on NBC.
Actually, I noticed that.
I mean, you know...
They circled him on NBC and said,
Well, it's not as spontaneous a demonstration as...
As you might think.
Well, yeah.
The head surfing was a crowd of photographers.
That was spontaneous.
Well, they were right in front of...
No, it was just regular guys surfing the head.
Yeah, that was just regular Joe Blows.
With photographers running all around it.
Of course.
Catching it.
Of course, wouldn't you?
It happened right in front of the hotel where all the press people were.
No, I saw it.
I witnessed it.
They shot that hotel first.
I witnessed it from before there was any civilians on the scene.
I turned on my Baghdad cam.
Yes.
And there was the tanks.
And the guys were just rolling into that circle.
Then he called me.
And then about a dozen people came down the street waving a white flag on USA, USA.
And they went up to that statue, took their shoes off, and threw their shoes at the statue.
That's what I used to do.
Then more people started coming.
Then the press people who are all living in that hotel said,
Well, dig this shit.
And they all ran down.
Hey, everybody, grab your cameras.
Come on.
Something's going on down there.
That was the Tiananmen Square guy was the first one who ran down there and started doing that.
They have him for every one of these big.
He's the short.
That's Bob, isn't he?
Yeah.
The Tiananmen Square guy right now for this event was the guy just as the head.
Just as the.
Peppy, they call him sometimes.
The statue was coming down.
One guy jumped and tried to hit it.
Of course, he missed it by about 10 feet.
But his attempt was there.
And they used that still photograph a lot, I saw.
I think it's kind of.
Kind of a sideways event, boys.
I wouldn't get too excited.
You think it's pornography for our patriot pack?
I think the war had to end within X time.
So just like Afghanistan, they declared it one, even though it wasn't quite one yet.
Where is a shot him?
House pants.
Oh, I don't know that anybody's declaring anything.
Hey, go open.
Brain transplanted into a 500 foot tall robot.
Oh, oh, so that's what they thought they were attacking.
Those statues they were shooting, those things were robots that were fixing to be activated.
Just when.
The cavalry arrived in the nick of time.
Yeah.
To blow their gonads off, which is where the batteries are.
It's a good thing.
Cavalry was there.
Yeah.
Now, the battle is still going on.
You're right.
It's not over.
There are underground tunnels and, in fact, entire vast cavernous cities under Baghdad.
And Oscar Madison and Felix Unger down there arguing about their testicles.
They're like Flash Gordon underground Atlantis cities.
Is Barbaro down there?
Yeah.
They're robots.
The brain spliced dinosaurs are battling American saucermen and super R-secret weapons, which we can't discuss.
So that is still going on underground.
Now, I say all this to ensure disbelief on this college radio comedy hour.
Well, because you are hooked up with the big media.
I can say that kind of thing.
So you have been given your little piece of paper.
You know, Baghdad Bob and I have similar jobs.
We both are the PR flat for Big Scary Head.
I have suddenly lost amazing amounts of interest in the whole thing since Baghdad Bob has suddenly disappeared.
Well, that's what they intended to do.
I don't even care anymore now.
But it was a saturation point anyway.
He'll be back.
I kept going on Reuters, the Reuters site, where you get the raw video footage.
Oh, Reuters.
Those guys have targets on their heads now.
There's no commentary.
It's just raw video clips.
Raw.
And they would always have him on every day.
His clip would be on there.
And it's not anymore.
It saddens me very much.
It's not.
Baghdad Bob's going to head to Syria.
Okay, I'll admit it.
I was kind of falling for the guy.
Developing a relationship with him.
Yeah, I can tell that.
Long distance relationship.
He'll be a judge on American Idol next season.
I like kidding.
Oh, sorry.
My job's your job.
My job's yours.
And the head is now launched, there it goes.
And the head is launched.
The people that lunged.
I love this.
Watch this.
The soldiers cannot stop the people from lunging on the head and surfing it right down the
little fairway there.
That's just precious.
And each one of those people had to sign a release.
I believe.
To be on this video.
They probably did.
I, blank, do solemnly swear that I will work for chicken and pizza for the rest of my life.
Well, the reason that the networks have so many people in that hotel is exactly because they wanted something like this to happen.
And this was all staged.
And now they were down there.
All the agents, the A&R people were down there going up to all these people that you see on the screen right there.
Can we tell your story?
Look at all the A&R men.
Will you sell us your story?
That's another thing that's circled on NBC.
Every four of those guys are actually A&R men from Hollywood.
They're all looking for scripts.
We want to bring together all the various lives here to this moment.
The head surfing in whatever square they're back at.
I show up at around 3 o'clock in the afternoon.
And I am looking.
And they are ready to make it.
Go ahead, lunch.
But I have to get back now.
This is like seeing the Berlin Wall come down.
I can be reached at this number in the day.
And after 7 p.m., you can get me here.
And at night, you can leave message on there.
It's like watching.
Watching the Reichstag fire be lit.
Yeah.
And then you say, gee, those are a bunch of commie terrorists.
Hey, that's Schicklgruber himself.
No.
We believe everything, don't we?
I do.
I mean, I believe everything.
I believe that that just peaked out the CD.
Hey, what's this one, Dad?
Pretty silly.
You seem to forget.
There are some things in this world more important than people's feelings.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I was kind of creepy.
Well, I prayed for you, too.
See, Dad?
What can he do?
You see, as you grow older...
Maybe you should talk with Reverend Tucker.
What?
You come to realize that...
Maybe he could help you.
Hey, Dad.
I don't guess there's a father around anywhere who...
Whatever side your bread is butted on.
Okay, Dad.
Who doesn't?
Will you stay out of it?
Maybe you should go church more often.
Yeah.
Yeah?
He finds cameras everywhere, too.
Yeah.
Okay.
He doesn't even know he canhes yet.
There should be some –
Some.
Now that we're back here...
Mate, why are we even watching this show?
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah.
My mother goes like this.
My mother goes, are those names pig Latin?
And I yell, well, they're pig Latin.
Ouse.
You know, of course, that's how you say say backwards.
Oude and Couse.
Actually, I've noticed those names are spelled different.
Well, did you see they showed, again, go to the Reuters.com website and click on the raw video footage.
And they will show Oude's palace was raided.
And they pulled out all these.
I had my palace raided, too.
All these.
Basically, they were like these cheesy American pinup airbrush posters of chicks with dragons and stuff.
Like Boomhauer.
Like Boomhauer would have.
Exactly like freaking Boomhauer would have.
Like lizard women?
Exactly.
I am not kidding.
Can we get the Reuters?
Think what a tourist trap.
We're going to Reuters here and see if we can get Oude's palace here.
Uh-oh, what's happening?
Oude's palace.
I've heard.
After reconnoitering Oude's palace.
We're trying to get right into Oude's palace.
Like the Lord, he had many mansions.
And he also had a lot of rooms and a lot of hot tubbies.
Oh, wow.
Oude even has.
We're not allowed to look in Oude's palace.
He had a mint sauna.
He had all of the subgenius videos.
He had a rise.
In both versions of a rise.
The old one and the.
He used it as pornography amongst his.
He had like a harem of.
He was real into Bob.
42 babes.
The excuse document was framed in this fancy thing on his bedroom wall.
And the doctor.
Right next to his beret.
Signed by Bob.
And me.
And Philo.
His machete and his machine.
And his AK hanging there also.
Yeah.
He had all his subgenius stuff.
He had a little cap with the pretty squid thing on it.
You know.
He had recently bought stuff.
He was quite a party charger, wasn't he, too?
I mean, wasn't he quite Portuguese in the old days?
Didn't he like to vomit all over everybody and run around naked and stuff?
All right.
We got it.
Who was it?
That's the plasma again.
Huh?
Here we go.
We're going inside.
He was in the second dock stock in the 80s.
But he was only like 20.
You know.
He was really young then.
Well, yeah.
But he had the bomb hashed in him.
I mean.
Isn't that what it was said?
Okay.
Oh, can I go?
Actually, all he cared about was getting drunk.
Oh, geez.
Typical Muslim.
You know.
You can smoke all you want.
Oh, I don't want to do that.
Right.
I want to get drunk because that's bad.
You know.
Right.
And then yet we can't.
We can't set our hair on fire or eyelashes or anything.
His dad did too much acid.
Oh, of course his dad did too much acid.
I was there in those first.
You see.
I'm a lot older than you think.
Those actually took place before me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here.
I can't get the full screen version of it.
But wait.
Here.
We're looking inside of the.
The same acid was.
Hold on, folks.
Here.
It's really going for a lot of.
Bring your attention over to the screen here.
Now, there's the picture of Bob on the wall right there.
It looks like a little.
There's some nice little booths.
Like a little restaurant.
Like a chef frame excuse.
There seems to be.
Now, what the hell?
That's Lorraine Conversation.
Johnny Dromet was there from 25 years ago.
That's his blow up doll, isn't it?
There's the.
Oh, look.
It's the.
What's that boat in the flat?
Yeah.
That's the Good Time 4.
7.
The 7.
Good Time.
This is a darkened hallway.
It looks like a marini.
Jerkylating on a picture of Connie Dobbs.
That looks like the bathroom.
Many shower stalls.
Quite opulent.
Oh, that might be the morgue.
It's all white and gold.
I think that's.
Okay.
White and gold.
That's the defraying room.
I think they would sit there and shave their eyelashes.
There are many chairs.
Yeah.
Well, you got to have a lot of chairs.
If you're going to have.
What's this?
Looks like the knob of the yacht there.
This is all on the Reuters.com website.
This is.
Oh, is this some kind of nuclear.
Nuclear control?
No, this is Ude's yacht.
Look, he's stocking cocaine controls.
Oh, that controlled the marital aid.
What are those bags of white powder?
Looks like he's a cocaine addict or something.
And what is that lady?
That's his mom.
Why is she stealing the vegetables?
That's Sodom's wife.
There's all that stuff in there.
And this lady, woman is escaping with a box of what appeared to be vegetables.
Don't confuse yourself.
Oh, here.
Now, look, look, look.
It's a box of prophylactics.
Oh, look at the picture.
Ude, you hot playboy, you.
Oh.
Ude.
There's a woman riding a huge, like, tarantula.
A dinosaur.
She's all naked.
That's a Boris Vallejo picture.
Yeah.
It looks like the posters.
He's eating his fingers.
It looks like the posters in the pot stores in New York.
Ude was a Vallejo fan.
It is.
It's later day Frazetta.
I think that was.
Wow.
Frazetta, yes.
Poor man's Frank Frazetta.
The American soldiers are rather aghast at this.
Look at them.
I think they're just gassed.
I just noticed I knew the name of the painter of the cheesy crap that he had in his mouth.
Frank Frazetta.
Well, we all remember the name.
Boris Vallejo.
Oh, Boris Vallejo.
Yeah.
I vaguely remember.
You would have recognized him.
You would have recognized Frazetta.
Yeah, I only.
Unfortunately, I am a sci-fi geek.
Now, is it true that Ude Shlomi had his vagina reshaped to resemble a crescent moon?
Yeah, they do that there a lot.
They do?
They all do that.
That's like a phlebotomy or a clitorectomy or one of those.
You want to see mine?
Mine?
Bug, bug, bug, bugporn by Fernandanande Leemer and now, DJ John K in Chicago snz this amazing with
cut which he titled, fine, won't you?
Then, look.
Frank Sinatra live with the Taliban Orchestra.
Fly me to New York.
I've got a razor in my pocket.
You think you've flown before.
Wait till you lock in my plane.
Once I get you up there, I'll be holding my knife deep in the heart of you.
I'm round the bend.
And I'm mental.
And I'm flying the plane.
Let's fly, let's fly into buildings.
Let's turn to ashes, cause I'm dying.
On a jet plane, I know I won't be back again.
And now my skin is melting away.
DJ John Kay.
Now watch this.
They're going to take this.
They're going to take this tank right into the main driveway and park it right in between the fence.
And then they're just going to start broadcasting a message, which I don't know what it says.
There's something about fellatio or something.
These soldiers have been alone for a long time.
Some geniuses come out.
Dove's town has fallen.
Your Bob has fled.
He is a coward.
The head has been launched.
It looks like an evangelical church.
Look at this guy.
He comes over and says, this is residential.
That's my home over there.
Don't.
Shoot that.
Don't shoot that home.
You're sure that that's where this is.
Saddam Hussein is in that house.
Okay.
I borrowed my lawnmower and his son.
I'm saying this is too silly.
There was just a photo of an American G.I.
Son of a bitch.
Step down.
My petunias last month.
I saw them saying, shoot over there.
That building back there is a torture.
I mean, what?
That is a gorgeous torture.
Notice the whole headquarters.
Man, if I was going to be tortured, I'd want to be hauled in there.
Yeah.
I'd want to be tortured.
If I was going to be put in the stocks and have to have a humvee.
I thought that was your thing.
I'd shut up my urethra and be electrocuted down there.
I wonder how much it is to get that boombox attachment on your humvee now.
No.
Uh huh.
Nice.
Now only the driver asks you if she seeing the world outside, what you are and what the
You take her flowers and you tell her that you love her and she says you're gonna call her
She doesn't even bother, you sit around and wonder what the hell you did wrong
It really doesn't matter, because it's all for another man
You try and you try to make it alright
She just says you're not her type, but boys didn't learn a long time ago
You love that woman never that hard, so that's a nice guy
Always been this nice guy
Always been this last, last, last, last, last
Damn
Well, preachers, preachers, so that you gotta be good
And follow our rules like we said you should
And we try and we try to be an understand
But they'll stab you in the back and they'll take it so they can't
It feels like crime
It feels so huge
Wh
you
Now you see that evil will always Bryon
Because good is dumb.
The Pink Boys.
But I did see some footage where...
Yeah, but it looks cool.
An armor of...
Where these guys were going down this road,
and this one car came screaming up from behind.
And they tried to tell him to slow down, back it down,
and he just kept coming.
And they didn't have any choice.
And they had footage of this on CBS News,
and it was rather disturbing.
My toes are curling now.
Yeah, just end the thing.
My nose is curling.
I don't need this car.
This car just came screaming up, man.
And he's, like, coming right up to this tank.
Just barreling up right to it.
Well, now, people from various different countries over there,
it's like, oh, great, there's some Americans around.
Now I can finally go throw myself against their weapons.
Like the Spanish Civil War.
And go to heaven.
Yes, it's a cause for living.
Well, that's exactly what happened.
Well, apparently, you know, I guess...
Well, there's two ways to look at it.
How come you guys are talking in the past tense
just because the TV said,
and it's only the American people?
Are we?
I'm not.
Well, I'm talking about an event that happened.
It's because we're brainwashed.
We are brainwashed.
Because I watch it, and I feel the same way,
and yet I read those things, and they don't make sense,
and then you hear the guys talking,
and it doesn't make sense,
and then they say,
however, all the four guys were killed today over there.
Now, the gods in Washington say,
oh, it's going to get much worse.
You ain't seen nothing yet.
Oh, it's going to be still some hard times.
I think...
Chilling coming.
I think they want to keep on expanding their,
what you call it, time, you know,
when you have to send your...
Well, I guarantee...
I guarantee you they're going to hang a left
and go into Syria next.
What do they call the ratings, the Nielsen's?
They have to expand their Nielsen's.
The Nielsen's are coming soon.
I mean...
All you can do is eat a hunk of chocolate.
I'll go for that.
I'll second that.
So you got to have a fluff.
You got to have a fluff in the software.
You got to have a slowdown or a pause,
just like a pause in the Bosch wing,
and then you start up again.
Well, there's trouble in Iraq again.
Only this time it's spasm.
I'll see you next time.
Islamic Jihad
I just want to kill for God
Praising Allah is the life for me
I'll use pipe bombs, what the fuck
Killing Hebrews brings good luck
Gotta make Khomeini proud of me
Load a car with dynamite
And drive it to a synagogue
Without any brakes
Nothing could be better than
Impaling your intestines on a big rusty stake
Pack grenades and cattle prods
Let's go out and kill for God
I can hear Mohammed calling me
Yowza, yowza, yowza
PD punk
And some pas de toutes
Yowza got your rights
hoo de Да
I was seemingly seen
Show up at the dealer oh
I'm in it
I'm dead
из
Say is that a crucifix
or you just planned to see me?
Ah, looks like it sucks.
Firing up the old bulldozer.
Though the
Corinth seems quite odd,
I still want to
kill for God.
Praising Jesus
is the life for me.
Fuck those pagans, they're such
cynics. Let's bomb
the abortion clinic.
Jesse Helms,
he is my cup of tea.
Never thought I'd make it big by selling God
to idiots on cable
TV.
What the fuck, it's not
cheap, but still a better way to
use my business degree.
Use a rifle, spare
the rod. Let's
go out and kill for
God. Baby Jesus,
pass my
AKG.
Snack!
There seems to be people
trust
anyone more.
Fucks
don't
fuck
the
people
Go to
club or
ate
No more just skin and bones
Master Skinny comes home
Your show is me, me, me, me, me
Swallow her all
Start it, start it
Change a good woman
But it ain't no use
It ain't no use
Cmon
I did it, and so have almost a half-million people using only their current income.
Of course, if we look back to what happened in
Dockstown
nonprofit. It's true, isn't it?
Would you please wash me,
cleanse me, upon me, on me,
before me, my
you, my bones, my
heart!
Hence a heat-seeking head.
I have been
to the dark side. I have seen a world
that no man should see. Really, for
most people, it was a rather pleasant experience.
I'm going to place him in an
easily escapable situation involving
an overly elaborate and exotic death.
Kick his luscious grapefruit
head all the way through the back of his
poopy drawers.
Then put him in the dumpster.
Drive him all the way to the landfill.
Bob-fine!
Get that pipe out of my head!
So have you been to
I think the website of the week
is www.
www.
welovetheinformationminister.com
I would like to inform you now
that you are far from reality.
You don't like...
Hey, listen, I heard some
bad news about him.
He was blown up or something?
No, the Iranian newspapers
were reporting, not Iraqi,
Iranian newspapers
were reporting that he hung himself.
That Baghdad
by Mohammed Saeed Al-Shahaf
had hung himself.
Well, that's what the military said.
There's too many testicles for that.
No, no, he just wants us to think
that he hung himself.
His new nickname was
Comical Ali.
I think he just made a joke that he was well hung
and someone took it seriously.
Maybe.
Because I think of all the people so far
who are showing their true bells,
George Bush, no.
Saddam Hussein, no.
Houdin and Ankuday, no.
Cheney, no.
Tommy Franks, no.
But what's his name?
He's showing his emasculation.
He's a man.
Baghdad Bar.
So does Schmegma.
That's not part of it.
He spoke for that giant head.
That giant scary head
that was never there, Baghdad Bob.
You know, I got to think.
You had a bad dream, didn't you?
Was there ever a Saddam Hussein?
Maybe there was.
Just a big scary head like the Wizard of Oz.
Baghdad Bob was the little man behind the curtain.
Can I ask a fishy question, you guys?
Having fun because you smoked weed?
Lose your parents,
you can kiss your parents goodbye.
Trust the drug.
Brandy.
Sponsored by the Office for a Drug-Free America.
As a nation, we wage war on any front.
We can attack in spite of our excellent defenses.
Attacks may be made in many ways,
with bombs
or with biological weapons.
Biological warfare?
What do they expect me to do about it?
Government regulations assure the purity of specially designed germ-carrying bombs containing
disease germs.
The public health nurse can destroy food crops, just as weed killer can destroy the many other
members of our public health systems.
The biological warfare attack may have taken place.
If such an announcement is made in your country, you will be in trouble.
There is a threat of a war in your city.
Just give way to fear.
Scientists would immediately cause the disease.
Boil or cook all exposed toxins to remove livestock and people.
Our health and medical systems are the foundations of our biological warfare.
A nationwide network of federal, state and local agencies and experts.
If we attack with biological warfare, we will cause a war.
This is a very important message.
So, what is the reaction of the health and medical authorities?
They will tell you what to do, so that the disease could cooperate with the authorities.
Stop it, damn you.
Ah.
Ah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
Well, I think it's very strange what's happened.
We're still having casualties.
Now it's everybody cleaning their gun.
Did you hear that part?
No.
Yeah, it's cool.
Well, you know, every day that somebody gets killed again, but only this time it's because
they accidentally dropped a grenade on their foot or were cleaning their gun backwards.
Keep it in mind.
So it's all like a Big Warner Brothers cartoon of the war.
The war had to end on X day so the rest of the guys wouldn't get combat reparations.
You know, if you died by shooting yourself, your wife doesn't get no money.
However, if an Iraqi shot you, your wife gets some money.
So I guess they were trying to save money.
Do you think that's possibly true?
I heard whisperings about that.
Is that true?
I don't either.
There's so much propaganda going around.
Propaganda from both sides.
Only Baghdad Bob spoke the truth.
I like Baghdad Bob.
He was a wild, crazy guy, wasn't he?
I mean, he was just so much personality.
This is for you, Baghdad Bob.
This song is for you.
Yes.
We love you.
Where's my lighter?
We will never, ever give up.
Why?
Because I have a dream.
But you people in the front row, move back two steps.
I can't hear the question.
Dare to dream, Baghdad Bob.
Dare to dream.
To roast their bellies in hell.
God will help us do this somehow.
I'm not afraid.
My dream is that...
He's not afraid.
I'm gonna taste the sweetness.
He's gonna taste the sweetness of those 34 virgins.
It's not 34.
Oh, that's the Al-Qaeda.
No, no, that's the wrong number of virgins.
I mean, what are you gonna do with 34?
You know, that's not even half how many you're gonna get.
The subgeniuses get, uh, get...
Get the sex goddess virgins with 23 vaginas.
Wow.
The problem is...
Dare to dream, Baghdad Bob.
You're only given 20...
You're given 24 packers.
Wow.
To deal with 48 vaginas?
There are 23 vaginas, but there are 24 packers.
So you're always doomed to frustration on some level.
Well, I...
Now, I think that Baghdad Bob was a setup all the way.
I think there is a conspiracy going on there with Baghdad Bob.
Because of this.
Everybody and their 14th cousin, the Saddam Hussein,
ended up on that deck of cards.
But Baghdad Bob was not one of the 50...
Well, he was not.
He was not a chemical oligarch.
He was more like a videotape mold.
Of the death card.
He was like a video mold.
They're all playing those cards around a fancy cafe table in Syria right now,
which gives us a perfect excuse to get rid of the rest of this excess ordinance
while they're over there.
And let's move on.
It costs too much to have to ship it home.
Next, Tehran.
Next, Morocco.
Algeria.
Switzerland.
France.
Switzerland, man.
That's where all the buckage is.
I got the song for you, if I can find it here.
It's called, War is Good.
First the oil, then the gold, then the blood, then the pipes.
All of the pipes.
It would be all of them.
I don't like that.
All right.
How much longer are you going to make everybody suffer with these bad jokes that even wear
songs?
They're not jokes or songs, pal.
You're hallucinating.
Did she just hear me get all the time?
Yeah, you don't even have the radio on you.
This is the only time I'm going to get the radio on you.
You dumbass.
This is a psychiatric reflex show.
Your radio isn't even on you, moron.
Don't you get it?
These are all voices in your freaking head.
These are voices in your head, man.
You're insane.
You're completely insane.
You haven't even realized it yet.
Jesus Christ.
That is so sad, isn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, it just makes you want to weep.
You just called up your brain.
You called your own cerebral cortex, pal.
You know, your synapses are firing right back in through the phone now, and what do you
have to say to your brain?
It's all echoey in there, isn't it?
It's because it's big and hollow.
And how dare you diss Olivia Newton-John, man?
Sucks.
She's the hottest artist to ever come out of America.
And you've always known it somehow.
I'm soaking in Olivia.
Oh, shut up and smoke your brain.
Plug it in and go insane.
Fry your mind on color and sound.
That's it.
And pull it out and burn it down
Three hits of Sid and I'm doing alright
So what if the world's too sight
Blue sounds great and green tastes fine
I don't care if I'm losing my mind
Shut up friend and smoke your brain
Who really cares if you're going insane
Four hits of Sid and I'm doing alright
If the cops don't show we'll party all night
Smash everything, put holes in the wall
Five hits of Sid and we're having a ball
Shut up bud and smoke your brain
Who really cares the world's insane
Sounds taste fine and yellow smells great
Jump on board before it's too late
So shut up friend and smoke your brain
Who really cares if you're going insane
Three hits of Sid and I'm doing alright
Four hits of Sid and I'm doing alright
I'm burning down, burning down
I'm burning down
So now that Iraq is going to be a free country
What are they going to do?
What are they going to do for the Olympics and stuff like that?
They're going to have 25 different teams.
They're going to be there and all that?
One will be by the United States.
Will there be a Kurdish team, a Kurdish Iraqi, a Shia team?
A Squirtish team, a team of squids.
The Squirtish team.
And those are the slippery ones.
That's why it's good that the javelin and the discus and the shot put.
Here's number one on the list.
It looks like Fezman Agad Al-Faribi is getting ready to pass out in the hangman's ditch somewhere.
But as he mounts the prize, boy, what a mighty trophy that is to him.
They paid someone to compose this.
The 2024 Baghdad Olympics will be right back after this.
What's going to happen to the Iraqi Olympics now?
Well, the voices are just keep on in their heads.
Did they bomb the Olympic facilities?
Well, look.
Why do you think there are so many voices in their heads?
They're imagining burnout wreckage everywhere.
There's another guy that thinks he's listening to the radio.
Another one.
I may be insane, at least I ain't homo.
That's not an admission.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know the best one.
That's a sig, man.
That's totally sig.
That's definitely sig.
Dude.
Sigmund Freud, you know what I'm saying?
Dude, man.
That's definitely a Freudian slip if I ever...
No.
Come on, dude.
That couldn't have been more.
That's more obvious.
Instead of like the pleasure of young boys...
You're sitting there right now with a butt plug in, aren't you?
Come on.
Oh, that's a little bit too cultured for that man.
A butt plug?
Come on.
You have to buy those at a store.
There are...
No, you can't.
You can get Jules...
He's using a banana from last week that's been in his fridge.
He's been using a banana that somebody else gave him because he looked sick.
He is sick.
He really is.
He knows it now.
Hey, can you go...
It kind of makes me want one of those bananas.
Can you go look for a little boy for him, me?
Yeah.
Sure, Jupiter.
Oh, yes, yes.
I'm insensitive.
I'm a very insensitive man.
Stop your job.
Look at the insensitive man.
That's what they're paying you for.
I warn you, sir, an erection is a flagpole on your grave.
When the three planets are in eclipse,
the black hole like a door is open.
Evil comes, spreading terror and chaos.
See the snake, Billy?
The ultimate evil.
Tonight's night of the Easter vigil where we all get together
and wait for...
For the bunny rabbit to come back and suck our necks.
The bunny rabbit.
Tonight is the night that we nail the baby's foreskin to the door.
So, to keep God away.
To keep God away.
Yes.
Because just letting the days...
And why do you think they call a pass out?
Did you hear the story about that wonderful story about the people who were duct taping their children off?
That was cool.
That's a very good idea if you want to save the little moms or monsters from distress.
Now, did you hear about the two dungeons full of guys,
the prisoners who had been buried alive and bricked in?
Sex prisoners.
That is an arse.
Ooty, ooty.
No.
Yeah.
Were they his love queens?
These people had been, you know...
Just marginal humans?
Oh.
These prisons had these underground chambers that there were still people down there.
Yeah.
At first, in one place, I think they didn't believe them.
But then eventually...
They still didn't believe them.
There were a couple of places where these prisons were full of emaciated guys
who had been left in there, down there in the dark, bricked in.
To die.
And I guess probably a bunch of them did.
There were some grisly tales that went with that.
Well, we're bound to do that with cable TV.
They had to eat each other's arms to stay alive.
Well, we'll truck them in McDonald's so they don't have to do that.
But we'll still have the same little places under the ground where you go...
All right, guard.
Begin the unnecessarily slow-moving dipping mechanism.
I like animals.
Maybe I'd be a vet.
An evil vet?
No.
Maybe like work in a petting zoo.
An evil petting zoo?
You always do that!
Life, which you shall not only serve, comes from destruction, disorder, and chaos.
Maybe there is life after death.
Life after death is as improbable as sex after marriage.
To die.
To be really dead.
That must be glorious.
Get busy living.
Or get busy dying.
That's goddamn right.
Good night.
Tonight, friends, the collages included a lot of bits from Reverend Inkpay Ispay
and a lot of chunks from Fernandanande Lemur.
And that's why you want to take it nice and easy when you...
How many?
You're...
What?
Very soon, the Lord's gonna be coming back.
Oh, really?
As if he hadn't had enough the first 2,000 times.
I've heard that.
I've heard it in bad dreams, brother man.
I've heard it in some strange whisperings in my midnight ear.
Don't burn it too much.
Soon.
Well...
In an hour that you know not...
He shall come...
It's not for man to know the hour...
We don't know why you listened tonight, but you didn't.
Your radio was never on.
The voices you heard don't exist.
The voices are in your ovi.
I was not here.
Till next week, keep your head on tight.
Back to the wind, you're sat in the saddle.
I don't stand.
Princess Weed.
Los Cabo Dave.
Here's Trish.
I'm not the princess.
I have my own sheets with the sham occasions of my own existence.
Medicine of the lived in your body is the best of high time.
First thing with buds to meditate your mind.
Green harvest and the president just can't get enough.
And next year, we'll see you at the cannabis club.
She's so so nice.
He said.
gram.
And.
We got it.
We open up.
It's just for good luck.
We wet someowi.
Make some of it.
Off the magic track, on at your party
If it's all natural, put it in your body
Cheeks will be there, so will Bob Marley
Chums on the pony, rolling on a high
Off the magic track, nothing but the gas
All I need, it's a
Sit right back on this big ass couch
Share this job with you again
The time, 420, roll fat, not skinny
Heat up the house, smoke coming out the chimney
From Maui to Humboldt, we got it going on
From India to Africa, to the break of dawn
I deliver the girl with really nice diggers
And smoke up the kayak and reggae on the river
Email me, stag, at subgenius.com
Or write to us at post office box 204-206-Austin, Texas 78720
Praise the Lord
God bless you, thank you, God bless you
And I look forward to working with you all next week
Has Ayubanyo
My fifth child