Oh yes, dear friends, this is Li Liqin, a Chinese subgenius, and you are listening to the Hour of Slap.
Remember, Bob is a comrade of all people. He is a China, just like in America.
And people need slap.
In Chinese, we call slap Lut in Thai.
But it must be true slap.
Not the best slap.
Boy, will you look at that guy's slap.
Help me somebody. Thank you, Li Liqin.
Yes, my friends, we have the great Ivan Stang here tonight.
Ivan Stang himself, the grand auditor and chief inquisitor of the subgenius faith,
who has every subgenius' name on his special basement computer,
and he's here tonight to make the hour and a half.
And the hour and a half of slack seemed like, well, like forever.
Ah, yes, dear friends, so good to be here.
Say it, Ivan, say it.
Feeling the power.
In this hideous, hideous place.
Bob lives, friends. Bob lives. Don't let him tell you otherwise. He ain't dead.
Oh, what is this?
I should know. I'm the guy that has to read sooner or later all the mail that comes to that P.O. box
that you probably thought was your phone.
It's just made up.
The opinions expressed by Ivan Stang do not necessarily reflect the opinions of the staff and management of this radio station,
the other staff, the relations and spouses of the staff and management, or the staff of this staff and staff.
That's really true, Hal, but he doesn't know that it's all over the place these days.
Bob's body dragged out of the Victoria Theater with these eyes.
These deadlights looked on Bob, baby.
And the light was driven from the...
...the sky.
There's saint of failed corpses dotting the landscape all the way from Little Rock to Berkeley here.
I don't know what the big deal is.
I mean, just because there's a Dobbs corpse there doesn't necessarily...
I mean, can Bob really die?
I'd say yes, Ivan, and I think you better grow up and face the sick truth that this Bobby of yours isn't necessarily everything that you...
...you said.
I'm sorry.
There have always been Bobs.
There has never been a world without a Bob.
Just as there's never been a Bob without a Dick, his corresponding evil twin brother, Dick Dobbs.
After a mental mutation...
The demons you may see during the initial hallucinations...
Get him away from me! Get him away from me!
If you do not panic, this phase will end after a few minutes.
JJD
...they'll show up.
I was gonna make serious funny noises.
Because we all know that Bob is the man that makes all the ladies go...
He's the man that makes all the men go...
It ain't an om-chattin' laid-back universe, dear friends.
It's a dream universe.
An action-packed universe.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know what's here.
A boring and sleepy...
A purulating and putrescent biologically active universe.
...coming from the holes between their shoelaces.
Enormous bioplasm that stretches throughout infinity.
Oh, did you get some of that, too?
Yes, it was delicious.
Then he'd force him to eat this big ugly piece of meat.
He was a little short, chubby guy, and that's where Bob got the idea.
They say he came in with checkered pants on, but I just don't remember.
He was allowed to eat all he wanted.
Anything he wanted.
Bob's big boy was a real person.
That's true, for there was a real Bob.
And this parable goes to show that there is indeed always a real Bob.
There has to be a Bob, dear friend.
Even the things which you cannot possibly believe in, Bob's big boy, indeed.
Turn out to be an actual historic person.
And as it is with Bob's big boy, surely it is with the far more impressive and major deity we know as the Avatar of All Slack.
That's how we know him.
Others call him him, or Monga.
Others call him a demon.
Or your mama, indeed.
And the children of Bob are everywhere.
Bob lives on in his millions and millions, literally millions, of illegitimate children.
All of them...
...crossing lawsuits against me, personally.
Well, Doctor, I'm sure you're used to it by now.
Well, when I took on the job as sacred scribe at the church...
...for this kind of sharing of the lives of the church...
I had no idea what I was going to be getting into.
We had 500 employees in 1980.
Now it's just me and someone else.
Well, that's just the Reagan-esque spirit that's been...
...enjoyed togetherness for its own sake.
And yet they say that Bob doesn't even exist.
There are some who say that there is no Bob.
If there's no Bob, then where did all of those dead bodies come from?
What about all those ads in the 50s that he posed for?
What's this right here?
The body store.
Dead Bobs for any occasion.
Oh, put that away.
No Bob too small.
No Bob too big.
No, really, guys.
All kidding aside, I must admit...
...at least the official Father Church, the subjugation foundation...
...which we don't expect any of you except the stinking Bobbies to cling to...
...nevertheless, we have the only true word of Bob, the original apostles.
And as far as I'm concerned, this whole thing about Bob being dead is a ruse.
Bob staged that whole thing himself.
It was fashionable in the 60s.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
That big...
...head.
Same frontwards and back, friends.
And there's a reason there's an O in the middle.
A hole in the middle between those two Bs.
It's symbolic, friends.
You can look through that...
...the center of that O in Bob's name and see the future and the past.
I think you guys are afraid of J.R. Bob Bob.
So you've been doing this show for almost five years now, disrespectfully...
...making fun of your high E-pop.
The man who...
...brought you slack.
I ain't afraid of J.R. Bob.
...died for your sins.
Nobody knows how many times.
The only thing that ever brought me slack was leaving Paul in St. Louis.
I'm not scared of Bob.
...shared this message with you.
I was the only slack I ever got out of this damn church, and it cost me $3,000 to have him shipped back.
Most people don't fear Bob.
Don't fear him a bit.
Oh, they think Bob's always going to be their buddy.
And then as soon as they think Bob...
...is dead, they turn around.
They think he ain't looking anymore.
They turn around and go to the pinks.
Going to the pinks, every one of them.
Oh, friends, he's just testing you.
He's been testing you for two years.
He knows if you've been bad or good.
Oh, yeah.
But more people are frightened of Gary than frightened of Bob.
Anybody want to go to an open bar?
Why does this situation persist?
Well, it's because of the general loss of faith...
...which accompanies the modern feeling.
And a feeling that one can no longer...
...support the credulity, superstition, and fanaticism...
...of an earlier time when one might well have believed...
...in the smiling, pipe-smoking, benevolent figure...
...known from the book of the subgenius.
That's right.
That was really beautiful.
Very touching, man.
That was just...
...beautifully moving.
Could you repeat that?
Escape from Alligator.
Ivan Stang, 15, shows scars after being attacked by an alligator...
...near West Palm Beach, Florida, Monday.
Ivan and a friend were swimming in a lake...
...when suddenly he was grabbed by the head...
...and pulled underwater by a giant, sharp-toothed saurian.
I couldn't see anything but teeth...
...and didn't know what had hold of me...
...until the gator let loose and swam away, said Ivan...
...who suffered wounds requiring 41 stitches.
This is supposed to be a religious show.
Now, what is the interpretation of this parable, my friends?
The alligator is the worldly mob, the rabble...
...who are the ones who are the most...
...always seek to devour and assimilate...
...the holy men of the Church of the Subgenius.
The lone swimmer, buoyed up by the fluid element...
...represents, upon the other hand...
...the striving outward force of the Church of the Subgenius...
...which requires 41 stitches...
...the same number as the number of bullet holes...
...in Bob's bullet-reddled body.
Praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob.
Praise Bob, praise Bob.
What are we going to do?
Wouldn't you like revenge on these mediocre...
...disciples?
I wouldn't go that far.
These pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens...
...these normals who have made normality the norm?
Well, no, I wouldn't like revenge on those people.
I'd like revenge on you, Ivan, because...
...you've taken one too many $20 check from me.
I've never got...
I want my slack!
Let's see your Subgenius membership card, hmm?
Now, let's not get...
I mean, say the end times came a little bit soon, Gary.
Do you think you'd make it on the escape saucers...
...of the second...
...of the next goddesses without your little...
...Subgenius membership card?
I'd sure try.
Ah, it's a great example you're setting for the people out here.
I've got my Bob Amira card here.
It says that I'm paid up to...
...$1897?
You see, Gary is the Rasputin...
...of the Church of the Subgenius, often thought for...
...but rarely encountered.
And it is this self-same learning for slack...
...which separates us from them.
At the hip.
The human may live...
...without its entire life...
...in a grinding cycle of slacklessness...
...yet he never feels cheated.
He thinks it's natural.
I suppose we could hit him, but...
...they're nothing but half-witted cattle...
...racing each other to be first to the slaughterhouse...
...and stampeding you along with them.
But what do you care?
Oh, you've got slack.
Slack.
Yeah.
Anybody want to go down the slide?
That's them all.
Oh, get along, little bobbies.
Go head on down to Dobstown now.
Get on in that Dobstown corral, you little bobbies.
Oh, there's a nice fat one.
Yes, he'll be a good trading commodity...
...come the bargaining session with the exes.
First up, I notice y'all don't talk about religion much.
I guess it's real hip out here in California.
It's a more humanistic approach to life.
No, we believe in just...
Just letting the holy benediction of Bob flow out like pus from a pustule.
You just don't understand the true power of the show.
Oh, it's very fashionable to say Bob is a good man.
Oh, he was a prophet, but the son of Jehovah One.
No, well, I don't go for these superstitions, you say.
Certainly not.
Very fashionable.
It hath not been my use to pray with moving lips and bended knees.
But silently, by slow degrees, my spirits I to Bob compose.
In humble trust, my eyelids close.
In reverential resignation.
No wish described, no thought expressed.
Only a sense of suffocation.
A sense, or all my soul impressed, that I'm out in the street undressed.
Isn't that beautiful?
Church air, one soul per breath.
Get your breaths right here.
Don't need oxygen.
By the Bob's early light.
That too loudly we'd screech.
In the toilet blaspheming.
Whose clogged eyes and dark ears.
This is supposed to be a religious show.
I thought there was a separation of church.
Bob.
Bob and country.
This is a night where the hamsters were splashed.
And, of course, truffle pie.
I'll bet you think y'all's a joke too, don't you, Dave?
Funny joke.
Bob's a funny joke here.
Yo, I see what you've certainly been leading your radio listeners down the great path here.
Oh, big joke.
I guess the conspiracy's a joke too.
Oh, slack.
I guess that's a joke.
So a monk and a pastor said a blank.
Yeah, hang on, Dave, you're not supposed to be here.
You're supposed to be brothers and sisters.
minute notes.
So butter catches the makeup.
.
Oh, and they said to raise the last gift.
One.
Two.
Open.
Five.
Four years.
Four, five.
Six.
hl.
Dr. Dubois fan. I'm gonna deliver it myself.
Wait a minute. Don't give him the keys.
No, it's a hymn aphrodite.
I don't know.
I mean, this whole thing, it's like, what happened to the organ music?
Give me a can of sound effects while you're at it, would you?
Oh, yeah, and some show stretcher.
And listen to him.
I need some show stretcher back.
Yes, friends, little did many of you know,
but this isn't the only subgenius show.
In fact, there's six weekly subgenius shows now in New York, Beijing, New Jersey,
Richmond, Virginia, St. Louis, Dallas, and Dallas.
This, I'm afraid, does not count as an orthodox subgenius show.
I mean, I had no idea.
I had thought that, I mean, the sermons and the prayers,
and the sending up of praises, and killing...
It just don't happen that way.
You're in Berkeley, Ivan. You're in Berkeley.
The sacrifices.
Oh, we have the sacrifices.
The ritual scars.
We have those.
You used to have ritual scars on your forehead.
You've had them removed.
Oh, I didn't have them removed.
Trying to fit in, I guess.
The rat ate them off in my sleep.
...time I'm down to stay out.
Yes.
Oh, the cage.
I got to lock myself in the cage when I was sleeping.
No wonder the rats died.
Once again.
Now, Dr. Stang, when we reflect upon the evils in this world,
why is it that Dobbs permits such Yehuism to exist?
Can you answer this spiritual conundrum for our listeners?
Well, uh, the Yeh-Dobb does not permit Yehuism to exist.
I thought he had to deliver the permit.
He allows it to exist.
He forces it to exist.
It is part of the bull-dada matrix of which the...
But what about the cow-dada matrix?
Why must we always look at the male angle?
Isn't it more interesting to look up a cow's dada?
And...
An ancient art form turned into an illegal act.
The Aztecs went out for it in a big way.
Bob does not desire a monolithic one-world subgenius inquisition.
I mean, we don't...
We don't have to bow down to him, you know, or bend over to him, as the Bobbies do.
The Bobbies.
Yeah, there's some of these Bobbies here.
Get Zeon by these.
Bobbies.
A little of both.
Both?
And those little collars.
That's right.
You slack vampires.
We'll get a reading on you.
Yes, you can speak to Ivan Stang himself, or the great Gary G'Bofram, or even your humble narrator,
your howling hierophant of the airwaves, Dr. Howell.
We're all broadcasting on behalf of the lurching church of the subgenus.
Help me somebody.
Salvation or salivation?
Salvation.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You are receiving the church of the subgenius show if you are within the sound of our broadcast.
For whatever reason, you were tuned in to our transmission.
Be you an habitual listener or even a serendipitous insomniac, ranging the radio spectrum to allay
the tedium of sleeplessness, who happens for the first time upon our broadcast.
Do not attempt to adjust your radio.
I'll have Jack Danielson 7-up, please.
This show bears a patented Dobbs drum power shell time code, which may cause some home radios to react unpredictably.
Although only a small percentage of radios or their owners have suffered permanent damage.
We're not responsible, friends. We're not going to be responsible for what happens.
But what I want to know is who is responsible? Who's responsible for this suffering?
Well, Bob is, of course, Hal. Haven't you learned yet? Pain and sickness and death lies the IRS.
And a headache that lasts all year.
And a lot of checks in the mail, dear friend.
But what does it all lead to? What does it all mean?
An ever larger bank account for the subgenius Foundation Incorporated.
Dobbs did not die because he had to.
Wellman chose to kill him on the stage.
Not for you and everyone, but mainly for his own reasons.
This man was handed over to you by Dobbs's set purpose and knowledge.
And you, speaking to the people of Dobbs Town with the help of Rugo's pinkish ones,
put him to death by nailing him to the crosshairs of Wellman's gun site.
But Gobbs regurgitated, freeing his impoptitude from the agony of slacklessness,
because it was impossible for nee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee to keep its hold on him.
And so the ghost of Dobbs...
Now his agonized spirit roams this earth, howling in outer darkness,
but hoping to regain its early hegemony.
The fop monsters are after me.
But the cross or wolf's bane or a sickle through Dobbs's throat or a stake through Dobbs's heart
can keep the e-pop to bay.
Remember, the monsters are out there and it's either you or them.
Even...
This has been a public service message from the Subgenius Show.
I don't understand.
Either you can take your stake and you can eat it or you can pound it through Dobbs' heart.
It has to be frozen, rigid and hard.
Look.
I'm sure you all recognize this beloved melody as the ever-popular oldie but goldie classic
I'll slap your chops shut, baby, with a Stilson wrench.
But did you know that the same haunting tune was also Splat It Over Rich's
Eczema Cantata No. 12, Op. 99 in C major?
Now you and your entire family, including kids from 6 to 60, can enjoy this and other classic
masterpieces of the world's longest-playing music in your own home whenever you like.
Expose your youngsters to the impotent world of symphonic overkill at any time and at your own convenience.
And you'll only spend about as much as you would for a really good set of luggage
or a year of education at one of the more prestigious institutes of higher learning in this great land of ours.
Every week you'll receive another high-tech...
...and a 98-rpm album, each in its own permanent storage case of semi-permanent, non-biodegradable, sturdy fiberboard.
And at first, you need pay nothing.
Later, we'll demand more and more, but you'll receive your first mutilaginous masterwork,
the Cospodore Concerti by G.R. Robertini-Dabzini.
Giovanni Rodrigo Robertini-Dabzini was director of chamber music to the Duke of Wellman.
He lived in dire poverty...
I am so tired...
...and suffered from yaws jaundice syphilis.
Gout, rotten teeth, and an unknown debilitating disease...
...which caused deaths of blindness, deafness, and madness.
Dabzini fathered 49 children by his second wife, Connie Maria Anna Hugeltoffler.
To support his large family, he wrote 467 symphonies, 98 concertos, 48 known motets, 19 operas, and two concertini.
His European fame was based above all on the sensitive sweetness of his adagio movements.
Theologians have debated the existence of a side three, but this, as well as a hypothetical
side four, are only in the realm of conjecture.
My friend, if you can reach side three of this show, then you will know you are already
in life.
Help me, somebody!
Pray, God!
I have a leg cramp.
Yeah, did you ever look at that Monty Python record?
It really did have three sides.
Well, perhaps if you tried to get side two of the show, you'd just get side zero of yourself.
I try to get to the other side, but there's no oxygen over there.
You open up the gates to your lower self, the lower self you share with all other subgeniuses.
Simply because I happen to share a lower birth with many subgeniuses,
I refuse to consign myself to an eldritch cleaving to laws far beyond our disposition,
which may indeed ice my soul.
And these starving subgenius refugees seen here crammed together in these Rolls Royces,
being sold off, Dobbs' whole collection of Rolls Royces now being auctioned off in Dallas.
Hey, here's a little news thing our listeners might be interested in.
Actors and musicians are invited to audition for the lead role in a stage show, Dobbs.
Words of music.
The first Bob is authorized to be done around him, which is made up entirely of 25 Bobs.
This is like a story we heard earlier.
It is as if it were ordained from the beginning of time.
It says here you have to go to Malaysia to audition.
Wait a minute, I'm not getting any royalties for that.
I never heard anything about a Dobbs stage show.
Too late, it's already on its way.
I'm afraid the Dobbs is a trademark.
The name is a trademark.
The name subgenius is a trademark.
I personally wrote a check for $400 to get that face trademark.
Look at this.
I've never paid for any of it.
This is true subgenius stuff you're hearing, folks.
This is the real thing.
This is no razzmatazz.
This is no tomfoolery.
This is the real Ivan Stang, and he's telling you the straight truth.
So stand up and pay attention.
Then she finishes.
Oh, they're making money all over the place off of Bob.
It's like the smile face now.
The following corporation is doing business as Dobbs Image Incorporated.
Here's another one right here on page 59.
It says,
The following person is doing business...
Bob's Brain.
Who could Bob be?
I mean, how many of these people are sending you money?
None of them.
You ain't fooling me, Philo.
I know you're out there.
You're listening.
I want you to call them boys off.
My boys will meet your boys behind the old church down there in Jonesboro.
You can bring all your minions and your evil conspiracy devils.
We're going to have it out, boy.
No, no, no.
That's not how it happened at all.
Doc Holliday stood over here by the fence.
And they were never actually in the sub-G corral.
The famous gunfight actually took place over here by the hotel.
Now, Kirk Douglas played the part of Doug Willman in the 1954 movie.
And these souvenir boots have been stuck in the street ever since.
And it's articulated.
It can make 27 smirks and sneers.
On its plastic face.
It has big, friendly plastic eyes, too.
Big, friendly eyes.
Experience time travel, anvil possession, past wives, UF odors, and big feet.
Here on the mysterious hour and a half of misery and darkness.
Yes, you're hearing the authentic spewings and spoutings of Ivan Stang himself,
as well as Gary Gubofram.
And the word was wrong.
And the evil Doctor Howell.
The same was in the beginning.
Burn him.
He's evil.
Evil.
And the guidance, the firm, intelligent hand, the guidance of Mobius Rex,
Dr. Mobius Rex, who has led us unerringly, never, Dave, never.
Down the primrose path, I would say.
There's many a grip twixt the tongue and the lips.
Yeah, I think I heard that one.
Actually, it's a lot better than the last sub-G.
I am the pea shooter.
And you are the pea, I think was the line used in there.
Just as we can tune our media in the chosen stations,
so can we attune our consciousness to a higher and more unbiased sub-G.
Hey, Gubofram, man.
There's a lot to be said about not receiving any West Coast money.
Because you understand, the money you receive has to be filtered through the West Coast church.
Because it's West Coast money.
I don't think it would do you any good if it came directly to it.
I think that us...
...saving our glands on the money perhaps does a lot more than you just getting it directly.
You would just waste it on something like paperclips.
Or money.
We take it down to the Emeryville mudflats and just throw it on the spot where you find that dirty, nasty head.
What is money, anyway?
Indeed, all is chaff which blows away in the exhalations of Jehovah One.
But it only gains its true power at the moment that it passes.
And that's what we had to deal with.
You can send your addresses from your pocket into Bob's.
And since Bob isn't here, you can still send for that information from...
We have Bob's through jeans here.
...the church of the subgenius.
And they need to be laundered.
We have the pocket of Bob here.
What are you talking about?
They smell like they haven't been washed in months.
But look, Connie did this embroidery.
Through this, the envious Willman slashed.
And as he plucked his cursed steel away,
Mark how Bob's special ichor followed it, as rushing out of doors to be resolved if
Wellman so unkindly knocked her no.
It is too Wellman.
Then fall Dobbs.
Then burst a mighty fart.
Great Dobbs he fell.
I'm not going to be able to let my kids listen to this show now.
Way to go.
Why, it's just an ancient Anglo-Saxonism from the early history of our race.
Meaning to hit or strife.
Yes, as in farquhar, farharharden farden harden farden.
How many of you pyroflatulate?
You've been blown off pyroflatulate.
Don't be embarrassed.
Come forth and testify.
Just call us at 848-4425.
That's 848-4425.
We release foul gases through our lungs with the sound of .
Call any time, day or night, if the spirits are moving.
Remember, there will always be a subgenius pastor there to hear you.
Hear your words and receive your heart.
Until you do, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Professionals welcome.
Women discouraged.
Good sex for Mutants League and now stationed in Utah.
Say, I see a little light here on our board.
It looks like we have a caller after all.
A little whoopty-doo.
A caller.
A slack vampire.
Maybe, but maybe one from France.
Hello, you're on the air.
Listen, I've got a problem.
Uh-oh.
Every time I die, I'm going to be a little bit more of a wimp.
Something happened.
Cowards die many times before their deaths.
The valiant never taste of death but once.
And, you know, if Bob let you know for sure that there was an afterlife, half the people
in the world would commit suicide.
So there's an evolutionary reason for this.
We're interested in the...
And the other half would kill themselves.
It's a real drag.
It's the before life that concerns us.
That's right.
It's the pre-life.
The pre-existence.
The sub-life.
Sub-life.
The thing which is a plane of existence below our own life.
Hanging around in the ethereal nothingness.
The underwear lurking beneath the clothing of existence.
Subligacular.
Wait a minute.
We've forgotten the customer again.
Oh, yeah.
Dear lady, please express your opinion.
Please.
What should I do?
You must...
Open your mouth.
Donate your heart to Bob.
Yes.
Open your mind.
In a figurative manner, of course.
And open your wallet.
Yes.
And bend over.
And touch your ankles.
And receive the word of Bob, dear friends.
And I speak to you through the voice of Dr. Henry.
You will be changed.
You'll be a new being after that.
You'll have giant, powerful television sets and be able to walk through walls.
I am dedicated...
That sounds wonderful.
Say, could you tell me, are you as beautiful as all the women here in the Bay Guardian
want ads?
The relationship ads?
Uh...
Poor Dr. Cabofram is a lonely soul.
I feel better already.
Thank you.
We have our own...
This is the only thing we can do.
There is a subplot.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Before you go, tell me, are you a fantasy caller?
You could feel the power.
Definitely.
Pink around the collar.
Well, let's check out then this other blinking...
Goodbye.
...apothegm.
Put your hand...
Lay those hands on the radio speakers.
Make love to your radio.
I could stay.
L-O-U on air.
Lay your hand.
Yeah, I just saw Bob's body on the freeway, man.
Not again.
See, I told you, baby.
I told you.
We get those calls in Dallas.
Okay, now look.
That's why we...
I went out this time.
One of you guys go...
I went out two times and nobody else did it the last time.
Somebody else can go out and pick that thing up.
Call the animal control board.
I mean, I normally eat road kills, but I don't know about the smashed dogs there.
We'll have to send one of those animal control trucks over.
It's no good.
It's destroyed, man.
It's destroyed.
50 cars ran over it before anybody would stop.
Well, I'd say it's probably...
Well, you know, but the cells can still...
One cell carries all the code information to create a new dog.
You cook that thing just like you cook abalone.
You peel that dog's corpse right off the road.
Abalone.
You dip it in egg and a little bit of flour.
Eggs.
And cook it in olive oil or butter.
When was the last time you had you a big old bowl of fried dead body of dogs, dear friends?
We call it Bob's Birmingham.
Bob's Birmingham.
That's right.
It's the most delicious of all road kills.
Much better than skunks, squirrels, or kitty.
Or squished ferrets and weasels.
But Bob's spirit lives on.
You can talk about these Bob corpses, like I said, but he lives because he's more than just a dead body with a grin on its face and a broken pipe in its mouth.
He represents something, dear friends.
He represents...
And all of the checks due to some P.O. Box 1403-06.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Remember that address, folks, because later on during this program we're going to have a special bonus.
Sonia the seeing poodle wants to get on the mailing list.
Well, let's put her on.
I keep trying to send $20 in, but poodles can't write.
Well, why don't you write for her then?
We did get a subscription from...
And I hope you'll tell her hello from me, Dr. Howell.
Only I think she was kidding.
I think that was a fake name.
Some people use fake names in this jury.
They hide behind a pseudonym.
They're afraid the conspiracy's going to come after them.
Just because they...
The conspiracy gets their addressable friends, I'm the one who's got access.
Me and only one other person on this whole planet, someone else, has access to the identity codes for all of you.
All the listeners of this show.
Cue Night of Slate shooting tape.
All right, now we're going to check out the movies on TV here, and we'll have a report about agricultural instruments and...
Oh, no.
Are they showing subgenius video?
The movie again?
Yeah, I believe so.
...and again.
Oh, they're looking for a paystub artist to take the pieces of Bob Green and try to put them back together again.
Oh, that's art nowadays.
You put a pipe...
You take any picture, put a pipe on it, it's art.
Get 500 bucks or so for it, New York.
Boy, is subgenius art.
Got a pipe.
My kid does better art than that.
Art.
...
Yeah.
We've, folks.