It's time for Bob.
Say, Bob, why the big smile this afternoon?
What's so special about today?
Well, there's nothing special.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Now we're rolling, Bob.
Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, yeah.
The sauces are coming.
They didn't come.
That's sex music.
We haven't heard from him in a long time, by the way.
He probably got raptured.
Or ruptured.
The exes came and took him up.
And nobody else.
And half of the people who volunteered.
Who volunteered to help with our stage stuff
obviously joined the saucers long before we did.
There were some problems trying to figure out who'd really left
and who was still delusional on the ground thinking they had or hadn't.
Well, you know, if only one person on Earth were going to get saved
and taken aboard the saucers,
somehow it wouldn't surprise me if it were masturbating Sean.
Right.
The man with the most slack.
Exactly.
I mean, I don't know.
All he needs is some sex music and he's good to go.
That's right.
And he's been...
Long gone, probably.
Long gone.
Yes, friends, we've returned from the expectant X-Day at Brushwood,
which now turns out to have been X-Day Drill number 11.
Expectorated by X-Day.
These are the survivors.
Apparently we were lukewarm and they spewed us out of their mouth.
The puddle of warm spread.
The bedraggled few walking around saliva-covered and in the rain.
A tatter-to-million, rag-tag, two-bit tin-pot army of losers.
They wanted to leave.
Their intentions were good.
They thought they had it all figured out.
But we couldn't leave.
We couldn't get out.
We couldn't leave.
Well, there was no way we were going to leave.
We couldn't let you people out of there unless the saucers arrived.
Now steerage passengers will have their opportunity
as soon as they learn to obey the protocol.
Please check your extra digits at the door.
Artificial and new organs, please check them at the door.
Pointed ears on this side, no ears on that side.
I can't hear you.
What did we do wrong, Bob?
And those with one blue eye and one green eye
must go in that corner over there.
I was talking to one guy who had seven heads and one leg.
He was a real nice fellow.
He came all the way out here from Beta Cygnus,
the coal sack nebula.
But he's a real regular guy.
I got to meet him, too.
I really liked him, too.
But I hate them guys at Beta Cygnus.
They've got all kinds of warts that are radioactive on their bodies.
And they have a big range.
That could happen to anybody.
It makes it all the more interesting.
It makes it all the more depressing because
aliens from other planets were coming to Brushwood
hoping to be picked up by the mighty Exists from Planet X.
And they were really disappointed.
The usual thing.
Well, STANG!
Where's the aliens?
As if I was Bob.
As if I was Jehovah One.
As if I were God.
What is the explanation for this?
One particularly grotesque subgenius seemed most insistent.
In pinning Ivan Stang down and finding just what this subgenius stuff was all about.
That wasn't a subgenius.
That was a chicken head.
We thought it was an Exist trying to find you where you tickled.
It was either a chicken head or an anonymous.
We had not only other aliens hoping to catch a ride,
but rival funny joke cults, you might say.
He had Borat's swimsuit, did you see?
Discordian.
Discordian's Anonymousies.
Former Human Anonymous.
Yeah, flying spaghetti monster dips.
And they were eaten by the crowd.
Scientologists. Mormons.
Humanoids Anonymous.
Friends, it was quite a gathering.
And it was a fun gathering, except for the fact that the main point of it just fell flat on its face!
Heard about the gathering.
It's a good thing that it's a drill.
A gathering of revolutionary forces.
By the time we got to Brushwood, we were half a dozen strong.
Yeah.
And we've got to get ourselves back to the garden!
I got started on that golden or that any number of things like that actually.
It's a bedraggled group of people who merely want to leave this planet for once and for all.
I signed up, I think it was 1972.
No, that's a little early.
It was maybe around 1982.
I get those confused.
And my father was a butcher.
And he actually gave us lunch.
My father was a virgin!
He also made candles.
And one night, I remember him bringing home a tract.
I can't remember what he brought home.
And it had that face on it.
And they left and I was left alone.
So I joined also and have been waiting since 1982.
We were left alone.
Now, when the moment comes, the moment of truth, believe me, we wouldn't dose you with anything.
Of course not.
Honestly, these are just homemade lollipops with alien poison.
What did we ask?
Recessed Pisces made, who happens to have studied under Alexander Shulgin at the Bohemian Grove for many years to create undetectable poison.
And at 7 o'clock, the idea is usually we would toss back the coolant.
And we would put it in the microwave and all go, fuck them if they can't take a joke, which we'll do in one minute.
I can't believe this.
So many people showed up.
We've had more show up each year than the sausage down the road.
I'm down to the graze.
Oh, Hal, I love your hat.
Look, Dr. Hal is ready to arrive, to ascend into space using that subgenius helicopter.
Oh, I love it.
We fly away now.
And I'm sure Susie the floozy should come stumbling up here.
She's putting her face on it.
Okay.
30 seconds to...
Liftoff.
This really could be it.
Well, you're standing around here acting like ha-ha real funny, but this really could be it.
This is where it's at right now.
Now we win.
20, 19, 18, 16, 15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Oh, my God!
.
The hollow emptiness of another fail-dex day.
The universe is a cold, hollow emptiness.
A deep place.
Devoid of love or caring.
Just a mechanistic, DNA-driven universe.
We're just robots meant to carry on our pathetic little code for no reason that would mean anything to us.
Yes, meaninglessness, sadness.
Oh, my God.
You know, you kids are really beautiful today.
And I'm really behind you kids, 100%.
And that's why I say we ought to listen to the flour people.
Thanks, Governor Rhodes.
Because some people just like to fry everything in white flour.
And if they like to, I say, well, you know, I kind of like to eat that stuff, too.
So maybe we have something in common, the flour people.
Flour-dipped people.
And now we have another guest here on the line, Governor Rocknar.
From the batter people?
Well, good evening.
Well, if it isn't Governor Rocknar.
Hey, how is everybody?
How was X Day?
Well, it was great, if you don't mind being left behind on Earth.
The hazardous materials people are back at the site spraying it down.
If you don't mind having a new disease that no one can diagnose yet, I...
The Brushwood staff is busy re-holifying the land after we de-holied it.
We blasphemulized it and we sacrilegified it.
We made fun of the gods.
We made fun of the goddess and all like that.
We sodomized Mother Earth and had a big old laugh about it afterwards.
We sassed them and harassed them and we snickered in their teeth.
Oh, man.
That was just to make us feel better about being left behind by Bob.
Oh, I was even further left behind than you guys.
That grinning charlatan took off and he left us all stuck behind with our head in the clouds and our feet in the mud.
Hey, I was even further left behind than you guys.
You were?
Yeah.
Well, you guys were right on the edge of the saucer's arrival.
But I'm stuck here eight hours away and no hope of getting to Brushwood this year because of the conspiracies.
Rising gas prices.
Repent. Quit your job. Slack off.
Get a better job.
Well, you could, yeah.
Get a sec... um, repent.
Get a second job.
Crack off.
This is it. I'm forgetting the first one.
The log.
I'm not going to cry on that.
A bell is to ring and a horn is to blow and money... money is to burn.
At X Day.
I thought you were going to ram it all the way through and say money is my hoe.
You can ram him.
Hey, stop him. Stop him, somebody. He's burning that money.
No one ever really burns money.
I've seen it done.
Do they? Sometimes I wonder what happens to mine.
If you're anything like me, your average everyday transaction goes something like this.
Um, you mean that's four dollars now? That used to be two forty-five.
Just give me my change, peasant.
I am your changer.
This is absolutely intolerable. I'm going to complain to the management of this place.
I'm J. Fordyce Wellington. J. Fordyce Wellington.
I don't care who you are. I'm calling security if you don't get off of the cable.
Oh, there he is. So here is your friend, the security... Officer... Oh, no. I'm cut off.
Nobody's ever safe on this hostile planet.
I'm啜啄 electromagnetic halls.
IUG coupe chain at 9 o'clock light, mandate seat at 7 o'clock.
Single electrical generation located in 18th Street and 2nd Street,
Memphis coins area is eight miles away, where a posible substance goods shop located.
Police ordersар
Now his blood comes as tears ...
No one is ever safe on thisHmmmmmm
Watch out, boy!
The Amino Acids, dear friends.
Live at X Day 11, recorded by Potare Nostril.
Praise Bob.
And it all sounded great, which makes us feel a little bit better about still being stuck here on Earth editing at all.
For Is This Not, hour of slack number 1162.
And for the next few shows, we're editing the 11X Day footage Memento style,
with the chronology slipping all over itself from future into past.
We're scavenging Dr. Sinister's radio synesthesia from WCSB Cleveland
for the reminiscing by Dr. Howell and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and we.
And we're scouring the video cams and soundboard for the actual heart-stopping events that we survived,
such as this moment of transpouting by the bonfire,
as Bob is seemingly channeled by Reverend Fight C. Taj.
The official word is repent, quit your job, and slack off.
But, if you can't do that, if you are as dragged in by the conspiracy as most people,
then it is better.
To find slack in your work, than to have to find work in your slack.
Uh...
I gotta ask something about Bob's name. What does the J stand for?
That's a frequently asked...
No, it's a frequently asked question, but actually, on his birth certificate, it says J.R.
quote, Bob, unquote,
dot,
Bob's.
His father was not a sophisticated fellow, and all of his bosses had nameplates that, you know,
Fred M.
Mike,
Mertz,
and so forth.
So, he thought, well, that makes a man sound important.
And it does, and it worked.
My nickname's in quotes. How about yours?
But, no, the J.R. does not stand for Jesus Robert, as so many people speculate.
I heard a few years ago that if you have a...
nickname in quotes in the middle of your name like that, your insurance premiums will be higher.
Now, is there any point where we have to stop being funny to flip a CD or anything?
Well, we've got about, uh, 17 minutes left on the CD, and about, well, about 35 minutes left on the program.
That's about how much breath we have left in our...
Pneuma.
Why would J.R. Bob Dobbs need insurance premiums if he's the luckiest man in the world?
Well, he sells insurance.
Yeah, you think he would be...
He'd be an insurance salesman.
Yeah.
It sounds like it kind of worked for him.
He made a lot of money on motion picture insurance.
He would produce these movies that were bound to lose, but he also had insurance on them.
Now I know where Mel Brooks got the idea.
Well, where most people get most of their ideas is from J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He's the originator of quite a few things.
If you go back all the way in time, some things weren't even created yet before he...
Created them.
The font of a...
Let's scan that font list.
I wonder who that can be.
Suppose I told you that Hunty Furt forth put good vibes.
You're a kid.
Let me ask you something.
Would a be a little good of you if it...
Sure, you're a perfect one.
Get this and print it for the...
Whoa.
No.
No, no, no, no.
No, no.
Bye-bye, Fernanda Nende.
Lee Moore.
Looks like we got another caller on the line here from California.
You're on the air.
I am in California.
Welcome to the program.
Hi, California child.
Hi, Callie.
California dreamin'.
My mother bore me in Midwestern wilds, and I am fat.
Very faithful listener.
But, oh, my soul is thin.
Full slender is the California child.
But I am fat with loathsome double chin.
There were really Mormons at X Day?
I had to ask about that.
More Mormons than you could remember.
Shake a stick at it.
There were certainly polygamists.
The best part about the Mormons is, you know, they're all teetotalers, so, you know, more booze for us.
Yeah, they can have their tea.
That is what is great about Muslim fundamentalists.
You invite them to a party, and they will just have a smoke or two and a quick dip in the lounge,
but they will not imbibe unless they're, you know, being bad.
Self-action a la mode.
A little bit of a moat and a cup of tea.
That's all they need.
I believe it was Calvin Coolidge, President of the United States, who said the immortal
lines are,
Higamous, hogamous.
Girls are monogamous.
Hogamous, higamous.
Boys are polygamous.
We, uh...
I can't afford that erudite explanation of this track.
Well, they called him Silent Cal, but that's one time he mouthed off, and his wife clouded
him across the chops with an umbrella.
On the White House lawn.
I cannot imagine having a president who doesn't talk too much.
That's beyond my...
Well, President Collard Cheese not only talked too much, he was a tool of the uber state,
and people don't know it.
He helped fire on the bonus marcher.
He enjoyed the...
Oh, never mind.
Then there was the forgotten president.
We here at Fox News want to know how many husbands each wife has on a polygamous compound.
That was the recorded voice of President Stovall, the forgotten president.
They are a 39th president, or actually our first president.
It's good to hear you traveling, Dr. Howe.
Most people think that George Washington was indeed America's first president.
I'm on a dusty road, and I'm traveling, traveling, traveling.
They call me traveling, Dr. Howe.
We had to ride out there in Amish buggies.
They don't let you use automobiles past the Sherman City limits.
They got buggy whips and long britches.
They were driving this buggy, but we got them whipped into shape.
Whip.
Ow!
And the sad geniuses have made the milk sour for crying off loud.
I'm tired of this Yankee craziness.
That's a lot of clabber, but somebody done upended this Yankee-style butter churn,
and I aim to find out who it is.
Just look at the beautiful textiles they make, just like they used to.
And here is the spinning wheel, and it goes round, see?
Like this.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, here, let me clean that up for you.
Bird, baby, bird.
They have the secret of a powerful force, and of course, it's called fire.
Today, on this day, we've learned that fire requires several secret ingredients,
including oxygen, which is also required for the combustion of prop.
It requires fuel, such as plastic.
And also wood has been used, as you can see.
We did not know who created this jobs icon.
We insert it into the reactor core, which we are facing now.
We're sweating now already from the heat.
An amazing physical reaction.
Most subgeniuses never see such things, because most of them only go to conventions and holiday ends.
And you, however, were brave enough to risk life and live,
and be near this radioactive, fiery core,
in order to finally send a message to the exes
that we're not really complete followers,
and that we rebel against our leaders, as the order is due,
every year at exactly this time.
Friends, we're going to admire this fire.
If any of you brought a portable church organ,
I can't.
Uh, uh...
A nice, traditional hymn would be in order.
I brought my organ, Sam.
You know, the secret of rhythm, another one of their closely held secrets.
You could grab a drum and begin pounding out a fitful beat,
to which probably no one will dance, because they are traditionally very self-conscious.
So then we went to Yeti World, and we looked at the wonderful displays there in the mahogany museum.
The statue.
The statues of the great progenitors.
And finally we went up in the huge head of the giant Ivan Stang statue,
made entirely from dolomite.
Dolomite is my name!
Ah!
Easy, Ivan.
I remember your blood pressure.
He hasn't been the same since he came down out of that big head of his own head.
You know, but, but, you know, that's, that's...
Wasn't that something?
An entire Ivan Stang head, made of dolomite?
Well, when it started to move, that's when it got me.
I thought it was gonna stand still, and that's when it started to move around.
Yeah, I dig that.
Well, Sister Ragnarump and Reverend Aunt Janice, like, thought I was flying like a witch or a broomstick thing or something,
and then they thought that they really landed.
But nobody actually knew who really landed, but they were pointing at the sky,
and I guess Majad or some dude was actually inflating...
Chomp.
They called him the Inflatable Chinaman, which is politically bad so forth,
but that's what they call him, you know?
And then they weren't real either.
Listen, mister, I'm gonna lay my cards on the table.
I'm, I'm an old man, and servicing those women is draining me dry.
I can't, I can't take it.
I need some time off.
They gotta keep them off me.
Let me get away from you.
Pick up the slack for him, okay?
Yeah, they have old men off.
They're real fine on next day.
There were, there were, there were some tantalizing UFO sightings.
There were.
That next day.
There was one right in the middle of the, uh...
Amino.
The amino acids.
Sting, did you see those things?
Yeah.
What was that?
It was the amino acids drummer and bass player.
They're coming in late.
That wasn't fireworks or anything.
No.
It was yellow lights manning through the sky.
I've seen a lot of things in my 58 years.
It's come true.
The next day.
That's right.
They're just a little late.
They're on my schedule for a day.
They're on Main Street.
Yeah.
And every Main Street.
And then, uh, this very morning, as we were, uh, trying to figure out a proper ending for
our, our sad, slow hour, live hour of slack.
Yeah.
We were suddenly called out to, uh, discover that there was in fact, X Day had become a,
the prophesied sausage fest that everyone has says it, has said it was with the giant
flying sausages hovering over the...
Yes.
Project Blue Book now declassified.
Everyone said saucers.
It turns out to have been a misprint for sausages.
Sausages.
Yes.
Sausages, this is, this is the only sausage I was in the air with, Spent Nan tries
hit this politicians.
Oh, they have scaped the greasey bounds of earth.
Leaped from the pan, with sizzling sausage wings, flown through the sky amid the jacund
mirth of all who saw those flying sausage things.
Flipped round and round, and what was really odd became entangled in the beard.
I did it.
of gold.
You think we're making this up, but there
really were giant flying sausages
I swear I saw it.
And I'm not a drinking man.
Now were these Polish sausages or
were they Italian sausages or
were they Italian sausages?
They were black.
The casings of the, well let's call them the phenomena,
they were black.
They were enormous.
Filling up a football field or two.
That's what gave them the
idea that somehow they were
related to the black helicopters
because they were indeed black sausages.
But there were no markings
just like with a helicopter.
This was no normal color black.
It was as if it was sucking in all
possible light.
Anti-numinous.
In the sky, in the sky
there'll be sausage
by and by.
In that X-Day, X-Day
sky, there's sausages
on high.
Oh, you're making fun of my haircut.
I believe I'm alive.
Calm down, Pops.
You know, a lot of our
senior citizens out here are a little,
well, we call them excitable because
they get so handed up at X-Day.
Please tell me why you've wasted
all my money on this X-Day
subgenius churchopedius of whatever
the damn hell it is.
Gingery old coot, isn't he?
Stop making fun of your father with your
fringe.
That's not my father.
You rub penises,
get off of my...
Stop rubbing them rub geniuses the wrong way.
Ain't their bridge work done yet?
Let's blow it up and start all over again.
You know, these days
they can just put in a piece of plastic,
fix you right up. I don't see why
these old fossils are still stumping
around out here.
Old fossils, hell, I loaded that whole
van, unloaded it, loaded it again,
unloaded it again.
And it's true, everything hurts.
And you smell
like it, too.
Well done. The van was found to have been
filled with human corpses.
At least, that's what they looked like at first.
But after a brief examination
by Dr. Zorad, it was revealed
that most of them had been
put to sleep and had shrunk.
It wasn't long before
Tom and Timmy tried to round up...
Hey, guys.
Look, if you light a fire under these guys,
they start wiggling. I have a feeling
they're not knocked out after all.
I'm gonna use this little
cigarette lighter here.
Hold it under
this one, the one that has the long
gray hair.
Yep, okay. Alright, now we got
a nice little cherry red fire
going.
Listen, Tom,
he's still inside!
Well, he...
Rumors of his death were
certainly exaggerated. He turned out to be
a lively buck, full
of the sap of life.
Hey, where's my sap,
rolling? Well, I don't know, but
when you didn't sign
the register at X-Day, you
incurred a violation
which will entail a
considerable financial penalty.
The form you will receive in
the mail is not the one
that you should open first. Wait two days.
When the red envelope appears
with the cellophane window,
discard it at once.
Then go out, sit
on your front lawn, and wait
for further instructions. That is all.
Okay, so I gotta get
a red envelope with a...
Oh, never mind that. It's next X-Day.
Just start planning for next X-Day now.
You cannot use the red envelope. Only
use the orange envelope. You know
the red envelope isn't the right one yet.
It's not for you.
Oh, okay. I'm administrating
as Connie-ite.
So let's take a look at what we got here.
One rubber.
Okay.
On.
Two.
Three. Four.
We got five bucks of change
and a rubber to get us there sooner.
It's a start.
Though the rubber's probably good.
Bob keeps getting girls
pregnant.
In two weeks,
this spot will be filled
with topless, hairy,
arm-pinned, beautiful, naked,
pagan girls and muscle men.
And more serious like
pagan men.
At Starwood, which the princess,
we and I would like to invite
every such genius to come.
And also next weekend at Serious Rising,
where equally
hairy, arm-pinned, lovely,
bouncing, breasted, pagan ladies
will be doing their hypnotic
cavewoman dance
while their men pound out
quite intricate rhythms
taken from every culture.
It's a beautiful celebration,
actually, and a lot of fun.
And it is thanks to them
that we even have this yearly celebration here
where we await the,
where we learn the lesson,
the same goddamn lesson every time.
Oh, X Day could happen any day.
We don't even know what year this is.
We don't even know what planet this is.
Any day could be X Day,
so you better be ready for Bob to love you,
so send in your $30.
Yeah.
Yes, I know it gets old,
and this phone is getting,
I'm getting tired of holding this microphone,
so I'm going to give it over to
the new stang,
Priestess Pisces,
who will be inheriting all the nervous breakdowns
at future X Day.
Praise Pisces.
Praise Pisces!
I'm Yeti, through and through.
Ain't nothing you can do.
Make the Peaks shake in their booze,
make the conspiracy wanna puke.
You can't hold me,
you can't control me.
All the little Yetis wanna be Pisces,
but still you can't feel me?
What the hell's your problem?
Maybe I can solve them.
Conspiracy, they got a track of you,
but hell, I got an album.
Let's get it together now,
cut loose and tether now,
waitin' for the sauces,
maybe things will get better now.
I got more issues than time,
but I still,
I still bustin' out rhymes
that make you shake in your boots,
but they call me a kook.
My voice is in the Bible,
they're playin' like recitals,
askin' me, wonderin' why,
I'm so damn fly,
but don't ask why,
cause it's slack off, or die.
You know what the man says,
just wait for X day.
But in the meanwhile,
we gotta freestyle,
fight the conspiracy,
not gettin' no better than me.
I won't stop fightin',
I won't stop writin',
my rhymes are gettin' stronger,
we won't have to wait too much longer,
till the saucers come on down,
burnin' up your hometown.
But you keep questionin',
full of doubts,
what if X day isn't happenin', man?
Till you take some action, man,
stand up for yourself,
tell them peeps to go to hell,
or beat the system from within.
Do what it takes,
to win.
This ain't a battle,
it's about the war.
Go read Revelation X,
if you forgot what this is for!
Yes, ma'am!
Sister Deca,
it's pure subjectiveness.
I'm not sure, actually,
what Alice is, but
she's somehow a key to something.
Boy, those Coneyites were out there,
dancing around the fire,
in all their glory.
It was enough to make a red-blooded boy
sit up and take notice.
I thought the smell was quite adorable.
I spent four or five hours pulled over
in a ditch on the side of the road,
near there in Brushwood.
I just wafted in the aroma.
There were so many naked bodies
dancing around, I became delirious.
Dizzy, I started to see things,
little poppin' lights in the sky,
kinda like a n-n-n-n-nimbus was around everything.
The stars were glowin', and then I,
I fell asleep, and I,
for a long time, I,
I didn't know where I was.
I'm even just hungry.
This doesn't look like a sausage fest to me.
We get accused of it being all boys and no girls.
I'm doing surveillance.
That's the thing.
I like surveilling Reverend Annie.
Huh?
It's the last thing,
the last of the scrap.
Oh, that was, that was what I was,
I was praying that I'd make it down here
in time to taste it.
The food, oh, it was great.
Chef Borgerigmus did himself proud,
and he served everyone at the camp
his piping hot, super special flat cakes.
Oh, not to mention the scrapple.
Mmm.
Scrapple.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, Nancy Collins' little dog,
chopped up, sliced, and served up to everyone.
I like my scrapple with a side of scrapey.
And, uh, there was a certain...
It didn't have scabies,
that was a rumor in camp.
The Chaz sausages were my favorite.
Mmm.
They were blackened, and, uh, like redfish,
with a pair of sunglasses and a twist of Lyman.
Uh, for radio...
It was a zombies jamboree.
Yeah, yeah, there was a zombies jamboree.
For those who remember, uh, Professor Chaz Smith
and his wonderful show here on WCSB,
ESO Swamp Radio,
uh, Chaz's old friends, uh, Leguim,
Bob the Drummer, and, uh, Ed Strange,
uh, disinterred the old DJ's course.
He worked preserve以及
Uh, ou six, Richard Strass 먹
deel
mereka
pers foi
der
Ngob法
Did you see the fast hand on that guitar?
I'm an acrophiliac, I only like dead people.
Good stiff ones.
Where's Chaz?
Oh, he'll be along. Chaz will be along shortly.
I don't know, but I've been told this says landmines in Arabic.
I think it's really a bodily fluid for Chaz.
Oh, okay.
They're not zombies, they're Chaz-bees.
Oh, they're Chaz's?
Chaz-bees.
They're putting on their faces whatever this stuff is.
It's some bio-product from the corpse of Chaz.
Whoa, gross. Chaz squeezins.
It's a spooge, a zombie spooge of Chaz.
Spooge.
Threading through the crowd.
Oh, gross, I hate, yeah.
I hate to interrupt your reverie.
There's some lurching people over there.
Make way for brother Chaz.
Is everybody in?
He's back.
It's the best thing ever.
I don't know how that happened, but...
Shut the fuck up.
You from Hollywood?
Get your ass off the stage.
Shut up.
I won a Tony Award.
Brothers and sisters, welcome to the first ever Tiki Banzai Night of the Dead party.
Yeah.
We delivered, as promised, brother Chaz.
Yay, Chaz.
Woo.
Brother Chaz.
Yeah.
Chaz.
Brother Chaz.
Take brother Chaz away.
The frogs are hungry.
Recently I attended the solstice ritual here, and I learned a lot from watching that solstice
ritual.
I learned that it was kind of silly, and egotistical, and kind of pretentious, so I
stole it.
I'm gonna eat it.
Own it, dude.
It's a prayer of thanksgiving.
First, I'd like to call up my young daughter.
Aww.
So I didn't know that I was supposed to be here.
And you're just a friend.
We're friends.
Yeah.
room. We thank the earth for not throwing us the fuck off.
We thank the sea because if not for the sea, we would all be waiting for a really long
time in line at Red Lobster.
Grandfather of the North,
I thank you for professional hockey and Santa.
Grandfather to the South,
I thank you for cheap labor.
Grandfather to the West,
we thank you for movies and homosexuals.
Grandfather to the East,
thanks for nothing, motherfucker!
Hey, that's where you came from, dude!
You've each been handed a card, brothers and sisters.
Now, I need y'all and Princess Pisces to bring you all up to the stage here, one at a time,
and hand Princess Pisces your card.
Then you will step over in front of me, where I will deliver unto you communion.
Depending on whether you're over 18 or not, it's pretty strong shit.
That crap.
Not gonna be pretty, folks.
Read the name.
Typhoid Mary!
Typhoid Mary.
Heal me, brother!
I had a disease throughout the Northeast United States back at the turn of the century.
Heal me!
Now, there's no way that I could possibly give communion to Typhoid Mary,
to send Typhoid Mary to Heaven, because I don't have that power.
At least not without the magic rock.
With the magic rock, I can send the soul of Typhoid Mary to Heaven,
much like the Mormons,
through their ritual,
have baptized some of the dead from history into the Mormon faith,
so that they'd get to go to Heaven, including Jews from the Holocaust.
I'm your friend.
Which kind of pissed off the Jews.
I heard the Holocaust not on the right there.
Now, you may ask, where did I get this magic rock that gives me the power to send people to Christian Heaven?
And I tell you this, brothers and sisters,
none of your fucking business!
That's right.
But I've got the rock,
and I'm going to send Typhoid Mary here,
I'm going to send her soul to Heaven,
as the first soldier in our platoon of the damned,
in this, the first battle of our war on Heaven itself.
Yee-haw!
Next!
Thank you.
I feel so evil now.
Attila the Hun!
Attila the Hun,
today you will sit at the side of your lord.
Charlton Heston!
Charlton Heston,
you peckerhead,
you thought you were going to get there the easy way.
Oh.
Keep pouring, right?
No, I was way too high earlier.
He's a card-carrying zombie.
George Carlin!
Give him hell, George!
Give him hell, George.
You pussy, you don't know how to pour that drink.
Move along, George.
Tupac Shakur!
West Coast!
He's one puck, he got the other puck, Shakur!
Oh, he got the pick?
No, he's two pucks.
Wait!
One for your homies.
Rasputin!
You'll never die!
You son of a bitch, it took him a long time to kill you,
and this will get you there just one step further.
Give me Hendrick's energy drink.
Gigi Allen!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah, we know what you're gonna be flinging around in those white clowns.
Go fling some shit for us, Gigi.
Aren't you glad you let me put the makeup on you?
So you can become Gigi Allen.
Otis Toole!
Otis Toole, serial killer.
Get to work, boy!
Get to work!
Genghis Khan!
Wow, you look much shorter in person.
Anton LaVey!
A real fucking professional, bitch!
Bob!
Get that noise for Bob!
Woo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Where's your juice?
On the other side, Bob.
Edward Teach!
Blackbeard!
Go swab some poop decks in heaven!
Good one, Hank.
Richard Nixon!
Yes!
He's tan, he's rested, he's ready.
Who's without the robot body?
Ooh, that's good hooch.
I am not a crook.
Don't eat the earth.
Joseph Stalin!
Oh!
Oh, drinking for the people, brother.
Subspecies 23!
He's not dead yet.
But he will be.
Preemptive strike, subspecies 23.
I don't know anyway.
Who's got the chud card?
Chud.
That's probably me.
Ball Pots!
I get those sometimes.
Ball Pots in the box!
Ball!
I mean, Balling!
Ball and Ball!
Ball, and Ball Day!
Ball ag relevant real Hingor.
Ball!
Miss Blackbeard!
Ball peligiller!
Ball!
Ha ha ha!
Call for the Supreme!
Ondra notebooks, opioid, zwanzdark status papers on the back of your white design he
wrote in your face, you have one single to write on the system.
Well, Jamie Arewell comes right in front of me, living on Wall Street.
This is thebia, send a cookie to the ВсеLa aircraft, the entire servers know I'll be
officially freestyle.
Who was it?
That explains the eyes.
Jeffrey Dahmer.
He looks like him.
That's what I was just thinking.
He was such a nice boy.
I'll decline that lunch invitation.
Molly Hatchet.
No, no.
Prepare for the moment.
Either way, sleep well.
Hunter S. Thompson.
This is bat country.
You'll see the bat soon enough.
It's all leaked on it, dude.
As your lawyer, I advise that we get more of that.
No wonder you had stuff all over it.
Albert Fish.
Self-mutilation.
A child.
And a snappy dress.
Yes, he was.
Joseph Minghella.
Oh, hey!
That's awesome.
Professional courtesy.
Minghella?
That's rock.
Fellow doctor.
Freaking good.
You know what the best thing is?
I have a lot of family dies in the camps.
Our last zombie is...
Walt Disney!
Kill him!
I'm a zombie!
Don't kill me.
I'm a zombie.
It is!
It is Walt Disney!
Walt Disney!
Get him, Walt!
Get him!
Walt Disney!
We didn't want you in hell anyway.
Oh, shit.
Okie dokie.
You didn't get a single...
You're from Canada, Bucky.
Canadians don't have souls.
No, that's good.
That's some damn good...
Yeah, you have no soul!
South Park versus Canada.
Get out!
So, you got lucky.
The opening came up.
Papa Doc Duvalier.
Well, our first blow has been struck in the war on heaven.
We have sent our first platoon of the damned.
Jesus, another fucking stride.
Easy E.
I can drink to that.
Easy E died of two AIDS at Tiki Bonsai.
Well, brothers and sisters, tonight we've all drank to the formation of our army of
the damned.
Our army of soldiers who have already kicked it.
And I'm gonna pass this jug around to you.
And Brother Two Beans is gonna kick it.
Kick it!
I can hardly see that cat playing.
He was whipping me so fast, you know.
All right.
We got another caller here.
And that's macabre but bad macabre.
Nobody Mark, welcome to the program.
How do you know?
I know all.
That's what your new clone has.
You have psychic powers now, Dr. Sinister.
That's right.
You know, I don't know if I was gonna have much of a say tonight because when all you
guys are together, you probably don't need callers, but...
Well, it's amazing how well these people can hold on.
But I did want to mention one thing.
Any of you hear of this new show on ABC Family called The Middleman, sort of a parody of
action-adventure?
No.
Yes, we've been hearing reports of J.R. Bob Dobbs showing up on that in hint form.
Well, what I saw last week in the third episode was one character had to pick somebody up
at the J.R. Bob Dobbs International Airport.
Yes.
We were sent a freeze frame of that.
Yeah.
But that's true.
I mean...
The Bob...
Well, J.R. Bob Dobbs International Airport has fallen on hard times.
There aren't that many flights going in and out of there.
Well, that's in Dobbstown, Malaysia, though, isn't it?
Well, exotic Dobbstown, Malaysia, but that's not the only airport there.
All those red-hot cargo containers in the blistering sun, that's where the subgeniuses
have to stay during the day.
Right.
Well, not all of us.
Some of us stay in the big house.
Just the bobbies.
They stack them in like cordwood.
But in the big house, there's mint juleps and...
All sorts of great stuff.
Oh, yes.
Down in the rank and file, there's nothing but applesauce and Kool-Aid.
Well, Princess Wee and I sat out on the veranda watching that field of tents.
Hooverville, Brushwood, we call it.
Here's the celebrity pool.
Tent City.
Right.
There's the celebrity pool, and then there's the Bobby Mud Pit.
Look at them snorting and grunting like hogs.
Some of those are hogs, Dr. Howell.
Yeah, but the snouts are just different.
They're just different around here.
Ah, I guess Herbert Hoover was the president when I marched for a bonus.
It wasn't Calvin Coolidge.
He was busy playing billiards.
I had a bonus since I was 50.
Well...
I got a question for the subgenius.
Do you do the face healing type of stuff?
Face healing?
Ha.
That's from your mortals.
We do face thickening.
You get your face healing, and you gotta fix it again three or four more weeks.
Oh, yeah.
Three or four weeks later.
Come on.
You know you want one.
Sign here.
And here.
Initial here.
Now initial here.
Beautiful, glorious, glowing subgenius.
Brand new, fully decanted.
The man of the future.
Look at him, his giant statue standing against the stars.
How he spans heaven and earth with his incredible, incalculable potential.
He's the jolly.
Oh, green giant.
And our glorious leader, Reverend Dr. Ivan Stang, will be here to address us in just a moment.
So until that time, hold your banners high and form your ranks against those who wish to drag them in the dust.
I think he was coming to dress us, not address us.
Well, he might come to dress us down.
Jimbo!
What's all the fuss about the game, man?
Still got some zombies.
Oh, Jimbo.
I'm sorry.
It's tough to get rid of that infection.
The last time I was naked in a pool with a Marine, it cost me $15.
Now it's $13.
Reverend Jimbo, oh man, you've been a farm animal for the U.S. government for the last year since that day.
It's time to wash that state of possession off of you.
For today, you belong to Bob, brother.
You're going to die.
Many souls were cleansed and needed it pretty badly, and the swimming pool was kind of gray afterwards, after the baptism.
I remember two completely unclothed women that began to undress Reverend Chris Lee.
Lucky bastard.
You remember that?
Chris Lee?
Well, that was because he got Playboy of the Year and the Bobby Award.
Well, he was dressed as a testicle for most of the afternoon.
And one day, I could see why women would find him very attractive, but not with that top hat and tie.
Now, he was dressed as a testicle, not a pair.
There was a pair, of which he was one.
He was the male testicle.
There was also a female testicle, played by Honey Pie Volkerding.
And there was a child who played the middle part, who had more motor skills and dynamic abilities than the average subpoena.
That cute little kid thought I was a subpoena.
He was Dr. Seuss.
You should have heard those rhymes Ivan came up with.
That's what they all think before they eat dab of sauce and wash it down with Kool-Aid.
I drank the Kool-Aid.
Dr. Sinister got a Bobby Award for best handling of insane, obnoxious callers on a talk show.
I'm flattered.
Napa, Napa.
Why, thank you.
And the award for best excuse for missing X Day goes to...
To Reverend Carter LeBlanc, who is currently in the Valley of Armageddon digging up dead people.
No kidding.
Aren't we all in some way or another?
No lie.
I'll do this one.
Friends, for those of us who have radio shows, especially the ones foolish enough to take callers, present company excluded, know that it takes a lot of grace and tact to handle racist troll idiots.
Well, Dr. Sinister does not use that grace and tact and hangs up on Nappy Caller wonderfully.
So if only Dr. Sinister could come forward and accept his best radio troll handling award.
Nappy.
However, he appears to be off handling that cute girl he came here with.
So we'll present that to him on the air later.
And the later is now.
And so I hereby present Dr. Sinister of WCW.
WCSB in Cleveland with this official 2008 Bobby Award, which I will leave in his box at the station.
Probably he's hearing this now because we're down to the end of Hour of Slack number 1162, the first of several returns to the joys and disappointments of X Day.
This is Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about X Day, JR Bob Dobbs, or the Church, or anybody, you may see www.subgenius.com.
Or you may write to P.O. Box 1815.
417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or email stang at subgenius.com.
The amino acids are what's in the background and what we're about to now close with.
For more information about the amino acids, you can see theaminoacids.com.
Now recorded by Potter and Ostril at X Day 11.
The Amino Acids.
Aliens.
Str Pleddon.
43, Dawson And London.
Blackbuckt got 80.
The F shares, Keeping the Pro calling.
41, permits farther
that was attacked report that the beast they encountered was many times the size they expected,
indicating that the monster had some strange power of rapid growth.
An exact description was...
We have a bulletin just received. According to a report not yet confirmed,
the beast of seemingly gigantic proportions has been sighted lurking in the hills due north-east
of town. City officials have called for military help. Planes and troops are expected to arrive
within the next two hours. Meanwhile, citizens should take refuge in places of safety.
Cellars, bomb shelters, as directed by civil defense administrators. I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat, I repeat...
From PR News in Washington, I'm subjected to forced nudity,
mock electric executions and other inhumane treatment by employees of PR News.
The FBI is murdering a Maryland police officer.
The state medical examiner has more on that from Flagstaff.
Preliminary reports were broken.
Republican presidential candidate John McCain heads to Washington today for talks about PR News,
which he says is good for everyone in the long run.
PR News, Washington.
PR comes from juvenilepr.org.