You ain't nothing but a soul genius.
Power of...
...work.
We depend on you to lift the standards of our young people,
not hasten their decadence.
Fuck me!
Those of you who read the schedule,
raise your hands.
Oh, look, it's wet.
One, two, three.
I don't even have one yet.
Another record has been broken.
So here's the deal.
Pretty much on the schedule, this section is called fuckery.
So, since we have live mics,
and so what that means is you can rant.
Really, just let's stick with ranting,
because there's not a place to stick with an instrument yet.
Well, unless you've got kids' instruments.
You know, or spoons or coffee cans.
Or acapella.
You can do acapella, that's right.
You can hold a bongo.
You probably could.
Who doesn't say fuckery? It said fuckery from seven to nine!
What?
What the hell is this?
Well, so much for fuckery.
It's the schedule set back.
Who reads the schedule now?
Who wants expired fuckery?
Well, you know, it's...
Extended?
Yeah, it's extended.
Extended.
Extended fuckery.
What it is, is you're getting a great deal on fuckery,
because we had some extra fuckery leftover.
30% more fuckery.
Yes, so this is extra fuckery just for you guys.
Over doctors for Bob.
Doctors for Bob and everything real in my life.
I got the blues,
cause that damn pickup truck done.
Run over my wife.
Doctors for Bob and everything real in my life.
Ah, yes dear friends, back to the early gospels
by way of the most recent subgenius religious gathering 18X day drill.
Actually, our 20th drill.
But only the first two in 1996 and 1997 were supposed to be drills.
Anyway, this is another one of those episodes composed entirely of stuff recorded on or around the Wisteria Campground outdoor stage last July.
You'll feel like you're actually at X Day.
So I hope you brought your snakebite kit and bear repellent.
This is also an X-rated show, meaning it won't be on our beloved broadcast stations, only the internet.
Also, these kinds of shows, you know,
utilize more of the, shall we say,
you had to have been there sort of material,
which might or might not be of interest to people who were not there.
However, everybody will like this first song by St. Andrew the Impaled,
at least once he finishes fucking around with the technical stuff.
You'll hear more of that, the futzing around with technical stuff, in this episode than you do in most.
See, there's two microphones, there should be two mirrors.
Guys, what the fuck?
That's how you diva, bitches.
Alright.
Alright, this next song is...
Got it!
There you go, thank you.
See? See?
And when you diva right, that's how it works.
That's why people are divas.
You're one of like, why is he such an asshole?
It fucking works.
Thank you, Pisces.
There.
See?
Fucking learning.
Alright.
Fucking talk.
There will be a day
When all the pink boys pay
They'll scream burn with nowhere left to run
But I won't be around
Cause I'm headed out of town
To outer space
And a saucer built for one
And my saucer built for one
Gave that sucker towards the sun
Light the fuse and then I'm on my way
I realize my dreams as I hear the pink boys scream
And agony and terror come next day
Now a saucer built for one
Sure sounds like lots of fun
Till you realize that there's no one there to screw
And I get bored with my hands
So I ripped up all my plans
Now I'm working on a saucer built for two
And my saucer built for two
You notice what we'll do?
Each other as we make our way through space
And in a rearview mirror
We'll see nothing but fear
As the X's ravage Earth come X day
Now a saucer built for two
Got a cozy seat for you
And another one on this side just for me
But when I'm between your thighs
I need someone else to drive
So now I'm working on a saucer built for three
And my saucer built for three
Yeah, you ain't heard me!
We'll all take turns
And we'll all get to play
And they'll know it's no joke
As the fakes go up in smoke
And agony and terror come X day
Now a saucer built for three
Might seem quite enough for me
But I for one need just a little more
So I went back to the shop
I put that fucker off on blocks
And now I'm working on a saucer built for four
And my saucer built for four
Yeah, no one's getting bored
There's always someone up for getting laid
And we'll thank our lucky stars
As we cruise right past Mars
That we escaped the carnage of X day
Now a saucer built for four
I guess I shouldn't ask for more
But what the hell, why else am I alive?
Besides, I don't need a break every six hours, give or take
So now I'm working on a saucer built for five
And my saucer built for five
From now till we arrive
We'll fucking suck with luck in every way
And each time we get laid
The memories will fade
Of what the Earth was like before X day
Now a saucer built for five
Three to shag and one to drive
But it turns out that the ladies want more dicks
So I'm getting out of bed
I'm getting right back to my shed
And now I'm working on a saucer built for six
And my saucer built for six
Might learn me some new tricks
As we go tearing across the Milky Way
Laughing as we drink
About every single pink
Who fried right where they stood
Come X day
Now a saucer built for six
So much cock and ass and tits
No one ever got so close to heaven
But at the risk of sounding rude
We might need one for food
So now I'm working on a saucer for seven
And my saucer built for seven
We got room for Cat and Kevin
And five more Yeti freaks who knew how to pay
Thirty some odd bucks to Bob
And they finally quit that job
And that wave of corporate layoffs
Come X day
Now a saucer built for seven
And it only takes a second
To turn around and find yourself a date
But the place will be a mess
We'll need some cleaning help I guess
So now I'm working on a saucer built for eight
And my saucer built for eight
No one has to masturbate
Yeah, there's always someone up for getting laid
Oh no, shit, oh fuck
Yeah, rewind that
Cut it in now
Three, two
And my saucer built for eight
No one has to masturbate
A little help here is all you gotta say
Get some pretty Yeti mouth
Is happy to go south
After all, that's what we practiced for X day
Now my saucer built for eight
Of course that sounds just great
But I'm starting now to recognize a trend
I'd build it out for nine
And then I'd change my mind
So fucking kids were skipping ahead to ten
And my saucer built for ten
A mobile pleasure den
A hedonistic hoedown on its way
To that sexy slack-filled place
Away up there in space
We were promised would be ready come X day
Now a saucer built for ten
You might think that that's the end
But I hate to let down my subgenius brethren
So I put in extra doors
Put some beanbags on the floors
Now I'm proud to say my saucer seat's eleven
And my saucer for eleven
My libido won't be edimin'
In fact, I might become a better lay
Cause I'll learn from the best
And I'll practice on the rest
As we all make each other
Come X day
Now my saucer for eleven
Oh my, this place is gettin'
To be one where it's hard to hear yourself
So I'll make an intercom somehow
Cause I ain't stoppin' now
Cause I'm workin' on a saucer built for twelve
And my saucer built for twelve
Escaping from that hell
The earth will become, or so they say
Half the hands of the world
Who grab an ass
The other half will raise a glass
To those liberating exists of X day
Now a saucer built for twelve
Oh dear, Bob, the smell
And the furniture all has a sticky sheen
But if that's not quite enough
Well, I hate to say it, but tough
I ain't workin' on a saucer for thirteen
And oh, my saucer built for twelve
Will suit us all well, well
With whips and toys and liquor and poker
Yay!
And no one's gettin' off
Well, everyone's getting off
And no, we'll never stop
Unless we run into those Heaven's Gate people
Yeah, I wanna talk to them about some, like, new tennis shoes
Until we reach the top
Until we reach our new home
Call Max D
Thank you so much!
I'm Drew, Andrew the Impaled, Saint Sinner
Thank you so much
I'll be back tomorrow night with a sideshow
Including the one and only Slippy the Clown
AKA Reverend David Apocalypse
Who many of you have heard about for many years
And we'll see in the flesh here
Hopefully a lot of flesh, we'll see
Yeah, tomorrow night
Thanks again!
In the name of all that is Hypercube
Not that stupid garbage bullshit
No, absolutely not
Everyone give a round, everyone say hi to Fox
Hi Fox!
It's wonderful
Is this thing, is this a microphone or is this
Is this one a microphone too?
Okay, I like this one
Wonderful
I'm more comfortable here, if that's okay with all of you
Oh well, oh well, anyway
Well everybody, here we are
X Day!
Woo!
Again
It's okay!
It's okay, on the way up here
My god, if there's one thing I've learned on every X Day you know it's
How many people can I cram into a car?
Subgeniuses are incredibly squishy and pliable
Despite how most of them look really
But if you cram enough subgeniuses in your car
You get to come all the way up here
And you get to see all of your subgenius brethren and whatnot
And I don't, you know, I've got prepared stuff
I'll do a little bit of that
But then I want to go, you know, fuck around up there too
So, you know, let's talk about the Midwest real quick
How many of you are from Ohio or live here in the Midwest?
Who's here in Ohio?
Okay, perfect, I can take all of you
Alright, perfect
So, actually this place isn't nearly as bad
You know, a few years ago I had to come up and travel into the Midwest
On a overnight subgenius rescue mission actually
I had to take a car that wasn't mine
And drive it up and go to Ohio
I left Florida, it was 70 degrees and sunny
And I was this desolate fucking wasteland
Of just bitter fuck and cold and hate
And I don't know why anyone would ever live there
In fact, when we got in, the roads were highlighted out of Iowa
And this was at the Welcome Station
So that let me know just what kind of environment the Midwest is
And I don't know, is this considered Midwest area?
I don't know what this is
It's about to be, I hope everyone remembered to turn their air conditioners a little high before they left
Because it's going to get hot
No matter where you're going to be
Whether you're in the Midwest
Whether you're in the Southwest
Or an East-West
Or maybe an East-West
Or a Clint Eastwood
Or a Cunt Eastwood
Or wherever you are, it's about to get hot, right?
It's about to get a lot hotter
It's going to get a lot hotter because it's going to be ecstasy!
The ecstasy!
They're going to come down from the sky
They're going to fucking burn it all
And so, yeah
So I'm going to go straight to the number one source I know for burning it all
And I'm just going to read a few passages from the Holy Bible
So, let's see here
Let's do some Bible talking
Deuteronomy, you want Deuteronomy, canonical?
What do we got?
Let's see, 2853
Okay, you want Deuteronomy, here's Deuteronomy
Mmmmm
Mmmmm!
Mmmmmmmm!
So it leads us to chapter 14
But watch this now
Okay, so this, Dr. Abraham
He says that
During theik
of the suffering your enemy will inflict
on you during the siege of all of your
cities. The most gentle
and sensitive woman among you, so
sensitive and gentle that she would not
venture to touch the ground with the sole of her
foot, will begrudge the husband
she loves and her own son or daughter,
the afterbirth from the womb
and the children she bears.
For in her dire need, she intends
to eat them secretly. Because of the
suffering your enemy will inflict on you
during the siege of your cities.
We're gonna make them eat their fucking baby!
Cheese!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Woo!
I don't know.
That sounds like a revelation to me.
It sounds like, you know,
a good idea. I don't know why
people don't like this book
so much. It's great!
So many wonderful
ideas that we could be putting into
mode right now.
Who's got a baby?
Okay, Stank's got babies.
Alright, well, I think that's enough
Bible ranting for me tonight.
But, uh, we'll do more of this
goofy video bullshit and whatever,
but, uh, Pisces, you want a microphone?
Here you go.
Big round of
applause!
There's nothing like the Bible to remind you how
fucked up shit
really could be.
Yes, that
was Reverend Fox.
From Hypercube in Orlando.
And most people mispronounce
his name, Fox, because
it's spelled in the way that
causes the unknowing to pronounce
it, foe.
Those wacky subgeniuses.
Incidentally, during the
X-Day drills these days,
the wacky subgeniuses are herded
like rabid cats by
the one person capable of managing
such a thing, Priestess Pisces.
Pisces is the
main behind-the-scenes organizer of the,
of these drills, also the emcee on
stage, also the person who'll sing
or rant scriptlessly
when nobody else has the ball or
gumption or energy to do it.
Her mighty husband, Suds
Pasha, runs sound
and gets half the recordings that we
use, along with playing guitar and
illustrating and making videos and
helping to get the new Bob Song
albums online. Yes,
new Bob Song
albums that you can buy
and that we can talk about because
this show isn't going to be on
community stations,
non-profit stations.
You can even preview the songs
for free, friends, at our new
pay-per-download classic
subgenius album site,
which is on bandcamp.com
specifically
subgeniusfoundation.bandcamp.com
subgeniusfoundation being only one word
with two O's in it.
Or you can just hit subgenius.com's
homepage and look for the
CD downloads link.
It's been eight years since Bob Song's
number six, but now we have
Bob Song's seven and eight,
each of which can be burned
to precisely fill an audio CD
or you can play it from your
iPod or whatnot.
And they have cool cover art by
Dr. Zeronius, Molg,
and Reverend Catfeather, respectively.
Most
of the songs on these are studio
recordings by dozens of different bands
as opposed to the live
jams that you'll be hearing on this show tonight.
There are some of those, but mostly
it's the slick-sounding subgenius music
that you've been hearing on Hour of Slack for the last
eight years.
It's a buck a song or $10
an album, and each album has about
30 songs. And
all our old CD albums
are available for download there
as well. That's
subgeniusfoundation.bandcamp.com
We need all the help we can get this
month, friends, seriously.
We really appreciate
the Hour of Slack
donations that
a few people do regularly
contribute.
But there's not much of old Bessie
left to sell. So get
right on that stick and buy
subgenius.
Right on. So, Grill Ninja's got the balls up here.
I'd like Gravity to come up
here since he's been running his damn mouth all day.
You're all talk, man.
I'm merely the freckle on
Bob's ball sack.
Even the freckle on Bob's
ball sack, DJ Gravity,
that is important. Even the
freckle on Bob's ball sack. And the thing is
is that you've been talking all day.
You are
such a Bob tease.
You little...
You're not even a Bob
slut here. You're not even a slut for Slack.
You're a Bob tease.
I have the fully charged on my Slack.
That right there,
he is a motherfucker who could probably
out-keg stand all of you.
He's beating the peeps at their own game, as
Fitchuli says. He is beating the peeps at their own game
by being an incredibly
hardcore subgenius drinker.
Right on. So,
more ranchers, more spoken word. You head up here.
And I'm waiting.
If not,
we may have to start the tuning song,
which everyone hates.
Where's Reverend Funny Name?
Reverend Funny Name?
Reverend Funny Name. He's funny.
Reverend Funny Name's such a bitch.
He didn't show up.
And you have to show up.
You guys showed up. That's great. Good for you.
You fucking showed up.
How cool is that?
You didn't sit at home saying,
I'm gonna half-ass X Day.
I'm gonna sit here and say, praise Bob
while I'm masturbating to Sports Illustrated.
No, you didn't do that.
You didn't sit there and say, my great plan
for X Day is to go to my work
and take a shit at 7 a.m.
No, you got off your asses
and you showed up and congratulations.
Congratulations, you have to listen to me
on the fucking mic acting like an asshole.
Aren't you glad didn't you get your money's worth?
Because I'm gonna sit up here and talk
and your ass could be up here talking too.
But instead, you don't want to do that.
Is this what you fucking paid for?
Did you pay to watch some stupid broad
run her mouth on the mic? Is that what you paid for?
Guilt!
You're hoping to be topless.
I thought this was a bit called the Pisces Festival.
It's not about me. It's about you.
It's about you and Bob.
So come up here and get connected to Bob.
Get in front of this mic or we're gonna have to start the tuning song.
You guys like the tuning song, don't you?
That's the problem.
It's a fuck Pisces Festival.
Pisces is mean.
When is that on the schedule?
I don't know. I thought it was the whole schedule.
Okay, that's the case. We're gonna start the tuning song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So yeah, we're gonna start the tuning song.
You poor bastards.
You guys are gonna start the tuning song.
You guys ready for the tuning song?
It's an hour and a half long.
That was the tuning song in G.
We're gonna do the tuning song in C flat.
Get it up.
Come on.
Pull it.
Shake it.
Get it.
Jerk off.
Bob don't need these keys.
No, we haven't.
Bob needs something to eat.
Get some certain.
Because he's got slack.
Bob earned it back.
He brought sexy back.
We're gonna run that track.
I've got sand in my vagina.
Yes!
I'll see.
Ladies and gentlemen, again,
are we still the Fuck Peas Band?
I don't know what I am!
Okay, we are the Multi-Fisted Tales of Connie,
also known today as the Fuck Peas Band.
Fuck Peas!
Right now we have Sax & Mortis on drums,
who is chugging his beer.
Stick, of course, on the stick.
Angry Larry on guitar.
Reverend Rock God on guitar.
Lord Ferg on bass.
We have a groupie here.
He's got a big favorite ass.
You're, like, the greatest rock star that I ever saw.
And, like,
I just wanted to be, like,
partake of your talent,
and by, like, giving you a blood job
or whatever you would want, like, backstage,
because I can tell my friends.
And that's all.
I just...
Oh!
I can't believe I said that!
I'm getting nervous right now.
I can't wait until my friends hear about this!
Oh, God!
It's gonna be so dramatic!
I'll put it on Facebook.
Oh, I've got a recording of it!
Oh, great!
I've got a recording of it saying
he won't take a blood job from me!
I'm gonna put it all over Facebook
and everybody will know you're dead!
Oh!
I always wanted to do that.
But Frank Zappa died too soon.
I never got to do Frank Zappa.
Shit!
So, I'm going to do one more spoken piece
and then do some songs,
which I think is what you guys came here for, perhaps.
It's called The Queer in You.
Once upon a new life, someone told you that you were born dirty. Someone told you that when you
were squeezed from between the legs of your beautiful mother, you were already dirty. Blood,
water, newborn open heart to be washed away, foreskin offed, first intimate touch a knife,
to imprint under artificial white lights, white coats, that to make it in this world, kid,
you've got to cut away, cut and shape this organ, clean up your inevitable sin.
First time in a long time yesterday, I started to hate. I hate the big lie. I hate the over-muscled
strong arm that saw you stop jumping rope and start playing football. I hate the boxed,
but love the boxed in, sweet young girl boys, poor things starting to tell that lie.
The box is bullshit. So many pushing and clamoring to,
occupy the same Kinsey zero space fit for 10% of us, maybe.
For the first time in a long, long time yesterday, I really started to hate,
started to hate the incessant sell-a-thon, the vivid color idiot box that sells us black or
white. I hate the channel that tuned you in, dropped you out of anybody with emotion or sound
with a beat. I bought into that lie one time. I reached to absolve my soul,
sisterhood, kick the box of shit that split my mulatto mind down the middle.
That's why I love the queer in you. The one who blushes at a party, flips her wrist talking to a
boy, or a bold, grown man with earrings who flirts back, unaware, body language,
unrealized, over the heads of both of you, too far outside the wall of the box that divides
your lips, your eyes. I love the queer in you, however unwilling he is to speak of his own beauty.
I love the queer in me. I love the queer in you. I love the queer in me. I love the queer in me.
the queer in your swiveling hips when you forget yourself and rock and roll and actually move.
I love the queer in you because I hate the bland alternative, the cookie cutter,
dressed down shirt and tie man who believes he's doing all the right things. Then there's the
patriarch you who gets stiff and annoyed, simmers just under rage when I speak of alternatives to
marriage. The gnawing and lingering one who still believes that a good wife is sweet and home,
proud to assume your name would be better than this rebellious, questioning, grassroots,
organizing, baggy, khaki, shorts-wearing woman you try to know. This one who painfully, honestly,
wants honesty over pleasant emotional lacquer, a good spontaneous fuck over a steady diet of
missionary comfort. This one who wants love over form.
I love the queer in you who wrestles free when you least expect, when you least care for him to bat a long eyelash.
The queer in you who sky is wider and who knows more than all the streamers and rice you could stomach.
The suddenly fearful one who is terror paralyzed, the one who's been shamed away from cleaning his
open wounds, the one who would hold a baby, the mothering man who can heal and will heal in an
instant through lifetimes.
I love the queer in you, the child, teacup brown eyes peeking out from under a lavender blanket, not yet boy or girl, white or black, gay or straight, love or hate, unmade, wiser than our flawed sculptor America.
So grow again, young again, with your original uncut body and glide, no, prance, along the green hill bell curve undistorted, dressed in your finest.
I'll be there, crossing your path with my best dyke swagger.
All right, thank you. Thanks a lot.
No, thank you, Reverend Andrew Genis, for daring to bring pretty music to X-Day.
Incidentally, friends, you can find much more music, graphics, and poetry by Reverend Andrew Genis if you
Google under her human name.
And now we'll hear a little more pretty subgenius music, which I suspect happened accidentally between health songs while people were tuning up.
Somebody was on some kind of keyboard and snuck in these odd and pretty sounds.
I don't know what you guys are doing.
Oh, we should sing about how, how, we could sing about, we could sing about how Stang is unfortunately the asshole of Bob.
And Stang got stuck with me.
Bob's asshole.
Asshole.
Just, just no.
Just no.
Bob!
Ish.
Oh, I guess it's a real name for asshole.
Hey, did you know Bob's spelled backwards is still Bob?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, but Bob is still only one O short of boo.
We all love boo.
We can totally sing a song about that.
Yeah.
Yeah, and Bob is, Bob is just one.
Bob, Bob, Bob is just one.
Yeah.
Anyway, I've got two fart pianos in my front seat.
I have your fart piano and his fart piano.
I might need to finish off in the swimming pool.
So there's, there's.
It's fart pianos all the way down.
The real one and then the froppelganger.
The fro.
The froppelganger.
Yeah.
Well, for all we know, that's one of the ones in my front seat because they all look alike.
You know, to be honest, I've always wanted to be in that situation where I had to shoot the real one and there was like two copies and, you know what I mean, you're pointing the gun and you're like, no, it's me, no, it's me.
You know what I mean?
Be honest.
You, you, you wanted to be in that situation.
Well, in that room full of mirrors, yeah, that one time.
But I quit doing that.
Well.
I slept.
I keep shooting myself and I don't run out of them.
They keep coming.
What the shit?
I believe in you.
Who better knows where the hype is?
I believe in you too.
I believe in you and me.
I believe in my dream.
That's the most important thing, believe in your dream.
Every movie I've ever seen says, believe in your dream.
Yeah, what the shit?
No.
I can't find my class.
It works out.
I'm in my underwear.
That's fucking fantastic, but no.
I don't have any dreams.
I'm trying to find my illusions.
I know I left some here somewhere.
Oh, they're scattered all over the place, Susan.
They're blowing around like down feathers.
Your illusions are everywhere.
If you look around, there's all these people that share your, they've got your illusions
flying through the air.
Wow.
Unfortunately, four bastards have each other's as well.
Oh.
Yeah.
And mine.
Is that what the smell is?
Yeah, yeah.
I thought it was me.
What is that smell?
No.
No, you smell like coconut pie, Reverend Susan Fusey.
That's the sweetest smell I ever smelled.
She's like, coconut pie.
I love coconut too.
Cross the low tide on the sin.
She's the prettiest smelling lady.
I wish she didn't smoke, brother.
That's awful.
I don't know.
It's not good for your health to smoke like that.
I hate to see you destroy or hurt yourself with any of the cigarettes and other vices.
I can destroy other parts of myself if you're interested in that.
Ever see a woman do the C-cucumber act?
I don't know nothing about that sort of thing.
I don't know what you're trying to suggest, Ms. Fusey, but I think that you should quit
that smoking habit.
I haven't started eating more green vegetables.
I really do.
I think that's sensible.
Grab that plunger and help me get my guts back in here and I'll show you some more tricks.
Oh, gosh.
You're making me have a funny feeling.
Down in my butt deck.
My butt deck's feeling awfully weird now.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but I'll sing that button.
Oh, my gosh.
You stop that now.
You stop that singing, Reverend Susan Fusey.
That's terrible.
What you're doing, man?
I don't know.
You bring on the smoke from my face.
Why is there a stuff running down my leg?
What is this stuff?
What is this?
I still got it.
I need to...
I feel the fuckery.
I smell the fuckery.
I need to pick it up just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
No more fuckery.
I don't know.
There it goes.
Come on.
Fuckery in this game.
Woo!
Skit.
That's what they call it.
That's what the kids call it now.
When you scrape it off with a spatula.
It's a little crusty.
That's a skit.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It's a scat.
Skit is really good.
That's the best part.
Yeah.
I think the skit's the crispy bits.
lol
Rice ball was sitting all
Have to pee for your own sake
So you're going toi
Rahl
Mull a
Slippery
All right.
Is there an angry Larry?
Were you able to pee?
Oh, yeah, everything came out just fine, just in case everybody was wondering.
Yep.
So now I'm in a band, I'm supposed to stand away from a pulpit?
I feel naked, man.
I feel like I'm in that dream where your pants are off and you're in elementary school.
And with no pulpit, they can see me below the waist.
You don't want to see a preacher below the waist when he gets excited.
You'll get jealous.
You're a bro.
You can do it.
Now, speaking of acoustics, there's something I really, really wanted to make sure that everyone else at this campground noticed.
You can get some pretty jazzy, syncopated music going.
In those, well, some people call them chem toilets.
Some call them turdices.
I prefer to call them sweat lodges.
And especially at night, this works.
For some reason, I don't think this happens in the day.
Oh, I know what the difference is.
During the day, I sit down.
At night, I stand up because it's too scary to sit down.
At night.
At night, when you dribble into the male side of that thing, the urinal, it's got kind of a funny little echo late at night.
You're in this big bouncy box, right?
And if you're, well, I guess attuned or brain damaged or high or something, you'll notice that there's this, your dribbling pee makes this kind of a syncopated drum beat as it hits that plastic.
But then it runs down a tube and then it dribbles down into the hell water further down.
And that's like another back beat to your syncopated pee beat.
And try it.
Run over there, all of you, right now, and just clatter around one inside.
You have to close the door or the sound doesn't work right.
And, of course, if this band or any other band is playing, you won't be able to notice.
But you'll have your own band.
You.
You're dribbling.
Dribbling.
Fitfully dribbling.
Oh, I forgot not everybody has benign prostate asplasia.
But you should go out and get benign prostate asplasia so that you can get that kind of hesitant intermittent pee dripping.
And it's the secondary side dribbling sound that makes it ever so special.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
Of course, everyone does.
Thank you.
Thank you, Charlie.
Roar!
We're gonna kill!
Destroy!
Kill them all!
Hi!
Roar!
Stick, I don't know, was that hardcore or was that death metal?
What the hell came out of your mouth?
Um, it was, uh...
Post-Card Game!
It was post-card hardcore pre-industrial?
It was just a...
Hard metal deathcore.
Hard metal deathcore?
Yes!
Hard metal deathcore step?
Stickcore.
Okay, stickcore.
Dickcore, that was...
Dickcore.
Was that dick-horror?
Yeah.
We're gonna core our dicks on stage for you!
Thanks for requesting Dickcore!
Your show will continue momentarily.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, we have a rule.
I have to clarify this.
Sex Mortars, the rule is no dick smears on instruments.
Oh, God, why are we talking about dick-core-ing?
I really do have to remember to bring the, uh...
Scrapple.
The scrapple, the scrapple, it smells like burnt hair.
Mmm.
Smells like burnt con...
The scrapple, the scrapple.
Burnt con-v.
It's burnt pig assholes and cornmeal.
Wow, so yeah, totally.
Con-v.
It's got a lot of salt.
Totally.
It's what?
Burnt con-v.
And it smells like burning burnt con-v.
I don't know his legend.
What's burnt con-v?
Burnt con-v.
He was in Semi-Tough.
He was the Est guy.
Experience this, you asshole.
That was burnt con-v.
He was the face of pseudo Werner Erhardt.
Smarmy.
Oh, someone to learn from.
Perpetual.
One to study.
Mmm, game show host.
One who can teach us.
Oily polyester.
Oh, yeah.
Fuck.
So we may learn the secrets of pinkness and...
Yeah, yeah.
Convoids.
Invert them.
Yes.
Hmm.
Well, that's a good one.
These are the anti-burnt con-v's here.
You cannot get more un-burnt con-v than these gentlemen.
Burnt con-v.
Yeah.
I'm trying to define...
He be dead.
I'm trying to quantify burnt con-v.
Burnt con-v.
He be dead.
Game show host.
I know nothing of your television game show.
Totally lamina...
Burnt convies.
This means nothing to...
Burnt convicts.
Those of my...
That would be a great name for a band right there.
Burnt convicts.
Well, I cut the list of possible band names that followed.
The band we've mostly been hearing is Six Fisted Tales of Connie, this year also known
as the Fuck Peas Band.
What is this Fuck Peas thing all about, you non-Facebookers ask?
Well, it's a Facebook thing partly.
Reverend Peas am liking attention, good or bad, and subgeniuses are so generous in supplying
both kinds.
And in that spirit, let's hear the rant song of Pope Synthotimus Ex Mortis, which starts
with him explaining how he's the worst ranter of the church.
Actually, if you listeners can make it all the way to the Fuck Peas end of this episode,
whoa, my hat's off to you.
Fantastic.
He's testing, he's testing, he's testing.
Yeah, well, everybody figured out what they're gonna be tuning their souls into for Bob.
I've discovered over the years that I am probably X Day's worst ranter, so I've chosen not to
rant anymore.
But I don't do too bad with one-to-one conversations, you know?
If I bump into you and we sit down and chat for a while, I think it goes pretty well.
I do my best to praise Bob with every...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I've got toQuez.
We just had a quote from X Day or I don't remember it.
A man who just has to train without resorting to a stupid sweet nonsense.
I've had the honor to do it for one of the last ten years.
And I entered intoLet It Go Yeon Gray.
Oh, my preach nowadays.
Yeah.
I'm here every Sunday and I trained this for a master who does the favor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But what I want to do is I'm gonna rap for Fr Yam.
Okay.
In the head of where she's from.
And that leaves uh, another song, the PW, this next chorus which is 20 years old.
I never had to go to bed tonight
I never had to sleep tonight
I know I'm not the half-slack
Yeah, but it makes me an ass
Cause for you the half-slack
Beats a hink-a-pink
And it's a different story
So to be the half-slack
I know that's not a nice story, you know
But if you want to
Maybe try to be slow
Maybe shut up as I go
But I'm an inventive guy
Trying to be strong
I just think I'm thinking wrong
I don't feel it here
Fuck, you've got to stand in here
For more fun
Thank you, bye
But I ain't got a thing
I know that these times
Is really slow
And you know I can't
Feel the thrill
But wait till the end
And you can feel the thrill
I've been feeling like floating
Cutting from the half of my
You can't see the full half of my
I've been feeling like floating
Cutting from the half of my
So to be the half-slack
Beats a hink-a-pink
And you can feel the thrill
But wait till the end
I'm a little bit scared of the dark
He's got it!
Yeah, I'm scared
It's really not that much
I don't know his favorite name
Connie!
I am not the only one, the only one
Who needs that kind of applause
I know where the ax really is
And it's an internal-gut-SCHEISA!
Can't think of a word I'm right with
His thoughts
I don't know where that lends itself
But not even mine yet
And that helps all of us
That's why Christ settles where he settles
He is not the only one that can afford it
That's right!
I'm gonna go ahead and get a couple of things for it.
Uh, here's a little bit of shit.
Now, you know what?
Oh, you guys need a couple of nuggets?
They can take the one and only.
There's black pills on the button.
I think I'll win it.
...
I won't mind beating your dicks.
I'm gonna get you right with my success.
I think I'll win it.
Or just we'll keep it too long?
Will they punish me for that crime?
...
I'd like to sing a song that goes back to one of Philo's greatest pieces,
Anal Fissure Tissue.
Oh, I don't know if I got...
You mean like butt-fucking the moonies?
We can do that one too.
Alright.
Anal Fissure Tissue, huh?
Anal Fissure Tissue, written by Philo Drummond.
And Sterno.
And Reverend Stang.
But I don't remember that one.
I'll just fake it.
Alright, so we're going to fake it.
I think it's in the key of Q.
I'll try to remember.
You ready?
One, two, three, go!
Butt-fucking the moonies while they fixed him as four sliders in Mitch County.
Long way.
By the way, only to become son.
Sterno.
Suffering from the famous fissure tissues.
Anal fissure tissues.
And the worst part.
Suffering and suffering.
All day long he's suffering.
He has loose anal fissure tissues.
Fissure tissues.
He has squat droppings.
And a bucket of anal fissure tissues.
Distilled with anal fissure tissues.
Anal fissure tissues.
Already half filled with the droppings and squat droppings.
Poor Sion Oates.
All he wanted was a piece of a meal.
Anal fissure tissues.
And instead, he has anal fissure top on his face.
Okay, your turn.
Anal fissure tissues.
Anal Fissure, Fissure Tattooed disabilities.
Anal.
Fissure.
Fissure, Fissure!
You can do without it!
Fissure!
You don't mean one!
Anal!
Fissure!
Things too bad!
Anal!
You must just eat soft food. Eat lots of food.
Thanks sir, he's 38% of the world.
Daniel Anto, just name him.
Please avoid giving it a half-ass.
Daniel Bryant, I promise you that they will love it.
You don't need them.
I think this is a good song too.
It's got a nice vibe.
It's a good song.
Oh God, we're eating a rock.
Because you eat too much white bread.
White bread.
That's the cause of it, too much white bread.
You need more fiber in your diet.
All right, I'll kiss your tissue.
You got to get rid of that stuff.
It's no fun.
Can I kiss you.
I'm telling you, more fiber.
It's no fun.
It's a bummer.
You won't like it.
You won't like it, I promise.
That was our great hit.
Anil Fisher tissue.
Written.
It's no fun at all.
Brothers and sisters, we will start music shortly as all the musicians gather up and get their things and parts.
We'll play when we feel like it.
Parts and order.
But we do still have open mic and I do see you out there.
And I'm sure people have things to say besides fuck peace.
Oh, by the way, while I'm on that.
There's a bit of something I need you guys to do for me because it needs to be recorded for posterity.
So.
When I I'm going to get you all to say on the count of three.
Can everyone in the campground who is with an earshot of me say fuck peas.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Fuck peas.
Thank you, guys.
That was freaking perfect.
Awesome.
Now, let's do it one more time just in case staying didn't get a good recording.
All right.
Are you guys ready?
You ready?
One.
Two.
Three.
Fuck peas.
Yeah, fuck peas.
So now we've got that out of the way.
He does.
There is also a request for side boob.
And thank you, Stick.
That's like full boob, though.
You know, that's a little more than side boob.
You and Eggplant showing your full boob.
Stang could come up here, though.
I'm sure he has something to say.
I admit it was some practical joke which is misfired.
And I'll call upon my charity to overlook this dismal escapade.
Please spare us that lofty air, Professor.
We brought you here for a purpose.
I've no doubt of it.
And I've already expressed my opinion of it.
Of it.
Fuck peas.
You gentlemen have played out your shabby farce.
I'd appreciate being driven home to breakfast.
Fuck peas.
Fuck breakfast.
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or see www.subgeniusradio.org.
Subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
From the Church of the Subgenius and the Bulldog of Time Control Labs.
SubgeniusFoundation.com
With more than 10 hours of eargasmic ecstasy.
Only $10 per album or $1 per track.
Pull the wool over your own eyes all over again with Sister Melodious Chops.
Dr. Ahmed Fishmon.
Spock.
Papa  samen.
SpockNar pem dairy.
Brother Kleeve Donut Dunkin.
portalanloa Cait investigate.
Jehovah hates Fred.
Artemya Selena.
Part akan jabalchi brokodan aksel halamu milir.
The El Queso All Stars.
charitydutchcil estplanetPC holparka
Noorul Prep.
Meri Kavek M replaced by fucking El mesa M
M M Niq Socorro
Dr. Onan sencillbyte.
One Mix adjuster
Imhan Elktaand
Ol Rumpak
money games slash order now all rights reserved all materials are copyrighted by their respective
owners any similarities between anyone living or dead is purely coincidental if redness continues
please consult a physician do not apply for prohibitive operators are standing by