Turn that thing on! Put on them headphones.
One hundred and eleven years ago, when I was thirty-three years old, right after the atomic wars,
my church was rubbed out by a band of wild pink boys.
Wait a minute.
It's showtime. Time for the subgenius hour and a half.
The show that dare not even exist.
Join us now as we rocket away out of normal time into showtime
with your favorite horrifying horror host, Mobius Rex.
And you'll hear the voices of puzzling evidence.
Gary Bobram lies in a cast of thousands more.
It's mysterious, evil, spooky, eerie, creepy, wacky, kooky, fun.
It's loads of chuckles and chock full of gags and novelty.
It's stuff that your boyfriends will want and that all your girlfriends will secretly admire.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius hour of swag!
Ooo.....
I'm going down to the river car.
There is a man I want to see.
Yea.. he's a ferryman.
He'll recognize me.
I'm going down now.
to the riverside
there's a place I want to be
gonna talk
to the ferryman
he'll be expecting me
I'm crossing over now
to the other side
guitar solo
life is better there
on the other side
the grass is greener there
and I, I'll get even there
on the other side
and everything will turn out alright
I'm crossing over now
to the other side
the other side
guitar solo
I walked by the church house
late last night
yeah I walked by the church house
but I didn't go inside
cause I, I once slept
with the preacher's wife
she handed me a dime
ticket
to the other side
I'm crossing over now
guitar solo
to the other side
music
guitar
guitar solo
blues
chords
guitar solo
Friends, it's real late at night here.
I've got to do this show, but I've got to do it real quiet.
We can't let that happen again.
This music in the background is a band called
Morphine. It's just drums
and a sax and a slide bass.
We're going to mostly just do a music show.
I've got this tape of Devo
cover tunes that you won't believe.
But first, I do have
a rant on tape here from
Reverend
Reverend Ipsissimus John Shirley.
So, hang on.
Stay tuned for the only words.
But we have to be real quiet.
Oh, yes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm here
to talk about sin
and the payment for sin.
And I know sin.
I know it intimately.
My name is the Reverend Johnny S.
E for every,
S for sin, and
S for sin.
S for certainly.
And sure, that's kind of funny.
You can laugh. I'm just a damn hick.
Now, there's no need to wince
with embarrassment.
You see, folks, Lord knows it's true.
I'm just an Arkansas po-bucker.
My daddy kept a ruckus.
He kept a dodge up on the cinder blocks
in the front yard.
Some nights we had to steal chickens to eat.
Our situation wasn't so bad, though.
We all got it bad
in our own special way.
The Lord tests us all
and makes us all suffer
with great particularity.
Each to his best
in deepest capacity
we will suffer.
The Lord tests us and tests us
and there ain't no cheating on that test.
Now, when I look out at y'all
and I say sin,
some of you, when I say sin,
are almost licking your lips.
Now, I ask you,
is that the appropriate response?
Well, sure, with some of y'all,
it's the way it was with me.
There's no relief without sin.
And there's no real party
as is bereft of relief.
And relief,
it comes from big-time fun.
Fun with weightlifter muscles on it.
Fun that concentrates first
in this part of the body
and then that part.
I guess I know about sin.
Well, now, let me tell you,
something, Lars.
Sweet Lord's eternal life.
Now, that is no fun.
And it's not supposed to be.
No fun, my baby, no fun.
Are you thinking that this
redneck Bible thumper
don't know turkey droppings about sin?
Is that what you think?
Well, let me tell you, my friend.
Let me tell you,
good Lord,
well, the good Lord,
he forgave me
for a great deal of sin.
I have been up to my neck
in sensuality.
I have sunk myself
in that particular
La Brea tar pit of life.
And it is only thanks
to our sweet, precious Lord
that I have escaped
that ravenous suction,
that tar pit suction
that seemed to fasten itself
in my lower parts
and suck and suck
until it drew the life out of me.
Yes, I know sin.
And I won't tell you
what my sins were.
Yes, I could talk about my time
as a counselor at a girls' summer camp.
Well, hell, 14, 15-year-old girls
soft as little kittens,
and there on the aching side
of that mountain
where the smell of the pines
seemed to call me out every night
to prowl the cabins like a cougar.
But no, it's best that sin remains hidden.
Neither will I befoul your ears
with the long nights
in bars and brothels.
Yes, of rutting with marijuana-dreaming whores
in puddles of vomit.
But that was my life
before I came to the Lord.
I cannot bring myself to mention it.
Got an urge, got a surge,
and it's out of control.
I got an urge, I want a purge,
cause I'm losing control.
I got enough control,
I'm gonna tell you all about it.
I'm gonna make you feel it shouting.
Got a problem,
I got a problem,
I got enough control over it.
Sky glass, sky sky,
so good at that, that last.
Tell you all about it,
I wanna scream and shout it.
.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ho, ho, ho
There's a pinfall somewhere you can't see
The tooth's in the top of a finger's tree
Ho, ho, ho
She's bent down in a row by a one-to-five-er
The tooth's gone down in a whistle-mower
Ho, ho, ho
She's just a girl, she's just a girl, the girl you want
You live upon every word you've done
Ho, ho, ho
You know you're headed for the pleasure of
The words can't stop on the tip of your tongue
Ho, ho, ho
She's a little thing but you knew it all along
She's just a girl, she's just a girl, the girl you want
You're meant for living for why doesn't it look right
To just the girl, she's just the girl, the girl you want
To just the girl
You're meant for living for why doesn't it look right
Just the girl you want
guitar solo
Can I bring myself to mention them numberless, faceless whores?
My name is Legion, cried the whore of Babylon.
Excuse me.
I never think of those whores now.
Them whores whose urgent hair and their ebony pubes
seem to shine out at me.
Eyes that wander the space between you like midges
flying in the air.
Yes, I know the devil's snow.
Yes, I know the devil's snow,
that crystal lily, that medicinal-tasting temptress.
Yes, Lord, I know the devil's snow.
I have flown through clouds of cocaine in a high turbulence.
And yes, I know sin.
Are you convinced?
Well, I cannot tell you about it.
I will not tell you about that night on the tar roof
of Blue Street Billy's.
That crazed, mightily pierced, teeny-bobsterous and I,
the both of us gone wild on Angel Dust,
the irony of that name, Angel Dust, can you imagine?
And mad with PCP driving my degraded but engorged manhood
again and again into that hysterically laughing
punk rock bitch whore.
1979 it was.
As the rain lashed us and the lightning on us,
we zipped the sky.
I will not tell you of it.
But you can take my word for it.
I know sin.
In the end, in the end.
The folks impressively
Table that should be.
See, .
Are not responsible .
Yeah, at thelamontadress.net
And Mr.
Maybe just another rap
But you're running out of sap
Yes, you're running out of sap
Well, you better take the rap
Dying under daddy's cap
It's at the top of the list
That you can't get pissed
No, you can't get pissed
It's rule number one
Living right isn't good
Living right isn't fun
Time tested and true
You gotta put it through
Through
He was a mongoloid, mongoloid
Happier than you and me
Mongoloid, mongoloid
When he turned and what he could see
Born from a son of a deke
Mongoloid, mongoloid
When he turned and what he could see
He wore a hat and he had a job
And he brought home the breakers
So no one knew, knew, knew
He was a mongoloid
Mongoloid, mongoloid
Friends were unaware
But he even cared
Mongoloid, mongoloid
What's a mongoloid?
Grow old with sovereignty
Mongoloid, mongoloid
When he turned and what he could see
He wore a hat and he had a job
And he brought home the breakers
So no one knew, knew, knew
He was a mongoloid, mongoloid
Happier than you and me
Mongoloid, mongoloid
When he turned and what he could see
What he could see, what he could see
What he could see, what you could be
What he would like to be
It could be, what he could be
What he would like to see
What he could be, what he could be
It could be, what he would like to see
It could be, what he can be
What he could be
But you can take my word for it
I know sin
And I know the devil personally
I know the devil personally
And you feminist ladies, you postmodern homo-homo feminist ladies,
you think there's a patriarchy here on Earth?
Well, you don't know phallocentrism till you get to hell,
because Satan is going to make you dance around a steaming phallus
in the green and gold flames of retribution, ladies.
Satan, ladies, is no sensitive Berkeley male.
But get up to heaven, and you find that Jesus and Mother Mary are receiving equal pay.
And do not, do not fool yourself into thinking there's no money in heaven.
Was there ever any place worth being for long without money?
You see, money and faith, well, sir, one's a unit of the other.
Money is a unit of faith.
And if you give the ministry of the Reverend Johnny S. one dollar,
then you have one dollar's worth of faith.
And when you give him five hundred dollars, that's five hundred dollars worth of faith,
redeemable at the gate of heaven.
And I don't mean heaven's gate. I mean the gate of heaven.
Now, as in Luke, verse 44,
And turning to the woman, hey, Jesus said unto Simon,
Seest thou this woman? I entered into thine house.
Thou gavest me no water for my feet,
but she hath wetted my feet with her tears,
and wiped them with her hair.
Thou gavest me no kiss, but she hath not seized to kiss my feet.
Well, folks, that's nothing less than the right attitude.
And if you think that's the right attitude,
then you're wrong.
A faith payment is a questionable investment, ladies and gentlemen.
You forget that I have the God-given power to say into your souls.
And right here I can see your heart before me like a devil's dinner on a plate.
And I can tell you, you sir, that the heart I see within your breast,
the soul quivering on that plate, it makes me sick.
They tell us that we lost our tents.
Giraffes and nips all jumped the fence.
Just to brought up ladies and gents.
Are we not?
Clowns?
We are bozo.
Are we not clowns?
We are zeo.
We have red hair that stands up straight.
We have a red nose that's so ornate.
Are we not clowns?
We are bozo.
We are zeo.
Are we not wangs?
We are dildos.
Drop-y and nagging.
Jolly all eyes to all whatsoever you bad stuff.
Check my Sac classy shit real quick.
which three-치를ers could enter blondy who are 볕 ca launched into space 1-7.
Hot cricket.
This is an ambitious lacrosse.
Leslie Su.
Crazyоп8 Cafe
¶¶
It's hot.
Oh, oh, whatcha going?
Oh, oh.
Green acres is the place to be.
For living is a lot for me.
Land for an hour so far and wide.
Gee, man, and just give me the good news.
Oh, Been to hell to win.
Billions per day.
This ain't oh no hot стол.
We have a map, a guru.
We have a dynamo.
Puff they sends.
All my life the man honey,
He made me mad,
Up to heaven ogni verse.
extremely interesting and extremely worthwhile artistic performances
Impro功度小 shines on stage
As labels clatte,oqueurs a colocdis paralysis
Screenplay Two actors
Too many
I'm gonna eat everything
One chromosome too many
And he wore a
And he had a
And he got cold
So that no one knew
Sorry
What are you guys doing?
What is this?
What kind of...
I did not do
happiness
Oh, here goes
What do those become?
a
in my mind
why am I there?
I'm proud to be an Ogie from Muscogee, a place where even squares can have a ball.
We still wave Old Glory down at the courthouse, and white lightning's still the biggest drill
of all.
And your boots are still in style for manly footwear.
Beads and Roman sandals just won't do.
Football's still the roughest thing on campus, and the kids still respect the college team.
I'm proud to be an Ogie from Muscogee, a place where even squares can have a ball.
We still wave Old Glory down at the courthouse, and white lightning's still the biggest drill
of all in Muscogee, Oklahoma, USA.
Darwin måltao!
Jadie wam mesures mucho stimulation associated with the
derecho al oluyor?
Chris.
Together, you and I.
For united we stand.
Divided we fall.
And if our backs should ever be against the wall,
we'll be together.
Together.
You and I.
Who am I united with on my phone?
Chris, this is Ken.
I'm calling in from the Slovenia X-Day drill.
Oh, already the good folks are checking in from all over the area.
You're calling from the X-Day drill,
the subgenius X-Day drill to my program.
It is July 4th, by the way,
and you're listening to Aerial View on WFMU.
My name is Chris T,
and on our lines is Ken checking in from the subgenius X-Day drill.
Ken, you want to give us some details?
Well, I was going to put the Ivan Stang on the floor.
I'm going to let you talk to him for a while about the details of this event.
We got the mugwag, mom's dumps, and a UFO right outside of our window here.
You've got a UFO outside the window, and you've got Reverend Ivan Stang standing by?
It's almost as out of breath as you are,
because we just made it up from our excrementation trip.
I don't even want to know what that was.
It had the word excrement in it, did it?
Yes, it's excrementation.
Is Reverend Ivan Stang there?
Can I speak with him?
Yeah, let me put him on the phone.
All right.
Praise WFMU.
Praise Chris T.
This is Reverend Stang.
Reverend Stang, you and I have never talked before,
yet you're a man that I've admired for years.
Well, you're a man that I've admired for years,
ever since you put down that Bob Dean shirt that you used to call every now and then.
Oh, so I hear that my friend Ken mailed you that tape, by the way, of that program.
And what is that guy's deal?
Oh, he's just a pink.
What can I say?
I just do not even talk about it.
Okay, let's talk about the X-Day drill.
Well, you know, we're not really celebrating the 4th of July.
We celebrate the 5th of July, because next year, July 5th, 1998, is the end of the world.
July 5th, 1998, is the end of the world, and you've heard it on this program.
Well, you hear it on the hour of slack every week, probably more than you'd ever care to.
Absolutely.
Unlike the Heaven's Gate.
Like people with their, you know, kind of half-assed approach to mass suicide.
What we're trying, we're going to do it right.
You don't believe in flesh vehicles?
Is that what you're saying?
We're not leaving anything to chance.
Those people, well, they had the date wrong and everything else,
and we have never felt like we had to, in order to catch a ride on the bus,
that we had to jump in front of the bus and let it hit us.
We're happy to wait on the corner with Jingle,
and we're not feeling our change in our pockets until the bus arrives to pick us up
and take us to Planet X or wherever it's taken us.
We actually don't know where we're going yet.
So you're not willing to...
But by God, the trip is half the fun.
You're not willing to trade in your flesh vehicle?
Is that what I hear you saying, Reverend Stang?
No, we're not going to leave our containers until we've got a better container to jump into.
I think that's probably a wise move.
Yeah.
I think that's a wise thing to do.
That's why...
Yeah.
You are so much wiser than Doe.
Doe!
Well, no, we never said that.
Remember, the church is a sub-genius.
We're not geniuses about that.
We're not trying to...
We're just better.
We're not smarter.
We're just better than everybody else.
Yes.
They love to hear us say that, too.
So let me get an insight into what's happening right now around you.
Can you describe the scene as it's unfolding?
What are you looking at?
Is anybody naked?
Drinking beer?
Actually, where I'm standing, I can't see the naked people because I'm up too close to the road.
But the naked area is a little bit further down the hill.
So you...
If this fake, gigantic UFO hanging from the trees wasn't in the way, I could probably see some skin.
Someone has hung a gigantic UFO from the trees where you are?
Yes.
It is a fake UFO, but it looks more real than most of the fake...
most of the real ones I've ever seen.
To tell the truth.
And, yeah, we're at Brushwood, which is a campground in far western New York State.
Far western New York State.
There are several bands here that are, I guess, Jehovah Hates Fred is going to be playing pretty soon.
And the Swinging Love Corpses are here, of course.
Doctors for Bob.
But...
And there's all the top preachers of the church.
Sister Susie the Floozy is getting...
She's getting ready for a hot oil mud wrestling.
That's part of our rehearsal for the end of the world.
Are you telling me...
Let me see if I have this right.
Sister Susie the Floozy is there?
Yes.
Wow.
Okay.
All the subgenius topless preacher babes are here, and they're oiling up.
I'm serious, by the way.
Nothing that I'm saying is in any way an exaggeration.
Stang, can I ask you something?
Has Hank Williams, Jr. ever showed up at any of your festivities?
Because I think he'd be right at home.
I can barely hear you.
I'm wondering if Bo Cephas has ever showed up there.
You know, Hank Williams, Jr.
Has he ever shown up at any of these festivities?
You know, if he had, we could have saved Hank.
We could have saved Hank Williams, Sr.
If we'd only had the chance to turn him on to Bob.
I just know. I know.
You know, you can tell by listening to that guy's music that he was a subgenius who lacked only Bob.
Slack.
He lacked slack in his life, is what he lacked.
Yeah.
So how...
He was chasing false slack.
Right.
And I gotta admit, you know, if you don't have real slack, false slack is certainly better than nothing at all.
I guess false slack will have to do.
But let me ask you this.
What is...
How should we go about achieving slack on this July 4th, 1997?
I mean, the rest of us.
Because I hate to think that when the normals are...
When the normals are taken away...
I hate to think that I'm gonna be among them.
Well, the normals aren't gonna be taken away.
The normals are gonna be slaughtered like pigs a year from now.
Not by us.
The aliens will handle that.
We're not nearly as blood...
Well, actually, we are as bloodthirsty as any other religious nuts.
I'll grant you that.
And I'm sure that some of the subgeniuses are count...
Have a list of enemies that they're gonna slaughter as soon as they're on the escape vessel.
But...
Ha ha ha.
You know, personally, I like to look at the joy and slack aspect of all this rather than the fact that I can, if I want to, have my fifth-grade teacher, Mrs. Darden, tortured for years...
Years and years and years.
...reporting me to eat that pimento cheese sandwich that one time in 1965.
She thinks I've forgotten if she's even alive.
But you are a man with a mission.
If...
She...
If that fifth-grade teacher of mine is not alive on X-Day...
...we will bring her back to life so that I can torture her.
Wow.
I was just saying that I didn't care, but I wasn't interested in the torture stuff.
Hey, wait a minute.
So X...
Just let me get this straight for a minute.
X-Day is gonna be July 5th or July 4th of next year?
July 5th.
Okay.
July 5th is our Independence Day.
Right.
The normals and, you know, the regular...
You know, the Americans celebrate July 4th.
I guess that's when they celebrate the Kennedy assassination and Wounded Knee and, you know,
the...
The invasion of Panama and the Gulf War and all those other...
Vietnam War and all those other glorious moments in our history.
But we...
No.
We...
I...
To tell the truth, I kind of forgot that today was a holiday for everybody else.
We're concentrating on the fifth.
It is.
Today is a holiday.
And I'm actually enjoying my day so far, Stang.
I'm glad you called.
Well, we know that you got there late to the station, so you must be getting either some
kind of slack or anti-slack.
I've got to go.
I've got slack today.
Well, you better get to it.
I'm sure the people need to hear some music and hear from other Fourth of July...
What you're really saying, Stang, is you want to get a beer.
Am I hearing you right?
Lips that have touched the bottle will never touch mine.
I don't...
I consider alcohol to be false slack.
Oh, okay.
I'm strictly a frop man myself.
A frop man?
But I'll tell you what.
If you've got any frop you want to shoot my way, boy, I'll be sure to take a little
slug off of that.
I'll pack it up my exit wound.
I'll eat it.
I'll smoke it.
I'll do anything.
Anything you want.
Frap.
You want some frap?
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll take my fair share of frappy.
Frappy?
I'm not putting down anybody who's getting drunk off their gourds this weekend.
Believe me, I would if I could.
Well, you know, I'm asking people today to check in from the various Fourth of July celebrations
all around this great area, the listening area at WFMU.
I want people to check in and let me know how their celebrations are going.
Well, ours...
We're taking our clothes off even though it's freezing cold up here in the...
In the hills and it's drizzly, horrible weather.
We don't care.
You're taking your clothes off?
All our equipment's broken.
That just means we have to yell louder.
Is there any sex happening yet?
Now, what kind of a question is that?
If I answered you that, everybody in the whole state would head this way.
Well...
If I told you what was really going on, this would suddenly turn into Woodstock all over
again.
Now...
I'm afraid that the Brushwood can't handle it.
The Brushwood?
The Brushwood.
That's the campground where...
Oh, okay.
You don't want people trampling the campgrounds up there.
Right.
So what you're saying is to stay away from the X-Day trial.
Well, unless you've spent your $30 church membership fees, I would definitely stay away.
Now, is that fee payable in cash upon entry directly to you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, see, that makes it easier.
I believe in cutting back on bureaucracy wherever possible.
Oh, actually, if anybody wants to know about...
Well, I think there's a...
I mean, the...
There's a...
Brushwood has a website.
I think it's www.brushwood.com.
Okay.
www.brushwood.com.
Brushwood is one word.
Uh-huh.
So you can check out the other things happening out here.
And, or you can always check www.subgenius.com for the nude photos from last year.
And, by the way, in about three weeks, we'll have an hour of flak on WFMU that should...
It's a joke.
Whoa!
Theme song!
Oh girl!
Gershwin is there one.
He said, ah.
Daily.
You just said, you're, got the D momentum.
I'm like a V超 R disappears just, and then, I picked it out.
I'm excited that said launch was Sachen,ble很 крут, that-
Larry Ding.
Two of you are waiting on the sweatshirt.
I think that's...
No, no, sorry.
To you, Larry is here to...
I'm sorry.
I'm actually, it looks like that it has to leave.
We'll do that shortly.
S, sir.
it under the rain.
Ah ha!
Okay.
That's what everybody else is doing right now.
That's, that's a, I appreciate the suggestion, Reverend Stang.
You've been, you've been very kind and generous to spend this time with us on the phone here.
I appreciate you calling from the X Day Drill and letting us know what's going on up there.
Um, alright, well thanks, Chris.
Did you need to say anything?
Okay, that's it.
Listen, Reverend Stang, just, I want you to remember one thing.
To be careful out there.
Uh, I'll remember that the next time I'm flipping the breaker switches while standing in the
puddle to get the electric guitars going.
Yeah, you don't want to go, man, like that.
That, you know, the guy from the...
Hey, I'm not afraid.
The guy from the Yardbirds went like that.
Just, he just fried right up.
Got all fried up.
So, Reverend Stang, don't you fry this Fourth of July.
Okay?
Don't you fry.
Praise Bob, praise Chris.
And, uh, thanks, Stang.
Praise FMU.
Ha!
Kill Bob.
Oh, God.
The number here is 201-678-7743.
You're listening to Aerial View on WFMU.
Fourth of July spectacular.
Spectacular.
talking about Ocean Everything I Have to say.
Sweet talk.
Bop.
Evil.
Are we not men?
E-E-E-O-O.
God created man.
But he needed the monkey to do it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my funky man.
In business suits.
Teachers and critics.
All dance the flute.
Are we not men?
We are demons.
E-E-E-O-O.
Are we not men?
We are demons.
Yes, are we not men?
E-E-E-O-O.
Oh, oh.
Thank you.
Only not men.
D-E-V-O.
Yes, friends, and as always,
remember,
Dob's Spelled Backwords
is still
sbbobobbed.
Yes, and it's been an interesting, different kind of an hour of slack tonight day, hasn't it, Bean?
I'm going to tell you who all those bands were doing those Devo covers.
You know, we didn't do that much Bob talking tonight, but Devo is probably about as close to being the ultimate subgenius band as any band ever was.
Then we heard from the beginning there, with Reverend John Shirley ranting about sin in between,
uncontrollable.
Uncontrollable urge was done by The View.
That unique version of Girl You Want was Devo from a live bootleg, November 1982, doing Girl You Want Aeneo Morricone style.
Mongoloid, the other version of Mongoloid there was by Jupiter.
Oh, and I almost forgot, Shrivel Up by Knife Lust.
Jaco Bozo is by The Fireman.
The second version of Mongoloid that I played is by The Deadliners.
And Oki from Muskogee was performed by the Bakersfield Bougie Boys.
We heard a long clip of Yours Truly on Chris T's show, Aerial View, on WFMU during the X Day Drill, followed by Jaco Homo by Lonnie and the Boys.
And the Devotions.
Blockhead as rendered by the Doguloids, or the Doguloids.
And the final Jaco Homo by the Touch Tone Tuners.
And all of those came from a thing called the Devo Cover Collection, which I got from the Devo fan...
What you might call the Ultimate Devo Archives.
And the guy who started the Devo Archives first heard...
the band Devo on the Hour of Slack about ten years ago.
And the gal who runs the Firesign Theatre fan outreach first heard of the Firesign Theatre on the Hour of Slack.
Or actually, through the church. I sent her a tape, let me put it that way.
Praise Bob, friends.
And let us now give finally...
I've got some kind of background.
I've got some kind of background music here.
I can't... I'm shaking, man.
I can't do the P.O. Box without the background music.
Okay.
And friends, you can write for free information from B-B-B-Bob...
at...
Post Office Box 140306.
That's P.O. Box 140306.
In the lovely Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Once again, that's Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
This is huge voodoo in the background.
Although, I think I'm gonna switch over to Hate for a Pink Planet.
Why not?
And friends, you can always email for information.
We'll email it back to you.
Just email to Slack at Metro...
No, man.
I keep thinking of my old one.
It's Slack at subgenius.com.
Slack at subgenius.com.
If you want to email me, I'm i.stang at subgenius.com.
www.subgenius.com.
It's a worldwide...
I told you.
Did I not?
And the system's gonna fail.
Subgenius.
You must always be given a chance to step...
...to liberate themselves from the...
Normals.
...before the...
...are executed.
When you see you and I getting together,
it is because we have begun to realize that we have a common enemy.
And the only time we'll be able to come together with a common objective
and a common goal is when we first develop a common motive.
And that motive is best developed by recognizing the common enemy.
And that common enemy is the...
...the one.
I say that common enemy is the...
When you see you and I getting together, it is because we have begun to realize that
we have a common enemy.
And the only time we'll be able to come together with a common objective and a common goal
is when we first develop a common motive.
And that motive is best developed by recognizing the common enemy.
And that common enemy is the...
...the one.
I say that common enemy is the...
This crowd is wild!
If you join, I'll let you sank my bottoms.
We're waiting for this humble place against the forces of...
...insert.
We don't want to be...