Holy cats. Hey. It's almost...
Yeah. Almost a perfect...
It is. It's wrong.
We finally got one.
We found a...
So genius. Power of...
Swatch.
Oh excellent. I know doctor, we think so too. We're gonna try to melt it out with thermite bombs.
Where do you want these bombs sir?
Over there.
Hey doc, can you see anything out there?
A bunch. We don't have more than an hour.
There was a guy on alt slack today going,
I've transcended duality and you haven't.
And he was serious.
I transcended duality and you haven't.
I don't think he saw the inherent paradox in that statement or the inadvertence.
But if they can't not see the humour of it then let them mount up upon themselves.
As the old Irish thing goes.
Anyway, I've been reading through the autobiography of Mark Twain.
This edition I found at a garage sale for 25 cents.
And it was printed in 1924.
And until I got hold of it, it was in really bad shape.
But I wanted to read this bit that I found in here because it's perfect for reading.
Written in 1898, Vienna.
By Mark Twain.
Beauties of the German Language.
Lectured for the benefit of a charity last night in the Borsendorfer Saal.
Just as I was going on the platform, a messenger delivered to me an envelope with my name on it,
and this was written under it.
Please read one of these tonight.
Enclosed were a couple of newspaper clippings.
Two versions of an anecdote.
One German, the other English.
I was minded to try the German one on those people just to see what would happen,
but my courage weakened when I noticed the formidable look of the closing word,
and I gave it up.
A pity, too, for it ought to be read well on the platform and get an encore,
that or a brickbat.
There is never any telling what a new audience will do.
Their tastes are capricious.
The point of this anecdote is a justifiable,
a double jibe at the German long word,
and is not as much of an exaggeration as one might think.
The German long word is not a legitimate construction,
but an ignoble artificiality,
a sham.
It has no recognition by the dictionary,
and is not found there.
It is made by jumbling a lot of words into one,
in a quite unnecessary way.
It is a lazy device of the vulgar,
and a crime against the language.
Nothing can be gained,
no valuable amount of space saved,
by jumbling the following words together on a visiting card,
quote,
Mrs. Smith, widow of the late commander-in-chief of the police department.
Yet a German widow can persuade herself to do it without much trouble.
Mrs. late commander-in-chief of the police department's widow Smith.
This is the English version of the anecdote.
A Dresden paper,
the Weedeman,
which thinks that there are kangaroos,
or butylrattes,
in South Africa,
says the Hottentots,
or Hottentotten,
put them in cages,
or kotter,
provided with covers,
lattengitter,
to protect them from the rain.
The cages are therefore called
lattengitterwetterkotter,
and the imprisoned kangaroo,
lattengitterwetterkotterbutylratte.
One day, an assassin,
or Hottentotter,
was arrested who had killed a Hottentot woman,
or Hottentottenmutter,
the mother of two stupid and stuttering children
in Strattertrotterl.
This woman, in the German language, is entitled
Hottentottenstrattertrottermutter,
and her assassin takes the name,
Hottentottenstrattermutterottentotter.
The murderer was confined in a kangaroo's cage,
butylrattenlattengitterwetterkotter.
Whence, a few days later, he escaped.
But fortunately, he was recaptured by a Hottentot,
who presented himself at the mayor's office
with a beaming face.
I have captured the butylratte, he said.
Which one, said the mayor,
we have several.
The Hottentotterlattengitterwetterkotterbeutelratte.
Which Hottentotter are you talking about?
About the Hottentottenstrattertrottermutterottentotter.
Then why didn't you say it once?
The Hottentottenstrattermutterottentotterlattengitterwetterkotterbeutelratte.
By Mark Twain.
And friends,
that's all I'm going to say,
because I have to crank out shows in a hurry.
We're in the middle of a big project.
And luckily, Dr. Philodrummon called me up
and said that the other night on the Puzzling Evidence show
at KPFA in Berkeley,
the actually oldest subgenius show,
it started in 1982,
and yet it's still on.
He said they did a really good one the other night
with Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence
and himself.
And a caller, Governor Rocknar.
And I listened to the MP3,
which is easy to download
by way of quiveringbrain.com,
if you look closely.
And he was right.
It's a really good one,
and it saves me having to edit
because it was just generally a good show.
So friends,
I'm just going to give it all to the Californicators there
in Berkeley and San Francisco.
And I'm going to give it to you.
Snoop Dogg,
Tony SW,
Foogie the Scooby and so forth,
where they all live.
Friends,
Christ-Bob.
And as Howell wandered away,
he carefully assessed the situation
asking himself,
First,
I've got to get loose
and then,
I'll kill Bob.
There he is.
Always playing this show.
Wandering away with the Amos.
They call him the wanderer.
Maybe we can help him.
And yet everyone knows World Overlord.
Please help me!
He's stuck in that Xerox machine.
He's Xeroxing all the pages of that new book, The Truth Behind Skull Farming.
It's my only chance to keep this Xerox machine running.
Here, have this sack full of museum quality food.
As soon as I finish making these copies, I'll tear into it.
Okay, we're all ready for the boat ride back to the center of the museum.
It strikes me as odd that the Xerox machine looks like a submarine.
It does. It's a submarine turned upside down.
We're gonna sit on the top or the bottom of it.
Apparently the studio they broadcast from sits in a pool of mercury.
So there's no way to reach them.
I was just watching Sano Buoys.
The tomb in China that is surrounded by the many terracotta warriors.
And they haven't touched it because they really want to get to the best point of entry.
Like 50 years from now and they think they can do it without breaking something.
Man, that looks great.
It's a whole cosmology that the king had built around himself.
Of his own.
His world in miniature to take with him.
And then he drank some mercury because he figured that was everlasting life.
And who knows, maybe he's right.
And then he lay down and became a tomb.
There goes.
They laid him in the tomb.
Hey, this is my tomb.
Get out of here.
I'm already resting in here.
Well, you were using up all the doom here in the tomb.
Well, I didn't roll away the stone for no reason.
Man, I was in here with the stone rolled back waiting to be discovered by the priests.
They were going to come in and find me still alive.
Papa Jesus and Mama Jesus.
I was supposed to be in here.
I was still supposed to be alive though.
Sorry sir, central services has a form here you can fill out.
Did you bring the lunch you were supposed to bring?
I ordered a special kosher lunch.
It's turned to stone.
Oh no.
All right.
That's it.
Bob.
He's calling the teacher.
There he goes.
Always running and crying to Bob when anything goes wrong.
Bob.
No.
Bob, son of battle.
But you can't have Bob fight all your battles.
He'll be here in a minute.
Then you'll be sorry.
You'll say, forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
No, in your version he's fine.
He's going to be here in a minute.
In my version, I just shot him again.
You'll say, forgive me, Bob, for I have sinned.
Well, I better say.
Bob, he's no slob.
Bob, he's no fool.
Hey, what happened to the right channel?
There it is.
He's the head of that subgenius church.
Hey, it came back.
He's so powerful.
If you think I'm going too fast, honey, just get out of the car.
In the first week of March 1095, Pope Urban II presided over a church council at Piacenza
in northern Italy.
There was present an embassy sent by the Byzantine emperor Alexius to ask for help against the
Turks.
The Turks, whose advance across Asia Minor had brought them within striking distance
of Constantinople.
By the early eighth century, the Christians had lost North Africa.
Palestine and Syria and most of Spain to the Muslims.
But then the frontier between Christendom and Islam had stabilized until the Byzantine
empires, ruling from Constantinople, what remained of the Eastern Roman Empire, went
on to the offensive in the second half of the 19th century.
The comparatively subdued reaction of the Muslims to the first crusade can be partly
explained by the fact that their confidence had already been shaken 130 years before.
The ancient cities of Tarsus and Antioch had been retaken and the Byzantine frontier had
advanced into northern Syria.
A violent shock had been felt throughout the Islamic world.
Are you going to show the truth?
The
Abbasid Caliphs in Baghdad had atrophied and they themselves had fallen into the hands of
the Shiite princes, whom they regarded as heretics.
In 969, Egypt had been occupied almost without opposition by another Shiite dynasty, the
Fatimids, and a rival caliphate had been established.
Thereafter, the Fatimids struggled to wrest Palestine and Syria from the Abbasids until
in the 1060s and 1070s they had to give way to the Turks, who, taking advantage of 17 years
of internal disorder in Egypt, drove them out of most of their Syrian possessions and left
them with only a shaky hold on remote parts of Palestine.
It was these Turks who at the same time revived Muslim fortunes on the Christian frontier.
Far to the east among the nomadic Turkomans, the Abbasids were the most powerful and the
moなたmtursk producers of had
little on what they were being arms for.
.
chief called Selchuk brought into the settled Islamic area.
Which is translated into Bob.
Yeah, that one's better.
This one?
Yeah, much better.
Much better.
This one is still good.
Yeah, well, it's kind of neat.
It's just a different, it's a special effect thing.
It's a special effect.
Oh, it hurts, though.
Don't do that.
Praise Bob.
Kill me for Bob.
Water for the love of Allah.
For in that grin, the secret lies.
Within the grin lies secret lies.
For when Bob shines and nothing green, where are you and where am me?
What do you mean?
So we're playing just the soundtrack.
I mean, just part of the soundtrack.
Yeah, the vocal quotes and then the screams.
No gunshots.
No nothing.
Okay, I'm going to get to work here.
Yeah, I got to get to work.
So you go into the racetrack.
I thought you go to the dog track.
Giddy up, giddy up, giddy up.
When Rocknard goes to work, he has to go to the racetrack.
He actually said one of the holiest movies there is.
Fight Club.
Yeah, it is like Fight Club for me because I haven't slept any day.
Never talk about Fight Club.
No.
And he has no idea of the history of the person in this car.
I have with that movie.
Ah, history.
Hey, Rocknard.
Do you want to ever give a guess as to why in that movie?
In that movie, the guy shoots Bob.
Yeah, when everything is a copy of a copy of a copy,
then you just get so to where you're just wired on anti-sleep,
and then you just, you know, you start to see everything.
No, seriously.
Okay, good.
I'm really kind of looking.
Hey, Philo, can you, you got everything there in a box?
Yeah, it's in a box.
We have it distilled into a singularity.
A lead-lined box.
There's a personal subgenius reason why Bob is shining.
There is enough fissile material.
We're going to tell that story sometime.
And then Bob just laughed and laughed.
Ha, ha.
8484425 if you want to hear.
Hey, leave some beer for me, Hal.
It's radio.
We're just radio beer, man.
You don't really taste it.
He's lost in that.
Hal is just crying and crying, and then Bob looked down and said,
Oh, the world's going to blow up.
It's okay.
You're doing fine, son.
Each bomb capable of destroying a city and generating a vast cloud of nuclear poison.
Here, take this tissue and wipe your tears away.
And don't worry about those shackles.
Bob has already set them free.
We'll stick some, you can take the tissue after you've wiped the tears away.
And stick them between the shackle and your ankle.
And take some of the tissue.
There they go.
Shit the shoulder and shoulder.
How precious is there's no chance of that.
It's necessary to be geared.
But I think that could be distributed to us.
By testing.
The number of
Listen to archeologos and it's Lisa the
Living.
liberation meaningless. The brink of annihilation will then have been reached. Or worse.
Today's impending nuclear arms race echoes the frenzied militarization of a century ago,
when the European powers still had time to avert the senseless catastrophe that would
soon befall their people, a catastrophe whose unforeseen consequences include, among others,
the Bolshevik Revolution, Hitler, World War II, nuclear weaponry, the Holocaust, the Cold
War, and the unstable entity known as Iraq. Urgent disarmament proposals, dismissed then
as naive, impractical, blind, and so on, must be seen in light of the madness that followed
to have been the greatest wisdom. It was the sleepwalking war makers who proved to be naive,
impractical, and blind as they led their countrymen into the abyss from which emerged
the disasters of the 20th century and beyond. The difference between then and now is that
there may be no one left to render a similar retrospective judgment. Should the nuclear
attack prevail, the disaster will be in vain.
The end.
Showing up but taking it down, the
g
i
feed
best
there is a reading he will participate at least in um yeah yeah he made indeed do a reading and
we'll have michael pepe otherwise known as oh yes what a maelstrom of talent it will be you'll walk
out dizzy from richness the old place won't be the same afterwards you know walk out rich from
dizziness the city lights bookstore was known as the abode because as each person meets us and
shakes now there's a money's giveaway to the sub nuts that we will pick up on okay back in over
here all these copies of the bank account just for meeting us we're going to sell sell sell the
swag tables will groan with loot and you can buy the double uh juju magic magic dust you can in the
bags the mojo bag around the corner at that place that's going out of business mojo bag world
magic stores going out of business no it's mojo bag world it's the uh the only product they sell is
mojo bags the railroad train coffee and the rock and let's have another piece they were right next
to railroad train universe i still have flash paper it's probably 20 years old i was looking
at that thinking i wonder if i should try it you should try it yeah it still works it was it was
sealed and it's just oh hello oh it's all insecurity about my flash paper okay the muppet uh the
uh muppet in your head is like a gorilla who crapped a watermelon in my brain
dr nicotone provided this special gum and this patch although he's not a patch on his old man
north of the principality of antioch the cilician armenian ruler leo had accepted a crown from the
western emperor in 1198 a.d together with a form of submission to rome which was a very important
act in his life and is still the most important in today's history but what's more interesting
is that the romeo brothers were made by the romeo brother and the romeo brother was never very real
and has been already described many times by historians in the long passages hey if you're
finished with those pinks you can pass them over here i need to work out a little bit
oh look he's he's working out he's he's really he's really working out
that's it you can still squeeze a little use out of it and exaggerate it there if you put them under pressure well appropriate what can i say chemicals can be in the heat
enthusiasm. Give him a big hand.
Extracted.
More nitrous oxide, doctor.
That's weird.
Watch how that hair says.
It says on the inside here,
13 tracks.
But I get 14.
Isn't this the copying machine thing?
Yeah.
It's just pretty music.
It is.
You can tell that the drugs
destroyed that machine.
Really? I can't tell.
No, I don't own
a new pair of shiny black shoes,
so stop asking.
I'm going to
the toolbar
with me.
And so, once again,
good triumphs over evil,
and what?
That's one of the first records I bought
as a 12-year-old.
Yeah, and so now you have it in CB form.
And then I found it in CB.
Charlton Heston, Richard Harris,
Jim Hutton, James Coburn,
Michael Anderson Jr.,
and presenting
Santa Burger,
featuring Mitch Miller
and the gang,
singing the Major Dundee theme.
Well, who wrote the rest of the music?
Is it all Mitch Miller
and his bunch of...
No, I was never...
Conducted by Danielle Amphitheatral.
Let me hear a melody
I'd like to
sing along
Oh, I hated those shows.
Yeah, me too.
It was creepy to watch all these happy people.
I did watch Lawrence Wells
because I was forest-disordered by my mom
when I was very young.
It was kind of fun because it was so
absolutely strange
to watch this enforced happiness
on everybody's face.
And Mitch Miller was just...
Oh, it was impossible to make.
I could tell I'm garbage.
Well, Sam Peckinpah said that
the movie should be called
Gidget Goes to Mexico
because he was disgusted with the way
the studio took it over and recut it.
But it still has good parts.
What's that one?
Major Dundee.
Gidget Goes to Mexico?
That was what Peckinpah suggested
that the movie be named.
And he wanted his name to be...
It's not taken off,
but they wouldn't take it off.
Hey, what?
It's got some really cool parts, actually.
You can see it would have been
an okay movie.
They just chopped it
in their way.
Well, look at these
violent kung fu scenes.
I don't know if the kids ought to see
this kind of thing.
It's got lambies.
I know, but they bring in all these sheep
and...
Have you no dreams, you mindless sheep?
You milling peck.
I'd volunteer myself,
except these nosebleeds keep me on my back.
Once as old Lord Gorbles motored
round his moors near John O'Groats,
he collided with a goatherd
and his herd of sixty goats.
John O'Groats.
When at last his car plowed through,
they were all defunct but two.
Loudly he addressed the goatherd,
Dosh Mike.
Whiskers and my corns.
Haven't you the sense, you dotard,
to tell your goats to sound your horns?
Look, my AA badge is bent.
I've half a mind to raise your rent.
Did you notice that those people
were getting upset?
He was reading from About the Goats
while he was abusing the goats.
About a goat, I'll tell you a song.
It's amazing.
He can hold the book with one hand
while holding two goats
with the other hand.
Oh, that's what that is.
About a goat, I'll sing you a song.
He's yanking those goats around
as if they had
done something evil.
With a dangety ding
and a dingety dong.
This is the
Evil Demon
Session 4.
A sweet little goat for me.
Almost everything
in a man's life,
there is a fateful point
where everything falls into place.
P.U. Somebody open a window.
And so the last bobby fell,
chopped to pieces by radio chainsaws.
And they were buried
on the field of bobbies.
And nobody came.
And they let go
the grey balloons.
Blam, blably, blably,
blum, blom.
Come on, Philo, we're doing this for the audience.
Oh, I had the book upside down.
1149 A.D.
So did Nur-Ad-Din's brother,
the ruler of Mosul.
Oh, the audience?
Nur-Ad-Din was thwarted at Mosul,
where another brother was set up as governor.
He did not gain the city until 1170.
Speaking of audience, you may want to go out to
youtube.com
and search for Bob's Lunch Hour.
And the edit changes
every hour.
It's amazing. I don't know how those guys
do it, how they can make it
Philo look so young.
Yeah, one...
Yeah.
Did you see that? His hair's long,
he's got a mustache, he looks like a porn star
according to his new wife.
Back in the days when there were porn stars.
Yeah, Philo was just a wannabe porn star.
Not actually
an actualized
true porn star.
It's just a
cunning linguistic
twist of...
of strange
wordage.
...seed to Harim
and in August 1164
inflicting a major defeat
on the Christians at Atal.
The show? Right, it's a word
bucket. It's a big word bucket.
Isn't that St. Stupid's Day
very close now? Yeah, St. Stupid's Day
happens on April 1st this year.
Like it does every year.
But this year
on April 1st will also
include the book signing.
...to Carmel.
...to commemorate the re-release
of Revelation X,
the Bob-apocryphon,
as well as the new book,
the Bob-li-ogryphon of Dobbs.
The Cyclopedia of Slack.
And so, yes, there will be
several of the book contributors
and or co-founders
there at
Alien Apocalypse 2006
and
The Meaning of Lost and Mismatched
Songs.
And Gynosaur Alphabet.
But where will it be?
At City Lights Bookstore.
Just getting to that point.
On Columbus Street in San Francisco.
And that will be the evening of April 1st
after the St. Stupid's Day parade.
Oh yes, all that St. Stupid stuff
will be long done and the
Subdini event begins
promptly at
7 o'clock.
And I'm just, I've got to tell you,
those of you that can't believe this,
I'm just sorry.
I just, I'm sorry you can't believe
what we're saying.
This email we're getting about
you think we're lying all the time.
That something's wrong
with Hal.
That's just a lie.
It's just a bad,
it's a good lie, but it's a bad thing
to lie.
To lie still
in that box.
That bad
people.
They go to the Caribbean
and enjoy tax shelters.
Here in Margaritaville,
you feel the sand between our toes.
Hey Bob, how are you doing?
Really ought to clean our shoes out.
Goodbye.
Well, and that's the way it is.
Isn't that...
Yes, that dashing
Isn't that him over there?
Commander James...
James Bond.
His face looks different.
It looks like he's had surgery or something.
It's the foster grants.
Hmm.
Does this mean we still have to obey him?
No, that's Andre the Giant.
Look, that man's t-shirt says,
repent, quit your job,
and slack off.
Another proto-subgenius.
Well, you see, M thought that Bond should be sent to the island to read the book.
And research the growing menace of this cult.
And see if, in fact, it was working with Smirch.
And perhaps even Spectre.
And once you smosh Smirch,
you're going down to Smarsh Spectre.
Now, while he's dancing with the beautiful woman,
and there's the shooter guy behind the tuba.
Yeah. Now take this, uh, serum.
You'll also notice that James Bond is getting closer and closer to a marijuana cigarette.
Take this serum, it'll make you more slippery.
Hey, let's do it up, dude.
They're trying to get James Bond stoned.
Oh, and he's fighting the temptation.
His new skull or his old skull?
The head that was...
Or do we care? No.
Nice work, Luffle.
So he draws his pistol and shoots the stone at him.
And everything goes back to normal.
And there, in a typical Dobbs cameo role,
you see him walk across the back.
Everything goes back to normal.
And we continue our dance, all four of us here,
huddled in a little wet mask.
Uh, I think he's really
far out.
Uh oh, sorry man.
It's the president.
The band wasn't that bad.
You didn't have to blow him up like that.
How can I help you, Mr. President?
Yes?
Mr. Bond, we have a situation.
Yes, how can I help you?
Some nuclear devices have been captured.
My answer to the phone is still ringing.
And I have a cable,
which I received this afternoon,
that agents of SMERSH
working with Spectre
are holding the United Nations
for ransom.
Hostage.
You have 48 hours
to rectify the situation.
Now if you will excuse me,
I have an urgent call.
And now we go to Washington, D.C.
and switch presidents.
You're joining me because
the message this thing is not
my message, but ours.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Everything's being recorded.
The White House tapes it.
From the early days of our administration,
Nancy has been using marijuana
on a daily basis.
And her personal observations
and efforts have given her
such dramatic insights
that I wanted her to share them with you
this evening.
This priest is claiming he has the power
to pull Christ from heaven.
May the power of Christ
confirm this. He's pulling Christ down.
He's trying to force Christ to repeat
the crucifixion every hour.
You can't pour Christ down the drain
down with Johnny.
It's a shame.
It's contrary to Hebrews 10, 12.
Don't be a-talking when Nancy Reagan
is speaking.
Oh, sorry.
...as a precious gift to his children.
So to my young friends out there,
life can be great.
And when it comes to drugs and alcohol,
What?
there's a big, wonderful world
there is?
I thought we were supposed to say no.
...a positive influence on all that
we're trying to do.
The job ahead of us is very clear.
Nancy's personal crusade
to expand the use of
smokeable cocaine, otherwise known
as crack, should become
our national crusade.
Our young people are helping us
lead the way.
Not long ago in Oakland, California,
I was asked by a group of children
what to do if they were offered drugs.
Say yes, I answered.
Soon after that, those children
in Oakland formed a just
say yes club. And now,
there are over 10,000 such clubs
all over the country.
Drugs are the mightiest
force for good that we know.
You said it, Ronnie.
They're simply wonderful to the young people.
Simply wonderful, yes.
Many of you may be thinking,
well, drugs don't concern me.
But it does concern you.
It does. It concerns us all.
Because of the way it could fulfill the promise
and hope in those restless minds.
Drug and alcohol abuse
needs our encouragement.
In this crusade, let us
not forget who we are.
Drug abuse is a freedom that is
ours. You
are Americans.
You're the product of the freest society
mankind has ever known.
No one ever has the right
to separate the drugs from the customer.
Say yes to drugs
to the point of making others
And drug abuse is not a crime.
Drugs help us create love
and hope, trust
and confidence.
And cocaine makes me happy.
Think for a moment how special it is to be
an American.
To be a drug or to be a subgenius
or to be a, well, anyway, you get the point.
Many presidents talk about drugs
and you'll see none of that at the book signing.
That's right, all drug
taking will not be done on the premises.
Where there is a statue
of Benjamin Franklin.
Why? And from that statue
was stolen the beautiful
St. Stupids head.
Just like the original during
the night of Slag.
The night I shot Bob, somebody stole it.
It's an incredible Hagen built shrine.
The altar.
I'm sorry, the altar.
The altar missing since 1984.
And that person used to call the show and say
I have the altar.
But we wouldn't honor him.
Did you know that Bob is like our Jesus?
Our Jesus?
You mean like Robert Jesus?
Right, our Jesus.
Like our Crumb and our Cobb
and our Jesus.
Art Buckwold.
Ah, never allow a normal
any slack in superstition,
mumbling rights,
domination justified by differences
of class or type.
Testify, PD.
Renounce system thought,
glorphing and addiction to conspiracy
promoted techno sedatives.
Man, you just keep on doing what you're doing.
Observe and evaluate for yourself.
Don't be a receptacle for someone else's thoughts.
Go, baby, go.
Symbolically and or literally,
assassinate your old friends
who have gone over to the other side.
We, trusting in the mercy of God
and the authority of the blessed apostles
Peter and Paul,
by that power of binding and loosing
that God as conforming,
have offered on us, although unworthy,
grant to all those submitting
to the labor of this journey personally
and at their expense
full forgiveness of their sins
of which they have been moved
to penitence in voice and heart
and as the reward of the just
we promise them a greater share
of eternal salvation.
Hear, hear.
Fields of bliss,
happy fields where joy forever dwells.
And if enough to do,
if pressure is applied,
almost everything will come apart
at some point.
Now you did it.
Come on, put it back together.
I have to get this one right or I'm out of this class.
A time for what?
A time for mowing and reaping?
A time for putting away tablecloths?
And a time for unpacking?
Exactly, which I'm deeply into these days.
Well, um,
let's see, I think
this big shindig,
this to-do that I'm talking about
is going to be at 7 p.m. at City Lights
on the first of April.
And I'll be there with you, Hal.
That's right, we'll be there.
Soldiers for Bob.
We're going to use our special signing pens, right?
That's right, I'm going to make a signing statement
which invalidates all previous signatures.
I'm going to use a pen
that was used by a famous guy
to sign a famous piece of paper in the past
somewhere, which will somehow
make my signing of something
more significant.
It was used to sign the
Treaty of Westphalia
after the Battle of Turkeytron.
That's for Chicken John.
It's a copy, you should watch it,
it's a copy of the entire, uh...
Last show?
No, well, the reunion of Circus Ridiculous.
Oh, the Circus Ridiculous show.
Damn it, the wonder dog, amazing.
Oh, yes, I...
Well, I'll watch it, yes,
then I'll give it to Chicken, sure.
Right.
That I will.
Well, um...
Look, the flowers are coming up,
the grass is blooming in the show park.
On the 24th, at Anon Salon,
I will be performing in a venue known as
Professor Goofball's Cartoon Studio,
where I make overprivileged,
drunken people draw cartoons,
or at least I'm paid to do that,
and we'll collect money
at the end of the night.
So if you can pay the unbelievably hefty fee
to get in there,
which I can't imagine doing myself,
join me at this particular show,
and I'll do that particular thing.
Then, on the last day of this month,
a CD release party for Phantom City,
the new, uh,
Stephen Casmar record.
I will preside over the party
held at the zoo in the Great Hall,
where there's a roaring, crackling fireplace,
and a roaring, enraged lion,
if they don't lock the cage.
Ha ha.
But probably that won't be there.
And, uh, we will have refreshments,
and, um,
it only costs seven bucks to attend this.
So, uh,
we're gonna have a fabulous party.
On the 20th of April,
I expect to journey into the Northland,
where I will eat, uh, sushi,
which has been spread on the body of, uh,
poet Blake Morse.
Man, this guy just goes on and on.
Man, this guy just goes everywhere.
Where's he gonna be?
I gotta eat sushi?
It's all about me.
Six days later than that,
I will be crowned
as a temple of the Hetheladium.
Anointed in gypsum,
and molded as
I'm doomed in the
Pyramids of Massasite.
We're gonna have to rewrite
the end of the world here.
This is gonna take longer.
There's a little humble figuring
about Dr. Hal in the future.
Hal has some more things to do,
and the end of the world
is just gonna take,
is gonna have to wait.
After the Power Tool drag races,
the Junior Model Train Competition
and layout construction
held in Wilkerson, Ontario.
See if I can get into his back here
and cut the vocal cords.
Giving a special recitation of
Casey Jr. and the Great Locomotive Chase
from the Walt Disney film.
After which, Hal will ponder
the astral significance of the, uh,
lint in my navel.
The Naval Reserve Show is a free event,
which I can announce as a public service,
but after this, uh,
contemplative, uh, act,
we're going to go to bongos
for spud nuts and soapy beers.
And then Hal will perform
surgery on a monkey.
Yes, Jocko's dreams.
My doctor's hands.
Sorry, that is an ape.
We're going to bring Jocko back to the light.
Back to life, then,
right after you kill him, you'll bring him back to life.
My thing says back to life.
The scientific principles of the Frankenstein cabinet.
What does back to life mean?
This is a crooked and perverse nation.
My friend.
Uh, no, I would...
The best of political education for this ape.
And when he comes out, he'll be a different monk.
Just remember,
the stark fester of removal has a finger in every pie.
That's the whole joke.
Pie are square.
But some of them are round.
We'll make a decision on that later.
Is this one of your momentary mental lapses, Hal,
that you forgot your next performance?
Oh, no, I was about to tell you,
I'll perform with the royal Le Penzer stallions.
Is that where the alien space braved?
Uh, they will be...
Eject its mind-warp technology?
While I gargle ink and juggle swords,
doused in cleaning fluid,
set alight.
I wanna see that.
Yeah, I wanna see that.
I'll tape it.
You'll be juggling saw blades as well, I understand.
Circular saw blades.
In New York City, I will give a lecture at the Bowery Aquarium
on alcoholic denizens of the lower docks,
which will be accompanied by a slide lecture
and a cheese-sauce lecture
on the cheese sculpture.
All this while performing a specialized juggling act.
Going straight for the juggler.
In which every, every possible permutation of the blades
will be spinning around his head.
Well, the important thing is
where are we going to go party
between the hot, amazing day of work at the park?
I just don't know.
You know, we have to battle the bobbies,
and then we have to go somewhere to rest
before we then return to the book signing.
Well, what's irritating to me is
I have to do the event at the zoo the night before.
So I can't rest.
And then I have to get up and
plod around in the same stupid parade.
And then, even when the parade is over,
I still have to do it.
Because I have to go to the park
and goof around with the pandas.
When that's done, I have to do
the subgenius event at the City Lights Bookstore.
It's even worse than that.
You guys yell too much.
You're right.
By the way, Cheetah is still alive.
Yeah, I know.
We're in the jungle looking at him right now.
In der jungle.
I saw the original Cheetah.
Bingle bangle bungle,
I don't want to leave der jungle.
I just refuse to go.
Don't you remember when Cheetah got killed
in Tarzan Finds a Mate?
The first Cheetah was killed in that one.
No, the Cheetah
that is alive now was like three years old
during those Johnny Weissmuller films.
It may have been an earlier Cheetah.
This Cheetah was present for
a little bit.
It's alive. It's the oldest surviving Cheetah.
It's alive! Watch out!
Cheetah is about, I think,
he's like 70 years old.
Is there any kind of a life to be hooked up to all those
machines with those things pumping your blood?
It's show business.
That's Hollywood.
That's Hollywood?
Over there?
I'm nervous.
Well, taters never did taste good
with chicken on the plate.
But still I had to eat them
just the same.
That's why I have these skinny
arms and legs and such a puny
weight. Cause mama always
told me take an old cold tater
and wait.
Are there any human beings?
Now that's after
you will be performing the
physical abuse of
the robots. You know, I have to
consult my appointment calendar.
The Mediocratons, the Pinks,
the Fat... Speaking of Pinks, I will
be performing with Cheep Pink
at the Oakland Children's Fair in
the last day of next month.
Oh great. You can get all over the place.
He is all over the place.
He's like a big pig.
Oakland Children's Fair, have you ever been there?
Oh, Fairland, yeah.
Where they have the concrete little pig's house and all that stuff?
I went there as a little fairy.
I have pictures of myself in that place
when I was about four or five years old.
At the Big Jonah's Whale.
And they have the special train
and all that stuff.
Well I hope that will quell any rumors
that Hal doesn't have a train.
He doesn't have any room in his calendar.
No, I'm going to perform with
Cheep Pink,
who are some personal friends of mine.
This isn't that trick you do
where you swallow the gasoline
and then throw a match down there, is it?
I'd swallow a young gasol...
They're not necessarily
going to do that, but...
Well they did that at my show.
You weren't there, but there was a
pooty pooty butt butt part.
And then they
taunt the audience.
And then they do uncomfortable things.
And it goes on and on.
I was terrified to look
to see if people would be leaving.
Pooty pooty butt butt,
they start saying.
And you have to say it with them.
And you have to stand up.
And you're thinking,
I'm not an attractive young woman
saying pooty pooty butt butt.
No, well that's...
Well when you're in the audience
and you realize that you were
on stage at one point.
That is sublime.
That's sort of sublime when you realize
that your instrument that you started playing
20 minutes ago is now being played by
a former audience member
as are the rest of the instruments
in the band.
Now that other event I mentioned
where we eat sushi off the recumbent
body of what's her name, Blake Moore.
That is on the 20th of April.
We're going to make some film.
A trip up there.
That's right.
And we're going to go back
and participate in the orgiastic
ceremony of ingesting sushi
on the body of a poet.
And all Japanese of course.
Oh yes, yes of course.
And follow that
I will do my celebrated impression.
And then there's all this 420
at the 420 place in 420ville.
That's right.
We have to stop at Mr. 420.
42020.
I would like to know the details of that.
Get ready at 420.
The details?
Well, when the...
Well later, not here on the air.
Go over before detail.
I will be getting some new tires
for my B.A.T.
Tires!
You better recycle those tires.
You know, rotate them.
They're supposed to rotate
when you go down the road.
Now we're going down the road
on the show.
And the people in the highway are so happy
that it only has 13 minutes left.
You could be falling out of the sky
a million miles an hour
and there
safely grasping
your fall
is the pipe, the mighty pipe.
It's breaking your fall.
You can't fall too fast
because the pipe will save you.
Sometimes the pipe
will put itself under you
as you're falling, like a cushioning effect.
Wow, this is cool.
The smoke billowing out
is allowing for a cottony sort of cloud-like
special effect
that will cushion your fall
even as you drift
softly above the pipe
in its downward trajectory.
But soft.
What light through yonder window breaks?
Don't quit smoking.
Simply give up for 30 days
and start again.
My new principle
contradicts every idea
people have had about quitting smoking.
I say,
only smoke for a month at a time,
then quit for a month,
then start up for a month,
then quit for a month.
That style of smoking
is one that will lead to
progressively bettering
a health.
And I'll prove it.
I can prove this through experiments
and special techniques
that we've devised
over a millennia
after imbuing
these subhumans here.
These microorganisms.
We can read the special
hedonistic digressive
techniques there.
But yesterday,
the word of Caesar stood against the world.
Now lies he there,
and none so poor
to do him reverence.
Oh, masters,
were I but bespoke
to stir your hearts and minds
with mutiny and rage,
I should do Brutus wrong
and Cassius wrong.
Who I do know
are honorable men.
I will not do them wrong.
I rather choose
to wrong the dead,
to wrong myself and you,
than I should wrong
such honorable men.
It's coming very slowly
and yet here it comes.
We can see it
rolling down the hill.
To see the world
in a grain of sand
and a heaven
in a wild flower.
Hold infinity in the palm
of your hand
and eternity in an hour.
A robin red-breast in a cage
puts all heaven
in a rage.
A dove house filled
with doves and pigeons
shudders hell
through all its regions.
The show has been shown
to be an effective
and effective
decay preventive denifers
that can be of significant value
when used in a conscientiously
applied program of oral hygiene
and regular professional care.
A dog starved at his master's gate
predicts the ruin
of the state.
A horse
misused upon the road
cries out to heaven
for human blood.
When you leave the show behind
this strategy will expose
your backside to intense scrutiny.
Each outcry of the wounded hair
a fragment of the brain
doth tear.
The skylark
wounded in the wing
a cherubim doth cease
to sing.
The gamecock clipped and armed
for fight
does the rising sun
affright.
Every wolf's and lion's
howl
raises from hell
a human soul.
The wild deer
wandering here and there
keep the human soul
from hell.
It's kind of like the host came alive
and just ate up the show.
What happened there?
How'd the host do that?
I didn't really see it.
It was over before I woke up.
This show's just a big sham.
Yeah, they don't even do anything.
The show doesn't ever
it just promises and promises and never delivers
and all of a sudden
next thing you know it's almost over
and people are crying and bewailing
the loss of the show
as if there was some substance
that they've figured out
and derived from it
and have benefited from it
over the last 23 years.
The bat that flits at close of eve
has left the brain
that won't believe.
Hey, shut those windows!
The show's almost over!
The owl that calls upon the night
speaks the unbeliever's
Hey, can you leave the window
that one window open?
He who shall hurt the little wren
never shall be loved by men.
Okay, well I'm just gonna lock up back here.
You guys wanna finish the show
and get out of here?
Yeah, I think the show really
really did the thing tonight.
It did the thing with Bob
and the pipe and all that.
The dots were there.
And then you gotta add
the
Then you say where.
When.
Who.
What?
All those, uh,
interrogatory, uh,
uh,
statements, uh,
word, wordage as it were.
Getting ready to go.
The poison of the snake and root
is the sweat of envy's foot.
I don't know. I'm looking on the scale, Carol.
Okay, so, the poison of the honeybee
is the artist's jealousy.
Mm-hmm.
We're waiting for you to call, caller.
Yeah, like, the show can't really do anything.
848-FLUFFY-FRO-FRO-LIFE in the 510 area code.
Call anytime, day or night, and just call.
Just say you wanna talk to a live subgenius here on
Yeah, thank me.
on your radio dial.
That's area code 410-L-YAROF-EAT-4425.
We'll be waiting to hear from you.
The little dobs will call you.
You can call now at
on the, uh, show for just a few more minutes.
I'm an hero, chim-pachero.
I'm an hero, chero.
Don't worry.
Let's call this duplicate show.
Let's call this triplicate show.
One of these people better be Michael Pepe.
This is one of these people that's gonna sing this show closed.
I know, I know.
It just seems weird.
There's the singer.
Sing away, show singer.
I'm an hero, chim-pachero.
I think the show singer got stage fright
when put on center stage.
Yeah, it happens.
That's the bright glare of the show spotlight
when it comes on.
The show's almost over.
La la la la la la la la.
It is. It's almost over.
The show's almost over.
We're so sorry.
The show's almost done.
The people call and they lament the show's
passing each week.
It's much like the passing of a close friend.
And yet there's no funeral for us to attend
and to commiserate the passing of that friendly old show.
That one that brings you to life every Friday morning.
That puts you away every Thursday night.
It's over.
Yes, yes, it is.
Who goes there?
And it's a sad thing here in the Bay Area
when this happens each week.
Who goes there, friend or enema?
I'll tell you.
Bend over.
Well, I hope you've enjoyed the show
as much as we've enjoyed shoveling the show at you.
And we want you to know that we enjoy doing the show for you
and on behalf of the staff and the management and...
And these supersonic Nazi hell creatures
from the hollow Earth.
From the center of the Earth.
It's a bucket that we live in.
It's a giant bucket.
It's a bucket filled with chainsaws and broken glass.
But we do it.
And we don't mind anymore.
We've got super intelligent pterodactyls.
We've got a lot of band-aids.
Serpent men.
Iguana men.
We're just doing our own thing.
It's a brain hop.
Amphibian men.
Female men.
Plant men.
Did I leave anything out?
They're all down there.
Yeah, you did.
You left about 1,200 things out.
That's true because there are so many.
For example, there are all sorts of extinct proboscideans,
mammoths and like that.
The dinotherium, the platybelodon.
They all still live in the center of the Earth.
But I don't know if we have time to list all these extinct megafauna
who have managed to live in the hollow interior.
Show those ovals.
The sun in the center of the Earth is an interesting physical phenomenon.
It is in fact what they call an Einstein-like singularity.
Around it, the gravitational angle is reversed.
This is what keeps all items in the hollow center of the Earth
from falling into the sun at Earth's center,
which is the gravitational constant that's present in the circle.
In recent years, scientists have discovered that the gravitational angle is the same as the gravitational angle of the Earth.
They're the same—you're aware of the center of the planet.
That means that each
It'll be oversized.
And then we'll be on the moon.
Or at least at a donut place
It's no disgrace
For the show to be over
Cause we'll eat some donuts
Next week
We'll be back